<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Personal Finance Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/personal-finance/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/personal-finance/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Personal Finance Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/personal-finance/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Intelligent Investor : The Classic Text on Value Investing &#8211; Benjamin Graham</title>
		<link>/intelligent-investor-the-classic-text-on-value-investing-benjamin-graham/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/intelligent-investor-the-classic-text-on-value-investing-benjamin-graham/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The greatest investment advisor of the twentieth century, Benjamin Graham taught and inspired people worldwide. Graham&#8217;s philosophy of `value investing`-which shields investors from substantial error and teaches them to develop long-term strategies-has made The Intelligent Investor the stock market bible ever since its original publication in 1949. Vital and indispensable, The Intelligent Investor is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/intelligent-investor-the-classic-text-on-value-investing-benjamin-graham/">Intelligent Investor : The Classic Text on Value Investing &#8211; Benjamin Graham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The greatest investment advisor of the twentieth century, Benjamin Graham taught and inspired people worldwide. Graham&#8217;s philosophy of `value investing`-which shields investors from substantial error and teaches them to develop long-term strategies-has made The Intelligent Investor the stock market bible ever since its original publication in 1949.    </p>
<p>                    Vital and indispensable, The Intelligent Investor is the most important book you will ever read on how to reach your financial goals.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/intelligent-investor-the-classic-text-on-value-investing-benjamin-graham/">Intelligent Investor : The Classic Text on Value Investing &#8211; Benjamin Graham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New Market Wizards : Conversations with America&#8217;s Top Traders &#8211; Jack D. Schwager</title>
		<link>/the-new-market-wizards-conversations-with-americas-top-traders-jack-d-schwager/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-market-wizards-conversations-with-americas-top-traders-jack-d-schwager/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The New Market Wizards, successful traders relate the financial strategies that have rocketed them to success. Asking questions that readers with an interest or involvement in the financial markets would love to pose to the financial superstars, Jack D. Schwager encourages these financial wizards to share their insights. Entertaining, informative, and invaluable, The New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-market-wizards-conversations-with-americas-top-traders-jack-d-schwager/">The New Market Wizards : Conversations with America&#8217;s Top Traders &#8211; Jack D. Schwager</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The New Market Wizards, successful traders relate the financial strategies that have rocketed them to success. Asking questions that readers with an interest or involvement in the financial markets would love to pose to the financial superstars, Jack D. Schwager encourages these financial wizards to share their insights. Entertaining, informative, and invaluable, The New Market Wizards is destined to become another Schwager classic.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-market-wizards-conversations-with-americas-top-traders-jack-d-schwager/">The New Market Wizards : Conversations with America&#8217;s Top Traders &#8211; Jack D. Schwager</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bogleheads&#8217; Guide to Investing &#8211; Mel Lindauer</title>
		<link>/the-bogleheads-guide-to-investing-mel-lindauer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bogleheads-guide-to-investing-mel-lindauer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The irreverent guide to investing, Boglehead style The Boglehead&#8217;s Guide to Investing is a DIY handbook that espouses the sage investment wisdom of John C. Bogle. This witty and wonderful book offers contrarian advice that provides the first step on the road to investment success, illustrating how relying on typical &#8220;common sense&#8221; promoted by Wall [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bogleheads-guide-to-investing-mel-lindauer/">The Bogleheads&#8217; Guide to Investing &#8211; Mel Lindauer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The irreverent guide to investing, Boglehead style The Boglehead&#8217;s Guide to Investing is a DIY handbook that espouses the sage investment wisdom of John C. Bogle. This witty and wonderful book offers contrarian advice that provides the first step on the road to investment success, illustrating how relying on typical &#8220;common sense&#8221; promoted by Wall Street is destined to leave you poorer. This updated edition includes new information on backdoor Roth IRAs and ETFs as mainstream buy and hold investments, estate taxes and gifting, plus changes to the laws regarding Traditional and Roth IRAs, and 401k and 403b retirement plans. With warnings and principles both precisely accurate and grandly counterintuitive, the Boglehead authors show how beating the market is a zero-sum game. Investing can be simple, but it&#8217;s certainly not simplistic. Over the course of twenty years, the followers of John C. Bogle have evolved from a loose association of investors to a major force with the largest and most active non-commercial financial forum on the Internet.<br />
                    The Boglehead&#8217;s Guide to Investing brings that communication to you with comprehensive guidance to the investment prowess on display at Bogleheads.org. You&#8217;ll learn how to craft your own investment strategy using the Bogle-proven methods that have worked for thousands of investors, and how to: * Choose a sound financial lifestyle and diversify your portfolio * Start early, invest regularly, and know what you&#8217;re buying * Preserve your buying power, keeping costs and taxes low * Throw out the &#8220;good&#8221; advice promoted by Wall Street that leads to investment failure Financial markets are essentially closed systems in which one&#8217;s gain garners another&#8217;s loss. Investors looking for a roadmap to successfully navigating these choppy waters long-term will find expert guidance, sound advice, and a little irreverent humor in The Boglehead&#8217;s Guide to Investing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bogleheads-guide-to-investing-mel-lindauer/">The Bogleheads&#8217; Guide to Investing &#8211; Mel Lindauer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unshakeable : Your Guide to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins</title>
		<link>/unshakeable-your-guide-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unshakeable-your-guide-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER* Tony Robbins, arguably the most recognizable life and business strategist and guru, is back with a timely, unique follow-up to his smash New York Times bestseller Money: Master the Game. Market corrections are as constant as seasons are in nature. There have been 30 such corrections in the past 30 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unshakeable-your-guide-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins/">Unshakeable : Your Guide to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER*</p>
<p>                     Tony Robbins, arguably the most recognizable life and business strategist and guru, is back with a timely, unique follow-up to his smash New York Times bestseller Money: Master the Game.<br />
                       Market corrections are as constant as seasons are in nature. There have been 30 such corrections in the past 30 years, yet there&#8217;s never been an action plan for how not only to survive, but thrive through each change in the stock market.<br />
                       Building upon the principles in Money: Master the Game, Robbins offers the reader specific steps they can implement to protect their investments while maximizing their wealth. It&#8217;s a detailed guide designed for investors, articulated in the common-sense, practical manner that the millions of loyal Robbins fans and students have come to expect and rely upon.<br />
                       Few have navigated the turbulence of the stock market as adeptly and successfully as Tony Robbins. His proven, consistent success over decades makes him singularly qualified to help investors (both seasoned and first-timers alike) preserve and add to their investments.</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Tony&#8217;s power is super-human&#8217; Oprah Winfrey<br />
                     &#8216;He has a great gift. He has the gift to inspire&#8217; Bill Clinton<br />
                     &#8216;Tony Robbins needs no introduction. He is committed to helping make life better for every investor&#8217; Carl Icahn<br />
                     &#8216;The high priest of human potential. The world can&#8217;t get enough of Anthony Robbins&#8217; The New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unshakeable-your-guide-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins/">Unshakeable : Your Guide to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Economics of Taxation: Principles, Policy and Practice 2012/13 &#8211; Simon R. James</title>
		<link>/the-economics-of-taxation-principles-policy-and-practice-2012-13-simon-r-james/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation & Duties Law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-economics-of-taxation-principles-policy-and-practice-2012-13-simon-r-james/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For over 30 years this textbook has been the leader in its field. Now revised and updated annually, the 2012/13 edition continues to provide a clear and authoritative introduction to the economic theory of taxation and to its practical operations. Part 1 of the text examines the principles of taxation, whilst Part 2 gives a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-economics-of-taxation-principles-policy-and-practice-2012-13-simon-r-james/">The Economics of Taxation: Principles, Policy and Practice 2012/13 &#8211; Simon R. James</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For over 30 years this textbook has been the leader in its field. Now revised and updated annually, the 2012/13 edition continues to provide a clear and authoritative introduction to the economic theory of taxation and to its practical operations. Part 1 of the text examines the principles of taxation, whilst Part 2 gives a broad-based description and evaluation of the policy and practice of the UK&#8217;s tax system, highlighting international comparisons.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-economics-of-taxation-principles-policy-and-practice-2012-13-simon-r-james/">The Economics of Taxation: Principles, Policy and Practice 2012/13 &#8211; Simon R. James</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck : A Counterintuitive Approach to Living a Good Life &#8211; Mark Manson</title>
		<link>/the-subtle-art-of-not-giving-a-fck-a-counterintuitive-approach-to-living-a-good-life-mark-manson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-subtle-art-of-not-giving-a-fck-a-counterintuitive-approach-to-living-a-good-life-mark-manson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller In this generation-defining self-help guide, a superstar blogger cuts through the crap to show us how to stop trying to be &#8220;positive&#8221; all the time so that we can truly become better, happier people. For decades, we&#8217;ve been told that positive thinking is the key to a happy, rich life. &#8220;F**k [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-subtle-art-of-not-giving-a-fck-a-counterintuitive-approach-to-living-a-good-life-mark-manson/">The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck : A Counterintuitive Approach to Living a Good Life &#8211; Mark Manson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller  In this generation-defining self-help guide, a superstar blogger cuts through the crap to show us how to stop trying to be &#8220;positive&#8221; all the time so that we can truly become better, happier people.  For decades, we&#8217;ve been told that positive thinking is the key to a happy, rich life. &#8220;F**k positivity,&#8221; Mark Manson says. &#8220;Let&#8217;s be honest, shit is f**ked and we have to live with it.&#8221; In his wildly popular Internet blog, Manson doesn&#8217;t sugarcoat or equivocate. He tells it like it is-a dose of raw, refreshing, honest truth that is sorely lacking today. The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F**k is his antidote to the coddling, let&#8217;s-all-feel-good mindset that has infected modern society and spoiled a generation, rewarding them with gold medals just for showing up. Manson makes the argument, backed both by academic research and well-timed poop jokes, that improving our lives hinges not on our ability to turn lemons into lemonade, but on learning to stomach lemons better. Human beings are flawed and limited-&#8220;not everybody can be extraordinary, there are winners and losers in society, and some of it is not fair or your fault.&#8221;<br />
                    Manson advises us to get to know our limitations and accept them. Once we embrace our fears, faults, and uncertainties, once we stop running and avoiding and start confronting painful truths, we can begin to find the courage, perseverance, honesty, responsibility, curiosity, and forgiveness we seek. There are only so many things we can give a f**k about so we need to figure out which ones really matter, Manson makes clear. While money is nice, caring about what you do with your life is better, because true wealth is about experience. A much-needed grab-you-by-the-shoulders-and-look-you-in-the-eye moment of real-talk, filled with entertaining stories and profane, ruthless humor, The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F**k is a refreshing slap for a generation to help them lead contented, grounded lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-subtle-art-of-not-giving-a-fck-a-counterintuitive-approach-to-living-a-good-life-mark-manson/">The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck : A Counterintuitive Approach to Living a Good Life &#8211; Mark Manson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Index Card &#8211; Helaine Olen, Harold Pollack (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-index-card-helaine-olen-harold-pollack-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-index-card-helaine-olen-harold-pollack-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The newbie investor will not find a better guide to personal finance.&#8221; &#8211;Burton Malkiel, author of A RANDOM WALK DOWN WALL STREET TV analysts and money managers would have you believe your finances are enormously complicated, and if you don&#8217;t follow their guidance, you&#8217;ll end up in the poorhouse. They&#8217;re wrong. When University of Chicago [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-index-card-helaine-olen-harold-pollack-abridged/">The Index Card &#8211; Helaine Olen, Harold Pollack (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The newbie investor will not find a better guide to personal finance.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Burton Malkiel, author of A RANDOM WALK DOWN WALL STREET       </p>
<p>                    TV analysts and money managers would have you believe your finances are enormously complicated, and if you don&#8217;t follow their guidance, you&#8217;ll end up in the poorhouse.     </p>
<p>                    They&#8217;re wrong.     </p>
<p>                    When University of Chicago professor Harold Pollack interviewed Helaine Olen, an award-winning financial journalist and the author of the bestselling Pound Foolish, he made an off­hand suggestion: everything you need to know about managing your money could fit on an index card. To prove his point, he grabbed a 4 x 6 card, scribbled down a list of rules, and posted a picture of the card online. The post went viral.     </p>
<p>                    Now, Pollack teams up with Olen to explain why the ten simple rules of the index card outperform more complicated financial strategies. Inside is an easy-to-follow action plan that works in good times and bad, giving you the tools, knowledge, and confidence to seize control of your financial life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-index-card-helaine-olen-harold-pollack-abridged/">The Index Card &#8211; Helaine Olen, Harold Pollack (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: The Elderly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pensions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface* Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time? Many of us have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface*    </p>
<p>                    Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time?     </p>
<p>                    Many of us have been raised on the traditional notion of a three-stage approach to our working lives: education, followed by work and then retirement.  But this well-established pathway is already beginning to collapse &#8211; life expectancy is rising, final-salary pensions are vanishing, and increasing numbers of people are juggling multiple careers. Whether you are 18, 45 or 60, you will need to do things very differently from previous generations and learn to structure your life in completely new ways.    </p>
<p>                    The 100-Year Life is here to help.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the unique pairing of their experience in psychology and economics, Lynda Gratton and Andrew J. Scott offer a broad-ranging analysis as well as a raft of solutions, showing how to rethink your finances, your education, your career and your relationships and create a fulfilling 100-year life.     </p>
<p>                    * How can you fashion a career and life path that defines you and your values and creates a shifting balance between work and leisure?    </p>
<p>                    * What are the most effective ways of boosting your physical and mental health over a longer and more dynamic lifespan?    </p>
<p>                    * How can you make the most of your intangible assets &#8211; such as family and friends &#8211; as you build a productive, longer life?    </p>
<p>                    * In a multiple-stage life how can you learn to make the transitions that will be so crucial and experiment with new ways of living, working and learning?    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award and featuring a new preface, The 100-Year Life is a wake-up call that describes what to expect and considers the choices and options that you will face. It is also fundamentally a call to action for individuals, politicians, firms and governments and offers the clearest demonstration that a 100-year life can be a wonderful and inspiring one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everything is Figureoutable : The #1 New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Marie Forleo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everything-is-figureoutable-the-1-new-york-times-bestseller-marie-forleo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chakras, Auras & Spiritual Energy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everything-is-figureoutable-the-1-new-york-times-bestseller-marie-forleo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>***THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER*** &#8216;Fast-paced, generous, wise, raw, funny, practical and helpful&#8217; Glennon Doyle, author of Untamed &#8216;Millions of young women look to Marie Forleo as their inspiration for empowerment and achievement&#8217; Oprah Winfrey &#8216;Reading these pages I experienced the sensation of limitless possibility. This book will change lives&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert Do you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-is-figureoutable-the-1-new-york-times-bestseller-marie-forleo-abridged/">Everything is Figureoutable : The #1 New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Marie Forleo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>***THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER***    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fast-paced, generous, wise, raw, funny, practical and helpful&#8217; Glennon Doyle, author of Untamed    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Millions of young women look to Marie Forleo as their inspiration for empowerment and achievement&#8217; Oprah Winfrey    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Reading these pages I experienced the sensation of limitless possibility. This book will change lives&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert    </p>
<p>                     Do you ever have trouble finishing what you start? Do amazing ideas come to you all the time but after the initial excitement wanes you struggle to follow through? If you&#8217;re creative and ambitious, the answer is likely yes.    </p>
<p>                     The problem isn&#8217;t you. It&#8217;s not that you&#8217;re not hardworking, intelligent or deserving, but that you haven&#8217;t yet installed the one key belief that will change everything: Everything is figureoutable.     </p>
<p>                     Whether you want to leave a dead-end job, heal a relationship, grow a business, master your money, or just find two free hours in your day, Everything is Figureoutable will train your brain to think more positively and help you break down any dream into manageable steps.     </p>
<p>                     Inside you&#8217;ll learn:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; How to deal with criticism and imposter syndrome<br />
                     &#8211; Why it&#8217;s crucial that you strive for progress not perfection<br />
                     &#8211; How to bounce back from failure<br />
                     &#8211; How to overcome a lack of time and money     </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll also hear triumphant stories of everyday people using the everything is figureoutable philosophy to transform their life. Everything is figureoutable is more than just a fun phrase to say. It&#8217;s a practical, actionable discipline. And it&#8217;s about to make you unstoppable!    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Smart, funny, and as brilliant as it is straightforward. LOVED it!&#8217; Brene Brown    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;This book delivers a knockout punch to whatever is holding you back&#8217; Cheryl Strayed</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-is-figureoutable-the-1-new-york-times-bestseller-marie-forleo-abridged/">Everything is Figureoutable : The #1 New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Marie Forleo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Barefoot Investor : The Only Money Guide You&#8217;ll Ever Need &#8211; Scott Pape (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-barefoot-investor-the-only-money-guide-youll-ever-need-scott-pape-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-barefoot-investor-the-only-money-guide-youll-ever-need-scott-pape-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** Reviewed and updated for the 2020-2021 financial year** This is the only money guide you&#8217;ll ever need That&#8217;s a bold claim, given there are already thousands of finance books on the shelves. So what makes this one different? Well, you won&#8217;t be overwhelmed with a bunch of &#8216;tips&#8217; &#8230; or a strict budget (that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-barefoot-investor-the-only-money-guide-youll-ever-need-scott-pape-abridged/">The Barefoot Investor : The Only Money Guide You&#8217;ll Ever Need &#8211; Scott Pape (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** Reviewed and updated for the 2020-2021 financial year**    </p>
<p>                     This is the only money guide you&#8217;ll ever need    </p>
<p>                     That&#8217;s a bold claim, given there are already thousands of finance books on the shelves.    </p>
<p>                     So what makes this one different?    </p>
<p>                     Well, you won&#8217;t be overwhelmed with a bunch of &#8216;tips&#8217; &#8230; or a strict budget (that you won&#8217;t follow).    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll get a step-by-step formula: open this account, then do this; call this person, and say this; invest money here, and not there. All with a glass of wine in your hand.    </p>
<p>                     This book will show you how to create an entire financial plan that is so simple you can sketch it on the back of a serviette &#8230; and you&#8217;ll be able to manage your money in 10 minutes a week.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll also get the skinny on:    </p>
<p>                     Saving up a six-figure house deposit in 20 months    </p>
<p>                     Doubling your income using the &#8216;Trapeze Strategy&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     Saving $78,173 on your mortgage and wiping out 7 years of payments    </p>
<p>                     Finding a financial advisor who won&#8217;t rip you off    </p>
<p>                     Handing your kids (or grandkids) a $140,000 cheque on their 21st birthday    </p>
<p>                     Why you don&#8217;t need $1 million to retire &#8230; with the &#8216;Donald Bradman Retirement Strategy&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     Sound too good to be true? It&#8217;s not.    </p>
<p>                     This book is full of stories from everyday Aussies &#8211; single people, young families, empty nesters, retirees &#8211; who have applied the simple steps in this book and achieved amazing, life-changing results.    </p>
<p>                     And you&#8217;re next.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-barefoot-investor-the-only-money-guide-youll-ever-need-scott-pape-abridged/">The Barefoot Investor : The Only Money Guide You&#8217;ll Ever Need &#8211; Scott Pape (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thou Shall Prosper : Ten Commandments for Making Money &#8211; Rabbi Daniel Lapin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thou-shall-prosper-ten-commandments-for-making-money-rabbi-daniel-lapin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewish Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Judaism: Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thou-shall-prosper-ten-commandments-for-making-money-rabbi-daniel-lapin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical approach to creating wealth-based on the established principles of ancient Jewish wisdom-made accessible to people of all backgrounds The ups and downs of the economy prove Rabbi Daniel Lapin&#8217;s famous principle that the more things change, the more we need to depend upon the things that never change. There&#8217;s no better source for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thou-shall-prosper-ten-commandments-for-making-money-rabbi-daniel-lapin-abridged/">Thou Shall Prosper : Ten Commandments for Making Money &#8211; Rabbi Daniel Lapin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical approach to creating wealth-based on the established principles of ancient Jewish wisdom-made accessible to people of all backgrounds  The ups and downs of the economy prove Rabbi Daniel Lapin&#8217;s famous principle that the more things change, the more we need to depend upon the things that never change. There&#8217;s no better source for both practical and spiritual financial wisdom than the time-tested knowledge found in the ancient Jewish faith and its culture. In the  Second Edition  of  Thou Shall Prosper,  Lapin offers a practical approach to creating wealth based on the established principles of ancient Jewish wisdom. This book details the ten permanent principles that never change, the ten commandments of making money if you will, and explores the economic and philosophic vision of business that has been part of Jewish culture for centuries. The book&#8217;s focus is on making accessible to individuals of all backgrounds, the timeless truths that Jews have used for centuries to excel in business.<br />
                    Outlines ten fundamental &#8220;commandments&#8221; relating to business and money  Includes insights that will increase your potential for creating wealth, no matter what your faith or background may be  Blends contemporary business stories and Lapin&#8217;s own business experiences with the wisdom of the Torah and Talmudic prescriptions This  Second Edition  provides new examples, especially of Internet related business opportunities. In addition, each chapter highlights specific action steps that can lead to wealth opportunities in both difficult economic times and periods of prosperity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thou-shall-prosper-ten-commandments-for-making-money-rabbi-daniel-lapin-abridged/">Thou Shall Prosper : Ten Commandments for Making Money &#8211; Rabbi Daniel Lapin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dollars and Sense : Money Mishaps and How to Avoid Them &#8211; Dan Ariely, Jeff Kreisler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dollars-and-sense-money-mishaps-and-how-to-avoid-them-dan-ariely-jeff-kreisler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dollars-and-sense-money-mishaps-and-how-to-avoid-them-dan-ariely-jeff-kreisler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blending humor and behavioral economics, the New York Times bestselling author of Predictably Irrational delves into the truly illogical world of personal finance to help people better understand why they make bad financial decisions, and gives them the knowledge they need to make better ones. Why does paying for things often feel like it causes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dollars-and-sense-money-mishaps-and-how-to-avoid-them-dan-ariely-jeff-kreisler-abridged/">Dollars and Sense : Money Mishaps and How to Avoid Them &#8211; Dan Ariely, Jeff Kreisler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blending humor and behavioral economics, the New York Times bestselling author of Predictably Irrational delves into the truly illogical world of personal finance to help people better understand why they make bad financial decisions, and gives them the knowledge they need to make better ones.    </p>
<p>                    Why does paying for things often feel like it causes physical pain?<br />
                    Why does it cost you money to act as your own real estate agent?<br />
                    Why are we comfortable overpaying for something now just because we&#8217;ve overpaid for it before?    </p>
<p>                    In Dollars and Sense, world renowned economist Dan Ariely answers these intriguing questions and many more as he explains how our irrational behavior often interferes with our best intentions when it comes to managing our finances. Partnering with financial comedian and writer Jeff Kreisler, Ariely takes us deep inside our minds to expose the hidden motivations that are secretly driving our choices about money.    </p>
<p>                    Exploring a wide range of everyday topics-from credit card debt and household budgeting to holiday sales-Ariely and Kreisler demonstrate how our ideas about dollars and cents are often wrong and cost us more than we know. Mixing case studies and anecdotes with tangible advice and lessons, they cut through the unconscious fears and desires driving our worst financial instincts and teach us how to improve our money habits.    </p>
<p>                    Fascinating, engaging, funny, and essential, Dollars and Sense is a sound investment, providing us with the practical tools we need to understand and improve our financial choices, save and spend smarter, and ultimately live better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dollars-and-sense-money-mishaps-and-how-to-avoid-them-dan-ariely-jeff-kreisler-abridged/">Dollars and Sense : Money Mishaps and How to Avoid Them &#8211; Dan Ariely, Jeff Kreisler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Quit Like a Millionaire : No Gimmicks, Luck, or Trust Fund Required &#8211; Kristy Shen, Bryce Leung (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/quit-like-a-millionaire-no-gimmicks-luck-or-trust-fund-required-kristy-shen-bryce-leung-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tips & Advice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/quit-like-a-millionaire-no-gimmicks-luck-or-trust-fund-required-kristy-shen-bryce-leung-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From two leaders of the FIRE (Financial Independence, Retire Early) movement, a bold, contrarian guide to retiring at any age, with a reproducible formula to financial independence A bull***t-free guide to growing your wealth, retiring early, and living life on your own terms Kristy Shen retired with a million dollars at the age of thirty-one, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/quit-like-a-millionaire-no-gimmicks-luck-or-trust-fund-required-kristy-shen-bryce-leung-abridged/">Quit Like a Millionaire : No Gimmicks, Luck, or Trust Fund Required &#8211; Kristy Shen, Bryce Leung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From two leaders of the FIRE (Financial Independence, Retire Early) movement, a bold, contrarian guide to retiring at any age, with a reproducible formula to financial independence     </p>
<p>                    A bull***t-free guide to growing your wealth, retiring early, and living life on your own terms     </p>
<p>                    Kristy Shen retired with a million dollars at the age of thirty-one, and she did it without hitting a home run on the stock market, starting the next Snapchat in her garage, or investing in hot real estate. Learn how to cut down on spending without decreasing your quality of life, build a million-dollar portfolio, fortify your investments to survive bear markets and black-swan events, and use the 4 percent rule and the Yield Shield&#8211;so you can quit the rat race forever. Not everyone can become an entrepreneur or a real estate baron; the rest of us need Shen&#8217;s mathematically proven approach to retire decades before sixty-five.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/quit-like-a-millionaire-no-gimmicks-luck-or-trust-fund-required-kristy-shen-bryce-leung-abridged/">Quit Like a Millionaire : No Gimmicks, Luck, or Trust Fund Required &#8211; Kristy Shen, Bryce Leung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Opposite of Spoiled : Raising Kids Who Are Grounded, Generous, and Smart About Money &#8211; Ron Lieber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the spirit of Wendy Mogel&#8217;s The Blessing of a Skinned Knee and Po Bronson and Ashley Merryman&#8217;s Nurture Shock, New York Times &#8220;Your Money&#8221; columnist Ron Lieber delivers a taboo-shattering manifesto that explains how talking openly to children about money can help parents raise modest, patient, grounded young adults who are financially wise beyond [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/">The Opposite of Spoiled : Raising Kids Who Are Grounded, Generous, and Smart About Money &#8211; Ron Lieber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the spirit of Wendy Mogel&#8217;s The Blessing of a Skinned Knee and Po Bronson and Ashley Merryman&#8217;s Nurture Shock, New York Times &#8220;Your Money&#8221; columnist Ron Lieber delivers a taboo-shattering manifesto that explains how talking openly to children about money can help parents raise modest, patient, grounded young adults who are financially wise beyond their years.  For Ron Lieber, a personal finance columnist and father, good parenting means talking about money with our kids. Children are hyper-aware of money, and they have scores of questions about its nuances. But when parents shy away from the topic, they lose a tremendous opportunity-not just to model the basic financial behaviors that are increasingly important for young adults but also to imprint lessons about what the family truly values.  Written in a warm, accessible voice, grounded in real-world experience and stories from families with a range of incomes, The Opposite of Spoiled is both a practical guidebook and a values-based philosophy.<br />
                    The foundation of the book is a detailed blueprint for the best ways to handle the basics: the tooth fairy, allowance, chores, charity, saving, birthdays, holidays, cell phones, checking accounts, clothing, cars, part-time jobs, and college tuition. It identifies a set of traits and virtues that embody the opposite of spoiled, and shares how to embrace the topic of money to help parents raise kids who are more generous and less materialistic.  But The Opposite of Spoiled is also a promise to our kids that we will make them better with money than we are. It is for all of the parents who know that honest conversations about money with their curious children can help them become more patient and prudent, but who don&#8217;t know how and when to start.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-opposite-of-spoiled-raising-kids-who-are-grounded-generous-and-smart-about-money-ron-lieber-abridged/">The Opposite of Spoiled : Raising Kids Who Are Grounded, Generous, and Smart About Money &#8211; Ron Lieber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck : A Counterintuitive Approach to Living a Good Life &#8211; Mark Manson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-subtle-art-of-not-giving-a-fck-a-counterintuitive-approach-to-living-a-good-life-mark-manson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-subtle-art-of-not-giving-a-fck-a-counterintuitive-approach-to-living-a-good-life-mark-manson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller In this generation-defining self-help guide, a superstar blogger cuts through the crap to show us how to stop trying to be &#8220;positive&#8221; all the time so that we can truly become better, happier people. For decades, we&#8217;ve been told that positive thinking is the key to a happy, rich life. &#8220;F**k [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-subtle-art-of-not-giving-a-fck-a-counterintuitive-approach-to-living-a-good-life-mark-manson-abridged/">The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck : A Counterintuitive Approach to Living a Good Life &#8211; Mark Manson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller  In this generation-defining self-help guide, a superstar blogger cuts through the crap to show us how to stop trying to be &#8220;positive&#8221; all the time so that we can truly become better, happier people.  For decades, we&#8217;ve been told that positive thinking is the key to a happy, rich life. &#8220;F**k positivity,&#8221; Mark Manson says. &#8220;Let&#8217;s be honest, shit is f**ked and we have to live with it.&#8221; In his wildly popular Internet blog, Manson doesn&#8217;t sugarcoat or equivocate. He tells it like it is-a dose of raw, refreshing, honest truth that is sorely lacking today. The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F**k is his antidote to the coddling, let&#8217;s-all-feel-good mindset that has infected modern society and spoiled a generation, rewarding them with gold medals just for showing up. Manson makes the argument, backed both by academic research and well-timed poop jokes, that improving our lives hinges not on our ability to turn lemons into lemonade, but on learning to stomach lemons better. Human beings are flawed and limited-&#8220;not everybody can be extraordinary, there are winners and losers in society, and some of it is not fair or your fault.&#8221;<br />
                    Manson advises us to get to know our limitations and accept them. Once we embrace our fears, faults, and uncertainties, once we stop running and avoiding and start confronting painful truths, we can begin to find the courage, perseverance, honesty, responsibility, curiosity, and forgiveness we seek. There are only so many things we can give a f**k about so we need to figure out which ones really matter, Manson makes clear. While money is nice, caring about what you do with your life is better, because true wealth is about experience. A much-needed grab-you-by-the-shoulders-and-look-you-in-the-eye moment of real-talk, filled with entertaining stories and profane, ruthless humor, The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F**k is a refreshing slap for a generation to help them lead contented, grounded lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-subtle-art-of-not-giving-a-fck-a-counterintuitive-approach-to-living-a-good-life-mark-manson-abridged/">The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck : A Counterintuitive Approach to Living a Good Life &#8211; Mark Manson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Make Your Money Last &#8211; Completely Updated for Planning Today : The Indispensable Retirement Guide &#8211; Jane Bryant Quinn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-make-your-money-last-completely-updated-for-planning-today-the-indispensable-retirement-guide-jane-bryant-quinn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-make-your-money-last-completely-updated-for-planning-today-the-indispensable-retirement-guide-jane-bryant-quinn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NOW COMPLETELY UPDATED to reflect the changes in tax legislation, health insurance, and the new investment realities. In this &#8220;highly valuable resource&#8221; (Publishers Weekly, starred review) Quinn &#8220;provides simple, straightforward&#8221; (The New York Times) solutions to the universal retirement dilemma&#8211;how to make your limited savings last for life&#8211;covering mortgages, social security, income investing, annuities, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-make-your-money-last-completely-updated-for-planning-today-the-indispensable-retirement-guide-jane-bryant-quinn-abridged/">How to Make Your Money Last &#8211; Completely Updated for Planning Today : The Indispensable Retirement Guide &#8211; Jane Bryant Quinn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NOW COMPLETELY UPDATED to reflect the changes in tax legislation, health insurance, and the new investment realities. In this &#8220;highly valuable resource&#8221; (Publishers Weekly, starred review) Quinn &#8220;provides simple, straightforward&#8221; (The New York Times) solutions to the universal retirement dilemma&#8211;how to make your limited savings last for life&#8211;covering mortgages, social security, income investing, annuities, and more!      </p>
<p>                    Will you run out of money in your older age? That&#8217;s the biggest worry for people newly retired or planning to retire. Fortunately, you don&#8217;t have to plan in the dark. Jane Bryant Quinn tells you how to squeeze a higher income from all your assets&#8211;including your social security account (get every dollar you&#8217;re entitled to), a pension (discover whether a lump sum or a lifetime monthly income will pay you more), your home equity (sell, rent, or take a reverse mortgage?), savings (how to use them safely to raise your monthly income), retirement accounts (invest the money for growth in ways that let you sleep at night), and&#8211;critically&#8211;how much of your savings you can afford to spend every year without running out. There are easy ways to figure all this out. Who knew?     </p>
<p>                    Quinn also shows you how to evaluate your real risks. If you stick with super-safe investment choices, your money might not last and your lifestyle might erode. The same might be true if you rely on traditional income investments. Quinn rethinks the meaning of &#8220;income investing,&#8221; by combining reliable cash flow during the early years of your retirement with low-risk growth investments, to provide extra money for your later years. Odds are, you&#8217;ll live longer than you might imagine, meaning that your savings will stretch for many more years than you might have planned for. With the help of this book, you can turn those retirement funds into a &#8220;homemade&#8221; paycheck that will last for life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-make-your-money-last-completely-updated-for-planning-today-the-indispensable-retirement-guide-jane-bryant-quinn-abridged/">How to Make Your Money Last &#8211; Completely Updated for Planning Today : The Indispensable Retirement Guide &#8211; Jane Bryant Quinn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>STARTUP WEALTH delivers engaging interviews with early- stage investors in Google, Invisalign, ZipCar, Uber, Twilio, Localytics, and other successful and not so successful companies. Find out how an amazing IPO can result in early investors getting pennies on the dollar&#8211;or a 10x+ return. Josh Maher profiles 23 of the country&#8217;s best investors over the last [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/">Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>STARTUP WEALTH delivers engaging interviews with early- stage investors in Google, Invisalign, ZipCar, Uber, Twilio, Localytics, and other successful and not so successful companies. Find out how an amazing IPO can result in early investors getting pennies on the dollar&#8211;or a 10x+ return.    </p>
<p>                    Josh Maher profiles 23 of the country&#8217;s best investors over the last two decades by way of real-world case studies. Through revealing interviews, readers are introduced to Mark Suster, Catherine Mott, Christopher Mirabile, Brad Feld, Allan May, Joanne Wilson, and many other accomplished angel investors and venture capitalists. In these interviews you&#8217;ll learn:<br />
                     &#8211; How the best investors think about identifying companies, negotiating terms, and partnering with founders and other investors<br />
                     &#8211; How angel investing can involve many different successful approaches<br />
                     &#8211; What the best investors have learned from their largest successes and failures<br />
                     &#8211; How investors design their portfolios and work with companies to achieve the most successful results.    </p>
<p>                    STARTUP WEALTH is an insightful and useful tool for anyone seeking to make better investments, select great investors, or raise early-stage capital for their business.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;There is nothing better when it comes to learning &#8216;best practices&#8217; than hearing from successful people in the trenches. Josh&#8217;s book captures the best of the best, as they reveal both what worked and what didn&#8217;t for them as angel investors and entrepreneurs. Required reading whatever side of the investing fence you&#8217;re on!&#8221;&#8211;Gerry Langeler, Managing Director at OVP Venture Partners. Co-founder of Mentor Graphics (NASDAQ: MENT). Author of The Success Matrix and Take the Money and Run! An Insider&#8217;s Guide to Venture Capital.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/">Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Find Your Why : A Practical Guide for Discovering Purpose for You and Your Team &#8211; Simon Sinek, David Mead, Peter Docker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/find-your-why-a-practical-guide-for-discovering-purpose-for-you-and-your-team-simon-sinek-david-mead-peter-docker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/find-your-why-a-practical-guide-for-discovering-purpose-for-you-and-your-team-simon-sinek-david-mead-peter-docker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Start With Why has led millions of readers to rethink everything they do &#8211; in their personal lives, their careers and their organizations. Now Find Your Why picks up where Start With Why left off. It shows you how to apply Simon Sinek&#8217;s powerful insights so that you can find more inspiration at work &#8212; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/find-your-why-a-practical-guide-for-discovering-purpose-for-you-and-your-team-simon-sinek-david-mead-peter-docker-abridged/">Find Your Why : A Practical Guide for Discovering Purpose for You and Your Team &#8211; Simon Sinek, David Mead, Peter Docker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Start With Why has led millions of readers to rethink everything they do &#8211; in their personal lives, their careers and their organizations.    </p>
<p>                     Now Find Your Why picks up where Start With Why left off. It shows you how to apply Simon Sinek&#8217;s powerful insights so that you can find more inspiration at work &#8212; and in turn inspire those around you.     </p>
<p>                     I believe fulfillment is a right and not a privilege. We are all entitled to wake up in the morning inspired to go to work, feel safe when we&#8217;re there and return home fulfilled at the end of the day. Achieving that fulfillment starts with understanding exactly WHY we do what we do.     </p>
<p>                     As Start With Why has spread around the world, countless readers have asked me the same question: How can I apply Start With Why to my career, team, company or nonprofit? Along with two of my colleagues, Peter Docker and David Mead, I created this hands-on, step-by-step guide to help you find your WHY.     </p>
<p>                    With detailed exercises, illustrations, and action steps for every stage of the process, Find Your Why can help you address many important concerns, including:     </p>
<p>                     * What if my WHY sounds just like my competitor&#8217;s?<br />
                    * Can I have more than one WHY?<br />
                    * If my work doesn&#8217;t match my WHY, what should I do?<br />
                    * What if my team can&#8217;t agree on our WHY?     </p>
<p>                     Whether you&#8217;ve just started your first job, are leading a team, or are CEO of your own company, the exercises in this book will help guide you on a path to long-term success and fulfillment, for both you and your colleagues.     </p>
<p>                     Thank you for joining us as we work together to build a world in which more people start with WHY.     </p>
<p>                     Inspire on!<br />
                    &#8212; Simon</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/find-your-why-a-practical-guide-for-discovering-purpose-for-you-and-your-team-simon-sinek-david-mead-peter-docker-abridged/">Find Your Why : A Practical Guide for Discovering Purpose for You and Your Team &#8211; Simon Sinek, David Mead, Peter Docker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge    </p>
<p>                    With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. This clear, concise, and accessible guide from two industry insiders shows you how to navigate this brave new blockchain world-and how to invest in these emerging assets to secure your financial future.    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets gives you all the tools you need:    </p>
<p>                    * An actionable framework for investigating and valuing cryptoassets     </p>
<p>                    * Portfolio management techniques to maximize returns while managing risk    </p>
<p>                    * Historical context and tips to navigate inevitable bubbles and manias    </p>
<p>                    * Practical guides to exchanges, wallets, capital market vehicles, and ICOs    </p>
<p>                    * Predictions on how blockchain technology may disrupt current portfolios    </p>
<p>                    In addition to offering smart investment strategies, this authoritative resource will help you understand how these assets were created, how they work, and how they are evolving amid the blockchain revolution. The authors define a clear and original cryptoasset taxonomy, composed of cryptocurrencies, cryptocommodities, and cryptotokens, with insights into how each subset is blending technology and markets. You&#8217;ll find a variety of methods to invest in these assets, whether through global exchanges that trade 24/7 or initial cryptoasset offerings (ICOs). By sequentially building on the concepts of each prior chapter, the book will provide you with a full understanding of the cryptoasset economy and the opportunities that await the innovative investor .    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets represent the future of money and markets. This book is your guide to that future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Playing with FIRE (Financial Independence Retire Early) : How Far Would You Go for Financial Freedom? &#8211; Scott Rieckens (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/playing-with-fire-financial-independence-retire-early-how-far-would-you-go-for-financial-freedom-scott-rieckens-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/playing-with-fire-financial-independence-retire-early-how-far-would-you-go-for-financial-freedom-scott-rieckens-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What if a happier life was only a few simple choices away? A successful entrepreneur living in Southern California, Scott Rieckens had built a &#8220;dream life&#8221; a happy marriage, a two-year-old daughter, a membership to a boat club, and a BMW in the driveway. But underneath the surface, Scott was creatively stifled, depressed, and overworked [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/playing-with-fire-financial-independence-retire-early-how-far-would-you-go-for-financial-freedom-scott-rieckens-abridged/">Playing with FIRE (Financial Independence Retire Early) : How Far Would You Go for Financial Freedom? &#8211; Scott Rieckens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What if a happier life was only a few simple choices away?    </p>
<p>                     A successful entrepreneur living in Southern California, Scott Rieckens had built a &#8220;dream life&#8221; a happy marriage, a two-year-old daughter, a membership to a boat club, and a BMW in the driveway. But underneath the surface, Scott was creatively stifled, depressed, and overworked trying to help pay for his family&#8217;s beach-town lifestyle. Then one day, Scott listened to a podcast interview that changed everything. Five months later, he had quit his job, convinced his family to leave their home, and cut their expenses in half. Follow Scott and his family as they devote everything to FIRE (financial independence retire early), a subculture obsessed with maximizing wealth and happiness. Filled with inspiring case studies and powerful advice, Playing with FIRE is one family&#8217;s journey to acquire the one thing that money can&#8217;t buy: a simpler &#8212; and happier &#8212; life.    </p>
<p>                     Based on the documentary</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/playing-with-fire-financial-independence-retire-early-how-far-would-you-go-for-financial-freedom-scott-rieckens-abridged/">Playing with FIRE (Financial Independence Retire Early) : How Far Would You Go for Financial Freedom? &#8211; Scott Rieckens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Be a Capitalist Without Any Capital : The Four Rules You Must Break to Get Rich &#8211; Nathan Latka (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-a-capitalist-without-any-capital-the-four-rules-you-must-break-to-get-rich-nathan-latka-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-a-capitalist-without-any-capital-the-four-rules-you-must-break-to-get-rich-nathan-latka-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You don&#8217;t need to be university educated, have money, be creative, or even have an idea to get rich. You just need to be willing to break the rules. How to be a Capitalist Without Any Capital will teach you how to be a modern opportunist &#8211; investor, entrepreneur, or side hustler &#8211; by breaking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-capitalist-without-any-capital-the-four-rules-you-must-break-to-get-rich-nathan-latka-abridged/">How to Be a Capitalist Without Any Capital : The Four Rules You Must Break to Get Rich &#8211; Nathan Latka (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You don&#8217;t need to be university educated, have money, be creative, or even have an idea to get rich. You just need to be willing to break the rules.    </p>
<p>                    How to be a Capitalist Without Any Capital will teach you how to be a modern opportunist &#8211; investor, entrepreneur, or side hustler &#8211; by breaking these four golden rules of the old guard:     </p>
<p>                    1. Focus on one skill: Wrong. Don&#8217;t cultivate one great skill to get ahead. In today&#8217;s business world, success goes to the multitaskers.    </p>
<p>                    2. Be unique: Wrong. The way to get rich is not by launching a new idea but by aggressively copying others and then adding your own twist.     </p>
<p>                    3. Focus on one goal: Wrong. Focus instead on creating a system to produce the outcome you want, not just once, but over and over again.     </p>
<p>                    4. Appeal to the masses: Wrong. The masses are broke ($4k average net worth in America?). Let others cut a trail through the jungle so you can peacefully walk in and capitalize on their hard work.    </p>
<p>                    By rejecting these defunct rules and following Nathan Latka&#8217;s unconventional path, you can copy other people&#8217;s ideas shamelessly, bootstrap a start-up with almost no funding, invest in small local businesses for huge payoffs, and reap all the benefits.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-capitalist-without-any-capital-the-four-rules-you-must-break-to-get-rich-nathan-latka-abridged/">How to Be a Capitalist Without Any Capital : The Four Rules You Must Break to Get Rich &#8211; Nathan Latka (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Here to Financial Happiness : Enrich Your Life in Just 77 Days &#8211; Jonathan Clements (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/from-here-to-financial-happiness-enrich-your-life-in-just-77-days-jonathan-clements-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/from-here-to-financial-happiness-enrich-your-life-in-just-77-days-jonathan-clements-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Just 77 days to a happier, more prosperous life! From Here to Financial Happiness is the day-by-day guide for anyone dreaming of a better life. Whether you&#8217;re dealing with debt, uncertain about retirement or simply want to get a grip on your finances, this book can put you on the road to happiness with a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/from-here-to-financial-happiness-enrich-your-life-in-just-77-days-jonathan-clements-abridged/">From Here to Financial Happiness : Enrich Your Life in Just 77 Days &#8211; Jonathan Clements (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just 77 days to a happier, more prosperous life!    </p>
<p>                     From Here to Financial Happiness is the day-by-day guide for anyone dreaming of a better life. Whether you&#8217;re dealing with debt, uncertain about retirement or simply want to get a grip on your finances, this book can put you on the road to happiness with a simple 11-week journey. Just 5-10 minutes a day to think about money, your habits, your goals, and your dreams. What steps can you take today to get your finances on track? What bad habits, bad investments, and misconceptions should you let go of? This book is packed with 77 days&#8217; worth of real, actionable guidance for getting your money right-for good. It&#8217;s not an investment scheme, not extreme couponing, not something else to add to your daily to-do list. Instead, it&#8217;s about changing you-and the way you handle and think about money-so you can start building the life of your dreams.         </p>
<p>                     The next 11 weeks will be a revelation: Some days you&#8217;ll learn about finance, other days you&#8217;ll learn about yourself. Many days, you will be given a concrete list of things to do-right at that moment-to start steering your financial situation onto the right path.    </p>
<p>                    Learn how to stack the financial odds in your favor<br />
                    Amass savings for retirement, the children&#8217;s college or that next financial emergency<br />
                    Change your perspective on money and its role in your life    </p>
<p>                    Get your financial house in order-and keep it that way    </p>
<p>                     A better life is possible. You do have the power to change things for the better. From Here to Financial Happiness is your personal roadmap to financial freedom.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/from-here-to-financial-happiness-enrich-your-life-in-just-77-days-jonathan-clements-abridged/">From Here to Financial Happiness : Enrich Your Life in Just 77 Days &#8211; Jonathan Clements (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Laws of Wealth : Psychology and the Secret to Investing Success &#8211; Daniel Crosby (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-laws-of-wealth-psychology-and-the-secret-to-investing-success-daniel-crosby-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-laws-of-wealth-psychology-and-the-secret-to-investing-success-daniel-crosby-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times and USA Today bestselling author, Dr Daniel Crosby, comes the behavioral finance book all investors have been waiting for. In The Laws of Wealth, psychologist and behavioral finance expert Daniel Crosby offers an accessible and applied take on a discipline that has long tended toward theory at the expense of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-laws-of-wealth-psychology-and-the-secret-to-investing-success-daniel-crosby-abridged/">The Laws of Wealth : Psychology and the Secret to Investing Success &#8211; Daniel Crosby (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times and USA Today bestselling author, Dr Daniel Crosby, comes the behavioral finance book all investors have been waiting for. In The Laws of Wealth, psychologist and behavioral finance expert Daniel Crosby offers an accessible and applied take on a discipline that has long tended toward theory at the expense of the practical. Readers are treated to real, actionable guidance as the promise of behavioral finance is realised and practical applications for everyday investors are delivered. Crosby presents a framework of timeless principles for managing your behavior and your investing process. He begins by outlining ten rules that are the hallmarks of good investor behavior, including &#8216;Forecasting is for Weathermen&#8217; and &#8216;If You&#8217;re Excited, It&#8217;s Probably a Bad Idea&#8217;. He then goes on to introduce a unique new taxonomy of behavioral investment risk that will enable investors and academics alike to understand behavioral risk in a newly coherent and complete way.From here, attention turns to the four ways in which behavioral risk can be combatted and the five equity selection methods investors should harness to take advantage of behaviorally-induced opportunities in the stock market.<br />
                    Throughout, readers are treated to anecdotes, research and graphics that illustrate the lessons in memorable ways. And in highly valuable &#8216;What now?&#8217; summaries at the end of each chapter, Crosby provides clear, concise direction on what investors should think, ask and do to benefit from the behavioral research. Dr. Crosby&#8217;s training as a clinical psychologist and work as an asset manager provide a unique vantage and result in a book that breaks new ground in behavioral finance. You need to follow the laws of wealth to manage your behavior and improve your investing process!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-laws-of-wealth-psychology-and-the-secret-to-investing-success-daniel-crosby-abridged/">The Laws of Wealth : Psychology and the Secret to Investing Success &#8211; Daniel Crosby (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Secrets of Power Negotiating &#8211; 25th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Roger Dawson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/secrets-of-power-negotiating-25th-anniversary-edition-roger-dawson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/secrets-of-power-negotiating-25th-anniversary-edition-roger-dawson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;This is perhaps the best book on negotiating ever written. Roger&#8217;s powerful, practical principles will save or make you a fortune in the months and years ahead.&#8221; &#8211;Brian Tracy, author, Eat That Frog! and Million Dollar Habits &#8220;This is the one negotiating book that really opened my eyes and gave me practical tools I could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secrets-of-power-negotiating-25th-anniversary-edition-roger-dawson-abridged/">Secrets of Power Negotiating &#8211; 25th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Roger Dawson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;This is perhaps the best book on negotiating ever written. Roger&#8217;s powerful, practical principles will save or make you a fortune in the months and years ahead.&#8221; &#8211;Brian Tracy, author, Eat That Frog! and Million Dollar Habits     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This is the one negotiating book that really opened my eyes and gave me practical tools I could use immediately.&#8221; &#8211;Timothy Ferriss, bestselling author of The 4-Hour Work Week     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A fast, entertaining read that should be required reading for anyone who deals with people. Highly recommended.&#8221; &#8211;Ken Blanchard, coauthor of The One Minute Manager     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I can&#8217;t believe it! Here&#8217;s a book that is packed with wisdom that will help anyone improve their life and yet it is easy and fun to read! Amazing!&#8221; &#8211;Og Mandino, author of The Greatest Salesman in the World     </p>
<p>                     Roger Dawson changed the way business thinks about negotiating.     </p>
<p>                    Secrets of Power Negotiating covers every aspect of the negotiating process with practical, proven advice, from beginning steps to critical final moves: how to recognize unethical tactics, key principles of the Power Negotiating strategy, why money is not as important as everyone thinks, negotiating pressure points, understanding the other party and gaining the upper hand, and analyses of different negotiating styles.<br />
                     Discover all of Roger&#8217;s best tactics, including: 20 surefire negotiating gambitsListening to hidden meanings in conversationWhat &#8220;powers&#8221; you have, such as situational, expertise, information, or charismaticHow to handle the different personalities you&#8217;ll encounter in negotiating</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secrets-of-power-negotiating-25th-anniversary-edition-roger-dawson-abridged/">Secrets of Power Negotiating &#8211; 25th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Roger Dawson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Picture Your Prosperity &#8211; Supplement by Ellen Rogin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/picture-your-prosperity-supplement-by-ellen-rogin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/picture-your-prosperity-supplement-by-ellen-rogin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everyone has a unique vision of a prosperous and secure future. What&#8217;s yours? If someone asked you to describe prosperity and security, what would you see in your mind&#8217;s eye? Is it finally taking that trip to Paris? A beautiful beach house? Or maybe making that last mortgage payment and staying right where you are? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/picture-your-prosperity-supplement-by-ellen-rogin-abridged/">Picture Your Prosperity &#8211; Supplement by Ellen Rogin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everyone has a unique vision of a prosperous and secure future. What&#8217;s yours?<br />
                    If someone asked you to describe prosperity and security, what would you see in your mind&#8217;s eye? Is it finally taking that trip to Paris? A beautiful beach house? Or maybe making that last mortgage payment and staying right where you are? In your vision are you captaining a sailboat? Hiking through a redwood forest? Or simply enjoying a precious moment of peace and contentment?<br />
                    When it comes to financial planning, it&#8217;s easy to jump right into the minutiae of investments, skipping over the deeper questions of what you really want from your money, both now and in the future. But in &#8220;Picture Your Prosperity,&#8221; Ellen Rogin and Lisa Kueng do the opposite. First they&#8217;ll help you figure out exactly what &#8220;you&#8221; need and want. Only then will they show you how to make the smart money decisions that can help turn your vision into reality.<br />
                    If the thought of financial planning and investing sounds about as appealing as a trip to the dentist, you&#8217;re not alone. Many of us avoid the process because it feels too stressful, boring, or difficult. But as Ellen and Lisa have learned from their years in financial services, thinking about money becomes exciting and fun when it&#8217;s tied to your personal vision instead of a pile of technical details. And it can be easier than you think.<br />
                    Once your goal is clear, the authors show you how to design your investments to create the life you&#8217;ve envisioned. Soon you&#8217;ll feel more in control of your finances and on the road to the things that matter most. You&#8217;ll be able to create a plan that&#8217;s broken down into manageable and, dare we say it, &#8220;enjoyable&#8221; steps. You&#8217;ll learn how to handle your money with more joy and less stress, even during turbulent times. And you&#8217;ll explore ways your financial moves can have a huge positive impact on other people.<br />
                    As Rogin and Kueng write, &#8220;Your money is important, but money is meaningless if it can&#8217;t be connected to the rest of your life. Who cares what the totals on your balance sheet or in your bank account are if you can&#8217;t use them to build the kind of future you want? What good is having a brilliant investment strategy if you worry incessantly about losing it, constantly fight with your partner about money, or come home and kick your dog on days the market drops? What if instead you felt positive, peaceful, and prosperous?<br />
                    Get ready to feel more excited than ever about your money, and about all the good things it can bring.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/picture-your-prosperity-supplement-by-ellen-rogin-abridged/">Picture Your Prosperity &#8211; Supplement by Ellen Rogin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Total Money Makeover: Classic Edition : A Proven Plan for Financial Fitness &#8211; Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-total-money-makeover-classic-edition-a-proven-plan-for-financial-fitness-dave-ramsey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funding Of Education & Student Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-total-money-makeover-classic-edition-a-proven-plan-for-financial-fitness-dave-ramsey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to build a budget that actually works for you? Are you ready to transform your relationship with money? This New York Times bestseller has already helped millions of people learn how to develop everyday money-saving habits with the help of America&#8217;s favorite finance coach, Dave Ramsey. By now, you&#8217;ve already heard all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-total-money-makeover-classic-edition-a-proven-plan-for-financial-fitness-dave-ramsey-abridged/">The Total Money Makeover: Classic Edition : A Proven Plan for Financial Fitness &#8211; Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to build a budget that actually works for you? Are you ready to transform your relationship with money? This New York Times bestseller has already helped millions of people learn how to develop everyday money-saving habits with the help of America&#8217;s favorite finance coach, Dave Ramsey.    </p>
<p>                    By now, you&#8217;ve already heard all of the nutty get-rich-quick schemes and the fiscal diet fads that leave you with a lot of quirky ideas but not a penny in your pocket. If you&#8217;re tired of the lies and sick of the false promises, Dave is here to provide practical, long-term help. The Total Money Makeover is the simplest, most straightforward game plan for completely changing your finances. And, best of all, these principles are based on results, not pie-in-the-sky fantasies. This is the financial reset you&#8217;ve been looking for.    </p>
<p>                    The Total Money Makeover: Classic Edition will give you the tools and the encouragement you need to:    </p>
<p>                    Design a sure-fire plan for paying off all debt&#8211;from your cars to your home and everything in between<br />
                    Break bad habits and make lasting changes when it comes to your relationship with money<br />
                    Recognize the 10 most dangerous money myths<br />
                    Secure a healthy nest egg for emergencies and set yourself up for retirement<br />
                    Become financially healthy for life    </p>
<p>                    This edition of The Total Money Makeover includes new, expanded &#8220;Dave Rants&#8221; that tackle marriage conflict, college debt, and so much more. Each copy of The Total Money Makeover: Classic Edition also includes brand new back-of-the-book resources to help you make Total Money Makeover your new reality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-total-money-makeover-classic-edition-a-proven-plan-for-financial-fitness-dave-ramsey-abridged/">The Total Money Makeover: Classic Edition : A Proven Plan for Financial Fitness &#8211; Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Latte Factor : Why You Don&#8217;t Have to Be Rich to Live Rich &#8211; David Bach, John David Mann (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-latte-factor-why-you-dont-have-to-be-rich-to-live-rich-david-bach-john-david-mann-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult Numeracy Guides & Handbooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-latte-factor-why-you-dont-have-to-be-rich-to-live-rich-david-bach-john-david-mann-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES, USA TODAY, WALL STREET JOURNAL, AND INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER Discover #1 New York Times bestselling author David Bach&#8217;s three secrets to financial freedom in an engaging story that will show you that you are richer than you think. Drawing on the author&#8217;s experiences teaching millions of people around the world to live [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-latte-factor-why-you-dont-have-to-be-rich-to-live-rich-david-bach-john-david-mann-abridged/">The Latte Factor : Why You Don&#8217;t Have to Be Rich to Live Rich &#8211; David Bach, John David Mann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES, USA TODAY, WALL STREET JOURNAL, AND INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                    Discover #1 New York Times bestselling author David Bach&#8217;s three secrets to financial freedom in an engaging story that will show you that you are richer than you think. Drawing on the author&#8217;s experiences teaching millions of people around the world to live a rich life, this fast, easy listen reveals how anyone-from millennials to baby boomers-can still make his or her dreams come true.    </p>
<p>                    In this compelling, heartwarming parable, Bach and his bestselling coauthor John David Mann (The Go-Giver) tell the story of Zoey, a twenty-something woman living and working in New York City. Like many young professionals, Zoey is struggling to make ends meet under a growing burden of credit card and student loan debt, working crazy hours at her dream job but still not earning enough to provide a comfortable financial cushion. At her boss&#8217;s suggestion, she makes friends with Henry, the elderly barista at her favorite Brooklyn coffee shop.    </p>
<p>                    Henry soon reveals his &#8220;Three Secrets to Financial Freedom,&#8221; ideas Zoey dismisses at first but whose true power she ultimately comes to appreciate. Over the course of a single week, Zoey discovers that she already earns enough to secure her financial future and realize her truest dreams-all she has to do is make a few easy shifts in her everyday routine.    </p>
<p>                    The Latte Factor demystifies the secrets to achieving financial freedom, inspiring you to realize that it&#8217;s never too late to reach for your dreams. By following the simple, proven path that Henry shows Zoey, anyone can make small changes today that will have big impact for a lifetime, proving once again that &#8220;David Bach is the financial expert to listen to when you&#8217;re intimidated by your finances&#8221; (Tony Robbins, #1 New York Times bestselling author of Money: Master the Game).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-latte-factor-why-you-dont-have-to-be-rich-to-live-rich-david-bach-john-david-mann-abridged/">The Latte Factor : Why You Don&#8217;t Have to Be Rich to Live Rich &#8211; David Bach, John David Mann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Millennial Money &#8211; Patrick O&#8217;Shaughnessy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/millennial-money-patrick-oshaughnessy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/millennial-money-patrick-oshaughnessy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We have witnessed one of the worst stock market beatings ever. As a result, abysmal returns are the new normal, financial experts are ringing the death knell of buy-and-hold, and investorsâ faith in equities has hit an all-time low. You have choices, you can abandon the stock market, or invest for tomorrow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millennial-money-patrick-oshaughnessy-abridged/">Millennial Money &#8211; Patrick O&#8217;Shaughnessy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We have witnessed one of the worst stock market beatings ever. As a result, abysmal returns are the new normal, financial experts are ringing the death knell of buy-and-hold, and investorsâ faith in equities has hit an all-time low. You have choices, you can abandon the stock market, or invest for tomorrow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millennial-money-patrick-oshaughnessy-abridged/">Millennial Money &#8211; Patrick O&#8217;Shaughnessy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The One-Page Financial Plan : A Simple Way To Be Smart About Your Money &#8211; Carl Richards, Jr. (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-one-page-financial-plan-a-simple-way-to-be-smart-about-your-money-carl-richards-jr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-one-page-financial-plan-a-simple-way-to-be-smart-about-your-money-carl-richards-jr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Distills what matters most into something that is easy and fun to read&#8217; Morgan Housel, columnist, The Wall Street Journal A simple, effective way to transform your finances and your life from leading financial advisor and New York Times columnist Carl Richards Creating a financial plan can seem overwhelming, but the best plans aren&#8217;t long [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-one-page-financial-plan-a-simple-way-to-be-smart-about-your-money-carl-richards-jr-abridged/">The One-Page Financial Plan : A Simple Way To Be Smart About Your Money &#8211; Carl Richards, Jr. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Distills what matters most into something that is easy and fun to read&#8217; Morgan Housel, columnist, The Wall Street Journal    </p>
<p>                    A simple, effective way to transform your finances and your life from leading financial advisor and New York Times columnist Carl Richards     </p>
<p>                    Creating a financial plan can seem overwhelming, but the best plans aren&#8217;t long or complicated. A great plan has nothing to do with the details of how to save and invest your money and everything to do with why you&#8217;re doing it in the first place. Knowing what&#8217;s important to you, you will be able to make better decisions in any market conditions.    </p>
<p>                    The One-Page Financial Plan will help you identify your values and goals. Carl Richard&#8217;s simple steps will show you how to prioritize what you really want in life and figure out how to get there.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;In a world where financial advice is (often purposely) complicated and filled with jargon, Carl Richards distils what matters most into something that is easy and fun to read&#8217;  Wall Street Journal    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Feeling tormented by your finances? Read this book. Now.The One-Page Financial Plan helps you identify what you truly want from life, get crystal clear about the financial position you are starting from today, and develop a simple, actionable plan to narrow the gap between the two&#8217;  Manisha Thakor, CEO at MoneyZen Wealth Management</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-one-page-financial-plan-a-simple-way-to-be-smart-about-your-money-carl-richards-jr-abridged/">The One-Page Financial Plan : A Simple Way To Be Smart About Your Money &#8211; Carl Richards, Jr. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Most Important Thing Illuminated : Uncommon Sense for the Thoughtful Investor &#8211; Howard Marks, Foreword by Bruce Greenwald (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Howard Marks&#8217;s The Most Important Thing distilled the investing insight of his celebrated client memos into a single volume and, for the first time, made his time-tested philosophy available to general readers. In this edition, Marks&#8217;s wisdom is joined by the comments, insights, and counterpoints of four renowned investors and investment educators: Christopher C. Davis [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/">The Most Important Thing Illuminated : Uncommon Sense for the Thoughtful Investor &#8211; Howard Marks, Foreword by Bruce Greenwald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Howard Marks&#8217;s The Most Important Thing distilled the investing insight of his celebrated client memos into a single volume and, for the first time, made his time-tested philosophy available to general readers. In this edition, Marks&#8217;s wisdom is joined by the comments, insights, and counterpoints of four renowned investors and investment educators: Christopher C. Davis (Davis Funds), Joel Greenblatt (Gotham Capital), Paul Johnson (Nicusa Capital), and Seth A. Klarman (Baupost Group). These experts lend insight into such concepts as &#8220;second-level thinking,&#8221; the price/value relationship, patient opportunism, and defensive investing. Marks also adds his own annotations, expanding on his book&#8217;s original themes and issues. A new chapter addresses the importance of reasonable expectations, and a foreword by Bruce C. Greenwald, called &#8220;a guru to Wall Street&#8217;s gurus&#8221; by the New York Times, speaks on value investing, productivity, and the economics of information.  ***  Howard Marks, the chairman and cofounder of Oaktree Capital Management, is renowned for his insightful assessments of market opportunity and risk.<br />
                    After four decades spent ascending to the top of the investment management profession, he is today sought out by the world&#8217;s leading value investors, and his client memos brim with insightful commentary and a time-tested, fundamental philosophy. Now for the first time, all readers can benefit from Marks&#8217;s wisdom, concentrated into a single volume that speaks to both the amateur and seasoned investor.  Informed by a lifetime of experience and study, The Most Important Thing explains the keys to successful investment and the pitfalls that can destroy capital or ruin a career. Utilizing passages from his memos to illustrate his ideas, Marks teaches by example, detailing the development of an investment philosophy that fully acknowledges the complexities of investing and the perils of the financial world. Brilliantly applying insight to today&#8217;s volatile markets, Marks offers a volume that is part memoir, part creed, with a number of broad takeaways.  Marks expounds on such concepts as &#8220;second-level thinking,&#8221; the price/value relationship, patient opportunism, and defensive investing.<br />
                    Frankly and honestly assessing his own decisions&#8211;and occasional missteps&#8211;he provides valuable lessons for critical thinking, risk assessment, and investment strategy. Encouraging investors to be &#8220;contrarian,&#8221; Marks wisely judges market cycles and achieves returns through aggressive yet measured action. Which element is the most essential? Successful investing requires thoughtful attention to many separate aspects, and each of Marks&#8217;s subjects proves to be the most important thing.  &#8220;This is that rarity, a useful book.&#8221;&#8211;Warren Buffett</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/">The Most Important Thing Illuminated : Uncommon Sense for the Thoughtful Investor &#8211; Howard Marks, Foreword by Bruce Greenwald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Facebook, PayPal, Alibaba, Uber-these companies have upended entire industries by harnessing a single phenomenon: the platform business model. Platform Revolution delivers the first comprehensive analysis of how platforms match producers and consumers in a multi-sided marketplace, unlocking hidden resources and creating new forms of value. Platform Revolution explores the what, how and why of this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/">Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Facebook, PayPal, Alibaba, Uber-these companies have upended entire industries by harnessing a single phenomenon: the platform business model. Platform Revolution delivers the first comprehensive analysis of how platforms match producers and consumers in a multi-sided marketplace, unlocking hidden resources and creating new forms of value.    </p>
<p>                     Platform Revolution explores the what, how and why of this revolution and provides the first &#8220;owner&#8217;s manual&#8221; for creating a platform marketplace. It provides the essential guide to unlocking the potential of an economic landscape transformed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/">Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Charlie Munger : The Complete Investor &#8211; Tren Griffin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/charlie-munger-the-complete-investor-tren-griffin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/charlie-munger-the-complete-investor-tren-griffin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Charlie Munger, Berkshire Hathaway&#8217;s visionary vice chairman and Warren Buffett&#8217;s indispensable financial partner, has outperformed market indexes again and again, and he believes any investor can do the same. His notion of &#8220;elementary, worldly wisdom&#8221;-a set of interdisciplinary mental models involving economics, business, psychology, ethics, and management-allows him to keep his emotions out of his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/charlie-munger-the-complete-investor-tren-griffin-abridged/">Charlie Munger : The Complete Investor &#8211; Tren Griffin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Charlie Munger, Berkshire Hathaway&#8217;s visionary vice chairman and Warren Buffett&#8217;s indispensable financial partner, has outperformed market indexes again and again, and he believes any investor can do the same. His notion of &#8220;elementary, worldly wisdom&#8221;-a set of interdisciplinary mental models involving economics, business, psychology, ethics, and management-allows him to keep his emotions out of his investments and avoid the common pitfalls of bad judgment.  Munger&#8217;s system has steered his investments for forty years and has guided generations of successful investors. This book presents the essential steps of Munger&#8217;s investing strategy, condensed here for the first time from interviews, speeches, writings, and shareholder letters, and paired with commentary from fund managers, value investors, and business-case historians. Derived from Ben Graham&#8217;s value-investing system, Munger&#8217;s approach is straightforward enough that ordinary investors can apply it to their portfolios. This book is not simply about investing. It is about cultivating mental models for your whole life, but especially for your investments.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/charlie-munger-the-complete-investor-tren-griffin-abridged/">Charlie Munger : The Complete Investor &#8211; Tren Griffin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Financial Diet : A Total Beginner&#8217;s Guide to Getting Good with Money &#8211; Chelsea Fagan, Lauren Ver Hage (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-financial-diet-a-total-beginners-guide-to-getting-good-with-money-chelsea-fagan-lauren-ver-hage-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-financial-diet-a-total-beginners-guide-to-getting-good-with-money-chelsea-fagan-lauren-ver-hage-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*A Refinery29 Best Book of 2018* *One of Real Simple&#8217;s Most Inspiring Books for Graduates* *Indie Personal Finance Bestseller* How to get good with money, even if you have no idea where to start. The Financial Diet is the personal finance book for people who don&#8217;t care about personal finance. Whether you&#8217;re in need of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-financial-diet-a-total-beginners-guide-to-getting-good-with-money-chelsea-fagan-lauren-ver-hage-abridged/">The Financial Diet : A Total Beginner&#8217;s Guide to Getting Good with Money &#8211; Chelsea Fagan, Lauren Ver Hage (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*A Refinery29 Best Book of 2018*<br />
                    *One of Real Simple&#8217;s Most Inspiring Books for Graduates*<br />
                    *Indie Personal Finance Bestseller*     </p>
<p>                    How to get good with money, even if you have no idea where to start.     </p>
<p>                    The Financial Diet is the personal finance book for people who don&#8217;t care about personal finance. Whether you&#8217;re in need of an overspending detox, buried under student debt, or just trying to figure out how to live on an entry-level salary, The Financial Diet gives you tools to make a budget, understand investments, and deal with your credit. Chelsea Fagan has tapped a range of experts to help you make the best choices for you, but she also knows that being smarter with money isn&#8217;t just about what you put in the bank. It&#8217;s about everything&#8211;from the clothes you put in your closet, to your financial relationship habits, to the food you put in your kitchen (instead of ordering in again). So The Financial Diet gives you the tools to negotiate a raise and the perfect cocktail recipe to celebrate your new salary.     </p>
<p>                    The Financial Diet will teach you:<br />
                    &#8211; how to get good with money in a year.<br />
                    &#8211; the ingredients everyone needs to have a budget-friendly kitchen.<br />
                    &#8211; how to talk about awkward money stuff with your friends.<br />
                    &#8211; the best way to make (and stick to!) a budget.<br />
                    &#8211; how to take care of your house like a grown-up.<br />
                    &#8211; what the hell it means to invest (and how you can do it).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-financial-diet-a-total-beginners-guide-to-getting-good-with-money-chelsea-fagan-lauren-ver-hage-abridged/">The Financial Diet : A Total Beginner&#8217;s Guide to Getting Good with Money &#8211; Chelsea Fagan, Lauren Ver Hage (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Money Master the Game : 7 Simple Steps to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/money-master-the-game-7-simple-steps-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mysteries & The Supernatural (Children's/YA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/money-master-the-game-7-simple-steps-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR TONY ROBBINS BRINGS YOU 7 SIMPLE STEPS TO FINANCIAL FREEDOM &#8216;Tony Robbins needs no introduction. He is committed to helping make life better for every investor. Every investor will find this book extremely interesting and illuminating&#8217; Carl Icahn, billionaire and investor &#8216;Tony Robbins is a catalyst for getting people to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-master-the-game-7-simple-steps-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins-abridged/">Money Master the Game : 7 Simple Steps to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR TONY ROBBINS BRINGS YOU 7 SIMPLE STEPS TO FINANCIAL FREEDOM    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Tony Robbins needs no introduction. He is committed to helping make life better for every investor. Every investor will find this book extremely interesting and illuminating&#8217; Carl Icahn, billionaire and investor     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Tony Robbins is a catalyst for getting people to change&#8217; Oprah Winfrey     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Tony Robbins is a genius . . .  His ability to strategically guide people through any challege is unparalleled&#8217; Steve Wynn, CEO and Founder of Wynn Resorts     </p>
<p>                    Tony Robbins, the multimillion-copy bestselling author of Awaken the Giant Within and Unlimited Power has created a 7-step blueprint for securing financial freedom.    </p>
<p>                     Based on extensive research and one-on-one interviews with more than 50 of the most legendary financial experts in the world &#8211; from Carl Icahn, to Warren Buffett, to Jack Bogle and Steve Forbes.     </p>
<p>                     Robbins has a brilliant way of using metaphor and story to illustrate even the most complex financial concepts &#8211; making them simple and actionable. With expert advice on our most important financial decisions, Robbins dispels the myths that often rob people of their financial dreams.    </p>
<p>                    Money: Master the Game contains expert advice for readers of every income level, providing guidance through the steps to become financially free by creating a lifetime income plan. This book delivers invaluable information and essential practices for getting your financial house in order. It&#8217;s the book millions of people have been waiting for.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-master-the-game-7-simple-steps-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins-abridged/">Money Master the Game : 7 Simple Steps to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Wealth of Common Sense : Why Simplicity Trumps Complexity in Any Investment Plan &#8211; Ben Carlson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A simple guide to a smarter strategy for the individual investor A Wealth of Common Sense sheds a refreshing light on investing, and shows you how a simplicity-based framework can lead to better investment decisions. The financial market is a complex system, but that doesn&#8217;t mean it requires a complex strategy; in fact, this false [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/">A Wealth of Common Sense : Why Simplicity Trumps Complexity in Any Investment Plan &#8211; Ben Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A simple guide to a smarter strategy for the individual investor A Wealth of Common Sense sheds a refreshing light on investing, and shows you how a simplicity-based framework can lead to better investment decisions. The financial market is a complex system, but that doesn&#8217;t mean it requires a complex strategy; in fact, this false premise is the driving force behind many investors&#8217; market &#8220;mistakes.&#8221; Information is important, but understanding and perspective are the keys to better decision-making. This book describes the proper way to view the markets and your portfolio, and show you the simple strategies that make investing more profitable, less confusing, and less time-consuming. Without the burden of short-term performance benchmarks, individual investors have the advantage of focusing on the long view, and the freedom to construct the kind of portfolio that will serve their investment goals best. This book proves how complex strategies essentially waste these advantages, and provides an alternative game plan for those ready to simplify.<br />
                    Complexity is often used as a mechanism for talking investors into unnecessary purchases, when all most need is a deeper understanding of conventional options. This book explains which issues you actually should pay attention to, and which ones are simply used for an illusion of intelligence and control. * Keep up with or beat professional money managers * Exploit stock market volatility to your utmost advantage * Learn where advisors and consultants fit into smart strategy * Build a portfolio that makes sense for your particular situation You don&#8217;t have to outsmart the market if you can simply outperform it. Cut through the confusion and noise and focus on what actually matters. A Wealth of Common Sense clears the air, and gives you the insight you need to become a smarter, more successful investor.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/">A Wealth of Common Sense : Why Simplicity Trumps Complexity in Any Investment Plan &#8211; Ben Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of the most important books of our modern era&#8221; -Amb. Jaime de Bourbon For anyone struggling with conflict, this book can transform you. Negotiating the Nonnegotiable takes you on a journey into the heart and soul of conflict, providing unique insight into the emotional undercurrents that too often sweep us out to sea. With [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/">Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of the most important books of our modern era&#8221; -Amb. Jaime de Bourbon    </p>
<p>                    For anyone struggling with conflict, this book can transform you. Negotiating the Nonnegotiable takes you on a journey into the heart and soul of conflict, providing unique insight into the emotional undercurrents that too often sweep us out to sea. With vivid stories of his closed-door sessions with warring political groups, disputing businesspeople, and families in crisis, Daniel Shapiro presents a universally applicable method to successfully navigate conflict.  A deep, provocative book to reflect on and wrestle with, this book can change your life.    </p>
<p>                     Be warned: This book is not a quick fix. Real change takes work. You will learn how to master five emotional dynamics that can sabotage conflict outside your awareness:    </p>
<p>                    1. Vertigo: How can you avoid      getting emotionally consumed in conflict?<br />
                    2. Repetition compulsion: How can you stop      repeating the same conflicts again and again?<br />
                    3. Taboos: How can you discuss      sensitive issues at the heart of the conflict?<br />
                    4. Assault on the sacred: What should you do if      your values feel threatened?<br />
                    5. Identity politics: What can you do if      others use politics against you?     </p>
<p>                    In our era of discontent, this is just the book we need to resolve conflict in our own lives and in the world around us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/">Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get a Financial Life : Personal Finance in Your Twenties and Thirties &#8211; Beth Kobliner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/get-a-financial-life-personal-finance-in-your-twenties-and-thirties-beth-kobliner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/get-a-financial-life-personal-finance-in-your-twenties-and-thirties-beth-kobliner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A completely revised and updated fourth edition of the New York Times bestseller, designed to guide younger adults through the world of personal finance. More than ever before, people in their twenties and thirties need help getting their financial lives in order. And who could blame them? These so-called millennials have come of age in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-a-financial-life-personal-finance-in-your-twenties-and-thirties-beth-kobliner-abridged/">Get a Financial Life : Personal Finance in Your Twenties and Thirties &#8211; Beth Kobliner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A completely revised and updated fourth edition of the New York Times bestseller, designed to guide younger adults through the world of personal finance.     </p>
<p>                    More than ever before, people in their twenties and thirties need help getting their financial lives in order. And who could blame them? These so-called millennials have come of age in the wake of the worst economic crisis in memory, and are now trying to get by in its aftermath. They owe record levels of student loan debt, face sky-high rents, and struggle to live on a budget in an uncertain economy.     </p>
<p>                     It&#8217;s time for them to get a financial life.     </p>
<p>                     For two decades, Beth Kobliner&#8217;s bestseller has been the financial bible for people in their twenties and thirties. With her down-to-earth style, she has taught them how to get out of debt, learn to save, and invest for their futures. In this completely revised and updated edition, Kobliner shares brand-new insights and concrete, actionable advice geared to help a new generation of readers form healthy financial habits that will last a lifetime. With fresh material that reflects the changing digital world, Get a Financial Life remains an essential tool for young people learning how to manage their money.     </p>
<p>                     From tackling taxes to boosting credit scores, Get a Financial Life can show those just starting out how to decrease their debt, avoid common money mistakes, and navigate the world of personal finance in today&#8217;s ever-changing landscape.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-a-financial-life-personal-finance-in-your-twenties-and-thirties-beth-kobliner-abridged/">Get a Financial Life : Personal Finance in Your Twenties and Thirties &#8211; Beth Kobliner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Geometry of Wealth : How to shape a life of money and meaning &#8211; Brian Portnoy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-geometry-of-wealth-how-to-shape-a-life-of-money-and-meaning-brian-portnoy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-geometry-of-wealth-how-to-shape-a-life-of-money-and-meaning-brian-portnoy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How does money figure into a happy life? In The Geometry of Wealth, behavioral finance expert Brian Portnoy delivers an inspired answer, building on the critical distinction between being rich and being wealthy. While one is an unsatisfying treadmill, the other is the ability to underwrite a meaningful life, however one chooses to define that. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-geometry-of-wealth-how-to-shape-a-life-of-money-and-meaning-brian-portnoy-abridged/">The Geometry of Wealth : How to shape a life of money and meaning &#8211; Brian Portnoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How does money figure into a happy life?    </p>
<p>                    In The Geometry of Wealth, behavioral finance expert Brian Portnoy delivers an inspired answer, building on the critical distinction between being rich and being wealthy. While one is an unsatisfying treadmill, the other is the ability to underwrite a meaningful life, however one chooses to define that. Truly viewed, wealth is funded contentment.    </p>
<p>                    At the heart of this groundbreaking perspective, Portnoy takes readers on a journey toward wealth, informed by disciplines ranging from ancient history to modern neuroscience. He contends that tackling the big questions about a joyful life and tending to financial decisions are complementary, not separate, tasks.     </p>
<p>                    These big questions include:<br />
                    &#8211; How is the human brain wired for two distinct experiences of happiness? And why can money &#8220;buy&#8221; one but not the other?<br />
                    &#8211; What are the touchstones of a meaningful life, and are they affordable?<br />
                    &#8211; Why is market savvy among the least important sources of wealth but self-awareness is among the most?<br />
                    &#8211; How does one strike a balance between striving for more while being content with enough?    </p>
<p>                    This journey memorably contours along three basic shapes: A circle, triangle and square help us to visualize how we adapt to evolving circumstances, set clear priorities, and find empowerment in simplicity. In this accessible and entertaining book, Portnoy reveals that true wealth is achievable for many &#8211; including those who despair it is out of reach &#8211; but only in the context of a life in which purpose and practice are thoughtfully calibrated.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-geometry-of-wealth-how-to-shape-a-life-of-money-and-meaning-brian-portnoy-abridged/">The Geometry of Wealth : How to shape a life of money and meaning &#8211; Brian Portnoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Breakfast Club for 40-Somethings : A Novel Approach to Unlearning Money and Reinventing Your Life &#8211; Vanessa Stoykov (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-breakfast-club-for-40-somethings-a-novel-approach-to-unlearning-money-and-reinventing-your-life-vanessa-stoykov-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-breakfast-club-for-40-somethings-a-novel-approach-to-unlearning-money-and-reinventing-your-life-vanessa-stoykov-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new way of seeing life and money High school&#8217;s over. We&#8217;re no longer the nerd, the athlete, the princess or the bad boy. Instead, we are the parent, worker, wife, husband, daughter or son. But we all have things in common &#8211; and one of them is money. People have always sought financial freedom, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-breakfast-club-for-40-somethings-a-novel-approach-to-unlearning-money-and-reinventing-your-life-vanessa-stoykov-abridged/">The Breakfast Club for 40-Somethings : A Novel Approach to Unlearning Money and Reinventing Your Life &#8211; Vanessa Stoykov (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new way of seeing life and money    </p>
<p>                    High school&#8217;s over. We&#8217;re no longer the nerd, the athlete, the princess or the bad boy. Instead, we are the parent, worker, wife, husband, daughter or son. But we all have things in common &#8211; and one of them is money.     </p>
<p>                    People have always sought financial freedom, but our influences, from our parents to our community, have made our grounding in money anything but helpful. In fact, that grounding might be the thing that is holding us back. The Breakfast Club for 40-Somethings draws upon the five major lessons you need to unlearn about the way you see your life and money to give you the best chance of getting the future you want.    </p>
<p>                    Written in the form of a novel from the perspective of six unique characters, the book explores how the different financial decisions and behaviours of each character have led to their current situations. Through this entertaining story, this guide presents the invaluable financial and life lessons you need to understand, to build a solid foundation for your life, no matter your situation.    </p>
<p>                    If you don&#8217;t like traditional self-help or finance books, this is for you. The Breakfast Club for 40-Somethings offers a new and entertaining way to change your long-term financial behaviours for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-breakfast-club-for-40-somethings-a-novel-approach-to-unlearning-money-and-reinventing-your-life-vanessa-stoykov-abridged/">The Breakfast Club for 40-Somethings : A Novel Approach to Unlearning Money and Reinventing Your Life &#8211; Vanessa Stoykov (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Millenial Money Makeover : Escape Debt, Save for Your Future and Live the Rich Life Now &#8211; Conor Richardson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/millenial-money-makeover-escape-debt-save-for-your-future-and-live-the-rich-life-now-conor-richardson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/millenial-money-makeover-escape-debt-save-for-your-future-and-live-the-rich-life-now-conor-richardson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over half of Millennials are freaked out by their finances. Luckily, with Millennial Money Makeover readers now have a guide to help them navigate the financial issues of their time. Certified public accountant Conor Richardson offers a refreshingly helpful and elegantly designed program to tackle essential money matters. Millennial Money Makeover takes readers on a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millenial-money-makeover-escape-debt-save-for-your-future-and-live-the-rich-life-now-conor-richardson-abridged/">Millenial Money Makeover : Escape Debt, Save for Your Future and Live the Rich Life Now &#8211; Conor Richardson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Over half of Millennials are freaked out by their finances. Luckily, with  Millennial Money Makeover readers now have a guide to help them navigate the financial issues of their time. Certified public accountant Conor Richardson offers a refreshingly helpful and elegantly designed program to tackle essential money matters.     </p>
<p>                    Millennial Money Makeover takes readers on a six-step journey to transform their financial life and set them up for lifelong success. From learning how to pay off student loans insanely fast to optimizing a financial ecosystem, Millennial Money Makeover teaches readers how to reclaim their financial future and jump-start the path to the rich life.    </p>
<p>                    Built for readers in their twenties and thirties, this book gives Millennials a proven playbook. Learn new hacks like how using robo-advisors can increase your returns and how leveraging delayed gratification when buying your first home can save you thousands. Whether you are planning a passion budget, figuring out how to finally purchase that big-ticket item, or thinking about taking your first dip into investing, Conor will show you the way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millenial-money-makeover-escape-debt-save-for-your-future-and-live-the-rich-life-now-conor-richardson-abridged/">Millenial Money Makeover : Escape Debt, Save for Your Future and Live the Rich Life Now &#8211; Conor Richardson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get What&#8217;s Yours : The Secrets to Maxing Out Your Social Security &#8211; Professor of Economics Laurence J Kotlikoff, Philip Moeller, Paul Solman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/get-whats-yours-the-secrets-to-maxing-out-your-social-security-professor-of-economics-laurence-j-kotlikoff-philip-moeller-paul-solman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare & Benefit Systems]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/get-whats-yours-the-secrets-to-maxing-out-your-social-security-professor-of-economics-laurence-j-kotlikoff-philip-moeller-paul-solman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Social Security law has changed! Get What&#8217;s Yours has been revised and updated to reflect new regulations that took effect on April 29, 2016. Get What&#8217;s Yours has proven itself to be the definitive book about how to navigate the forbidding maze of Social Security and emerge with the highest possible benefits. It is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-whats-yours-the-secrets-to-maxing-out-your-social-security-professor-of-economics-laurence-j-kotlikoff-philip-moeller-paul-solman-abridged/">Get What&#8217;s Yours : The Secrets to Maxing Out Your Social Security &#8211; Professor of Economics Laurence J Kotlikoff, Philip Moeller, Paul Solman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Social Security law has changed! Get What&#8217;s Yours has been revised and updated to reflect new regulations that took effect on April 29, 2016.     </p>
<p>                    Get What&#8217;s Yours has proven itself to be the definitive book about how to navigate the forbidding maze of Social Security and emerge with the highest possible benefits. It is an engaging manual of tactics and strategies written by well-known financial commentators that is unobtainable elsewhere. You could try reading all 2,728 rules of the Social Security system (and the thousands of explanations of these rules), but academia&#8217;s Kotlikoff, the popular press&#8217;s Moeller, and public television&#8217;s Solman explain the Social Security system just as comprehensively, and a lot more comprehensibly. Moreover, they demonstrate that what you don&#8217;t know can seriously hurt you: wrong decisions about which Social Security benefits to apply for cost individual retirees tens of thousands of dollars in lost income every year. (Some of those people are even in the book.)     </p>
<p>                    Changes to Social Security that take effect in 2016 make it more important than ever to wait as long as possible (until age 70, if possible) to claim Social Security benefits. The new law also has significant implications for those who wish to claim divorced spousal benefits (and how many Social Security recipients even know about divorced spousal benefits?). Besides addressing these and other issues, this revised edition contains a chapter explaining how Medicare rules can shape Social Security decisions.     </p>
<p>                    Many other personal-finance books briefly address Social Security, but none offers the full, authoritative, yet conversational analysis of Get What&#8217;s Yours.     </p>
<p>                    Get What&#8217;s Yours explains Social Security benefits through basic strategies and stirring stories. It covers the most frequent benefit scenarios faced by married retired couples; by divorced retirees; by widows and widowers. It explains what to do if you&#8217;re a retired parent of dependent children; disabled; an eligible beneficiary who continues to work. It addresses the tax consequences of your choices, as well as the financial implications for other investments. It does all this and more.     </p>
<p>                    There are more than 52 million Americans aged 54 to 69. Ten thousand of them reach Social Security&#8217;s full retirement age of 66 every day. For all these people&#8211;and for their families and friends&#8211;Get What&#8217;s Yours has proven to be an invaluable, and therefore indispensable, tool.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-whats-yours-the-secrets-to-maxing-out-your-social-security-professor-of-economics-laurence-j-kotlikoff-philip-moeller-paul-solman-abridged/">Get What&#8217;s Yours : The Secrets to Maxing Out Your Social Security &#8211; Professor of Economics Laurence J Kotlikoff, Philip Moeller, Paul Solman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Science of Getting Rich : Attracting Financial Success through Creative Thought &#8211; Wallace D. Wattles (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-science-of-getting-rich-attracting-financial-success-through-creative-thought-wallace-d-wattles-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-science-of-getting-rich-attracting-financial-success-through-creative-thought-wallace-d-wattles-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his bestselling book, Wallace D. Wattles explains that &#8220;universal mind&#8221; underlies and permeates all creation. Through the process of visualization we can engage the law of attraction&#8211;impressing our thoughts upon &#8220;formless substance&#8221; and bringing the desired object or circumstances into material form. The author emphasizes the critical importance of attitude: only by aligning ourselves [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-of-getting-rich-attracting-financial-success-through-creative-thought-wallace-d-wattles-abridged/">The Science of Getting Rich : Attracting Financial Success through Creative Thought &#8211; Wallace D. Wattles (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his bestselling book, Wallace D. Wattles explains that &#8220;universal mind&#8221; underlies and permeates all creation. Through the process of visualization we can engage the law of attraction&#8211;impressing our thoughts upon &#8220;formless substance&#8221; and bringing the desired object or circumstances into material form. The author emphasizes the critical importance of attitude: only by aligning ourselves with the positive forces of natural law can we gain unlimited access to the creative mind and its abundant rewards. The Science of Getting Richholds the secret to how economic and emotional security can be achieved in a practical, imaginative, and noncompetitive way, while maintaining a loving and harmonious relationship with all of life. By living in accordance with the positive principles outlined in this book, we can find our rightful place in the cosmic scheme and create for ourselves an environment in which to grow in wealth, wisdom, and happiness. Rhonda Byrne, in her book and DVD, The Secret, tells how a 100-year-old book entered her life and changed it forever. Here is that book. Written in 1910, The Science of Getting Richinspired Byrne to create her bestselling DVD, and subsequently, to write her book. She has said that it &#8220;gave me a glimpse of The Secret. It was like a flame inside of my heart. And with every day since, it&#8217;s just become a raging fire of wanting to share all of this with the world.&#8221; &#8220;There is a science of getting rich. It is an exact science, like algebra or arithmetic. There are certain laws which govern the process of acquiring riches. Once a person learns and obeys these laws, he will get rich with mathematical certainty.&#8221; &#8211;Wallace D. Wattles, The Science of Getting Rich</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-of-getting-rich-attracting-financial-success-through-creative-thought-wallace-d-wattles-abridged/">The Science of Getting Rich : Attracting Financial Success through Creative Thought &#8211; Wallace D. Wattles (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Your Retirement Salary : How to use your lifetime of pension savings to pay yourself an income in your retirement &#8211; Richard Dyson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/your-retirement-salary-how-to-use-your-lifetime-of-pension-savings-to-pay-yourself-an-income-in-your-retirement-richard-dyson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/your-retirement-salary-how-to-use-your-lifetime-of-pension-savings-to-pay-yourself-an-income-in-your-retirement-richard-dyson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You have spent a few decades working, earning a salary from your employers, and saving into company and personal pensions along the way. Now, retirement is approaching. How will you turn your savings into a salary to pay for essentials and leisure time in retirement? How will you make sure that you don&#8217;t run out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/your-retirement-salary-how-to-use-your-lifetime-of-pension-savings-to-pay-yourself-an-income-in-your-retirement-richard-dyson-abridged/">Your Retirement Salary : How to use your lifetime of pension savings to pay yourself an income in your retirement &#8211; Richard Dyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You have spent a few decades working, earning a salary from your employers, and saving into company and personal pensions along the way. Now, retirement is approaching.<br />
                     How will you turn your savings into a salary to pay for essentials and leisure time in retirement? How will you make sure that you don&#8217;t run out of money too soon? What do the UK pension freedoms mean for you?     </p>
<p>                    In this one-of-a-kind book, personal finance experts Richard Dyson and Richard Evans answer these questions and equip you with everything you need to know to turn your pension savings into an income that will last throughout your retirement.<br />
                     You will learn:<br />
                    &#8212; How to take control of your pension savings by tracking down all of your pension pots and combining them.<br />
                    &#8212; When you can afford to retire.<br />
                    &#8212; Steps to take to avoid running out of money.<br />
                    &#8212; How to build an income-paying portfolio of fund investments from scratch.<br />
                    &#8212; How to withdraw a sustainable income from your portfolio.<br />
                    &#8212; How annuities work and whether they have a role for you.<br />
                    &#8212; How to make the most of the tax rules.<br />
                    &#8212; The contribution made by the State Pension.<br />
                    &#8212; When to seek professional advice.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/your-retirement-salary-how-to-use-your-lifetime-of-pension-savings-to-pay-yourself-an-income-in-your-retirement-richard-dyson-abridged/">Your Retirement Salary : How to use your lifetime of pension savings to pay yourself an income in your retirement &#8211; Richard Dyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The best-selling index investing &#8220;bible&#8221; offers new information and is updated to reflect the latest market data The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the classic guide to getting smart about the market. Legendary mutual fund veteran John C. Bogle reveals his key to getting more out of investing: low-cost index funds. Bogle describes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/">The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The best-selling index investing &#8220;bible&#8221; offers new information and is updated to reflect the latest market data The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the classic guide to getting smart about the market. Legendary mutual fund veteran John C. Bogle reveals his key to getting more out of investing: low-cost index funds. Bogle describes the simplest and most effective investment strategy for building wealth over the long term: buy and hold, at very low cost, a mutual fund that tracks the S&#038;P 500 Stock Index. Such an index portfolio is the only investment that guarantees your fair share of stock market returns. This strategy is favored by Warren Buffett, who has endorsed this best selling 10th Anniversary Edition. The book shows you how to make index investing work for you and help you achieve your financial goals, cut through the hype to see what&#8217;s really in your best interest, and analyze the metrics that truly matter. You&#8217;ll gain candid insight from some of the world&#8217;s best financial minds: not only Warren Buffett, but Benjamin Graham, Paul Samuelson, Burton Malkiel, and others.<br />
                    Updated with current data and laced with two new chapters on asset allocation and retirement investing, the new Little Book of Common Sense Investing gives you a solid strategy for building your financial future. * Build a broadly diversified, low-cost portfolio without the risks of individual stocks, manager selection, and sector rotation * Forget the fads and focus on what works in the real world * Emphasize business reality over market expectations * Understand how index investing is the only game that assures your fair share of stock market returns Too many investors trade franticly, turning a winners game into a losers game, while index investing allows you to sit back and let the market do the work for you. Learn how to harness the magic of compounding returns while avoiding the tyranny of compounding costs. Bogle describes his simple method for developing rational expectations for future market returns, and what he sees coming over the next decade.  The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the guidebook to your financial future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/">The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019    </p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review    </p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.    </p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.    </p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.    </p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sprint : How To Solve Big Problems and Test New Ideas in Just Five Days &#8211; Jake Knapp, John Zeratsky, Braden Kowitz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sprint-how-to-solve-big-problems-and-test-new-ideas-in-just-five-days-jake-knapp-john-zeratsky-braden-kowitz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sprint-how-to-solve-big-problems-and-test-new-ideas-in-just-five-days-jake-knapp-john-zeratsky-braden-kowitz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES bestseller WALL STREET JOURNAL bestseller &#8216;Sprint offers a transformative formua for testing ideas that works whether you&#8217;re at a startup or a large organization. Within five days, you&#8217;ll move from idea to prototype to decision, saving you and your team countless hours and countless dollars. A must read for entrepreneurs of all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sprint-how-to-solve-big-problems-and-test-new-ideas-in-just-five-days-jake-knapp-john-zeratsky-braden-kowitz-abridged/">Sprint : How To Solve Big Problems and Test New Ideas in Just Five Days &#8211; Jake Knapp, John Zeratsky, Braden Kowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES bestseller<br />
                    WALL STREET JOURNAL bestseller    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Sprint offers a transformative formua for testing ideas that works whether you&#8217;re at a startup or a large organization. Within five days, you&#8217;ll move from idea to prototype to decision, saving you and your team countless hours and countless dollars. A must read for entrepreneurs of all stripes&#8217; Eric Ries, author of The Lean Startup    </p>
<p>                    From three partners at Google Ventures, a unique five-day process for  solving tough business problems, proven at more than 100 companies.          </p>
<p>                    Entrepreneurs and leaders face big questions every day: What&#8217;s the most important place to focus your effort, and how do you start? What will your idea look like in real life? How many meetings and discussions does it take before you can be sure you have the right solution?    </p>
<p>                    Now there&#8217;s a surefire way to answer these important questions: the sprint. Designer Jake Knapp created the five-day process at Google, where sprints were used on everything from Google Search to Google X. He joined Braden Kowitz and John Zeratsky at Google Ventures, and together they have completed more than one hundred sprints with companies in mobile, e-commerce, healthcare, finance, and more.    </p>
<p>                    A practical guide to answering critical business questions, Sprint is a book for teams of any size, from small startups to Fortune 100s, from teachers to nonprofits. It&#8217;s for anyone with a big opportunity, problem, or idea who needs to get answers today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sprint-how-to-solve-big-problems-and-test-new-ideas-in-just-five-days-jake-knapp-john-zeratsky-braden-kowitz-abridged/">Sprint : How To Solve Big Problems and Test New Ideas in Just Five Days &#8211; Jake Knapp, John Zeratsky, Braden Kowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Millionaire Next Door : The Surprising Secrets of America&#8217;s Wealthy &#8211; Thomas J. Stanley, William D. Danko, Ph.D (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-millionaire-next-door-the-surprising-secrets-of-americas-wealthy-thomas-j-stanley-william-d-danko-ph-d-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-millionaire-next-door-the-surprising-secrets-of-americas-wealthy-thomas-j-stanley-william-d-danko-ph-d-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling The Millionaire Next Door identifies seven common traits that show up again and again among those who have accumulated wealth. Most of the truly wealthy in this country don&#8217;t live in Beverly Hills or on Park Avenue-they live next door. This new edition, the first since 1998, includes a new foreword for the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-millionaire-next-door-the-surprising-secrets-of-americas-wealthy-thomas-j-stanley-william-d-danko-ph-d-abridged/">The Millionaire Next Door : The Surprising Secrets of America&#8217;s Wealthy &#8211; Thomas J. Stanley, William D. Danko, Ph.D (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling The Millionaire Next Door identifies seven common traits that show up again and again among those who have accumulated wealth. Most of the truly wealthy in this country don&#8217;t live in Beverly Hills or on Park Avenue-they live next door. This new edition, the first since 1998, includes a new foreword for the twenty-first century by Dr. Thomas J. Stanley.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-millionaire-next-door-the-surprising-secrets-of-americas-wealthy-thomas-j-stanley-william-d-danko-ph-d-abridged/">The Millionaire Next Door : The Surprising Secrets of America&#8217;s Wealthy &#8211; Thomas J. Stanley, William D. Danko, Ph.D (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Strategies for Wealth &#038; Happiness : Power Ideas from America&#8217;s Foremost Business Philosopher &#8211; Jim Rohn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/7-strategies-for-wealth-happiness-power-ideas-from-americas-foremost-business-philosopher-jim-rohn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/7-strategies-for-wealth-happiness-power-ideas-from-americas-foremost-business-philosopher-jim-rohn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unlock the Fountain of Prosperity Inside You! &#8220;I truly believe Jim Rohn is an extraordinary human being whose philosophy can enhance the quality of life for anyone.&#8221; &#8211;Anthony Robbins &#8220;Few men are endowed with Jim Rohn&#8217;s ability to motivate and effect changes in other human beings.&#8221; &#8211;Tom Hopkins &#8220;Jim Rohn . . . is one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/7-strategies-for-wealth-happiness-power-ideas-from-americas-foremost-business-philosopher-jim-rohn-abridged/">7 Strategies for Wealth &#038; Happiness : Power Ideas from America&#8217;s Foremost Business Philosopher &#8211; Jim Rohn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unlock the Fountain of Prosperity Inside You!<br />
                     &#8220;I truly believe Jim Rohn is an extraordinary human being whose philosophy can enhance the quality of life for anyone.&#8221; &#8211;Anthony Robbins    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Few men are endowed with Jim Rohn&#8217;s ability to motivate and effect changes in other human beings.&#8221; &#8211;Tom Hopkins  &#8220;Jim Rohn . . . is one of the most profound thinkers and mind expanding individuals I&#8217;ve ever had a chance to listen to.&#8221; &#8212; Les Brown  &#8220;Jim Rohn is a master motivator&#8211;he has style, substance, charisma, relevance, charm, and what he says makes a difference . . . The world would be a better place if everyone heard my friend Jim Rohn.&#8221; &#8211;Mark Victor Hansen  You don&#8217;t have to choose between wealth and happiness&#8211;they spring from the same fountain of abundance. With this book, you&#8217;ll discover the seven essential strategies you need for success:  -Unleash the Power of Goals<br />
                     -Seek Knowledge<br />
                     -Learn the Miracle of Personal Development<br />
                     -Control Your Finances<br />
                     -Master Time<br />
                     -Surround Yourself with Winners<br />
                     -Learn the Art of Living Well Author Jim Rohn&#8217;s philosophy has helped millions change their lives for the better. Find out what it can do for you!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/7-strategies-for-wealth-happiness-power-ideas-from-americas-foremost-business-philosopher-jim-rohn-abridged/">7 Strategies for Wealth &#038; Happiness : Power Ideas from America&#8217;s Foremost Business Philosopher &#8211; Jim Rohn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everyday Millionaires &#8211; Chris Hogan, Foreword by Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everyday-millionaires-chris-hogan-foreword-by-dave-ramsey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everyday-millionaires-chris-hogan-foreword-by-dave-ramsey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Everyday Millionaires, #1 national best-selling author Chris Hoganwill show you how ordinary people built extraordinary wealth&#8211;and how you can too. You&#8217;ll learn how millionaires live on less than they make, avoid debt, invest, are disciplined and responsible! This book is based on the largest study EVER conducted on 10,000 U.S. millionaires&#8211;and the results will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everyday-millionaires-chris-hogan-foreword-by-dave-ramsey-abridged/">Everyday Millionaires &#8211; Chris Hogan, Foreword by Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Everyday Millionaires, #1 national best-selling author Chris Hoganwill show you how ordinary people built extraordinary wealth&#8211;and how you can too. You&#8217;ll learn how millionaires live on less than they make, avoid debt, invest, are disciplined and responsible!    </p>
<p>                    This book is based on the largest study EVER conducted on 10,000 U.S. millionaires&#8211;and the results will shock you! You&#8217;ll learn that building wealth has almost NOTHING to do with your income or your background! It doesn&#8217;t matter where you come from. It matters where you&#8217;re going.    </p>
<p>                    Most people think it takes crazy investing knowledge, a giant salary, a streak of luck, or a huge inheritance to become a millionaire. But that couldn&#8217;t be further from the truth! Here&#8217;s what you need to understand: if you&#8217;re willing to do the work&#8211;if you&#8217;ll follow the stuff we teach, if you&#8217;ll commit to our plan&#8211;then you CAN become a millionaire.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everyday-millionaires-chris-hogan-foreword-by-dave-ramsey-abridged/">Everyday Millionaires &#8211; Chris Hogan, Foreword by Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Education of a Value Investor : My Transformative Quest for Wealth, Wisdom, and Enlightenment &#8211; Guy Spier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-education-of-a-value-investor-my-transformative-quest-for-wealth-wisdom-and-enlightenment-guy-spier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-education-of-a-value-investor-my-transformative-quest-for-wealth-wisdom-and-enlightenment-guy-spier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What happens when a young Wall Street investment banker spends a small fortune to have lunch with Warren Buffett? He becomes a real value investor. In this fascinating inside story, Guy Spier details his career from Harvard MBA to hedge fund manager. But the path was not so straightforward. Spier reveals his transformation from a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-a-value-investor-my-transformative-quest-for-wealth-wisdom-and-enlightenment-guy-spier-abridged/">The Education of a Value Investor : My Transformative Quest for Wealth, Wisdom, and Enlightenment &#8211; Guy Spier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What happens when a young Wall Street investment banker spends a small fortune to have lunch with Warren Buffett? He becomes a real value investor. In this fascinating inside story, Guy Spier details his career from Harvard MBA to hedge fund manager. But the path was not so straightforward. Spier reveals his transformation from a Gordon Gekko wannabe, driven by greed, to a sophisticated investor who enjoys success without selling his soul to the highest bidder. Spier&#8217;s journey is similar to the thousands that flock to Wall Street every year with their shiny new diplomas, aiming to be King of Wall Street. Yet what Guy realized just in the nick of time was that the King really lived 1,500 miles away in Omaha, Nebraska. Spier determinedly set out to create a new career in his own way. Along the way he learned some powerful lessons which include: why the right mentors and partners are critical to long term success on Wall Street; why a topnotch education can sometimes get in the way of your success; that real learning doesn&#8217;t begin until you are on your own; and how the best lessons from Warren Buffett have less to do with investing and more to do with being true to yourself.<br />
                    Spier also reveals some of his own winning investment strategies, detailing deals that were winners but also what he learned from deals that went south. Part memoir, part Wall Street advice, and part how-to, Guy Spier takes readers on a ride through Wall Street but more importantly provides those that want to take a different path with the insight, guidance, and inspiration they need to carve out their own definition of success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-a-value-investor-my-transformative-quest-for-wealth-wisdom-and-enlightenment-guy-spier-abridged/">The Education of a Value Investor : My Transformative Quest for Wealth, Wisdom, and Enlightenment &#8211; Guy Spier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rich Dad Poor Dad : What the Rich Teach Their Kids About Money That the Poor and Middle Class Do Not! &#8211; Robert T. Kiyosaki (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rich-dad-poor-dad-what-the-rich-teach-their-kids-about-money-that-the-poor-and-middle-class-do-not-robert-t-kiyosaki-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rich-dad-poor-dad-what-the-rich-teach-their-kids-about-money-that-the-poor-and-middle-class-do-not-robert-t-kiyosaki-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s been nearly 25 years since Robert Kiyosaki&#8217;s Rich Dad Poor Dad first made waves in the Personal Finance arena. It has since become the #1 Personal Finance book of all time&#8230; translated into dozens of languages and sold around the world. Rich Dad Poor Dad is Robert&#8217;s story of growing up with two dads [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rich-dad-poor-dad-what-the-rich-teach-their-kids-about-money-that-the-poor-and-middle-class-do-not-robert-t-kiyosaki-abridged/">Rich Dad Poor Dad : What the Rich Teach Their Kids About Money That the Poor and Middle Class Do Not! &#8211; Robert T. Kiyosaki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s been nearly 25 years since Robert Kiyosaki&#8217;s Rich Dad Poor Dad first made waves in the Personal Finance arena.<br />
                    It has since become the #1 Personal Finance book of all time&#8230; translated into dozens of languages and sold around the world.    </p>
<p>                    Rich Dad Poor Dad is Robert&#8217;s story of growing up with two dads   his real father and the father of his best friend, his rich dad   and the ways in which both men shaped his thoughts about money and investing. The book explodes the myth that you need to earn a high income to be rich and explains the difference between working for money and having your money work for you.    </p>
<p>                    20 Years&#8230; 20/20 Hindsight    </p>
<p>                    In the 20th Anniversary Edition of this classic, Robert offers an update on what we&#8217;ve seen over the past 20 years related to money, investing, and the global economy. Sidebars throughout the book will take readers &#8220;fast forward&#8221;   from 1997 to today   as Robert assesses how the principles taught by his rich dad have stood the test of time.    </p>
<p>                    In many ways, the messages of Rich Dad Poor Dad, messages that were criticized and challenged two decades ago, are more meaningful, relevant and important today than they were 20 years ago.    </p>
<p>                    As always, readers can expect that Robert will be candid, insightful&#8230; and continue to rock more than a few boats in his retrospective.    </p>
<p>                    Will there be a few surprises? Count on it.    </p>
<p>                    Rich Dad Poor Dad&#8230;    </p>
<p>                      Explodes the myth that you need to earn a high income to become rich<br />
                      Challenges the belief that your house is an asset<br />
                      Shows parents why they can&#8217;t rely on the school system to teach their kids<br />
                      about money<br />
                      Defines once and for all an asset and a liability<br />
                      Teaches you what to teach your kids about money for their future financial<br />
                      success</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rich-dad-poor-dad-what-the-rich-teach-their-kids-about-money-that-the-poor-and-middle-class-do-not-robert-t-kiyosaki-abridged/">Rich Dad Poor Dad : What the Rich Teach Their Kids About Money That the Poor and Middle Class Do Not! &#8211; Robert T. Kiyosaki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Entreleadership : 20 Years of Practical Business Wisdom from the Trenches &#8211; Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/entreleadership-20-years-of-practical-business-wisdom-from-the-trenches-dave-ramsey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/entreleadership-20-years-of-practical-business-wisdom-from-the-trenches-dave-ramsey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author of The Total Money Makeover and radio and podcast host Dave Ramsey comes an informative guide based on how he grew a successful, multimillion dollar company from a card table in his living room. Your company is only as strong as your leaders. These are the men and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/entreleadership-20-years-of-practical-business-wisdom-from-the-trenches-dave-ramsey-abridged/">Entreleadership : 20 Years of Practical Business Wisdom from the Trenches &#8211; Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author of The Total Money Makeover and radio and podcast host Dave Ramsey comes an informative guide based on how he grew a successful, multimillion dollar company from a card table in his living room.     </p>
<p>                    Your company is only as strong as your leaders. These are the men and women doing battle daily beneath the banner that is your brand. Are they courageous or indecisive? Are they serving a motivated team or managing employees? Are they valued?     </p>
<p>                    Your team will never grow beyond you, so here&#8217;s another question to consider&#8211;are you growing? Whether you&#8217;re sitting at the CEO&#8217;s desk, the middle manager&#8217;s cubicle, or a card table in your living-room-based start-up, EntreLeadership provides the practical, step-by-step guidance to grow your business where you want it to go. Dave Ramsey opens up his championship playbook for business to show you how to:     </p>
<p>                    -Inspire your team to take ownership and love what they do<br />
                     -Unify your team and get rid of all gossip<br />
                     -Handle money to set your business up for success<br />
                     -Reach every goal you set<br />
                     -And much, much more!     </p>
<p>                    EntreLeadership is a one-stop guide filled with accessible advice for businesses and leaders to ensure success even through the toughest of times.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/entreleadership-20-years-of-practical-business-wisdom-from-the-trenches-dave-ramsey-abridged/">Entreleadership : 20 Years of Practical Business Wisdom from the Trenches &#8211; Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Achievement Habit : Stop Wishing, Start Doing, and Take Command of Your Life &#8211; Bernard Roth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-achievement-habit-stop-wishing-start-doing-and-take-command-of-your-life-bernard-roth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-achievement-habit-stop-wishing-start-doing-and-take-command-of-your-life-bernard-roth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The co-founder of the Stanford d.School introduces the power of design thinking to help you achieve goals you never thought possible. Achievement can be learned. It&#8217;s a muscle, and once you learn how to flex it, you&#8217;ll be able to meet life&#8217;s challenges and fulfill your goals, Bernard Roth, Academic Director at the Stanford d.school [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-achievement-habit-stop-wishing-start-doing-and-take-command-of-your-life-bernard-roth-abridged/">The Achievement Habit : Stop Wishing, Start Doing, and Take Command of Your Life &#8211; Bernard Roth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The co-founder of the Stanford d.School introduces the power of design thinking to help you achieve goals you never thought possible.  Achievement can be learned. It&#8217;s a muscle, and once you learn how to flex it, you&#8217;ll be able to meet life&#8217;s challenges and fulfill your goals, Bernard Roth, Academic Director at the Stanford d.school contends.  In The Achievement Habit, Roth applies the remarkable insights that stem from design thinking-previously used to solve large scale projects-to help us realize the power for positive change we all have within us. Roth leads us through a series of discussions, stories, recommendations, and exercises designed to help us create a different experience in our lives.<br />
                    He shares invaluable insights we can use to gain confidence to do what we&#8217;ve always wanted and overcome obstacles that hamper us from reaching our potential, including:  *  Don&#8217;t try-DO; *  Excuses are self-defeating; *  Believe you are a doer and achiever and you&#8217;ll become one; *  Build resiliency by reinforcing what you do rather than what you accomplish; *  Learn to ignore distractions that prevent you from achieving your goals; *  Become open to learning from your own experience and from those around you; *  And more. The brain is complex and is always working with our egos to sabotage our best intentions. But we can be mindful; we can create habits that make our lives better. Thoughtful and powerful The Achievement Habit shows you how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-achievement-habit-stop-wishing-start-doing-and-take-command-of-your-life-bernard-roth-abridged/">The Achievement Habit : Stop Wishing, Start Doing, and Take Command of Your Life &#8211; Bernard Roth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Automatic Millionaire, Expanded and Updated : A Powerful One-Step Plan to Live and Finish Rich &#8211; David Bach (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-automatic-millionaire-expanded-and-updated-a-powerful-one-step-plan-to-live-and-finish-rich-david-bach-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-automatic-millionaire-expanded-and-updated-a-powerful-one-step-plan-to-live-and-finish-rich-david-bach-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD&#8211;#1 NEW YORK TIMES, WALL STREET JOURNAL, USA TODAY, BUSINESSWEEK BESTSELLER What&#8217;s the secret to becoming a millionaire? For years people have asked David Bach, the national bestselling author of Smart Women Finish Rich, Smart Couples Finish Rich, and Start Late, Finish Rich what&#8217;s the real secret to getting rich? What&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-automatic-millionaire-expanded-and-updated-a-powerful-one-step-plan-to-live-and-finish-rich-david-bach-abridged/">The Automatic Millionaire, Expanded and Updated : A Powerful One-Step Plan to Live and Finish Rich &#8211; David Bach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD&#8211;#1 NEW YORK TIMES, WALL STREET JOURNAL, USA TODAY, BUSINESSWEEK BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                    What&#8217;s the secret to becoming a millionaire?     </p>
<p>                     For years people have asked David Bach, the national bestselling author of Smart Women Finish Rich, Smart Couples Finish Rich,  and Start Late, Finish Rich what&#8217;s the real secret to getting rich? What&#8217;s the one thing I need to do?     </p>
<p>                     Now, in the newly revised The Automatic Millionaire, expanded and updated, David Bach is sharing that secret.     </p>
<p>                     The Automatic Millionaire starts with the powerful story of an average American couple&#8211;he&#8217;s a low-level manager, she&#8217;s a beautician&#8211;whose joint income never exceeds $55,000 a year, yet who somehow manage to own two homes debt-free, put two kids through college, and retire at 55 with more than $1 million in savings. Through their story you&#8217;ll learn the surprising fact that you cannot get rich with a budget! You have to have a plan to pay yourself first that is totally automatic, a plan that will automatically secure your future and pay for your present.     </p>
<p>                     What makes The Automatic Millionaire unique:      </p>
<p>                     &#8211; You don&#8217;t need a budget<br />
                     &#8211; You don&#8217;t need willpower<br />
                     &#8211; You don&#8217;t need to make a lot of money<br />
                     &#8211; You don&#8217;t need to be that interested in money<br />
                     &#8211; You can set up the plan in an hour     </p>
<p>                     David gives you a totally realistic system, based on timeless principles, with everything you need to know, including phone numbers, websites and apps, so you can put the secret to becoming an Automatic Millionaire in place from the comfort of your own home.     </p>
<p>                     This powerful little book has the potential to secure your financial future. Do it once&#8211;the rest is automatic!     </p>
<p>                     The Automatic Millionaire is one of the most popular financial books of our time. It was a runaway hit when it was first published in 2004, spending thirty-one weeks on the New York Times bestseller list and appearing at at number one simultaneously on the New York Times, USA Today, BusinessWeek,  and Wall Street Journal business bestseller lists. It has sold over 1.5 million copies and been translated around the world in over a dozen languages. This is the first update since 2005 and includes updated information on taxes, investments, technologies and apps to automate your financial life as well as David&#8217;s latest systems for making the entire process even easier.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-automatic-millionaire-expanded-and-updated-a-powerful-one-step-plan-to-live-and-finish-rich-david-bach-abridged/">The Automatic Millionaire, Expanded and Updated : A Powerful One-Step Plan to Live and Finish Rich &#8211; David Bach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The E-Myth Revisited : Why Most Small Businesses Don&#8217;t Work and What to Do About It &#8211; Michael E. Gerber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-e-myth-revisited-why-most-small-businesses-dont-work-and-what-to-do-about-it-michael-e-gerber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-e-myth-revisited-why-most-small-businesses-dont-work-and-what-to-do-about-it-michael-e-gerber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>E-Myth &#8216;e-,&#8217;mith n 1: the entrepreneurial myth: the myth that most people who start small businesses are entrepreneurs 2: the fatal assumption that an individual who understands the technical work of a business can successfully run a business that does that technical work Voted #1 business book by Inc. 500 CEOs. An instant classic, this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-e-myth-revisited-why-most-small-businesses-dont-work-and-what-to-do-about-it-michael-e-gerber-abridged/">The E-Myth Revisited : Why Most Small Businesses Don&#8217;t Work and What to Do About It &#8211; Michael E. Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>E-Myth  &#8216;e-,&#8217;mith n 1: the entrepreneurial myth: the myth that most people who start small businesses are entrepreneurs 2: the fatal assumption that an individual who understands the technical work of a business can successfully run a business that does that technical work  Voted #1 business book by Inc. 500 CEOs.  An instant classic, this revised and updated edition of the phenomenal bestseller dispels the myths about starting your own business. Small business consultant and author Michael E. Gerber, with sharp insight gained from years of experience, points out how common assumptions, expectations, and even technical expertise can get in the way of running a successful business.  Gerber walks you through the steps in the life of a business-from entrepreneurial infancy through adolescent growing pains to the mature entrepreneurial perspective: the guiding light of all businesses that succeed-and shows how to apply the lessons of franchising to any business, whether or not it is a franchise. Most importantly, Gerber draws the vital, often overlooked distinction between working on your business and working in your business.<br />
                    The E-Myth Revisited will help you grow your business in a productive, assured way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-e-myth-revisited-why-most-small-businesses-dont-work-and-what-to-do-about-it-michael-e-gerber-abridged/">The E-Myth Revisited : Why Most Small Businesses Don&#8217;t Work and What to Do About It &#8211; Michael E. Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Will Teach You To Be Rich (2nd Edition) : No guilt, no excuses &#8211; just a 6-week programme that works &#8211; Ramit Sethi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-will-teach-you-to-be-rich-2nd-edition-no-guilt-no-excuses-just-a-6-week-programme-that-works-ramit-sethi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-will-teach-you-to-be-rich-2nd-edition-no-guilt-no-excuses-just-a-6-week-programme-that-works-ramit-sethi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you think financial health is beyond your reach, think again. I Will Teach You To Be Rich is the modern money classic that has revolutionised the lives of countless people all over the world, teaching them how to effectively manage their finances, demolish their debt, save better and get the most out of their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-will-teach-you-to-be-rich-2nd-edition-no-guilt-no-excuses-just-a-6-week-programme-that-works-ramit-sethi-abridged/">I Will Teach You To Be Rich (2nd Edition) : No guilt, no excuses &#8211; just a 6-week programme that works &#8211; Ramit Sethi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you think financial health is beyond your reach, think again. I Will Teach You To Be Rich is the modern money classic that has revolutionised the lives of countless people all over the world, teaching them how to effectively manage their finances, demolish their debt, save better and get the most out of their bank accounts, credit cards and investments.     </p>
<p>                    Now, Ramit Sethi, who has been described by Forbes as a &#8216;wealth wizard&#8217; and by Fortune as &#8216;the new finance guru&#8217;, is back with a completely revised second edition of I Will Teach You To Be Rich, updating it with new tools and insights on money and psychology, along with fantastic stories of how previous readers have used the book to enrich their lives. From crushing your debt and student loans to talking your way out of late fees, to dead simple investment strategies and negotiating that big raise at work, this is the no-guilt, no-excuses, no-BS 6-week programme that will help you get your finances where you want them to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-will-teach-you-to-be-rich-2nd-edition-no-guilt-no-excuses-just-a-6-week-programme-that-works-ramit-sethi-abridged/">I Will Teach You To Be Rich (2nd Edition) : No guilt, no excuses &#8211; just a 6-week programme that works &#8211; Ramit Sethi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Millionaire Fastlane : Crack the Code to Wealth and Live Rich for a Lifetime &#8211; MJ DeMarco (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-millionaire-fastlane-crack-the-code-to-wealth-and-live-rich-for-a-lifetime-mj-demarco-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-millionaire-fastlane-crack-the-code-to-wealth-and-live-rich-for-a-lifetime-mj-demarco-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is the financial plan of mediocrity &#8212; a dream-stealing, soul-sucking dogma known as &#8220;The Slowlane&#8221; your plan for creating wealth? You know how it goes; it sounds a little something like this: &#8220;Go to school, get a good job, save 10% of your paycheck, buy a used car, cancel the movie channels, quit drinking expensive [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-millionaire-fastlane-crack-the-code-to-wealth-and-live-rich-for-a-lifetime-mj-demarco-abridged/">The Millionaire Fastlane : Crack the Code to Wealth and Live Rich for a Lifetime &#8211; MJ DeMarco (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is the financial plan of mediocrity &#8212; a dream-stealing, soul-sucking dogma known as &#8220;The Slowlane&#8221; your plan for creating wealth? You know how it goes; it sounds a little something like this: &#8220;Go to school, get a good job, save 10% of your paycheck, buy a used car, cancel the movie channels, quit drinking expensive Starbucks lattes, save and penny-pinch your life away, trust your life-savings to the stock market, and one day, when you are oh, say, 65 years old, you can retire rich.&#8221; The mainstream financial gurus have sold you blindly down the river to a great financial gamble: You&#8217;ve been hoodwinked to believe that wealth can be created by recklessly trusting in the uncontrollable and unpredictable markets: the housing market, the stock market, and the job market. This impotent financial gamble dubiously promises wealth in a wheelchair &#8212; sacrifice your adult life for a financial plan that reaps dividends in the twilight of life. Accept the Slowlane as your blueprint for wealth and your financial future will blow carelessly asunder on a sailboat of HOPE: HOPE you can find a job and keep it, HOPE the stock market doesn&#8217;t tank, HOPE the economy rebounds, HOPE, HOPE, and HOPE.<br />
                    Do you really want HOPE to be the centerpiece for your family&#8217;s financial plan? Drive the Slowlane road and you will find your life deteriorate into a miserable exhibition about what you cannot do, versus what you can. For those who don&#8217;t want a lifetime subscription to mediocrity and a slight chance of elderly riches, there is an alternative; an expressway to extraordinary wealth that can burn a trail to financial independence faster than any road out there. &#8212; Why jobs, 401(k)s, mutual funds, and 40-years of mindless frugality will never make you rich young. &#8212; Why most entrepreneurs fail and how to immediately put the odds in your favor. &#8212; The real law of wealth: Leverage this and wealth has no choice but to be magnetized to you. &#8212; The leading cause of poorness: Change this and you change everything. &#8211;How the rich really get rich &#8211; and no, it has nothing to do with a paycheck or a 401K match. &#8212; Why the guru&#8217;s grand deity &#8211; compound interest &#8211; is an impotent wealth accelerator. &#8212; Why the guru myth of &#8220;do what you love&#8221; will most likely keep you poor, not rich. &#8212; And 250+ more poverty busting distinctions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-millionaire-fastlane-crack-the-code-to-wealth-and-live-rich-for-a-lifetime-mj-demarco-abridged/">The Millionaire Fastlane : Crack the Code to Wealth and Live Rich for a Lifetime &#8211; MJ DeMarco (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clever Girl Finance : Ditch debt, save money and build real wealth &#8211; Bola Sokunbi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/clever-girl-finance-ditch-debt-save-money-and-build-real-wealth-bola-sokunbi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/clever-girl-finance-ditch-debt-save-money-and-build-real-wealth-bola-sokunbi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Take charge of your finances and achieve financial independence &#8211; the Clever Girl way Join the ranks of thousands of smart and savvy women who have turned to money expert and author Bola Sokunbi for guidance on ditching debt, saving money, and building real wealth. Sokunbi, the force behind the hugely popular Clever Girl Finance [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clever-girl-finance-ditch-debt-save-money-and-build-real-wealth-bola-sokunbi-abridged/">Clever Girl Finance : Ditch debt, save money and build real wealth &#8211; Bola Sokunbi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Take charge of your finances and achieve financial independence &#8211; the Clever Girl way    </p>
<p>                     Join the ranks of thousands of smart and savvy women who have turned to money expert and author Bola Sokunbi for guidance on ditching debt, saving money, and building real wealth. Sokunbi, the force behind the hugely popular Clever Girl Finance website, draws on her personal money mistakes and financial redemption to educate and empower a new generation of women on their journey to financial freedom. Lighthearted and accessible, Clever Girl Finance encourages women to talk about money and financial wellness and shows them how to navigate their own murky financial waters and come out afloat on the other side.    </p>
<p>                    Monitor your expenses, build a budget, and stick with it<br />
                    Make the most of a modest salary and still have money to spare<br />
                    Keep your credit in check and clean up credit card chaos<br />
                    Start and succeed at your side hustle<br />
                    Build a nest egg and invest in your future<br />
                    Transform your money mindset and be accountable for your financial well-being<br />
                    Feel the power of real-world stories from other &#8220;clever girls&#8221;    </p>
<p>                     Put yourself on the path to financial success with the valuable lessons learned from Clever Girl Finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clever-girl-finance-ditch-debt-save-money-and-build-real-wealth-bola-sokunbi-abridged/">Clever Girl Finance : Ditch debt, save money and build real wealth &#8211; Bola Sokunbi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Myths of Innovation &#8211; Scott Berkun (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this new paperback edition of the classic bestseller, you&#8217;ll be taken on a hilarious, fast-paced ride through the history of ideas. Author Scott Berkun will show you how to transcend the false stories that many business experts, scientists, and much of pop culture foolishly use to guide their thinking about how ideas change the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/">The Myths of Innovation &#8211; Scott Berkun (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this new paperback edition of the classic bestseller, you&#8217;ll be taken on a hilarious, fast-paced ride through the history of ideas. Author Scott Berkun will show you how to transcend the false stories that many business experts, scientists, and much of pop culture foolishly use to guide their thinking about how ideas change the world. With four new chapters on putting the ideas in the book to work, updated references and over 50 corrections and improvements, now is the time to get past the myths, and change the world. You&#8217;ll have fun while you learn:  * Where ideas come from * The true history of history * Why most people don&#8217;t like ideas * How great managers make ideas thrive * The importance of problem finding * The simple plan (new for paperback)  Since its initial publication, this classic bestseller has been discussed on NPR, MSNBC, CNBC, and at Yale University, MIT, Carnegie Mellon University, Microsoft, Apple, Intel, Google, Amazon.com, and other major media, corporations, and universities around the world. It has changed the way thousands of leaders and creators understand the world.<br />
                    Now in an updated and expanded paperback edition, it&#8217;s a fantastic time to explore or rediscover this powerful view of the world of ideas. &#8220;Sets us free to try and change the world.&#8221; &#8211;Guy Kawasaki, Author of Art of The Start &#8220;Small, simple, powerful: an innovative book about innovation.&#8221; &#8211;Don Norman, author of Design of Everyday Things &#8220;Insightful, inspiring, evocative, and just plain fun to read. It&#8217;s totally great.&#8221; &#8211;John Seely Brown, Former Director, Xerox Palo Alto Research Center (PARC) &#8220;Methodically and entertainingly dismantling the cliches that surround the process of innovation.&#8221; &#8211;Scott Rosenberg, author of Dreaming in Code; cofounder of Salon.com &#8220;Will inspire you to come up with breakthrough ideas of your own.&#8221; &#8211;Alan Cooper, Father of Visual Basic and author of The Inmates are Running the Asylum &#8220;Brimming with insights and historical examples, Berkun&#8217;s book not only debunks widely held myths about innovation, it also points the ways toward making your new ideas stick.&#8221; &#8211;Tom Kelley, GM, IDEO; author of The Ten Faces of Innovation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/">The Myths of Innovation &#8211; Scott Berkun (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crushing It in Apartments and Commercial Real Estate : How a Small Investor Can Make It Big &#8211; Brian H Murray (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crushing-it-in-apartments-and-commercial-real-estate-how-a-small-investor-can-make-it-big-brian-h-murray-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crushing-it-in-apartments-and-commercial-real-estate-how-a-small-investor-can-make-it-big-brian-h-murray-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Think apartments and commercial real estate are just for the big boys? Think again. Brian Murray was not an investment pro when he bought his first commercial property. He was a teacher looking to build some side income. Armed with his passion for business and a lot of common sense, he developed a simple yet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crushing-it-in-apartments-and-commercial-real-estate-how-a-small-investor-can-make-it-big-brian-h-murray-abridged/">Crushing It in Apartments and Commercial Real Estate : How a Small Investor Can Make It Big &#8211; Brian H Murray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Think apartments and commercial real estate are just for the big boys? Think again.    </p>
<p>                    Brian Murray was not an investment pro when he bought his first commercial property. He was a teacher looking to build some side income. Armed with his passion for business and a lot of common sense, he developed a simple yet highly effective approach to investing that he still uses today at his multimillion-dollar real estate company.     </p>
<p>                    Crushing It in Apartments and Commercial Real Estate is a beginner&#8217;s guide to investing based on Murray&#8217;s experience bootstrapping his way from newbie investor to award-winning CEO of Washington Street Properties. Murray shares the secrets to his success through straightforward, actionable advice that will help you get started no matter what your experience level, or how much cash you have on hand. You&#8217;ll learn how to:     </p>
<p>                      Find and creatively finance commercial property Grow a portfolio without any help from outside investors and without taking on excessive debt Use your small-investor status as a competitive advantage over corporate investors Identify simple, practical ways to increase profits while keeping costs low      </p>
<p>                    Murray also shares real-life stories that reveal exactly how he grew his business, and the hard lessons he learned along the way (so you don&#8217;t have to). Whether you already invest in real estate and want to go bigger, or you&#8217;ve never owned a property, this book gives you the tools and wisdom you need to crush it in apartments and commercial real estate.    </p>
<p>                    Brian Murray is the founder and CEO of Washington Street Properties, a commercial real estate investment company that has been ranked on the Inc. 5000 list of the fastest-growing private companies in the United States for three years in a row. In 2015, Murray was recognized with a Gold Stevie Award for Executive of the Year in the Real Estate Industry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crushing-it-in-apartments-and-commercial-real-estate-how-a-small-investor-can-make-it-big-brian-h-murray-abridged/">Crushing It in Apartments and Commercial Real Estate : How a Small Investor Can Make It Big &#8211; Brian H Murray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You Are a Badass at Making Money : Master the Mindset of Wealth: Learn how to save your money with one of the world&#8217;s most exciting self help authors &#8211; Jen Sincero (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/you-are-a-badass-at-making-money-master-the-mindset-of-wealth-learn-how-to-save-your-money-with-one-of-the-worlds-most-exciting-self-help-authors-jen-sincero-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/you-are-a-badass-at-making-money-master-the-mindset-of-wealth-learn-how-to-save-your-money-with-one-of-the-worlds-most-exciting-self-help-authors-jen-sincero-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of You Are A Badass, the New Your Times bestselling book everyone is talking about. YOU ARE A BADASS AT MAKING MONEY is the book you need if you&#8217;ve spent too much time watching money land in your bank account and then roll through your fingers. Jen Sincero went from living in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-are-a-badass-at-making-money-master-the-mindset-of-wealth-learn-how-to-save-your-money-with-one-of-the-worlds-most-exciting-self-help-authors-jen-sincero-abridged/">You Are a Badass at Making Money : Master the Mindset of Wealth: Learn how to save your money with one of the world&#8217;s most exciting self help authors &#8211; Jen Sincero (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of You Are A Badass, the New Your Times bestselling book everyone is talking about.    </p>
<p>                    YOU ARE A BADASS AT MAKING MONEY is the book you need if you&#8217;ve spent too much time watching money land in your bank account and then roll through your fingers. Jen Sincero went from living in a converted garage to traveling the world in 5-star luxury in a matter of years, and knows all too well the layers of BS one can get wrapped up in around money, as well as what it takes to dig your way out.     </p>
<p>                    In this funny, fascinating and practical book she goes in-depth on how powerful our thoughts are and how our bank accounts are mirrors for our beliefs about money.  YOU ARE A BADASS AT MAKING MONEY combines laugh out loud comedy with life-changing concepts, all boiled down into manageable, bite-sized tips so that YOU can put them into practice and get life changing results.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-are-a-badass-at-making-money-master-the-mindset-of-wealth-learn-how-to-save-your-money-with-one-of-the-worlds-most-exciting-self-help-authors-jen-sincero-abridged/">You Are a Badass at Making Money : Master the Mindset of Wealth: Learn how to save your money with one of the world&#8217;s most exciting self help authors &#8211; Jen Sincero (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Money : Know More, Make More, Give More: Learn how to make more money and transform your life &#8211; Rob Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to get to the stage &#8211; soon &#8211; where you are truly financially independent, able to use your money in the way you&#8217;d like, and be completely confident in your ability to take care of yourself and your family? That is a universal desire, but many of us regard wealth and financial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/">Money : Know More, Make More, Give More: Learn how to make more money and transform your life &#8211; Rob Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to get to the stage &#8211; soon &#8211; where you are truly financially independent, able to use your money in the way you&#8217;d like, and be completely confident in your ability to take care of yourself and your family?     </p>
<p>                    That is a universal desire, but many of us regard wealth and financial independence as a goal which we&#8217;ll likely never achieve &#8211; there are just too many bills that need paying and there is a widespread belief that the money game is rigged. Even people who win the lottery or inherit money often seem to wind up losing it. The evidence suggests you can&#8217;t win a game that you don&#8217;t understand &#8211; even if you start out winning &#8211; because you never understood the game in the first place.    </p>
<p>                    So how can you win with money? How can you create independent wealth and hold on to it? This inspiring book by self-made multi-millionaire Rob Moore explains the rules of the game, shares simple tricks for managing money better, details how to create a plan for an ambitious future, and shows you the very best way to become a millionaire &#8211; to think and behave like one!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/">Money : Know More, Make More, Give More: Learn how to make more money and transform your life &#8211; Rob Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Think and Grow Rich : The Landmark Bestseller Now Revised and Updated for the 21st Century &#8211; Napoleon Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/think-and-grow-rich-the-landmark-bestseller-now-revised-and-updated-for-the-21st-century-napoleon-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/think-and-grow-rich-the-landmark-bestseller-now-revised-and-updated-for-the-21st-century-napoleon-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Think and Grow Rich has been called the Granddaddy of All Motivational Literature. It was the first book to boldly ask, What makes a winner? The man who asked and listened for the answer, Napoleon Hill, is now counted in the top ranks of the world&#8217;s winners himself. The most famous of all teachers of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/think-and-grow-rich-the-landmark-bestseller-now-revised-and-updated-for-the-21st-century-napoleon-hill-abridged/">Think and Grow Rich : The Landmark Bestseller Now Revised and Updated for the 21st Century &#8211; Napoleon Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Think and Grow Rich has been called the Granddaddy of All Motivational Literature. It was the first book to boldly ask, What makes a winner? The man who asked and listened for the answer, Napoleon Hill, is now counted in the top ranks of the world&#8217;s winners himself.    </p>
<p>                    The most famous of all teachers of success spent a fortune and the better part of a lifetime of effort to produce the Law of Success philosophy that forms the basis of his books and that is so powerfully summarized in this one.    </p>
<p>                    In the original Think and Grow Rich, published in 1937, Hill draws on stories of Andrew Carnegie, Thomas Edison, Henry Ford, and other millionaires of his generation to illustrate his principles. In the updated version, Arthur R. Pell, Ph.D., a nationally known author, lecturer, and consultant in human resources management and an expert in applying Hill&#8217;s thought, deftly interweaves anecdotes of how contemporary millionaires and billionaires, such as Bill Gates, Mary Kay Ash, Dave Thomas, and Sir John Templeton, achieved their wealth. Outmoded or arcane terminology and examples are faithfully refreshed to preclude any stumbling blocks to a new generation of readers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/think-and-grow-rich-the-landmark-bestseller-now-revised-and-updated-for-the-21st-century-napoleon-hill-abridged/">Think and Grow Rich : The Landmark Bestseller Now Revised and Updated for the 21st Century &#8211; Napoleon Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commodities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jim Paul&#8217;s meteoric rise took him from a small town in Northern Kentucky to governor of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, yet he lost it all-his fortune, his reputation, and his job-in one fatal attack of excessive economic hubris. In this honest, frank analysis, Paul and Brendan Moynihan revisit the events that led to Paul&#8217;s disastrous [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/">What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jim Paul&#8217;s meteoric rise took him from a small town in Northern Kentucky to governor of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, yet he lost it all-his fortune, his reputation, and his job-in one fatal attack of excessive economic hubris. In this honest, frank analysis, Paul and Brendan Moynihan revisit the events that led to Paul&#8217;s disastrous decision and examine the psychological factors behind bad financial practices in several economic sectors.  This book-winner of a 2014 Axiom Business Book award gold medal-begins with the unbroken string of successes that helped Paul achieve a jet-setting lifestyle and land a key spot with the Chicago Mercantile Exchange. It then describes the circumstances leading up to Paul&#8217;s $1.6 million loss and the essential lessons he learned from it-primarily that, although there are as many ways to make money in the markets as there are people participating in them, all losses come from the same few sources. Investors lose money in the markets either because of errors in their analysis or because of psychological barriers preventing the application of analysis.<br />
                    While all analytical methods have some validity and make allowances for instances in which they do not work, psychological factors can keep an investor in a losing position, causing him to abandon one method for another in order to rationalize the decisions already made. Paul and Moynihan&#8217;s cautionary tale includes strategies for avoiding loss tied to a simple framework for understanding, accepting, and dodging the dangers of investing, trading, and speculating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/">What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rich Dad, Poor Dad : What the Rich Teach Their Kids About Money &#8211; Robert T. Kiyosaki, Sharon L. Lechter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rich-dad-poor-dad-what-the-rich-teach-their-kids-about-money-robert-t-kiyosaki-sharon-l-lechter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rich-dad-poor-dad-what-the-rich-teach-their-kids-about-money-robert-t-kiyosaki-sharon-l-lechter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Personal finance author and lecturer Robert T. Kiyosaki developed his unique economic perspective from two very different influences &#8211; his two fathers. One father (Robert&#8217;s real father) was a highly educated man but fiscally poor. The other father was the father of Robert&#8217;s best friend &#8211; that Dad was an eighth-grade drop-out who became a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rich-dad-poor-dad-what-the-rich-teach-their-kids-about-money-robert-t-kiyosaki-sharon-l-lechter-abridged/">Rich Dad, Poor Dad : What the Rich Teach Their Kids About Money &#8211; Robert T. Kiyosaki, Sharon L. Lechter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Personal finance author and lecturer Robert T. Kiyosaki developed his unique economic perspective from two very different influences &#8211; his two fathers. One father (Robert&#8217;s real father) was a highly educated man but fiscally poor. The other father was the father of Robert&#8217;s best friend &#8211; that Dad was an eighth-grade drop-out who became a self-made multi-millionaire. The lifelong monetary problems experienced by his &#8216;poor dad&#8217; pounded home the counterpoint communicated by his &#8216;rich dad&#8217;. Taking that message to heart, Kiyosaki was able to retire at 47. RICH DAD, POOR DAD, written with consultant and CPA Sharon L. Lechter, lays out his philosophy behind Kiyosaki&#8217;s relationship with money and opens readers eyes by: * Exploding the myth that you need to earn a high income to be rich * Challenging the belief that your house is an asset * Showing parents why they can&#8217;t rely on schools to teach their children about money * Defining once and for all an asset versus a liability &#8230;* Explaining what to teach your children about money for their future financial success</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rich-dad-poor-dad-what-the-rich-teach-their-kids-about-money-robert-t-kiyosaki-sharon-l-lechter-abridged/">Rich Dad, Poor Dad : What the Rich Teach Their Kids About Money &#8211; Robert T. Kiyosaki, Sharon L. Lechter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elevate : Push Beyond Your Limits and Unlock Success in Yourself and Others &#8211; Robert Glazer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/elevate-push-beyond-your-limits-and-unlock-success-in-yourself-and-others-robert-glazer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/elevate-push-beyond-your-limits-and-unlock-success-in-yourself-and-others-robert-glazer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NOW A USA TODAY AND WALL STREET JOURNAL BESTSELLER! What are your limits? Care to break them? To inspire change in yourself and your team, you must break free from what&#8217;s holding you down. In Elevate, Robert Glazer reveals four life-changing principles &#8211; or capacities &#8211; that will allow you to overcome self-limiting beliefs, establish [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/elevate-push-beyond-your-limits-and-unlock-success-in-yourself-and-others-robert-glazer-abridged/">Elevate : Push Beyond Your Limits and Unlock Success in Yourself and Others &#8211; Robert Glazer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NOW A USA TODAY AND WALL STREET JOURNAL BESTSELLER!<br />
                    What are your limits? Care to break them?<br />
                    To inspire change in yourself and your team, you must break free from what&#8217;s holding you down.<br />
                    In Elevate, Robert Glazer reveals four life-changing principles &#8211; or capacities &#8211; that will allow you to overcome self-limiting beliefs, establish positive habits, and find your &#8220;why.&#8221; As we look to elevate ourselves, we mean so much more than beating the competition. After all, our greatest competition is ourselves! We need to find ways to consistently outperform ourselves and our own expectations.<br />
                    Robert Glazer has built a career on accelerating productivity and careers. ELEVATE is based on his five foundational elements necessary for increasing our capacity: Finding Your Why, Overcoming Self-Limiting Beliefs, Setting Goals and Creating Accountability, Maintaining Health and Wellness, and Establishing Routine and Positive Habits.<br />
                    The key is elevating yourself beyond the edge of your current abilities. Challenge yourself, and the result will inspire others to rise along with you. It&#8217;s time to break free of your limits.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/elevate-push-beyond-your-limits-and-unlock-success-in-yourself-and-others-robert-glazer-abridged/">Elevate : Push Beyond Your Limits and Unlock Success in Yourself and Others &#8211; Robert Glazer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
