<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Botany &amp; Plant Sciences Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/botany-plant-sciences/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/botany-plant-sciences/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Botany &amp; Plant Sciences Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/botany-plant-sciences/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>This Is Your Mind On Plants : Opium-Caffeine-Mescaline &#8211; Michael Pollan</title>
		<link>/this-is-your-mind-on-plants-opium-caffeine-mescaline-michael-pollan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Botany & Plant Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drug-induced States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trees]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildflowers & Plants]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-your-mind-on-plants-opium-caffeine-mescaline-michael-pollan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s a trip &#8211; engrossing, eye-opening, mind altering&#8217; New Statesman &#8216;Fascinating. Pollan is the perfect guide &#8230; curious, careful, open minded&#8217; The Guardian From the international bestselling author of How to Change Your Mind comes a ground-breaking exploration of our relationship with natural drugs Of all the many things humans rely on plants for, surely [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-mind-on-plants-opium-caffeine-mescaline-michael-pollan/">This Is Your Mind On Plants : Opium-Caffeine-Mescaline &#8211; Michael Pollan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s a trip &#8211; engrossing, eye-opening, mind altering&#8217; New Statesman</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating. Pollan is the perfect guide &#8230; curious, careful, open minded&#8217; The Guardian</p>
<p>                    From the international bestselling author of How to Change Your Mind comes a ground-breaking exploration of our relationship with natural drugs</p>
<p>                    Of all the many things humans rely on plants for, surely the most curious is our use of them to change consciousness: to stimulate, calm, or completely alter the qualities of our mental experience. In This Is Your Mind On Plants, Michael Pollan explores three very different drugs &#8211; opium, caffeine and mescaline &#8211; and throws the fundamental strangeness of our thinking about them into sharp relief. Exploring and participating in the cultures that have grown up around these drugs, while consuming (or in the case of caffeine, trying not to consume) them, Pollan reckons with the powerful human attraction to psychoactive plants, and the equally powerful taboos. </p>
<p>                    In a unique blend of history, science, memoir and reportage, Pollan shines a fresh light on a subject that is all too often treated reductively. In doing so, he proves that there is much more to say about these plants than simply debating their regulation, for when we take them into our bodies and let them change our minds, we are engaging with nature in one of the most profound ways we can. This ground-breaking and singular book holds up a mirror to our fundamental human needs and aspirations, the operations of our minds and our entanglement with the natural world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-mind-on-plants-opium-caffeine-mescaline-michael-pollan/">This Is Your Mind On Plants : Opium-Caffeine-Mescaline &#8211; Michael Pollan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Braiding Sweetgrass : Indigenous Wisdom, Scientific Knowledge and the Teachings of Plants &#8211; Robin Wall Kimmerer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/braiding-sweetgrass-indigenous-wisdom-scientific-knowledge-and-the-teachings-of-plants-robin-wall-kimmerer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Ecology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Botany & Plant Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trees, Wildflowers & Plants]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/braiding-sweetgrass-indigenous-wisdom-scientific-knowledge-and-the-teachings-of-plants-robin-wall-kimmerer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A hymn of love to the world &#8230; A journey that is every bit as mythic as it is scientific, as sacred as it is historical, as clever as it is wise&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert, author of Eat, Pray, Love As a botanist, Robin Wall Kimmerer has been trained to ask questions of nature with the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/braiding-sweetgrass-indigenous-wisdom-scientific-knowledge-and-the-teachings-of-plants-robin-wall-kimmerer-abridged/">Braiding Sweetgrass : Indigenous Wisdom, Scientific Knowledge and the Teachings of Plants &#8211; Robin Wall Kimmerer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A hymn of love to the world &#8230; A journey that is every bit as mythic as it is scientific, as sacred as  it is historical, as clever as it is wise&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert, author of Eat, Pray, Love    </p>
<p>                    As a botanist, Robin Wall Kimmerer has been trained to ask questions of nature with the tools of science. As a member of the Citizen Potawatomi Nation, she embraces the notion that plants and animals are our oldest teachers. In Braiding Sweetgrass, Kimmerer brings these two ways of knowledge together.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on her life as an indigenous scientist, a mother, and a woman, Kimmerer shows how other living beings &#8211; asters and goldenrod, strawberries and squash, salamanders, algae, and sweetgrass &#8211; offer us gifts and lessons, even if we&#8217;ve forgotten how to hear their voices. In a rich braid of reflections that range from the creation of Turtle Island to the forces that threaten its flourishing today, she circles toward a central argument: that the awakening of a wider ecological consciousness requires the acknowledgment and celebration of our reciprocal relationship with the rest of the living world. For only when we can hear the languages of other beings will we be capable of understanding the generosity of the earth, and learn to give our own gifts in return.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/braiding-sweetgrass-indigenous-wisdom-scientific-knowledge-and-the-teachings-of-plants-robin-wall-kimmerer-abridged/">Braiding Sweetgrass : Indigenous Wisdom, Scientific Knowledge and the Teachings of Plants &#8211; Robin Wall Kimmerer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Botany of Desire : A Plant&#8217;s-Eye View of the World &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-botany-of-desire-a-plants-eye-view-of-the-world-michael-pollan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Ecology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Botany & Plant Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gardening Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horticulture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trees, Wildflowers & Plants]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-botany-of-desire-a-plants-eye-view-of-the-world-michael-pollan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The book that helped make Michael Pollan, the New York Times bestselling author of How to Change Your Mind, Cooked and The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma, one of the most trusted food experts in America Every schoolchild learns about the mutually beneficial dance of honeybees and flowers: The bee collects nectar and pollen to make honey and, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-botany-of-desire-a-plants-eye-view-of-the-world-michael-pollan-abridged/">The Botany of Desire : A Plant&#8217;s-Eye View of the World &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The book that helped make Michael Pollan, the New York Times bestselling author of How to Change Your Mind, Cooked and The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma, one of the most trusted food experts in America     </p>
<p>                    Every schoolchild learns about the mutually beneficial dance of honeybees and flowers: The bee collects nectar and pollen to make honey and, in the process, spreads the flowers&#8217; genes far and wide. In The Botany of Desire,  Michael Pollan ingeniously demonstrates how people and domesticated plants have formed a similarly reciprocal relationship. He masterfully links four fundamental human desires&#8211;sweetness, beauty, intoxication, and control&#8211;with the plants that satisfy them: the apple, the tulip, marijuana, and the potato. In telling the stories of four familiar species, Pollan illustrates how the plants have evolved to satisfy humankind&#8217;s most basic yearnings. And just as we&#8217;ve benefited from these plants, we have also done well by them. So who is really domesticating whom?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-botany-of-desire-a-plants-eye-view-of-the-world-michael-pollan-abridged/">The Botany of Desire : A Plant&#8217;s-Eye View of the World &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
