<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Political Parties Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/political-parties/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/political-parties/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Political Parties Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/political-parties/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>It Was All a Lie : How the Republican Party Became Donald Trump &#8211; Stuart Stevens</title>
		<link>/it-was-all-a-lie-how-the-republican-party-became-donald-trump-stuart-stevens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/it-was-all-a-lie-how-the-republican-party-became-donald-trump-stuart-stevens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER In his bare-knuckles account, Stevens confesses to the reader that the entire apparatus of his Republican Party is built on a pack of lies&#8230; This reckoning inspired Stevens to publish this blistering, tell-all history&#8230; Although this book will be a hard read for any committed conservatives, they would do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-was-all-a-lie-how-the-republican-party-became-donald-trump-stuart-stevens/">It Was All a Lie : How the Republican Party Became Donald Trump &#8211; Stuart Stevens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER </p>
<p>                    In his bare-knuckles account, Stevens confesses to the reader that the entire apparatus of his Republican Party is built on a pack of lies&#8230; This reckoning inspired Stevens to publish this blistering, tell-all history&#8230; Although this book will be a hard read for any committed conservatives, they would do well to ponder it.<br />
                    &#8211;Julian E. Zelizer, The New York Times </p>
<p>                    From the most successful Republican political operative of his generation, a searing, unflinching, and deeply personal exposé of how his party became what it is today </p>
<p>                    Stuart Stevens spent decades electing Republicans at every level, from presidents to senators to local officials. He knows the GOP as intimately as anyone in America, and in this new book he offers a devastating portrait of a party that has lost its moral and political compass. </p>
<p>                    This is not a book about how Donald J. Trump hijacked the Republican Party and changed it into something else. Stevens shows how Trump is in fact the natural outcome of five decades of hypocrisy and self-delusion, dating all the way back to the civil rights legislation of the early 1960s. Stevens shows how racism has always lurked in the modern GOP&#8217;s DNA, from Goldwater&#8217;s opposition to desegregation to Ronald Reagan&#8217;s welfare queens and states&#8217; rights rhetoric. He gives an insider&#8217;s account of the rank hypocrisy of the party&#8217;s claims to embody family values, and shows how the party&#8217;s vaunted commitment to fiscal responsibility has been a charade since the 1980s. When a party stands for nothing, he argues, it is only natural that it will be taken over by the loudest and angriest voices in the room. </p>
<p>                    It Was All a Lie is not just an indictment of the Republican Party, but a candid and often lacerating mea culpa. Stevens is not asking for pity or forgiveness; he is simply telling us what he has seen firsthand. He helped to create the modern party that kneels before a morally bankrupt con man and now he wants nothing more than to see what it has become burned to the ground.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-was-all-a-lie-how-the-republican-party-became-donald-trump-stuart-stevens/">It Was All a Lie : How the Republican Party Became Donald Trump &#8211; Stuart Stevens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</title>
		<link>/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019 Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump. The 2016 election was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019</p>
<p>                    Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump.</p>
<p>                    The 2016 election was a watershed for the United States. But, as Tim Alberta explains in American Carnage, to understand Trump&#8217;s victory is to view him not as the creator of this era of polarization and bruising partisanship, but rather as its most manifest consequence.</p>
<p>                    American Carnage is the story of a president&#8217;s rise based on a country&#8217;s evolution and a party&#8217;s collapse. As George W. Bush left office with record-low approval ratings and Barack Obama led a Democratic takeover of Washington, Republicans faced a moment of reckoning: They had no vision, no generation of new leaders, and no energy in the party&#8217;s base. Yet Obama&#8217;s forceful pursuit of his progressive agenda, coupled with the nation&#8217;s rapidly changing cultural and demographic landscape, lit a fire under the right, returning Republicans to power and inviting a bloody struggle for the party&#8217;s identity in the post-Bush era. The factions that emerged-one led by absolutists like Jim Jordan and Ted Cruz, the other led by pragmatists like John Boehner and Mitch McConnell-engaged in a series of devastating internecine clashes and attempted coups for control. With the GOP&#8217;s internal fissures rendering it legislatively impotent, and that impotence fueling a growing resentment toward the political class and its institutions, the stage was set for an outsider to crash the party. When Trump descended a gilded escalator to announce his run in the summer of 2015, the candidate had met the moment.</p>
<p>                    Only by viewing Trump as the culmination of a decade-long civil war inside the Republican Party-and of the parallel sense of cultural, socioeconomic, and technological disruption during that period-can we appreciate how he won the White House and consider the fundamental questions at the center of America&#8217;s current turmoil. How did a party obsessed with the national debt vote for trillion-dollar deficits and record-setting spending increases? How did the party of compassionate conservatism become the party of Muslim bans and walls? How did the party of family values elect a thrice-divorced philanderer? And, most important, how long can such a party survive?</p>
<p>                     Loaded with exclusive reporting and based off hundreds of interviews-including with key players such as President Trump, Paul Ryan, Ted Cruz, John Boehner, Mitch McConnell, Jim DeMint, and Reince Priebus, and many others-American Carnage takes us behind the scenes of this tumultuous period as we&#8217;ve never seen it before and establishes Tim Alberta as the premier chronicler of this political era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Of course, everything [D&#8217;Souza] says here is accurate&#8230; But it&#8217;s not going to sit well with people on the American left who, of course, are portraying themselves as the exact opposite of all of this. &#8211;RUSH LIMBAUGH The explosive new book from Dinesh D&#8217;Souza, author of the #1 New York Times bestsellers Hillary&#8217;s America, America, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/">The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Of course, everything [D&#8217;Souza] says here is accurate&#8230; But it&#8217;s not going to sit well with people on the American left who, of course, are portraying themselves as the exact opposite of all of this. &#8211;RUSH LIMBAUGH     </p>
<p>                    The explosive new book from Dinesh D&#8217;Souza, author of the #1 New York Times bestsellers Hillary&#8217;s America, America, and Obama&#8217;s America.      </p>
<p>                     What is the big lie of the Democratic Party? That conservatives&#8211;and President Donald Trump in particular&#8211;are fascists. Nazis, even. In a typical comment, MSNBC host Rachel Maddow says the Trump era is reminiscent of what it was like when Hitler first became chancellor.     </p>
<p>                     But in fact, this audacious lie is a complete inversion of the truth. Yes, there is a fascist threat in America&#8211;but that threat is from the Left and the Democratic Party. The Democratic left has an ideology virtually identical with fascism and routinely borrows tactics of intimidation and political terror from the Nazi Brownshirts.     </p>
<p>                     To cover up their insidious fascist agenda, Democrats loudly accuse President Trump and other Republicans of being Nazis&#8211;an obvious lie, considering the GOP has been fighting the Democrats over slavery, genocide, racism and fascism from the beginning.     </p>
<p>                     Now, finally, Dinesh D&#8217;Souza explodes the Left&#8217;s big lie. He expertly exonerates President Trump and his supporters, then uncovers the Democratic Left&#8217;s long, cozy relationship with Nazism: how the racist and genocidal acts of early Democrats inspired Adolf Hitler&#8217;s campaign of death; how fascist philosophers influenced the great 20th century lions of the American Left; and how today&#8217;s anti-free speech, anti-capitalist, anti-religious liberty, pro-violence Democratic Party is a frightening simulacrum of the Nazi Party.     </p>
<p>                     Hitler coined the term the big lie to describe a lie that the great masses of the people will fall for precisely because of how bold and monstrous the lie is. In The Big Lie, D&#8217;Souza shows that the Democratic Left&#8217;s orchestrated campaign to paint President Trump and conservatives as Nazis to cover up its own fascism is, in fact, the biggest lie of all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/">The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Them : Why We Hate Each Other&#8211;and How to Heal &#8211; Ben Sasse (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Something is wrong. We all know it. American life expectancy is declining for a third straight year. Birth rates are dropping. Nearly half of us think the other political party isn&#8217;t just wrong; they&#8217;re evil. We&#8217;re the richest country in history, but we&#8217;ve never been more pessimistic. What&#8217;s causing the despair? In Them, bestselling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/">Them : Why We Hate Each Other&#8211;and How to Heal &#8211; Ben Sasse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Something is wrong. We all know it. American life expectancy is declining for a third straight year. Birth rates are dropping. Nearly half of us think the other political party isn&#8217;t just wrong; they&#8217;re evil. We&#8217;re the richest country in history, but we&#8217;ve never been more pessimistic. What&#8217;s causing the despair?    </p>
<p>                    In Them, bestselling author and U.S. senator Ben Sasse argues that our crisis isn&#8217;t really about politics. It&#8217;s that we&#8217;re so lonely we can&#8217;t see straight &#8211; and it bubbles out as anger. Local communities are collapsing. Across the nation, little leagues are disappearing, Rotary clubs are dwindling, and in all likelihood, we don&#8217;t know the neighbour two doors down. Work isn&#8217;t what we&#8217;d hoped: less certainty, few lifelong coworkers, shallow purpose. Stable families and enduring friendships &#8211; life&#8217;s fundamental pillars &#8211; are in statistical freefall.    </p>
<p>                    As traditional tribes of place evaporate, we rally against common enemies so we can feel part of a team. No institutions command widespread public trust, enabling foreign intelligence agencies to use technology to pick the scabs on our toxic divisions. We&#8217;re in danger of half of us believing different facts than the other half, and the digital revolution throws gas on the fire.    </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s a path forward &#8211; but reversing our decline requires something radical: a rediscovery of real places and human-to-human relationships. Even as technology nudges us to become rootless, Sasse shows how only a recovery of rootedness can heal our lonely souls. America wants you to be happy, but more urgently, America needs you to love your neighbour and connect with your community. Fixing what&#8217;s wrong with the country depends on it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/">Them : Why We Hate Each Other&#8211;and How to Heal &#8211; Ben Sasse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Do Nothing : Resisting the Attention Economy &#8211; Jenny Odell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-do-nothing-resisting-the-attention-economy-jenny-odell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art & Photography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic & Video Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-do-nothing-resisting-the-attention-economy-jenny-odell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** A New York Times Bestseller ** NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY: Time &#8211; The New Yorker &#8211; NPR &#8211; GQ &#8211; Elle &#8211; Vulture &#8211; Fortune &#8211; Boing Boing &#8211; The Irish Times &#8211; The New York Public Library &#8211; The Brooklyn Public Library A complex, smart and ambitious [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-do-nothing-resisting-the-attention-economy-jenny-odell-abridged/">How To Do Nothing : Resisting the Attention Economy &#8211; Jenny Odell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** A New York Times Bestseller **     </p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY: Time &#8211; The New Yorker &#8211; NPR &#8211; GQ &#8211; Elle &#8211; Vulture &#8211; Fortune &#8211; Boing Boing &#8211; The Irish Times &#8211; The New York Public Library &#8211; The Brooklyn Public Library     </p>
<p>                    A complex, smart and ambitious book that at first reads like a self-help manual, then blossoms into a wide-ranging political manifesto.&#8211;Jonah Engel Bromwich, The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    One of President Barack Obama&#8217;s Favorite Books of 2019<br />
                    Porchlight&#8217;s Personal Development &#038; Human Behavior Book of the Year     </p>
<p>                    In a world where addictive technology is designed to buy and sell our attention, and our value is determined by our 24/7 data productivity, it can seem impossible to escape. But in this inspiring field guide to dropping out of the attention economy, artist and critic Jenny Odell shows us how we can still win back our lives.     </p>
<p>                     Odell sees our attention as the most precious&#8211;and overdrawn&#8211;resource we have. And we must actively and continuously choose how we use it. We might not spend it on things that capitalism has deemed important &#8230; but once we can start paying a new kind of attention, she writes, we can undertake bolder forms of political action, reimagine humankind&#8217;s role in the environment, and arrive at more meaningful understandings of happiness and progress.     </p>
<p>                     Far from the simple anti-technology screed, or the back-to-nature meditation we read so often, How to do Nothing is an action plan for thinking outside of capitalist narratives of efficiency and techno-determinism. Provocative, timely, and utterly persuasive, this book will change how you see your place in our world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-do-nothing-resisting-the-attention-economy-jenny-odell-abridged/">How To Do Nothing : Resisting the Attention Economy &#8211; Jenny Odell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Way Back : Restoring the Promise of America &#8211; F. H. Buckley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-way-back-restoring-the-promise-of-america-f-h-buckley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-way-back-restoring-the-promise-of-america-f-h-buckley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The promise of America is that, with ambition and hard work, anyone can rise to the top. But now the promise has been broken, and weve become an aristocracy where rich parents raise rich kids and poor parents raise poor kids. Weve been told that the changes are structural, that theres nothing we can do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-way-back-restoring-the-promise-of-america-f-h-buckley-abridged/">The Way Back : Restoring the Promise of America &#8211; F. H. Buckley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The promise of America is that, with ambition and hard work, anyone can rise to the top. But now the promise has been broken, and weve become an aristocracy where rich parents raise rich kids and poor parents raise poor kids.     </p>
<p>                    Weve been told that the changes are structural, that theres nothing we can do about this. But that doesnt explain why other First World countries are beating us hands down on the issue of mobility.     </p>
<p>                    What&#8217;s different about America is our politics. An ostensibly progressive New Class of comfortably rich professionals, media leaders, and academics has shaped the contours of American politics and given us a country of fixed economic classes. It is supported by the poorest of Americans, who have little chance to rise, an alliance of both ends against the middle that recalls the Red Tories of parliamentary countries. Because they support an aristocracy, the members of the New Class are Tories, and because of their feigned concern for the poor, they are Red Tories.    </p>
<p>                    The Way Back explains the revolution in American politics, where political insurgents have challenged the complacent establishment of both parties, and shows how we can restore the promise of economic mobility and equality by pursuing socialist ends through capitalist means.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-way-back-restoring-the-promise-of-america-f-h-buckley-abridged/">The Way Back : Restoring the Promise of America &#8211; F. H. Buckley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Senator Bernie Sanders explains where he comes from. He describes in detail how, after cutting his teeth in the Civil Rights movement, Sanders helped build an extraordinary grassroots political movement in Vermont, making it possible for him to become the first independent elected to the U.S. House of Representatives in forty years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/">Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Senator Bernie Sanders explains where he comes from. He describes in detail how, after cutting his teeth in the Civil Rights movement, Sanders helped build an extraordinary grassroots political movement in Vermont, making it possible for him to become the first independent elected to the U.S. House of Representatives in forty years and now the longest-serving independent in U.S. political history. An extensive afterword by The Nation&#8217;s National Affairs correspondent John Nichols continues the story with Sanders&#8217;s entrance into the Senate, the drama of the 2016 Democratic Primary, his ongoing resistance to Trump, and the thrilling launch of his 2020 bid for the White House. A new foreword by Nina Turner, former president of Our Revolution and co-chair of the Sanders for President campaign, provides a rare glimpse of Bernie as a person. Outsider in the White House tells the story of a passionate and principled political life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/">Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Read the inspiring Sunday Times bestselling memoir from the first woman, and woman of colour, to serve as Vice President of the United States. &#8216;A life story that genuinely entrances&#8217; Los Angeles Times The daughter of immigrants and civil rights activists, Vice President Kamala Harris was raised in a California community that cared deeply about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/">The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read the inspiring Sunday Times bestselling memoir from the first woman, and woman of colour, to serve as Vice President of the United States.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A life story that genuinely entrances&#8217; Los Angeles Times    </p>
<p>                    The daughter of immigrants and civil rights activists, Vice President Kamala Harris was raised in a California community that cared deeply about social justice. As she rose to prominence as a political leader, her experiences would become her guiding light as she grappled with an array of complex issues and learned to bring a voice to the voiceless.    </p>
<p>                    Now, in The Truths We Hold, Harris reckons with the big challenges we face together. Drawing on the hard-won wisdom and insight from her own career and the work of those who have most inspired her, she communicates a vision of shared struggle, shared purpose, and shared values as we confront the great work of our day.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Personal integrity shines through every page&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/">The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Profiles in Corruption : Abuse of Power by America&#8217;s Progressive Elite &#8211; Peter Schweizer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER! Washington insiders operate by a proven credo: When a Peter Schweizer book drops, duck and brace for impact. For over a decade, the work of six-time New York Times bestselling investigative reporter Peter Schweizer has sent shockwaves through the political universe. Clinton Cash revealed the Clintons&#8217; international money flow, exposed global [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/">Profiles in Corruption : Abuse of Power by America&#8217;s Progressive Elite &#8211; Peter Schweizer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER!    </p>
<p>                    Washington insiders operate by a proven credo: When a Peter Schweizer book drops, duck and brace for impact.    </p>
<p>                    For over a decade, the work of six-time New York Times bestselling investigative reporter Peter Schweizer has sent shockwaves through the political universe.    </p>
<p>                    Clinton Cash revealed the Clintons&#8217; international money flow, exposed global corruption, and sparked an FBI investigation. Secret Empires exposed bipartisan corruption and launched congressional investigations. And Throw Them All Out and Extortion prompted passage of the STOCK Act. Indeed, Schweizer&#8217;s &#8220;follow the money&#8221; bombshell revelations have been featured on the front pages of the New York Times and the Wall Street Journal, and regularly appear on national news programs, including 60 Minutes.    </p>
<p>                    Now Schweizer and his team of seasoned investigators turn their focus to the nation&#8217;s top progressives-politicians who strive to acquire more government power to achieve their political ends.    </p>
<p>                    Can they be trusted with more power?    </p>
<p>                    In Profiles in Corruption, Schweizer offers a deep-dive investigation into the private finances, and secrets deals of some of America&#8217;s top political leaders. And, as usual, he doesn&#8217;t disappoint, with never-before-reported revelations that uncover corruption and abuse of power-all backed up by a mountain of corporate documents and legal filings from around the globe. Learn about how they are making sweetheart deals, generating side income, bending the law to their own benefits, using legislation to advance their own interests, and much more.    </p>
<p>                    Profiles in Corruption contains tomorrow&#8217;s headlines.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/">Profiles in Corruption : Abuse of Power by America&#8217;s Progressive Elite &#8211; Peter Schweizer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nationalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Rick Wilson-longtime Republican strategist, political commentator, Daily Beast contributor-the #1 New York Times bestseller about the disease that is destroying the conservative movement and burning down the GOP: Trumpism. Includes an all-new chapter analyzing Trump&#8217;s impact on the 2018 elections. In the #1 New York Times bestselling Everything Trump Touches Dies, political campaign strategist [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/">Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Rick Wilson-longtime Republican strategist, political commentator, Daily Beast contributor-the #1 New York Times bestseller about the disease that is destroying the conservative movement and burning down the GOP: Trumpism.    </p>
<p>                    Includes an all-new chapter analyzing Trump&#8217;s impact on the 2018 elections.    </p>
<p>                    In the #1 New York Times bestselling Everything Trump Touches Dies, political campaign strategist and commentator Rick Wilson delivers &#8220;a searingly honest, bitingly funny, comprehensive answer to the question we find ourselves asking most mornings: &#8216;What the hell is going on?&#8217; (Chicago Tribune). The Guardian hails Everything Trump Touches Dies, saying it gives, &#8220;more unvarnished truths about Donald Trump than anyone else in the American political establishment has offered. Wilson never holds back.&#8221; Rick mercilessly exposes the damage Trump has done to the country, to the Republican Party, and to the conservative movement that has abandoned its principles for the worst President in American history.    </p>
<p>                    Wilson unblinkingly dismantles Trump&#8217;s deceptions and the illusions to which his supporters cling, shedding light on the guilty parties who empower and enable Trump in Washington and in the media. He calls out the race-war dead-enders who hitched a ride with Trump, the alt-right basement dwellers who worship him, and the social conservatives who looked the other way. Publishers Weekly calls it, &#8220;a scathing, profane, unflinching, and laugh-out-loud funny rebuke of Donald Trump and his presidency.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    No left-winger, Wilson is a lifelong conservative who delivers his withering critique of Trump from the right. A leader of the Never Trump movement, he warned from the start that Trump would destroy the lives and reputations of everyone in his orbit, and Everything Trump Touches Dies is a deft chronicle the tragicomic political story of our time. From the early campaign days through the shock of election night, to the inconceivable train-wreck of Trump&#8217;s first year. Rick Wilson provides not only an insightful analysis of the Trump administration, but also an optimistic path forward for the GOP, the conservative movement, and the country.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Hilarious, smartly written, and usually spot-on&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews), Everything Trump Touches Dies is perfect for those on either side of the aisle who need a dose of unvarnished reality, a good laugh, a strong cocktail, and a return to sanity in American politics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/">Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Socialism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Michael Newman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/socialism-a-very-short-introduction-michael-newman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/socialism-a-very-short-introduction-michael-newman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is socialism? Does it have a future, or has it become an outdated ideology in the 21st century? This Very Short Introduction considers the major theories in socialism, and explores its historical evolution from the French Revolution to the present day. Michael Newman argues that socialism has always been a diverse doctrine, while nevertheless [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/socialism-a-very-short-introduction-michael-newman-abridged/">Socialism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Michael Newman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What is socialism? Does it have a future, or has it become an outdated ideology in the 21st century?    </p>
<p>                    This Very Short Introduction considers the major theories in socialism, and explores its historical evolution from the French Revolution to the present day. Michael Newman argues that socialism has always been a diverse doctrine, while nevertheless containing a central core of interconnected values and goals: a critique of capitalism; an optimistic view of human beings; and the belief that it is possible to establish societies based on egalitarianism, social solidarity, and<br />
                    co-operation. In this new edition, he draws on case studies such as Cuba, Sweden, and Bolivia, to consider attempts to implement socialism in practice, before discussing New Left challenges to conventional notions of socialism on such questions as feminism, climate change, and direct action. Rejecting the widespread<br />
                    view that socialism is an out-dated doctrine, Newman argues that it remains ultimately relevant in today&#8217;s world.      </p>
<p>                    ABOUT THE SERIES: The Very Short Introductions series from Oxford University Press contains hundreds of titles in almost every subject area. These pocket-sized books ar the perfect way to get ahead in a new subject quickly. Our expert authors combine facts, analysis, perspective, new ideas, and enthusiasm to make interesting and challenging topics highly readable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/socialism-a-very-short-introduction-michael-newman-abridged/">Socialism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Michael Newman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the 2018 Waterstones Book of the Year Winner at the 2018 Parliamentary Book Awards Longlisted for the Orwell Prize, 2019 ____________ &#8220;A really good book&#8230; Well-structured and well-written.&#8221; Observer &#8220;Well written and incisive.&#8221; The Times &#8220;Vital and compelling.&#8221; New Statesman In an era when politicians are responsible for the Brexit logjam and embroiled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/">Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the 2018 Waterstones Book of the Year<br />
                    Winner at the 2018 Parliamentary Book Awards<br />
                    Longlisted for the Orwell Prize, 2019<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A really good book&#8230;  Well-structured and well-written.&#8221; Observer<br />
                    &#8220;Well written and incisive.&#8221; The Times<br />
                    &#8220;Vital and compelling.&#8221; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    In an era when politicians are responsible for the Brexit logjam and embroiled in sexual-harassment and expenses scandals, it&#8217;s no wonder we&#8217;ve lost our faith in government. Every year, they introduce new legislation that doesn&#8217;t do what it sets out to achieve &#8211; often with terrible financial and human costs. But, with some notable exceptions, they are decent, hard-working people, doing a hugely difficult and demanding job. In this searching examination of our political class, award-winning journalist Isabel Hardman investigates the strange and demanding world of Westminster, and asks why we end up with representatives we no longer trust &#8211; and how might faith be restored.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/">Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019 Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump. The 2016 election was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019    </p>
<p>                    Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump.    </p>
<p>                    The 2016 election was a watershed for the United States. But, as Tim Alberta explains in American Carnage, to understand Trump&#8217;s victory is to view him not as the creator of this era of polarization and bruising partisanship, but rather as its most manifest consequence.    </p>
<p>                    American Carnage is the story of a president&#8217;s rise based on a country&#8217;s evolution and a party&#8217;s collapse. As George W. Bush left office with record-low approval ratings and Barack Obama led a Democratic takeover of Washington, Republicans faced a moment of reckoning: They had no vision, no generation of new leaders, and no energy in the party&#8217;s base. Yet Obama&#8217;s forceful pursuit of his progressive agenda, coupled with the nation&#8217;s rapidly changing cultural and demographic landscape, lit a fire under the right, returning Republicans to power and inviting a bloody struggle for the party&#8217;s identity in the post-Bush era. The factions that emerged-one led by absolutists like Jim Jordan and Ted Cruz, the other led by pragmatists like John Boehner and Mitch McConnell-engaged in a series of devastating internecine clashes and attempted coups for control. With the GOP&#8217;s internal fissures rendering it legislatively impotent, and that impotence fueling a growing resentment toward the political class and its institutions, the stage was set for an outsider to crash the party. When Trump descended a gilded escalator to announce his run in the summer of 2015, the candidate had met the moment.    </p>
<p>                    Only by viewing Trump as the culmination of a decade-long civil war inside the Republican Party-and of the parallel sense of cultural, socioeconomic, and technological disruption during that period-can we appreciate how he won the White House and consider the fundamental questions at the center of America&#8217;s current turmoil. How did a party obsessed with the national debt vote for trillion-dollar deficits and record-setting spending increases? How did the party of compassionate conservatism become the party of Muslim bans and walls? How did the party of family values elect a thrice-divorced philanderer? And, most important, how long can such a party survive?    </p>
<p>                     Loaded with exclusive reporting and based off hundreds of interviews-including with key players such as President Trump, Paul Ryan, Ted Cruz, John Boehner, Mitch McConnell, Jim DeMint, and Reince Priebus, and many others-American Carnage takes us behind the scenes of this tumultuous period as we&#8217;ve never seen it before and establishes Tim Alberta as the premier chronicler of this political era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
