<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Financial Crises &amp; Disasters Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/financial-crises-disasters/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/financial-crises-disasters/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Financial Crises &amp; Disasters Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/financial-crises-disasters/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Coronavirus: Leadership and Recovery: The Insights You Need from Harvard Business Review : Leadership + Recovery &#8211; Harvard Business Review</title>
		<link>/coronavirus-leadership-and-recovery-the-insights-you-need-from-harvard-business-review-leadership-recovery-harvard-business-review/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/coronavirus-leadership-and-recovery-the-insights-you-need-from-harvard-business-review-leadership-recovery-harvard-business-review/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lead through the crisis and prepare for recovery. As the Covid-19 pandemic is exacting its toll on the global economy, forward-looking organizations are moving past crisis management and positioning themselves to leap ahead when the worst is over. What should you and your organization be doing now to address today&#8217;s unprecedented challenges while laying the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coronavirus-leadership-and-recovery-the-insights-you-need-from-harvard-business-review-leadership-recovery-harvard-business-review/">Coronavirus: Leadership and Recovery: The Insights You Need from Harvard Business Review : Leadership + Recovery &#8211; Harvard Business Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lead through the crisis and prepare for recovery.</p>
<p>                    As the Covid-19 pandemic is exacting its toll on the global economy, forward-looking organizations are moving past crisis management and positioning themselves to leap ahead when the worst is over. What should you and your organization be doing now to address today&#8217;s unprecedented challenges while laying the foundation needed to emerge stronger?</p>
<p>                    Coronavirus: Leadership and Recovery provides you with essential thinking about managing your company through the pandemic, keeping your employees (and yourself) healthy and productive, and spurring your business to continue innovating and reinventing itself ahead of the recovery.</p>
<p>                    Business is changing. Will you adapt or be left behind? Get up to speed and deepen your understanding of the topics that are shaping your company&#8217;s future with the Insights You Need from Harvard Business Review series. Featuring HBR&#8217;s smartest thinking on fast-moving issues&#038;#8212blockchain, cybersecurity, AI, and more&#038;#8212each book provides the foundational introduction and practical case studies your organization needs to compete today and collects the best research, interviews, and analysis to get it ready for tomorrow.</p>
<p>                    You can&#8217;t afford to ignore how these issues will transform the landscape of business and society. The Insights You Need series will help you grasp these critical ideas&#038;#8212and prepare you and your company for the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coronavirus-leadership-and-recovery-the-insights-you-need-from-harvard-business-review-leadership-recovery-harvard-business-review/">Coronavirus: Leadership and Recovery: The Insights You Need from Harvard Business Review : Leadership + Recovery &#8211; Harvard Business Review</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unshakeable : Your Guide to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins</title>
		<link>/unshakeable-your-guide-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unshakeable-your-guide-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER* Tony Robbins, arguably the most recognizable life and business strategist and guru, is back with a timely, unique follow-up to his smash New York Times bestseller Money: Master the Game. Market corrections are as constant as seasons are in nature. There have been 30 such corrections in the past 30 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unshakeable-your-guide-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins/">Unshakeable : Your Guide to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER*</p>
<p>                     Tony Robbins, arguably the most recognizable life and business strategist and guru, is back with a timely, unique follow-up to his smash New York Times bestseller Money: Master the Game.<br />
                       Market corrections are as constant as seasons are in nature. There have been 30 such corrections in the past 30 years, yet there&#8217;s never been an action plan for how not only to survive, but thrive through each change in the stock market.<br />
                       Building upon the principles in Money: Master the Game, Robbins offers the reader specific steps they can implement to protect their investments while maximizing their wealth. It&#8217;s a detailed guide designed for investors, articulated in the common-sense, practical manner that the millions of loyal Robbins fans and students have come to expect and rely upon.<br />
                       Few have navigated the turbulence of the stock market as adeptly and successfully as Tony Robbins. His proven, consistent success over decades makes him singularly qualified to help investors (both seasoned and first-timers alike) preserve and add to their investments.</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Tony&#8217;s power is super-human&#8217; Oprah Winfrey<br />
                     &#8216;He has a great gift. He has the gift to inspire&#8217; Bill Clinton<br />
                     &#8216;Tony Robbins needs no introduction. He is committed to helping make life better for every investor&#8217; Carl Icahn<br />
                     &#8216;The high priest of human potential. The world can&#8217;t get enough of Anthony Robbins&#8217; The New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unshakeable-your-guide-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins/">Unshakeable : Your Guide to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panic! : The Story of Modern Financial Insanity &#8211; Michael Lewis</title>
		<link>/panic-the-story-of-modern-financial-insanity-michael-lewis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/panic-the-story-of-modern-financial-insanity-michael-lewis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Black Monday to the Asian financial crisis, from the internet bubble to mortgage meltdown, our lives are ruled by crazy cycles of euphoria and hysteria that manage to grip the world but are all-too-soon forgotten. In this unique collection of articles Michael Lewis &#8211; ex-trader and bestselling chronicler of greed and frenzy in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/panic-the-story-of-modern-financial-insanity-michael-lewis/">Panic! : The Story of Modern Financial Insanity &#8211; Michael Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Black Monday to the Asian financial crisis, from the internet bubble to mortgage meltdown, our lives are ruled by crazy cycles of euphoria and hysteria that manage to grip the world but are all-too-soon forgotten.     </p>
<p>                    In this unique collection of articles Michael Lewis &#8211; ex-trader and bestselling chronicler of greed and frenzy in the markets &#8211; casts a sceptical eye back over the most panicked-about panics of recent decades. He tells a story of boom and bust, deranged greed, outsized egos and over-inflated salaries, where the only thing that can ever be predicted is our constant inability to predict anything.     </p>
<p>                    Using contemporary accounts from commentators such as Joseph Stiglitz, Jeffrey Sachs and Paul Krugman, plus many of his own best writings, Lewis conveys the mood before each catastrophe, what it was like in the heat of the moment, how, afterwards, we tried to explain away the chaos &#8211; and then failed to learn from it before the whole process started all over again.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/panic-the-story-of-modern-financial-insanity-michael-lewis/">Panic! : The Story of Modern Financial Insanity &#8211; Michael Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EU & European Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** The Sunday Times #1 Bestseller** &#8216;One of the greatest political memoirs of all time&#8217; Guardian What happens when you take on the European establishment? Read as world-famous, provocative economist, and former Greece finance minister, Yanis Varoufakis, blows the lid on his battle with EU officials over the Greek debt crisis. Varoufakis sparked one of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/">Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** The Sunday Times #1 Bestseller**    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the greatest political memoirs of all time&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    What happens when you take on the European establishment?     </p>
<p>                    Read as world-famous, provocative economist, and former Greece finance minister, Yanis Varoufakis, blows the lid on his battle with EU officials over the Greek debt crisis.     </p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                              Varoufakis sparked one of the most spectacular and controversial battles in recent political history with his attempt to renegotiate Greece&#8217;s relationship with the European Union. Yet despite the mass support of the Greek people, and simple logic of his arguments, he succeeded only in provoking the fury of Europe&#8217;s political, financial and media elite.<br />
                                                                                                                                                                                          Exposing the real business taking place behind the EU&#8217;s closed doors, Varoufakis reveals all in this fearless, personal account. Adults In The Room is an extraordinary tale of brinkmanship, hypocrisy, collusion and betrayal that will shake the European and economic establishment to its foundations.     </p>
<p>                    Varoufakis is sending out an urgent wake-up call to renew European democracy before it is too late.    </p>
<p>                    **ONE OF THE GUARDIAN&#8217;S 100 BEST BOOKS OF THE 21st CENTURY**</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/">Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Hour Between Dog and Wolf : Risk-Taking, Gut Feelings and the Biology of Boom and Bust &#8211; John Coates (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-hour-between-dog-and-wolf-risk-taking-gut-feelings-and-the-biology-of-boom-and-bust-john-coates-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-hour-between-dog-and-wolf-risk-taking-gut-feelings-and-the-biology-of-boom-and-bust-john-coates-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now shortlisted for the 2012 Financial Times Business Book of the Year Award and the Wellcome Trust Book Prize, The Hour Between Dog and Wolf is a resonant exploration of economic behaviour and its consequences. Shortlisted for the 2012 Financial Times and Goldman Sachs Business Book of the Year Award and the Wellcome Trust Book [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hour-between-dog-and-wolf-risk-taking-gut-feelings-and-the-biology-of-boom-and-bust-john-coates-abridged/">The Hour Between Dog and Wolf : Risk-Taking, Gut Feelings and the Biology of Boom and Bust &#8211; John Coates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now shortlisted for the 2012 Financial Times Business Book of the Year Award and the Wellcome Trust Book Prize, The Hour Between Dog and Wolf is a resonant exploration of economic behaviour and its consequences.    </p>
<p>                              Shortlisted for the 2012 Financial Times and Goldman Sachs Business Book of the Year Award and the Wellcome Trust Book Prize, this startling and unconventional book from neuroscientist and former Wall Street trader John Coates shows us the bankers in their natural environment, revealing how their biochemistry has a lasting and significant impact on our economy.    </p>
<p>                              We learn how risk stimulates the most primitive part of the banker&#8217;s brain and how making the deals our bank balances depend on provokes an overwhelming fight-or-flight response. Constant swinging between aggression and apprehension impairs their judgment, causing economic upheaval in the wider world. The transformation between each split-second decision is what Coates calls the hour between dog and wolf, and understanding the biology behind bubbles and crashes may be the key to stabilising the markets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hour-between-dog-and-wolf-risk-taking-gut-feelings-and-the-biology-of-boom-and-bust-john-coates-abridged/">The Hour Between Dog and Wolf : Risk-Taking, Gut Feelings and the Biology of Boom and Bust &#8211; John Coates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Square and the Tower : Networks, Hierarchies and the Struggle for Global Power &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-square-and-the-tower-networks-hierarchies-and-the-struggle-for-global-power-niall-ferguson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-square-and-the-tower-networks-hierarchies-and-the-struggle-for-global-power-niall-ferguson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Silicon Valley needed a history lesson and Ferguson has provided it&#8217; Eric Schmidt Most history is about the people at the top of the towers of power. But what if the real action is in the social networks down below, in the town squares? Niall Ferguson, the international bestselling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-square-and-the-tower-networks-hierarchies-and-the-struggle-for-global-power-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The Square and the Tower : Networks, Hierarchies and the Struggle for Global Power &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    &#8216;Silicon Valley needed a history lesson and Ferguson has provided it&#8217;  Eric Schmidt    </p>
<p>                    Most history is about the people at the top of the towers of power. But what if the real action is in the social networks down below, in the town squares? Niall Ferguson, the international bestselling author of Empire, The Ascent of Money and Civilization,  brilliantly recasts past and present as an unending contest between hierarchies and networks.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Provocative, snappy, a rare book &#8230; fasten your seatbelts&#8217; Peter Frankopan, Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Immensely stimulating, absorbing, illuminating &#8230; sends ideas blazing all over the place &#8230; one of the best popular historians of our time&#8217; David Goodhart, Prospect    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Powerful, fast-paced &#8230; a pull-yourself-together warning to the present by way of arresting historical precedent&#8217; Andrew Anthony, Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Captivating and compelling&#8217; Jonathan A. Knee, The New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-square-and-the-tower-networks-hierarchies-and-the-struggle-for-global-power-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The Square and the Tower : Networks, Hierarchies and the Struggle for Global Power &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Austerity : The History of a Dangerous Idea &#8211; Mark Blyth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Selected as a Financial Times Best Book of 2013 Governments today in both Europe and the United States have succeeded in casting government spending as reckless wastefulness that has made the economy worse. In contrast, they have advanced a policy of draconian budget cuts-austerity-to solve the financial crisis. We are told that we have all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/">Austerity : The History of a Dangerous Idea &#8211; Mark Blyth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Selected as a Financial Times Best Book of 2013    </p>
<p>                    Governments today in both Europe and the United States have succeeded in casting government spending as reckless wastefulness that has made the economy worse. In contrast, they have advanced a policy of draconian budget cuts-austerity-to solve the financial crisis. We are told that we have all lived beyond our means and now need to tighten our belts. This view conveniently forgets where all that debt came from. Not from an orgy of government spending, but as the direct result of bailing out,<br />
                    recapitalizing, and adding liquidity to the broken banking system. Through these actions private debt was rechristened as government debt while those responsible for generating it walked away scot free, placing the blame on the state, and the burden on the taxpayer.     </p>
<p>                    That burden now takes the form of a global turn to austerity, the policy of reducing domestic wages and prices to restore competitiveness and balance the budget. The problem, according to political economist Mark Blyth, is that austerity is a very dangerous idea. First of all, it doesn&#8217;t work. As the past four years and countless historical examples from the last 100 years show, while it makes sense for any one state to try and cut its way to growth, it simply cannot work when all states try it<br />
                    simultaneously: all we do is shrink the economy. In the worst case, austerity policies worsened the Great Depression and created the conditions for seizures of power by the forces responsible for the Second World War: the Nazis and the Japanese military establishment. As Blyth amply demonstrates,<br />
                    the arguments for austerity are tenuous and the evidence thin. Rather than expanding growth and opportunity, the repeated revival of this dead economic idea has almost always led to low growth along with increases in wealth and income inequality. Austerity demolishes the conventional wisdom, marshaling an army of facts to demand that we austerity for what it is, and what it costs us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/austerity-the-history-of-a-dangerous-idea-mark-blyth-abridged/">Austerity : The History of a Dangerous Idea &#8211; Mark Blyth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crashed : How a Decade of Financial Crises Changed the World &#8211; Adam Tooze (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the 2019 Lionel Gelber Prize &#8216;Majestic, informative and often delightful &#8230; insights on every page&#8217; Yanis Varoufakis, Observer The definitive history of the Great Financial Crisis, from the acclaimed author of The Deluge and The Wages of Destruction. In September 2008 the Great Financial Crisis, triggered by the collapse of Lehman brothers, shook [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/">Crashed : How a Decade of Financial Crises Changed the World &#8211; Adam Tooze (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the 2019 Lionel Gelber Prize    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Majestic, informative and often delightful &#8230; insights on every page&#8217; Yanis Varoufakis, Observer    </p>
<p>                    The definitive history of the Great Financial Crisis, from the acclaimed author of The Deluge and The Wages of Destruction.     </p>
<p>                    In September 2008 the Great Financial Crisis, triggered by the collapse of Lehman brothers, shook the world. A decade later its spectre still haunts us. As the appalling scope and scale of the crash was revealed, the financial institutions that had symbolised the West&#8217;s triumph since the end of the Cold War, seemed &#8211; through greed, malice and incompetence &#8211; to be about to bring the entire system to its knees.    </p>
<p>                    Crashed is a brilliantly original and assured analysis of what happened and how we were rescued from something even worse &#8211; but at a price which continues to undermine democracy across Europe and the United States. Gnawing away at our institutions are the many billions of dollars which were conjured up to prevent complete collapse. Over and over again, the end of the crisis has been announced, but it continues to hound us &#8211; whether in Greece or Ukraine, whether through Brexit or Trump. Adam Tooze follows the trail like no previous writer and has written a book compelling as history, as economic analysis and as political horror story.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/">Crashed : How a Decade of Financial Crises Changed the World &#8211; Adam Tooze (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are mass violence and catastrophes the only forces that can seriously decrease economic inequality? To judge by thousands of years of history, the answer is yes. Tracing the global history of inequality from the Stone Age to today, Walter Scheidel shows that it never dies peacefully. The Great Leveler is the first book to chart [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/">The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are mass violence and catastrophes the only forces that can seriously decrease economic inequality? To judge by thousands of years of history, the answer is yes. Tracing the global history of inequality from the Stone Age to today, Walter Scheidel shows that it never dies peacefully. The Great Leveler is the first book to chart the crucial role of violent shocks in reducing inequality over the full sweep of human history around the world. The &#8220;Four Horsemen&#8221; of leveling-mass-mobilization warfare, transformative revolutions, state collapse, and catastrophic plagues-have repeatedly destroyed the fortunes of the rich. Today, the violence that reduced inequality in the past seems to have diminished, and that is a good thing. But it casts serious doubt on the prospects for a more equal future. An essential contribution to the debate about inequality, The Great Leveler provides important new insights about why inequality is so persistent-and why it is unlikely to decline anytime soon.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/">The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
