<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Astronomy, Space &amp; Time Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/astronomy-space-time/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/astronomy-space-time/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Astronomy, Space &amp; Time Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/astronomy-space-time/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Magic of Reality : How we know what&#8217;s really true &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-magic-of-reality-how-we-know-whats-really-true-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Space Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-magic-of-reality-how-we-know-whats-really-true-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Magic takes many forms. The ancient Egyptians explained the night by suggesting that the goddess Nut swallowed the sun. The Vikings believed a rainbow was the gods&#8217; bridge to earth. These are magical, extraordinary tales. But there is another kind of magic, and it lies in the exhilaration of discovering the real answers to these [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-magic-of-reality-how-we-know-whats-really-true-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Magic of Reality : How we know what&#8217;s really true &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Magic takes many forms. The ancient Egyptians explained the night by suggesting that the goddess Nut swallowed the sun. The Vikings believed a rainbow was the gods&#8217; bridge to earth. These are magical, extraordinary tales. But there is another kind of magic, and it lies in the exhilaration of discovering the real answers to these questions. It is the magic of reality &#8211; science.    </p>
<p>                    Packed with inspiring explanations of space, time and evolution, laced with humour and clever thought experiments, The Magic of Reality explores a stunningly wide range of natural phenomena. What is stuff made of? How old is the universe? What causes tsunamis? Who was the first man, or woman? This is a page-turning, inspirational detective story that not only mines all the sciences for its clues but primes the reader to think like a scientist too.    </p>
<p>                    Richard Dawkins elucidates the wonders of the natural world to all ages with his inimitable clarity and exuberance in a text that will enlighten and inform for generations to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-magic-of-reality-how-we-know-whats-really-true-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Magic of Reality : How we know what&#8217;s really true &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmosapiens : Human Evolution from the Origin of the Universe &#8211; John Hands (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Daily Telegraph and TLS Book of the Year &#8216;An audacious tour of all that science can teach us&#8217; Edward O. Wilson Specialist scientific fields are developing at incredibly swift speeds, but what can they really tell us about how the universe began and how humans evolved to play such a dominant role on Earth? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/">Cosmosapiens : Human Evolution from the Origin of the Universe &#8211; John Hands (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Daily Telegraph and TLS Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An audacious tour of all that science can teach us&#8217; Edward O. Wilson    </p>
<p>                    Specialist scientific fields are developing at incredibly swift speeds, but what can they really tell us about how the universe began and how humans evolved to play such a dominant role on Earth? John Hands&#8217;s extraordinarily ambitious quest brings together our scientific knowledge and evaluates the theories and evidence about the origin and evolution of matter, life, consciousness, and humankind.    </p>
<p>                    Cosmosapiens provides the most comprehensive account yet of current ideas such as cosmic inflation, dark energy, the selfish gene, and neurogenetic determinism. In clear and accessible language, Hands differentiates the firmly established from the speculative and examines the claims of various fields such as string theory to approach a unified theory of everything. In doing so he challenges the orthodox consensus in those branches of cosmology, biology, and neuroscience that have ossified into dogma. His striking analysis reveals underlying patterns of cooperation, complexification, and convergence that lead to the unique emergence in humans of a self-reflective consciousness that enables us to determine our future evolution. This groundbreaking book is destined to become a classic of scientific thinking.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/">Cosmosapiens : Human Evolution from the Origin of the Universe &#8211; John Hands (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmos &#8211; Carl Sagan, Foreword by Neil deGrasse Tyson, Introduction by Ann Druyan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meteorology & Climatology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>RETURNING TO TELEVISION AS AN ALL-NEW MINISERIES ON FOX Cosmos is one of the bestselling science books of all time. In clear-eyed prose, Sagan reveals a jewel-like blue world inhabited by a life form that is just beginning to discover its own identity and to venture into the vast ocean of space. Featuring a new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/">Cosmos &#8211; Carl Sagan, Foreword by Neil deGrasse Tyson, Introduction by Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>RETURNING TO TELEVISION AS AN ALL-NEW MINISERIES ON FOX     </p>
<p>                    Cosmos is one of the bestselling science books of all time. In clear-eyed prose, Sagan reveals a jewel-like blue world inhabited by a life form that is just beginning to discover its own identity and to venture into the vast ocean of space. Featuring a new Introduction by Sagan&#8217;s collaborator, Ann Druyan, full color illustrations, and a new Foreword by astrophysicist Neil deGrasse Tyson, Cosmos retraces the fourteen billion years of cosmic evolution that have transformed matter into consciousness, exploring such topics as the origin of life, the human brain, Egyptian hieroglyphics, spacecraft missions, the death of the Sun, the evolution of galaxies, and the forces and individuals who helped to shape modern science.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Cosmos     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Magnificent . . . With a lyrical literary style, and a range that touches almost all aspects of human knowledge, Cosmos often seems too good to be true.&#8221;&#8211;The Plain Dealer     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Sagan is an astronomer with one eye on the stars, another on history, and a third&#8211;his mind&#8217;s&#8211;on the human condition.&#8221;&#8211;Newsday     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Brilliant in its scope and provocative in its suggestions . . . shimmers with a sense of wonder.&#8221;&#8211;The Miami Herald     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Sagan dazzles the mind with the miracle of our survival, framed by the stately galaxies of space.&#8221;&#8211;Cosmopolitan     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Enticing . . . iridescent . . . imaginatively illustrated.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/">Cosmos &#8211; Carl Sagan, Foreword by Neil deGrasse Tyson, Introduction by Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Astronaut&#8217;s Guide to Life on Earth &#8211; Chris Hadfield (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/an-astronauts-guide-to-life-on-earth-chris-hadfield-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aerospace & Aviation Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronautics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Astronomy & Space]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-astronauts-guide-to-life-on-earth-chris-hadfield-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Back on the earth after three spaceflights, Chris Hadfield&#8217;s captivating memoir An Astronaut&#8217;s Guide to Life on Earth reveals extraordinary stories from his life as an astronaut, and shows how to make the impossible a reality. Colonel Chris Hadfield has spent decades training as an astronaut and has logged nearly 4,000 hours in space. During [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-astronauts-guide-to-life-on-earth-chris-hadfield-abridged/">An Astronaut&#8217;s Guide to Life on Earth &#8211; Chris Hadfield (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Back on the earth after three spaceflights, Chris Hadfield&#8217;s captivating memoir An Astronaut&#8217;s Guide to Life on Earth reveals extraordinary stories from his life as an astronaut, and shows how to make the impossible a reality.    </p>
<p>                    Colonel Chris Hadfield has spent decades training as an astronaut and has logged nearly 4,000 hours in space. During this time he has broken into a Space Station with a Swiss army knife, disposed of a live snake while piloting a plane, been temporarily blinded while clinging to the exterior of an orbiting spacecraft, and become a YouTube sensation with his performance of David Bowie&#8217;s &#8216;Space Oddity&#8217; in space. The secret to Chris Hadfield&#8217;s success &#8211; and survival &#8211; is an unconventional philosophy he learned at NASA: prepare for the worst &#8211; and enjoy every moment of it.    </p>
<p>                    In his book, An Astronaut&#8217;s Guide to Life on Earth, Chris Hadfield takes readers deep into his years of training and space exploration to show how to make the impossible possible. Through eye-opening, entertaining stories filled with the adrenaline of launch, the mesmerizing wonder of spacewalks and the measured, calm responses mandated by crises, he explains how conventional wisdom can get in the way of achievement &#8211; and happiness. His own extraordinary education in space has taught him some counter-intuitive lessons: don&#8217;t visualize success, do care what others think, and always sweat the small stuff.    </p>
<p>                    You might never be able to build a robot, pilot a spacecraft, make a music video or perform basic surgery in zero gravity like Colonel Hadfield. But his vivid and refreshing insights in this book will teach you how to think like an astronaut, and will change, completely, the way you view life on Earth &#8211; especially your own.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-astronauts-guide-to-life-on-earth-chris-hadfield-abridged/">An Astronaut&#8217;s Guide to Life on Earth &#8211; Chris Hadfield (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time (chronology), Time Systems & Standards]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR From the acclaimed author of The Information and Chaos, a mind-bending exploration of time travel: its subversive origins, its evolution in literature and science, and its influence on our understanding of time itself. Gleick&#8217;s story begins at the turn of the twentieth century with the young H. G. Wells [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/">Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                              From the acclaimed author of The Information and Chaos, a mind-bending exploration of time travel: its subversive origins, its evolution in literature and science, and its influence on our understanding of time itself.    </p>
<p>                              Gleick&#8217;s story begins at the turn of the twentieth century with the young H. G. Wells writing and rewriting the fantastic tale that became his first book, an international sensation, The Time Machine. A host of forces were converging to transmute the human understanding of time, some philosophical and some technological &#8211; the electric telegraph, the steam railroad, the discovery of buried civilisations, and the perfection of clocks. Gleick tracks the evolution of time travel as an idea in the culture &#8211; from Marcel Proust to Doctor Who, from Woody Allen to Jorge Luis Borges. He explores the inevitable looping paradoxes and examines the porous boundary between pulp fiction and modern physics. Finally, he delves into a temporal shift that is unsettling our own moment: the instantaneous wired world, with its all-consuming present and vanishing future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/">Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time (chronology), Time Systems & Standards]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER One of TIME&#8217;s Ten Best Nonfiction Books of the Decade &#8216;Captivating, fascinating, profoundly beautiful. . . Rovelli is a wonderfully humane, gentle and witty guide for he is as much philosopher and poet as he is a scientist&#8217; John Banville &#8216;We are time. We are this space, this clearing opened [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    One of TIME&#8217;s Ten Best Nonfiction Books of the Decade    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Captivating, fascinating, profoundly beautiful. . . Rovelli is a wonderfully humane, gentle and witty guide for he is as much philosopher and poet as he is a scientist&#8217; John Banville    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We are time. We are this space, this clearing opened by the traces of memory inside the connections between our neurons. We are memory. We are nostalgia. We are longing for a future that will not come&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Time is a mystery that does not cease to puzzle us. Philosophers, artists and poets have long explored its meaning while scientists have found that its structure is different from the simple intuition we have of it. From Boltzmann to quantum theory, from Einstein to loop quantum gravity, our understanding of time has been undergoing radical transformations. Time flows at a different speed in different places, the past and the future differ far less than we might think, and the very notion of the present evaporates in the vast universe.    </p>
<p>                    With his extraordinary charm and sense of wonder, bringing together science, philosophy and art, Carlo Rovelli unravels this mystery. Enlightening and consoling, The Order of Time shows that to understand ourselves we need to reflect on time &#8212; and to understand time we need to reflect on ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    Translated by Simon Carnell and Erica Segre</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
