<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>International Business Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/international-business/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/international-business/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>International Business Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/international-business/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: The Elderly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pensions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface* Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time? Many of us have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface*    </p>
<p>                    Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time?     </p>
<p>                    Many of us have been raised on the traditional notion of a three-stage approach to our working lives: education, followed by work and then retirement.  But this well-established pathway is already beginning to collapse &#8211; life expectancy is rising, final-salary pensions are vanishing, and increasing numbers of people are juggling multiple careers. Whether you are 18, 45 or 60, you will need to do things very differently from previous generations and learn to structure your life in completely new ways.    </p>
<p>                    The 100-Year Life is here to help.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the unique pairing of their experience in psychology and economics, Lynda Gratton and Andrew J. Scott offer a broad-ranging analysis as well as a raft of solutions, showing how to rethink your finances, your education, your career and your relationships and create a fulfilling 100-year life.     </p>
<p>                    * How can you fashion a career and life path that defines you and your values and creates a shifting balance between work and leisure?    </p>
<p>                    * What are the most effective ways of boosting your physical and mental health over a longer and more dynamic lifespan?    </p>
<p>                    * How can you make the most of your intangible assets &#8211; such as family and friends &#8211; as you build a productive, longer life?    </p>
<p>                    * In a multiple-stage life how can you learn to make the transitions that will be so crucial and experiment with new ways of living, working and learning?    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award and featuring a new preface, The 100-Year Life is a wake-up call that describes what to expect and considers the choices and options that you will face. It is also fundamentally a call to action for individuals, politicians, firms and governments and offers the clearest demonstration that a 100-year life can be a wonderful and inspiring one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EU & European Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** The Sunday Times #1 Bestseller** &#8216;One of the greatest political memoirs of all time&#8217; Guardian What happens when you take on the European establishment? Read as world-famous, provocative economist, and former Greece finance minister, Yanis Varoufakis, blows the lid on his battle with EU officials over the Greek debt crisis. Varoufakis sparked one of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/">Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** The Sunday Times #1 Bestseller**    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the greatest political memoirs of all time&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    What happens when you take on the European establishment?     </p>
<p>                    Read as world-famous, provocative economist, and former Greece finance minister, Yanis Varoufakis, blows the lid on his battle with EU officials over the Greek debt crisis.     </p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                              Varoufakis sparked one of the most spectacular and controversial battles in recent political history with his attempt to renegotiate Greece&#8217;s relationship with the European Union. Yet despite the mass support of the Greek people, and simple logic of his arguments, he succeeded only in provoking the fury of Europe&#8217;s political, financial and media elite.<br />
                                                                                                                                                                                          Exposing the real business taking place behind the EU&#8217;s closed doors, Varoufakis reveals all in this fearless, personal account. Adults In The Room is an extraordinary tale of brinkmanship, hypocrisy, collusion and betrayal that will shake the European and economic establishment to its foundations.     </p>
<p>                    Varoufakis is sending out an urgent wake-up call to renew European democracy before it is too late.    </p>
<p>                    **ONE OF THE GUARDIAN&#8217;S 100 BEST BOOKS OF THE 21st CENTURY**</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/">Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leading : Lessons in leadership from the legendary Manchester United manager &#8211; Alex Ferguson, With Michael Moritz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leading-lessons-in-leadership-from-the-legendary-manchester-united-manager-alex-ferguson-with-michael-moritz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football (Soccer, Association Football)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sport & Leisure Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leading-lessons-in-leadership-from-the-legendary-manchester-united-manager-alex-ferguson-with-michael-moritz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the World&#8217;s all-time great leaders&#8217;Professor Anita Elberse, Harvard Business SchoolWhat does it take to lead a team to world-class success over a sustained period of time?Sir Alex Ferguson is one of the few leaders who truly knows. In his 38 years in management, Sir Alex won an astonishing 49 trophies and helped grow [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leading-lessons-in-leadership-from-the-legendary-manchester-united-manager-alex-ferguson-with-michael-moritz-abridged/">Leading : Lessons in leadership from the legendary Manchester United manager &#8211; Alex Ferguson, With Michael Moritz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the World&#8217;s all-time great leaders&#8217;Professor Anita Elberse, Harvard Business SchoolWhat does it take to lead a team to world-class success over a sustained period of time?Sir  Alex Ferguson is one of the few leaders who truly knows. In his 38  years in management, Sir Alex won an astonishing 49 trophies and helped  grow Manchester United into one of the biggest commercial brands in the  world.  In this inspirational and straight-talking book, Sir Alex reveals the secrets behind his record-breaking career.LEADING  is structured around the key skills that Sir Alex values most highly.  It includes subjects we immediately associate with his managerial style:  Discipline, Control, Teamwork and Motivation. But it also addresses  subjects that are less obvious but no less important when seeking  success: Delegation, Data Analysis and Dealing with Failure.Written  with the investor Sir Michael Moritz, a longstanding friend of Sir  Alex, LEADING is packed with insight, wisdom, humour and honesty. The  individual stories inevitably concern themselves with football, and the  phenomenal success that came along the way, but the lessons can be  applied by anyone.<br />
                    Whether you run a business, teach in a classroom, or  work in a small team, LEADING will help you become a better leader.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leading-lessons-in-leadership-from-the-legendary-manchester-united-manager-alex-ferguson-with-michael-moritz-abridged/">Leading : Lessons in leadership from the legendary Manchester United manager &#8211; Alex Ferguson, With Michael Moritz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Edge : Inside Information, Dirty Money, and the Quest to Bring Down the Most Wanted Man on Wall Street &#8211; Sheelah Kolhatkar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nominated for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Nominated for the Carnegie Medal for Excellence in Nonfiction Amazon Top 5 Business Books of 2017 &#8216;A prodigious feat of reporting&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell &#8216;Black Edge has the grip of a thriller &#8230; Everyone should read this book&#8217; &#8211; David Grann, New York Times bestselling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/">Black Edge : Inside Information, Dirty Money, and the Quest to Bring Down the Most Wanted Man on Wall Street &#8211; Sheelah Kolhatkar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nominated for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year<br />
                    Nominated for the Carnegie Medal for Excellence in Nonfiction<br />
                    Amazon Top 5 Business Books of 2017    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A prodigious feat of reporting&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Black Edge has the grip of a thriller &#8230; Everyone should read this book&#8217; &#8211; David Grann, New York Times bestselling author of THE LOST CITY OF Z     </p>
<p>                    How do super-rich bankers get away with it?    </p>
<p>                    There is a powerful new class of billionaire financiers in the world, who use their phenomenal wealth to write their own rules and laws.  Chief among them is Steven Cohen, a Wall Street legend, and the basis for Damian Lewis&#8217;s character in BILLIONS, who built his hedge fund into a $15 billion empire on the basis of wizard-like stock trading, and who flies to work by helicopter and owns one of the largest private art collections in the world.  But his iconic status was shattered when his fund became the target of a sprawling FBI investigation into insider trading, charged with using illegal inside information &#8211; or &#8216;black edge&#8217; &#8211; to beat the market.  His firm, SAC Capital, was ultimately indicted and pled guilty to charges of securities and wire fraud, and paid record criminal and civil fines of nearly $2 billion.  But even as the company bearing his name pled guilty, Cohen himself was never charged, and is free to start trading publicly again from January 2018.    </p>
<p>                    Black Edge offers a revelatory look at the grey zone in which so much of Wall Street functions, and a window into the transformation of the worldwide economy. With meticulous reporting and powerful storytelling, this is a riveting, true-life legal thriller that takes readers inside the US government&#8217;s pursuit of Cohen and his employees, and raises urgent questions about the power and wealth of those who sit at the pinnacle of the financial world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/">Black Edge : Inside Information, Dirty Money, and the Quest to Bring Down the Most Wanted Man on Wall Street &#8211; Sheelah Kolhatkar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Losing the Signal : The Untold Story Behind the Extraordinary Rise and Spectacular Fall of BlackBerry &#8211; Jacquie McNish, Sean Silcoff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/losing-the-signal-the-untold-story-behind-the-extraordinary-rise-and-spectacular-fall-of-blackberry-jacquie-mcnish-sean-silcoff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/losing-the-signal-the-untold-story-behind-the-extraordinary-rise-and-spectacular-fall-of-blackberry-jacquie-mcnish-sean-silcoff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Canadian National Business Book Award 2016 Shortlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award 2015 In 2009, BlackBerry controlled half of the US smartphone market. Today that number is less than one per cent. What went so wrong? Losing the Signal is the riveting story of a company that toppled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/losing-the-signal-the-untold-story-behind-the-extraordinary-rise-and-spectacular-fall-of-blackberry-jacquie-mcnish-sean-silcoff-abridged/">Losing the Signal : The Untold Story Behind the Extraordinary Rise and Spectacular Fall of BlackBerry &#8211; Jacquie McNish, Sean Silcoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Canadian National Business Book Award 2016<br />
                    Shortlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award 2015    </p>
<p>                    In 2009, BlackBerry controlled half of the US smartphone market. Today that number is less than one per cent. What went so wrong?    </p>
<p>                    Losing the Signal is the riveting story of a company that toppled global giants before succumbing to the ruthlessly competitive forces of Silicon Valley. This is not a conventional tale of modern business failure by fraud and greed; instead, the rise and fall of BlackBerry reveals the dangerous speed at which innovators race along the information superhighway.    </p>
<p>                    With unprecedented access to key players, senior executives, directors, and competitors, Losing the Signal unveils the remarkable rise of a company that started above a bagel store in a small Canadian city and went on to control half of the US smartphone market. However, at the very moment BlackBerry was ranked the world&#8217;s fastest-growing company, internal feuds and chaotic growth crippled the company as it faced its gravest test: the entry of Apple and Google into the mobile phone market.    </p>
<p>                    Expertly told by acclaimed journalists Jacquie McNish and Sean Silcoff, this is an entertaining, whirlwind narrative that goes behind the scenes to reveal one of the most compelling business stories of the new century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/losing-the-signal-the-untold-story-behind-the-extraordinary-rise-and-spectacular-fall-of-blackberry-jacquie-mcnish-sean-silcoff-abridged/">Losing the Signal : The Untold Story Behind the Extraordinary Rise and Spectacular Fall of BlackBerry &#8211; Jacquie McNish, Sean Silcoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China&#8217;s Super Consumers : What 1 Billion Customers Want and How to Sell it to Them &#8211; Savio Chan, Michael Zakkour (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chinas-super-consumers-what-1-billion-customers-want-and-how-to-sell-it-to-them-savio-chan-michael-zakkour-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chinas-super-consumers-what-1-billion-customers-want-and-how-to-sell-it-to-them-savio-chan-michael-zakkour-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chinese Consumers are Changing The World Understand Them and Sell To Them China has transformed itself from a feudal economy in the 19th century, to Mao and Communism in the 20th century, to the largest consumer market in the world by the early 21st century. China&#8217;s Super Consumers explores the extraordinary birth of consumerism in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chinas-super-consumers-what-1-billion-customers-want-and-how-to-sell-it-to-them-savio-chan-michael-zakkour-abridged/">China&#8217;s Super Consumers : What 1 Billion Customers Want and How to Sell it to Them &#8211; Savio Chan, Michael Zakkour (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chinese Consumers are Changing The World Understand Them and Sell To Them China has transformed itself from a feudal economy in the 19th century, to Mao and Communism in the 20th century, to the largest consumer market in the world by the early 21st century. China&#8217;s Super Consumers explores the extraordinary birth of consumerism in China and explains who these super consumers are. China&#8217;s Super Consumers offers an in-depth explanation of what&#8217;s inside the minds of Chinese consumers and explores what they buy, where they buy, how they buy, and most importantly why they buy. The book is filled with real-world stories of the foreign and domestic companies, leading brands, and top executives who have succeeded in selling to this burgeoning marketplace. This remarkable book also takes you inside the boardrooms of the people who understand Chinese consumers and have had success in the Chinese market.<br />
                    * A hands-on resource for succeeding in the Chinese marketplace * Filled with real-world stories of companies who have made an impact in China * Discover what the Chinese consumer wants and how to deliver the goods * Written by Savio Chan and Michael Zakkour, two leading experts on the Chinese market This book is an invaluable resource for anyone who wants a clear understanding of how China&#8217;s Super Consumers are changing the world and how to sell to them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chinas-super-consumers-what-1-billion-customers-want-and-how-to-sell-it-to-them-savio-chan-michael-zakkour-abridged/">China&#8217;s Super Consumers : What 1 Billion Customers Want and How to Sell it to Them &#8211; Savio Chan, Michael Zakkour (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Every Nation for Itself : Winners and Losers in a G-Zero World &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Following the acclaim for The End of the Free Market, Ian Bremmer is back with Every Nation for Itself, now in paperback, where he addresses the next big issue for the shifting world economy. &#8216;Smart and snappy &#8230; provides the most cogent prediction of how the politics of a post-America world will play out&#8217; New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Every Nation for Itself : Winners and Losers in a G-Zero World &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following the acclaim for The End of the Free Market, Ian Bremmer is back with Every Nation for Itself, now in paperback, where he addresses the next big issue for the shifting world economy.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Smart and snappy &#8230; provides the most cogent prediction of how the politics of a post-America world will play out&#8217;  New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    What happens when nobody&#8217;s running the world?    </p>
<p>                    The United States is in financial crisis and can&#8217;t hold onto the reins of the G-20. But China has no interest in international leadership, Europe is trying to save the euro, and emerging powers like Brazil and India are focused on domestic development. No government has the time, resources or political capital needed to take an international lead. The world power structure is about to have a vacancy&#8230;at the top.    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to the G-Zero world, in which no single country has the power to shape a truly global agenda. That means we are about to see 20 years of conflict over economics, finance and climate change.    </p>
<p>                    Bestselling author and strategist Ian Bremmer reveals how world powers are rapidly turning into gated communities, locked in competition. Who will prevail?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A prodigy in the US global commentariat. Mr Bremmer&#8217;s rehearsal of the consequences should make us all wise up&#8217; Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An author who is always full of insights&#8217; George Osborne    </p>
<p>                    Ian Bremmer is the president of the world&#8217;s leading global political risk research and consulting firm, Eurasia Group. He has written for the Wall Street Journal, Washington Post, Newsweek, and Harvard Business Review. His six books include The J Curve and The End Of The Free Market.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Every Nation for Itself : Winners and Losers in a G-Zero World &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazillionaires : The Godfathers of Modern Brazil &#8211; Alex Cuadros (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brazillionaires-the-godfathers-of-modern-brazil-alex-cuadros-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brazillionaires-the-godfathers-of-modern-brazil-alex-cuadros-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the Financial Times Business Book of the Year Award Wealth and power on the trail of the super-rich In 2012, Brazilian tycoon Eike Batista was the eighth richest man in the world, his $30bn fortune built on Brazil&#8217;s incredible natural resources. By the middle of 2013 he had lost it all, engulfed in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brazillionaires-the-godfathers-of-modern-brazil-alex-cuadros-abridged/">Brazillionaires : The Godfathers of Modern Brazil &#8211; Alex Cuadros (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the Financial Times  Business Book of the Year Award     </p>
<p>                    Wealth and power on the trail of the super-rich    </p>
<p>                    In 2012, Brazilian tycoon Eike Batista was the eighth richest man in the world, his $30bn fortune built on Brazil&#8217;s incredible natural resources. By the middle of 2013 he had lost it all, engulfed in scandal.    </p>
<p>                    Brazillionaires is a fast-paced account of Batista&#8217;s rise and fall: a story of helicopter flights, beach-front penthouses and high-speed car crashes. Along the way, it tells the parallel story of Brazil itself, a country caught in the cycle of boom and bust, renewed hope and dashed promise; a country where the hyper-rich are at the heart of the economy &#8211; and where their wealth can buy immense political power.    </p>
<p>                    Stefan Zweig said in 1941 that Brazil was the country of the future; Brazilians joke that it always will be. Today, rampant corruption and endemic inequality threaten to derail the new Brazilian Dream. The brazillionaires are the key to understanding that dream; through them Brazillionaires tells the story of their country&#8217;s past, present and future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brazillionaires-the-godfathers-of-modern-brazil-alex-cuadros-abridged/">Brazillionaires : The Godfathers of Modern Brazil &#8211; Alex Cuadros (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An absorbing and original narrative history of American capitalism NAMED A BEST BOOK OF 2017 BY THE ECONOMIST From the days of the Mayflower and the Virginia Company, America has been a place for people to dream, invent, build, tinker, and bet the farm in pursuit of a better life. Americana takes us on a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/">Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An absorbing and original narrative history of American capitalism    </p>
<p>                    NAMED A BEST BOOK OF 2017 BY THE ECONOMIST    </p>
<p>                    From the days of the Mayflower and the Virginia Company, America has been a place for people to dream, invent, build, tinker, and bet the farm in pursuit of a better life. Americana takes us on a four-hundred-year journey of this spirit of innovation and ambition through a series of Next Big Things &#8212; the inventions, techniques, and industries that drove American history forward: from the telegraph, the railroad, guns, radio, and banking to flight, suburbia, and sneakers, culminating with the Internet and mobile technology at the turn of the twenty-first century. The result is a thrilling alternative history of modern America that reframes events, trends, and people we thought we knew through the prism of the value that, for better or for worse, this nation holds dearest: capitalism.     </p>
<p>                    In a winning, accessible style, Bhu Srinivasan boldly takes on four centuries of American enterprise, revealing the unexpected connections that link them. We learn how Andrew Carnegie&#8217;s early job as a telegraph messenger boy paved the way for his leadership of the steel empire that would make him one of the nation&#8217;s richest men; how the gunmaker Remington reinvented itself in the postwar years to sell typewriters; how the inner workings of the Mafia mirrored the trend of consolidation and regulation in more traditional business; and how a 1950s infrastructure bill triggered a series of events that produced one of America&#8217;s most enduring brands: KFC. Reliving the heady early days of Silicon Valley, we are reminded that the start-up is an idea as old as America itself.    </p>
<p>                    Entertaining, eye-opening, and sweeping in its reach, Americana is an exhilarating new work of narrative history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/">Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leadership is Half the Story : A Fresh Look at Followership, Leadership, and Collaboration &#8211; Marc Hurwitz, Samantha Hurwitz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leadership-is-half-the-story-a-fresh-look-at-followership-leadership-and-collaboration-marc-hurwitz-samantha-hurwitz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-profitmaking Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leadership-is-half-the-story-a-fresh-look-at-followership-leadership-and-collaboration-marc-hurwitz-samantha-hurwitz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Can you imagine a choreographer only training one dancer to lead while his or her partner sits in the lobby staring at the wall? Yet we do this all the time in organizations. Half the partnership is missing. Leadership is Half the Story introduces the first model to seamlessly integrate leadership, followership, and partnerships. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leadership-is-half-the-story-a-fresh-look-at-followership-leadership-and-collaboration-marc-hurwitz-samantha-hurwitz-abridged/">Leadership is Half the Story : A Fresh Look at Followership, Leadership, and Collaboration &#8211; Marc Hurwitz, Samantha Hurwitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Can you imagine a choreographer only training one dancer to lead while his or her partner sits in the lobby staring at the wall? Yet we do this all the time in organizations. Half the partnership is missing.  Leadership is Half the Story introduces the first model to seamlessly integrate leadership, followership, and partnerships. This research-backed, field-tested book contributes many new ideas and practical advice for everyone in an organization &#8211; from CEO to HR director to front-line manager to consultant.  All of us lead, not just those with the formal title. All of us follow, not just front-line staff. In great collaborations, one moment we are leading and then we flip to following; in other words, the relationship between leadership and followership is dynamic, context-specific, and ever-evolving. This empowering perspective opens up leadership to everyone, normalizes followership, and enables more productive and innovative collaborations. Candid discussions about both roles allow for better coaching, mentoring, skill development, and interpersonal agility, and result in stronger teams.<br />
                    Marc and Samantha Hurwitz give us a category-busting book that &#8220;practically glows with energy and vision,&#8221; according to Marshall Goldsmith, executive coach and best-selling author of What Got You Here Won&#8217;t Get You There.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leadership-is-half-the-story-a-fresh-look-at-followership-leadership-and-collaboration-marc-hurwitz-samantha-hurwitz-abridged/">Leadership is Half the Story : A Fresh Look at Followership, Leadership, and Collaboration &#8211; Marc Hurwitz, Samantha Hurwitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good Economics for Hard Times : Better Answers to Our Biggest Problems &#8211; Abhijit V. Banerjee, Esther Duflo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FROM THE WINNERS OF THE 2019 NOBEL PRIZE IN ECONOMICS &#8216;Wonderfully refreshing . . . A must read&#8217; Thomas Piketty In this revolutionary book, prize-winning economists Abhijit V. Banerjee and Esther Duflo show how economics, when done right, can help us solve the thorniest social and political problems of our day. From immigration to inequality, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/">Good Economics for Hard Times : Better Answers to Our Biggest Problems &#8211; Abhijit V. Banerjee, Esther Duflo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FROM THE WINNERS OF THE 2019 NOBEL PRIZE IN ECONOMICS    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderfully refreshing . . . A must read&#8217; Thomas Piketty     </p>
<p>                    In this revolutionary book, prize-winning economists Abhijit V. Banerjee and Esther Duflo show how economics, when done right, can help us solve the thorniest social and political problems of our day. From immigration to inequality, slowing growth to accelerating climate change, we have the resources to address the challenges we face but we are so often blinded by ideology.    </p>
<p>                    Original, provocative and urgent, Good Economics for Hard Times offers the new thinking that we need. It builds on cutting-edge research in economics &#8211; and years of exploring the most effective solutions to alleviate extreme poverty &#8211; to make a persuasive case for an intelligent interventionism and a society built on compassion and respect. A much-needed antidote to polarized discourse, this book shines a light to help us appreciate and understand our precariously balanced world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/">Good Economics for Hard Times : Better Answers to Our Biggest Problems &#8211; Abhijit V. Banerjee, Esther Duflo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD. This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career. An MBA at a top business school is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold     </p>
<p>                    ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD.    </p>
<p>                    This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career.    </p>
<p>                    An MBA at a top business school is an enormous investment in time and cash. And if you don&#8217;t want to work for a consulting firm or an investment bank, the chances are it simply isn&#8217;t worth it.    </p>
<p>                    The Personal MBA gives you simple mental models for every subject that&#8217;s key to commercial success. From the basics of products and marketing to the nuances of teamwork and systems, this book distils everything you need to know to take on the MBA graduates and win.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;File this book under: NO EXCUSES&#8217; Seth Godin    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;No matter what they tell you, an MBA is not essential. If you combine reading this book with actually trying stuff, you&#8217;ll be far ahead in the business game&#8217; Kevin Kelly, founder of Wired</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Work Rules! : Insights from Inside Google That Will Transform How You Live and Lead &#8211; Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/work-rules-insights-from-inside-google-that-will-transform-how-you-live-and-lead-laszlo-bock-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/work-rules-insights-from-inside-google-that-will-transform-how-you-live-and-lead-laszlo-bock-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times and Wall Street Journal Bestseller Daily Telegraph, Huffington Post &#038; Business Insider Top Business Book to Read &#8216;Every year, 2 million people apply for a job at Google &#8211; so what&#8217;s the secret?&#8217; Guardian A compelling manifesto with the potential to change how we work and live, Work Rules! offers both [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/work-rules-insights-from-inside-google-that-will-transform-how-you-live-and-lead-laszlo-bock-abridged/">Work Rules! : Insights from Inside Google That Will Transform How You Live and Lead &#8211; Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times and Wall Street Journal Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    Daily Telegraph, Huffington Post &#038; Business Insider Top Business Book to Read     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Every year, 2 million people apply for a job at Google &#8211; so what&#8217;s the secret?&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    A compelling manifesto with the potential to change how we work and live, Work Rules! offers both a philosophy of the new world of work and a blueprint for attracting the most spectacular talent and ensuring the brightest and best prosper. The way we work is changing &#8211; are you?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/work-rules-insights-from-inside-google-that-will-transform-how-you-live-and-lead-laszlo-bock-abridged/">Work Rules! : Insights from Inside Google That Will Transform How You Live and Lead &#8211; Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Asia Works : Success and Failure in the World&#8217;s Most Dynamic Region &#8211; Joe Studwell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-asia-works-success-and-failure-in-the-worlds-most-dynamic-region-joe-studwell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-asia-works-success-and-failure-in-the-worlds-most-dynamic-region-joe-studwell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Until the catastrophic economic crisis of the late 1990s, East Asia was perceived as a monolithic success story. But heady economic growth rates masked the most divided continent in the world &#8211; one half the most extraordinary developmental success story ever seen, the other half a paper tiger. Joe Studwell explores how policies ridiculed by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-asia-works-success-and-failure-in-the-worlds-most-dynamic-region-joe-studwell-abridged/">How Asia Works : Success and Failure in the World&#8217;s Most Dynamic Region &#8211; Joe Studwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Until the catastrophic economic crisis of the late 1990s, East Asia was perceived as a monolithic success story. But heady economic growth rates masked the most divided continent in the world &#8211; one half the most extraordinary developmental success story ever seen, the other half a paper tiger.     </p>
<p>                    Joe Studwell explores how policies ridiculed by economists created titans in Japan, Korea and Taiwan, and are now behind the rise of China, while the best advice the West could offer sold its allies in South-East Asia down the economic river. The first book to offer an Asia-wide deconstruction of success and failure in economic development, Studwell&#8217;s latest work is provocative and iconoclastic &#8211; and sobering reading for most of the world&#8217;s developing countries. How Asia Works is a must-read book that packs powerful insights about the world&#8217;s most misunderstood continent.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-asia-works-success-and-failure-in-the-worlds-most-dynamic-region-joe-studwell-abridged/">How Asia Works : Success and Failure in the World&#8217;s Most Dynamic Region &#8211; Joe Studwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba&#8217;s World : How One Remarkable Chinese Company Is Changing the Face of Global Business &#8211; Porter Erisman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In September 2014, a Chinese company that most Westerners had never heard of held the largest IPO in history &#8211; bigger than Google, Facebook and Twitter combined. Alibaba, now the world&#8217;s largest e-commerce company, mostly escaped Western notice for over ten years, while building a customer base larger than Amazon&#8217;s, and handling the bulk of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/">Alibaba&#8217;s World : How One Remarkable Chinese Company Is Changing the Face of Global Business &#8211; Porter Erisman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In September 2014, a Chinese company that most Westerners had never heard of held the largest IPO in history &#8211; bigger than Google, Facebook and Twitter combined. Alibaba, now the world&#8217;s largest e-commerce company, mostly escaped Western notice for over ten years, while building a customer base larger than Amazon&#8217;s, and handling the bulk of e-commerce transactions in China. How did it happen? And what was it like to be along for such a revolutionary ride?    </p>
<p>                    In Alibaba&#8217;s World, author Porter Erisman, one of Alibaba&#8217;s first Western employees, who helped spearhead its international expansion, shows how Jack Ma, a Chinese schoolteacher who twice failed his college entrance exams, rose from obscurity to found Alibaba and lead it from struggling startup to the world&#8217;s most dominant e-commerce player.     </p>
<p>                    Now, in the first English language account of Alibaba&#8217;s extraordinary success, Erisman shares stories of weathering the dotcom crash, facing down eBay and Google, negotiating with the unpredictable Chinese government, and enduring the misguided advice of foreign experts, all to build the behemoth that&#8217;s poised to sweep the ecommerce world today. And he analyzes Alibaba&#8217;s role as a harbinger of the new global business landscape &#8211; with its focus on the East rather than the West, emerging markets over developed ones, and the nimble entrepreneur over the industry titan. As we face this near future, the story of Alibaba &#8211; and its inevitable descendants &#8211; is both essential and instructive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/">Alibaba&#8217;s World : How One Remarkable Chinese Company Is Changing the Face of Global Business &#8211; Porter Erisman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Industries of the Future &#8211; Alec Ross (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-industries-of-the-future-alec-ross-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-industries-of-the-future-alec-ross-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book answers the question: &#8216;What&#8217;s next?&#8217; The Internet had a world-changing impact on businesses and the global community over the twenty years from 1994 to 2014. In the next ten years, change will happen even faster. As Hillary Clinton&#8217;s Senior Advisor for Innovation, Alec Ross travelled nearly a million miles to forty-one countries, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-industries-of-the-future-alec-ross-abridged/">The Industries of the Future &#8211; Alec Ross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book answers the question: &#8216;What&#8217;s next?&#8217; The Internet had a world-changing impact on businesses and the global community over the twenty years from 1994 to 2014. In the next ten years, change will happen even faster.     </p>
<p>                    As Hillary Clinton&#8217;s Senior Advisor for Innovation, Alec Ross travelled nearly a million miles to forty-one countries, the equivalent of two round-trips to the moon. From refugee camps in the Congo and Syrian war zones, to visiting the world&#8217;s most powerful people in business and government, Ross&#8217;s travels amounted to a four-year masterclass in the changing nature of innovation.     </p>
<p>                    In The Industries of the Future, Ross distils his observations on the forces that are changing the world. He highlights the best opportunities for progress and explains how countries thrive or sputter. Ross examines the specific fields that will most shape our economic future over the next ten years, including robotics, artificial intelligence, the commercialization of genomics, cybercrime and the impact of digital technology.     </p>
<p>                    Blending storytelling and economic analysis, he answers questions on how we will need to adapt. Ross gives readers a vivid and informed perspective on how sweeping global trends are affecting the ways we live, now and tomorrow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-industries-of-the-future-alec-ross-abridged/">The Industries of the Future &#8211; Alec Ross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Treasure Islands : Tax Havens and the Men who Stole the World &#8211; Nicholas Shaxson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/treasure-islands-tax-havens-and-the-men-who-stole-the-world-nicholas-shaxson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Tax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/treasure-islands-tax-havens-and-the-men-who-stole-the-world-nicholas-shaxson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WITH NEW AND UPDATED MATERIAL Billionaire Warren Buffet, currently the third wealthiest man in the world, paid the lowest rate of tax among his office staff, including his receptionist. In 2006 the world&#8217;s three biggest banana companies did nearly GBP400 million worth of business in Britain but paid just GBP128,000 in tax between them. In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/treasure-islands-tax-havens-and-the-men-who-stole-the-world-nicholas-shaxson-abridged/">Treasure Islands : Tax Havens and the Men who Stole the World &#8211; Nicholas Shaxson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WITH NEW AND UPDATED MATERIAL    </p>
<p>                    Billionaire Warren Buffet, currently the third wealthiest man in the world, paid the lowest rate of tax among his office staff, including his receptionist.    </p>
<p>                    In 2006 the world&#8217;s three biggest banana companies did nearly GBP400 million worth of business in Britain but paid just GBP128,000 in tax between them.    </p>
<p>                    In January 2009, US law enforcement fined Lloyds TSB $350 million after it admitted secretly channelling Iranian and Sudanese money into the US banking system.    </p>
<p>                    Tax havens are the most important single reason why poor people and poor countries stay poor. They lie at the very heart of the global economy, with over half the world trade processed through them. They have been instrumental in nearly every major economic event, in every big financial scandal, and in every financial crisis since the 1970s, including the latest global economic downturn.     </p>
<p>                    In Treasure Islands, Nicholas Shaxson shows how this happened, and what this means for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/treasure-islands-tax-havens-and-the-men-who-stole-the-world-nicholas-shaxson-abridged/">Treasure Islands : Tax Havens and the Men who Stole the World &#8211; Nicholas Shaxson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film The Wolf of Wall Street is about the finance industry&#8217;s greediest adults, Kevin Roose&#8217;s Young Money is a look at those wolves as cubs&#8217; Amazon.com &#8216;Best Book of the Month&#8217; Every year, thousands of eager graduates are hired by the world&#8217;s financial giants, where they&#8217;re taught the secrets of making obscene [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/">Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film The Wolf of Wall Street is about the finance industry&#8217;s greediest adults, Kevin Roose&#8217;s Young Money is a look at those wolves as cubs&#8217; Amazon.com &#8216;Best Book of the Month&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Every year, thousands of eager graduates are hired by the world&#8217;s financial giants, where they&#8217;re taught the secrets of making obscene amounts of money &#8212; as well as how to dress, talk, date, drink, and schmooze like real financiers. Young Money is the exclusive, inside story of this well-guarded world.<br />
                    Investigative reporter Kevin Roose shadows eight rookies as they are exposed to the exhausting workloads, huge bonuses, and recreational drugs that have always characterized Wall Street life. But they experience something new, too: an industry forever changed by the massive financial collapse of 2008. And as they get their Wall Street educations, they face hard questions about morality, prestige, and the value of their work.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A great new read that doubles as a post-crash update to Michael Lewis&#8217; Liar&#8217;s Poker &#8211; Mother Jones    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fun fast read that will make you laugh out loud&#8217; Fortune Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/">Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China&#8217;s Second Continent : How a Million Migrants Are Building a New Empire in Africa &#8211; Howard W. French (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chinas-second-continent-how-a-million-migrants-are-building-a-new-empire-in-africa-howard-w-french-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Migration, Immigration & Emigration]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chinas-second-continent-how-a-million-migrants-are-building-a-new-empire-in-africa-howard-w-french-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book Chinese immigrants of the recent past and unfolding twenty-first century are in search of the African dream. So explains indefatigable traveler Howard W. French, prize-winning investigative journalist and former New York Times bureau chief in Africa and China, in the definitive account of this seismic geopolitical development. China&#8217;s burgeoning [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chinas-second-continent-how-a-million-migrants-are-building-a-new-empire-in-africa-howard-w-french-abridged/">China&#8217;s Second Continent : How a Million Migrants Are Building a New Empire in Africa &#8211; Howard W. French (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book     </p>
<p>                    Chinese immigrants of the recent past and unfolding twenty-first century are in search of the African dream. So explains indefatigable traveler Howard W. French, prize-winning investigative journalist and former New York Times bureau chief in Africa and China, in the definitive account of this seismic geopolitical development. China&#8217;s burgeoning presence in Africa is already shaping, and reshaping, the future of millions of people. From Liberia to Senegal to Mozambique, in creaky trucks and by back roads, French introduces us to the characters who make up China&#8217;s dogged emigrant population: entrepreneurs singlehandedly reshaping African infrastructure, and less-lucky migrants barely scraping by but still convinced of Africa&#8217;s opportunities. French&#8217;s acute observations offer illuminating insight into the most pressing unknowns of modern Sino-African relations: Why China is making these cultural and economic incursions into the continent; what Africa&#8217;s role is in this equation; and what the ramifications for both parties and their people&#8211;and the watching world&#8211;will be in the foreseeable future.     </p>
<p>                    One of the Best Books of the Year at &#8211; The Economist &#8211; The Guardian &#8211; Foreign Affairs</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chinas-second-continent-how-a-million-migrants-are-building-a-new-empire-in-africa-howard-w-french-abridged/">China&#8217;s Second Continent : How a Million Migrants Are Building a New Empire in Africa &#8211; Howard W. French (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutionary Groups & Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. To manage the risks and spread the benefits, we have to act now, and in the interest of stakeholders everywhere&#8217; Andrew McAfee, Co-Founder, MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy, MIT, USA    </p>
<p>                    We are on the brink of the Fourth Industrial Revolution. And this one will be unlike any other in human history.    </p>
<p>                    Characterized by new technologies fusing the physical, digital and biological worlds, the Fourth Industrial Revolution will impact all disciplines, economies and industries &#8211; and it will do so at an unprecedented rate. World Economic Forum data predicts that by 2025 we will see: commercial use of nanomaterials 200 times stronger than steel and a million times thinner than human hair; the first transplant of a 3D-printed liver; 10% of all cars on US roads being driverless; and much more besides.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Industrial Revolution, Schwab outlines the key technologies driving this revolution, discusses the major impacts on governments, businesses, civil society and individuals, and offers bold ideas for what can be done to shape a better future for all.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The technologies of the Fourth Industrial Revolution are extraordinary. Leadership has to be equally extraordinary to manage the complexities of systemic change&#8217; Eric Schmidt, Technical Advisor, Alphabet, USA</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Business Adventures : Twelve Classic Tales from the World of Wall Street: The New York Times bestseller Bill Gates calls &#8216;the best business book I&#8217;ve ever read&#8217; &#8211; John Brooks (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/business-adventures-twelve-classic-tales-from-the-world-of-wall-street-the-new-york-times-bestseller-bill-gates-calls-the-best-business-book-ive-ever-read-john-brooks-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/business-adventures-twelve-classic-tales-from-the-world-of-wall-street-the-new-york-times-bestseller-bill-gates-calls-the-best-business-book-ive-ever-read-john-brooks-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The best business book I&#8217;ve ever read.&#8217; Bill Gates, Wall Street Journal&#8217;The Michael Lewis of his day.&#8217; New York TimesWhat do the $350 million Ford Motor Company disaster known as the Edsel, the fast and incredible rise of Xerox, and the unbelievable scandals at General Electric and Texas Gulf Sulphur have in common? Each is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/business-adventures-twelve-classic-tales-from-the-world-of-wall-street-the-new-york-times-bestseller-bill-gates-calls-the-best-business-book-ive-ever-read-john-brooks-abridged/">Business Adventures : Twelve Classic Tales from the World of Wall Street: The New York Times bestseller Bill Gates calls &#8216;the best business book I&#8217;ve ever read&#8217; &#8211; John Brooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The best business book I&#8217;ve ever read.&#8217; Bill Gates, Wall Street Journal&#8217;The Michael Lewis of his day.&#8217; New York TimesWhat do the $350 million Ford Motor Company disaster known as the Edsel, the fast and incredible rise of Xerox, and the unbelievable scandals at General Electric and Texas Gulf Sulphur have in common? Each is an example of how an iconic company was defined by a particular moment of fame or notoriety. These notable and fascinating accounts are as relevant today to understanding the intricacies of corporate life as they were when the events happened.Stories about Wall Street are infused with drama and adventure and reveal the machinations and volatile nature of the world of finance. John Brooks&#8217;s insightful reportage is so full of personality and critical detail that whether he is looking at the astounding market crash of 1962, the collapse of a well-known brokerage firm, or the bold attempt by American bankers to save the British pound, one gets the sense that history really does repeat itself.This business classic written by longtime New Yorker contributor John Brooks is an insightful and engaging look into corporate and financial life in America.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/business-adventures-twelve-classic-tales-from-the-world-of-wall-street-the-new-york-times-bestseller-bill-gates-calls-the-best-business-book-ive-ever-read-john-brooks-abridged/">Business Adventures : Twelve Classic Tales from the World of Wall Street: The New York Times bestseller Bill Gates calls &#8216;the best business book I&#8217;ve ever read&#8217; &#8211; John Brooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crashed : How a Decade of Financial Crises Changed the World &#8211; Adam Tooze (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the 2019 Lionel Gelber Prize &#8216;Majestic, informative and often delightful &#8230; insights on every page&#8217; Yanis Varoufakis, Observer The definitive history of the Great Financial Crisis, from the acclaimed author of The Deluge and The Wages of Destruction. In September 2008 the Great Financial Crisis, triggered by the collapse of Lehman brothers, shook [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/">Crashed : How a Decade of Financial Crises Changed the World &#8211; Adam Tooze (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the 2019 Lionel Gelber Prize    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Majestic, informative and often delightful &#8230; insights on every page&#8217; Yanis Varoufakis, Observer    </p>
<p>                    The definitive history of the Great Financial Crisis, from the acclaimed author of The Deluge and The Wages of Destruction.     </p>
<p>                    In September 2008 the Great Financial Crisis, triggered by the collapse of Lehman brothers, shook the world. A decade later its spectre still haunts us. As the appalling scope and scale of the crash was revealed, the financial institutions that had symbolised the West&#8217;s triumph since the end of the Cold War, seemed &#8211; through greed, malice and incompetence &#8211; to be about to bring the entire system to its knees.    </p>
<p>                    Crashed is a brilliantly original and assured analysis of what happened and how we were rescued from something even worse &#8211; but at a price which continues to undermine democracy across Europe and the United States. Gnawing away at our institutions are the many billions of dollars which were conjured up to prevent complete collapse. Over and over again, the end of the crisis has been announced, but it continues to hound us &#8211; whether in Greece or Ukraine, whether through Brexit or Trump. Adam Tooze follows the trail like no previous writer and has written a book compelling as history, as economic analysis and as political horror story.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/">Crashed : How a Decade of Financial Crises Changed the World &#8211; Adam Tooze (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
