<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>General Cookery Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/general-cookery/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/general-cookery/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>General Cookery Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/general-cookery/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A must-read for anyone interested in food and the future&#8217; Yotam Ottolenghi Based on ten years of surveying farming communities around the world, top New York chef Dan Barber&#8217;s The Third Plate offers a radical new way of thinking about food that will heal the land and taste incredible. The &#8216;first plate&#8217; was a classic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/">The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A must-read for anyone interested in food and the future&#8217; Yotam Ottolenghi    </p>
<p>                    Based on ten years of surveying farming communities around the world, top New York chef Dan Barber&#8217;s The Third Plate offers a radical new way of thinking about food that will heal the land and taste incredible.    </p>
<p>                     The &#8216;first plate&#8217; was a classic meal centred on a large cut of meat with few vegetables. On the &#8216;second plate&#8217;, championed by the farm-to-table movement, meat is free-range and vegetables are locally sourced. It&#8217;s better-tasting, and better for the planet, but the second plate&#8217;s architecture is identical to that of the first. It, too, disrupts ecological balances, causing soil depletion and nutrient loss &#8211; it just isn&#8217;t a sustainable way to farm or eat.    </p>
<p>                     The &#8216;third plate&#8217; offers a solution: an integrated system of vegetable, cereal and livestock production that is fully supported &#8211; in fact, dictated &#8211; by what we choose to cook for dinner. The Third Plate is where good farming and good food intersect.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/">The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat Salt, Fat, Acid &#8211; Samin Nosrat (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery By Ingredient]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now a Netflix series! New York Times Bestseller and Winner of the 2018 James Beard Award for Best General Cookbook and multiple IACP Cookbook Awards Named one of the Best Books of 2017 by: NPR, BuzzFeed, The Atlantic, The Washington Post, Chicago Tribune, Rachel Ray Every Day, San Francisco Chronicle, Vice Munchies, Elle.com, Glamour, Eater, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/">Heat Salt, Fat, Acid &#8211; Samin Nosrat (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now a Netflix series!     </p>
<p>                     New York Times Bestseller and Winner of the 2018 James Beard Award for Best General Cookbook and multiple IACP Cookbook Awards      </p>
<p>                     Named one of the Best Books of 2017 by: NPR, BuzzFeed, The Atlantic, The Washington Post, Chicago Tribune, Rachel Ray Every Day, San Francisco Chronicle, Vice Munchies, Elle.com, Glamour, Eater, Newsday, Minneapolis Star Tribune,  The Seattle Times, Tampa Bay Times, Tasting Table, Modern Farmer, Publishers Weekly,  and more.     </p>
<p>                     A visionary new master class in cooking that distills decades of professional experience into just four simple elements, from the woman declared &#8220;America&#8217;s next great cooking teacher&#8221; by Alice Waters.     </p>
<p>                    In the tradition of The Joy of Cooking and How to Cook Everything comes Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat, an ambitious new approach to cooking by a major new culinary voice. Chef and writer Samin Nosrat has taught everyone from professional chefs to middle school kids to author Michael Pollan to cook using her revolutionary, yet simple, philosophy. Master the use of just four elements&#8211;Salt, which enhances flavor; Fat, which delivers flavor and generates texture; Acid, which balances flavor; and Heat, which ultimately determines the texture of food&#8211;and anything you cook will be delicious. By explaining the hows and whys of good cooking, Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat will teach and inspire a new generation of cooks how to confidently make better decisions in the kitchen and cook delicious meals with any ingredients, anywhere, at any time.     </p>
<p>                    Echoing Samin&#8217;s own journey from culinary novice to award-winning chef, Salt, Fat Acid, Heat immediately bridges the gap between home and professional kitchens. With charming narrative, illustrated walkthroughs, and a lighthearted approach to kitchen science, Samin demystifies the four elements of good cooking for everyone. Refer to the canon of 100 essential recipes&#8211;and dozens of variations&#8211;to put the lessons into practice and make bright, balanced vinaigrettes, perfectly caramelized roast vegetables, tender braised meats, and light, flaky pastry doughs.     </p>
<p>                    Featuring 150 illustrations and infographics that reveal an atlas to the world of flavor by renowned illustrator Wendy MacNaughton, Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat will be your compass in the kitchen. Destined to be a classic, it just might be the last cookbook you&#8217;ll ever need.     </p>
<p>                    With a foreword by Michael Pollan.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/">Heat Salt, Fat, Acid &#8211; Samin Nosrat (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Way We Eat Now : Strategies for Eating in a World of Change &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-way-we-eat-now-strategies-for-eating-in-a-world-of-change-bee-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-way-we-eat-now-strategies-for-eating-in-a-world-of-change-bee-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We never snacked like this and we never binged like this. We never had so many superfoods, or so many chips. We were never quite so confused about food, and what it actually is. This is a book about the good, the terrible and the avocado toast. A riveting exploration of the hidden forces behind [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-way-we-eat-now-strategies-for-eating-in-a-world-of-change-bee-wilson-abridged/">The Way We Eat Now : Strategies for Eating in a World of Change &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We never snacked like this and we never binged like this. We never had so many superfoods, or so many chips. We were never quite so confused about food, and what it actually is.    </p>
<p>                              This is a book about the good, the terrible and the avocado toast. A riveting exploration of the hidden forces behind what we eat, The Way We Eat Now explains how modern food, in all its complexity, has transformed our lives and our world. To re-establish eating as something that gives us both joy and health, we need to find out where we are right now, how we got here and what it is that we share.    </p>
<p>                              Award-winning food writer Bee Wilson explores everything from meal replacements such as Huel, the disappearing lunch hour, the rise of veganism, the lack of time to cook and prepare food and the rapid increase in food delivery services. And Bee provides her own doable strategies for how we might navigate the many options available to us to have a balanced, happier relationship with the food we eat.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-way-we-eat-now-strategies-for-eating-in-a-world-of-change-bee-wilson-abridged/">The Way We Eat Now : Strategies for Eating in a World of Change &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Bite : How We Learn to Eat &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cooking For/with Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cooking With Meat & Game]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fortnum &#038; Mason Food Book of the Year 2016 We are not born knowing what to eat; we each have to figure it out for ourselves. From childhood onwards, we learn how big a portion is and how sweet is too sweet. The way we learn to eat holds the key to why food has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/">First Bite : How We Learn to Eat &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fortnum &#038; Mason Food Book of the Year 2016    </p>
<p>                              We are not born knowing what to eat; we each have to figure it out for ourselves. From childhood onwards, we learn how big a portion is and how sweet is too sweet. The way we learn to eat holds the key to why food has gone so disastrously wrong for so many people. But how does this happen? And can we ever change our food habits for the better?    </p>
<p>                              An exploration of the extraordinary and surprising origins of our taste and eating habits, in First Bite award-winning food writer Bee Wilson explains how we can change our palates to lead healthier, happier lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/">First Bite : How We Learn to Eat &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Story Of Sushi : An Unlikely Story of Raw Fish and Rice &#8211; Trevor Corson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-story-of-sushi-an-unlikely-story-of-raw-fish-and-rice-trevor-corson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cooking With Fish & Seafood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Aquatic Creatures]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-story-of-sushi-an-unlikely-story-of-raw-fish-and-rice-trevor-corson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Editor&#8217;s Choice Everything you never knew about sushi&#8211; its surprising origins, the colorful lives of its chefs, and the bizarre behavior of the creatures that compose it Trevor Corson takes us behind the scenes at America&#8217;s first sushi-chef training academy, as eager novices strive to master the elusive art of cooking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-sushi-an-unlikely-story-of-raw-fish-and-rice-trevor-corson-abridged/">The Story Of Sushi : An Unlikely Story of Raw Fish and Rice &#8211; Trevor Corson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Editor&#8217;s Choice    </p>
<p>                    Everything you never knew about sushi&#8211; its surprising origins, the colorful lives of its chefs, and the bizarre behavior of the creatures that compose it    </p>
<p>                    Trevor Corson takes us behind the scenes at America&#8217;s first sushi-chef training academy, as eager novices strive to master the elusive art of cooking without cooking. He delves into the biology and natural history of the edible creatures of the sea, and tells the fascinating story of an Indo-Chinese meal reinvented in nineteenth-century Tokyo as a cheap fast food. He reveals the pioneers who brought sushi to the United States and explores how this unlikely meal is exploding into the American heartland just as the long-term future of sushi may be unraveling.    </p>
<p>                    The Story of Sushi is at once a compelling tale of human determination and a delectable smorgasbord of surprising food science, intrepid reporting, and provocative cultural history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-sushi-an-unlikely-story-of-raw-fish-and-rice-trevor-corson-abridged/">The Story Of Sushi : An Unlikely Story of Raw Fish and Rice &#8211; Trevor Corson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since his New York Times op-ed column debuted in 2011, Mark Bittman has emerged as one of our most impassioned and opinionated observers of the food landscape. The Times&#8217; only dedicated opinion columnist covering the food beat, Bittman routinely makes readers think twice about how the food we eat is produced, distributed, and cooked, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/">A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since his New York Times op-ed column debuted in 2011, Mark Bittman has emerged as one of our most impassioned and opinionated observers of the food landscape. The Times&#8217; only dedicated opinion columnist covering the food beat, Bittman routinely makes readers think twice about how the food we eat is produced, distributed, and cooked, and shines a bright light on the profound impact that diet&#8211;both good and bad&#8211;can have on our health and that of the planet.     </p>
<p>                     In A Bone to Pick, Mark&#8217;s most memorable and thought-provoking columns are compiled into a single volume for the first time. As abundant and safe as the American food supply appears to be, the state of our health reveals the presence of staggering deficiencies in both the system that produces food and the forces that regulate it. Bittman leaves no issue unexamined; agricultural practices, government legislation, fad diets, and corporate greed all come under scrutiny and show that the issues governing what ends up in our market basket and on our tables are both complex and often deliberately confusing. Unabashedly opinionated and invariably thought provoking, Bittman&#8217;s columns have helped readers decipher arcane policy, unpack scientific studies, and deflate affronts to common sense when it comes to determining what &#8220;eating well&#8221; truly means. As urgent as the situation is, Mark contends that we can be optimistic about the future of our food and its impact on our health, as slow-food movements, better school-lunch programs, and even &#8220;healthy fast food&#8221; become part of the norm.     </p>
<p>                     At once inspiring, enraging, and enlightening, A Bone to Pick is an essential resource for every reader eager to understand not only the complexities inherent in the American food system, but also the many opportunities that exist to improve it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/">A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cooking Up a Business : Lessons from Food Lovers Who Turned Their Passion into a Career &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Rachel Hofstetter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stories and advice for creating a business out of the food you love. Do you have a passion for delicious food and want to create your own business out of it, but have no idea where to start? Cooking Up a Business is essential reading for aspiring entrepreneurs and gives you a real-world, up-close-and-personal preview [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/">Cooking Up a Business : Lessons from Food Lovers Who Turned Their Passion into a Career &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Rachel Hofstetter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stories and advice for creating a business out of the food you love.      </p>
<p>                    Do you have a passion for delicious food and want to create your own business out of it, but have no idea where to start? Cooking Up a Business is essential reading for aspiring entrepreneurs and gives you a real-world, up-close-and-personal preview of the exciting journey. Through profiles and interviews with nationally known food entrepreneurs from Popchips, Vosges Haut-Chocolat, Hint Water, Mary&#8217;s Gone Crackers, Love Grown Foods, Kopali Organics, Tasty, Evol, Justin&#8217;s Nut Butters, Cameron Hughes Wine, and more, you will gain applicable, practical guidance that teaches you how to succeed today:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; How to create a national brand&#8211;with no connections or experience<br />
                    &#8211; The secret to getting meetings with grocery store buyers<br />
                    &#8211; The number one thing you need to know about food safety regulations<br />
                    &#8211; Why a grassroots budget might actually help you succeed<br />
                    &#8211; Specific advice for gluten-free, organic, wine, and beverage companies<br />
                    &#8211; What every entrepreneur wishes someone had told them at the beginning &#8211; Why doing what you love is always a good idea</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/">Cooking Up a Business : Lessons from Food Lovers Who Turned Their Passion into a Career &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Rachel Hofstetter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agricultural Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Beverage Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainable Agriculture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is the future of food looking bleak &#8211; or better than ever? At a time when every day brings news of drought and famine, Amanda Little investigates what it will take to feed a hotter, hungrier, more crowded world. She explores the past along with the present and discovers startling innovations: remote-control crops, vertical farms, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/">The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is the future of food looking bleak &#8211; or better than ever?    </p>
<p>                    At a time when every day brings news of drought and famine, Amanda Little investigates what it will take to feed a hotter, hungrier, more crowded world.    </p>
<p>                    She explores the past along with the present and discovers startling innovations: remote-control crops, vertical farms, robot weedkillers, lab-grown meat, 3D-printed meals, water networks run by supercomputers, cloud seeding and sensors that monitor the microclimate of individual plants. She meets the creative and controversial minds changing the face of modern food production, and tackles fears over genetic modification with hard facts.    </p>
<p>                    The Fate of Food is a fascinating look at the threats and opportunities that lie ahead as we struggle for food security.    </p>
<p>                    Faced with a perilous future, it gives us reason to hope.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/">The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author). We are in the grip of a food [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author).<br />
                       We are in the grip of a food crisis. Obesity has become a leading cause of preventable death, after only smoking. For nearly half a century we&#8217;ve been trying to pin the blame somewhere, fat, carbs, sugar, wheat, high-fructose corn syrup. But that search has been in vain, because the food problem that&#8217;s killing us is not a nutrient problem. It&#8217;s a behavioural problem, and it&#8217;s caused by the changing flavour of the food we eat.<br />
                       Ever since the 1940s, with the rise of industrialized food production, we have been gradually leeching the taste out of what we grow. Simultaneously, we have taken great leaps forward in technology, creating a flavour industry, worth billions annually; in an attempt to put back the tastes we&#8217;ve engineered out of our food. The result is a cuisine that increasingly resembles the paragon of flavour manipulation: Doritos. As food becomes increasingly bland, we dress it up with calories and flavour chemicals to make it delicious again. We have rewired our palates and our brains, and the results are making us sick and killing us.<br />
                       With in-depth historical and scientific research, The Dorito Effect casts the food crisis in a fascinating new light, weaving an enthralling tale of how we got to this point and where we are headed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should We Eat Meat? : Evolution and Consequences of Modern Carnivory &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/should-we-eat-meat-evolution-and-consequences-of-modern-carnivory-vaclav-smil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Beverage Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/should-we-eat-meat-evolution-and-consequences-of-modern-carnivory-vaclav-smil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Meat eating is often a contentious subject, whether considering the technical, ethical, environmental, political, or health-related aspects of production and consumption. This book is a wide-ranging and interdisciplinary examination and critique of meat consumption by humans, throughout their evolution and around the world. Setting the scene with a chapter on meat s role in human [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/should-we-eat-meat-evolution-and-consequences-of-modern-carnivory-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Should We Eat Meat? : Evolution and Consequences of Modern Carnivory &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meat eating is often a contentious subject, whether considering the technical, ethical, environmental, political, or health-related aspects of production and consumption. This book is a wide-ranging and interdisciplinary examination and critique of meat consumption by humans, throughout their evolution and around the world. Setting the scene with a chapter on meat s role in human evolution and its growing influence during the development of agricultural practices, the book goes on to examine modern production systems, their efficiencies, outputs, and impacts. The major global trends of meat consumption are described in order to find out what part its consumption plays in changing modern diets in countries around the world. The heart of the book addresses the consequences of the &#8220;massive carnivory&#8221; of western diets, looking at the inefficiencies of production and at the huge impacts on land, water, and the atmosphere. Health impacts are also covered, both positive and negative.<br />
                    In conclusion, the author looks forward at his vision of rational meat eating , where environmental and health impacts are reduced, animals are treated more humanely, and alternative sources of protein make a higher contribution. Should We Eat Meat? is not an ideological tract for or against carnivorousness but rather a careful evaluation of meat&#8217;s roles in human diets and the environmental and health consequences of its production and consumption. It will be of interest to a wide readership including professionals and academics in food and agricultural production, human health and nutrition, environmental science, and regulatory and policy making bodies around the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/should-we-eat-meat-evolution-and-consequences-of-modern-carnivory-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Should We Eat Meat? : Evolution and Consequences of Modern Carnivory &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Life, on the Line : A Chef&#8217;s Story of Chasing Greatness, Facing Death, and Redefining the Way We Eat &#8211; Grant Achatz, Nick Kokonas (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-on-the-line-a-chefs-story-of-chasing-greatness-facing-death-and-redefining-the-way-we-eat-grant-achatz-nick-kokonas-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hotel & Catering Trades]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-on-the-line-a-chefs-story-of-chasing-greatness-facing-death-and-redefining-the-way-we-eat-grant-achatz-nick-kokonas-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of America&#8217;s great chefs&#8221; (Vogue), Grant Achatz, shares how his drive to cook immaculate food fueled his miraculous triumph over tongue cancer. By 2007 chef Grant Achatz had been named one of the best new chefs in America by Food &#038; Wine, he had received the James Beard Foundation Rising Star Chef of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-on-the-line-a-chefs-story-of-chasing-greatness-facing-death-and-redefining-the-way-we-eat-grant-achatz-nick-kokonas-abridged/">Life, on the Line : A Chef&#8217;s Story of Chasing Greatness, Facing Death, and Redefining the Way We Eat &#8211; Grant Achatz, Nick Kokonas (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of America&#8217;s great chefs&#8221; (Vogue), Grant Achatz, shares how his drive to cook immaculate food fueled his miraculous triumph over tongue cancer.     </p>
<p>                    By 2007 chef Grant Achatz had been named one of the best new chefs in America by Food &#038; Wine, he had received the James Beard Foundation Rising Star Chef of the Year Award, and he and Nick Kokonas had opened the conceptually radical restaurant Alinea, which was named Best Restaurant in America by Gourmet magazine. Then, positioned firmly in the world&#8217;s culinary spotlight, Achatz was diagnosed with stage IV squamous cell carcinoma-tongue cancer.    </p>
<p>                    The prognosis grim, Grant undertook an alternative treatment of aggressive chemotherapy and radiation that ravaged his body and left him without a sense of taste. Tapping into his profound discipline and passion, he trained his chefs to mimic his palate and learned how to cook with his other senses. As Kokonas was able to attest, the food was never better. Five months later, Grant was declared cancer-free and went on to achieve some of the highest honors in the culinary world. Life, on the Line is not only a chef&#8217;s memoir, it is also a book about survival, about nurturing creativity, and about profound friendship.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-on-the-line-a-chefs-story-of-chasing-greatness-facing-death-and-redefining-the-way-we-eat-grant-achatz-nick-kokonas-abridged/">Life, on the Line : A Chef&#8217;s Story of Chasing Greatness, Facing Death, and Redefining the Way We Eat &#8211; Grant Achatz, Nick Kokonas (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
