<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Business Ethics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/business-ethics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/business-ethics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:08:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Business Ethics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/business-ethics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>How Successful People Think : Change Your Thinking, Change Your Life &#8211; John C. Maxwell</title>
		<link>/how-successful-people-think-change-your-thinking-change-your-life-john-c-maxwell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 01:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-successful-people-think-change-your-thinking-change-your-life-john-c-maxwell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The perfect, compact read for today&#8217;s fast-paced world, How Successful People Think (derived from Maxwell&#8217;s previous book, Thinking for a Change) guides readers through the 11 secrets successful people know. Arranged in an easy-to-follow format, America&#8217;s leadership expert John C. Maxwell will teach readers how to expand their thinking and achieve their dreams. The 11 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-successful-people-think-change-your-thinking-change-your-life-john-c-maxwell/">How Successful People Think : Change Your Thinking, Change Your Life &#8211; John C. Maxwell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The perfect, compact read for today&#8217;s fast-paced world, How Successful People Think (derived from Maxwell&#8217;s previous book, Thinking for a Change) guides readers through the 11 secrets successful people know. Arranged in an easy-to-follow format, America&#8217;s leadership expert John C. Maxwell will teach readers how to expand their thinking and achieve their dreams. The 11 keys to successful thinking include: Big-Picture Thinking &#8211; seeing the world beyond your own needs and how that leads to great ideas Focused Thinking &#8211; removing mental clutter and distractions to realize your full potential Creative Thinking &#8211; thinking in unique ways and making breakthroughs Shared Thinking &#8211; working with others to compound results Reflective Thinking &#8211; looking at the past to gain a better understanding of the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-successful-people-think-change-your-thinking-change-your-life-john-c-maxwell/">How Successful People Think : Change Your Thinking, Change Your Life &#8211; John C. Maxwell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Person You Mean to Be : How Good People Fight Bias &#8211; Dolly Chugh, Foreword by Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-person-you-mean-to-be-how-good-people-fight-bias-dolly-chugh-foreword-by-laszlo-bock-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-person-you-mean-to-be-how-good-people-fight-bias-dolly-chugh-foreword-by-laszlo-bock-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Finally: an engaging, evidence-based book about how to battle biases, champion diversity and inclusion, and advocate for those who lack power and privilege. Dolly Chugh makes a convincing case that being an ally isn&#8217;t about being a good person-it&#8217;s about constantly striving to be a better person.&#8221; -Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-person-you-mean-to-be-how-good-people-fight-bias-dolly-chugh-foreword-by-laszlo-bock-abridged/">The Person You Mean to Be : How Good People Fight Bias &#8211; Dolly Chugh, Foreword by Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Finally: an engaging, evidence-based book about how to battle biases, champion diversity and inclusion, and advocate for those who lack power and privilege. Dolly Chugh makes a convincing case that being an ally isn&#8217;t about being a good person-it&#8217;s about constantly striving to be a better person.&#8221;  -Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of Give and Take, Originals, and Option B with Sheryl Sandberg    </p>
<p>                    Foreword by Laszlo Bock, the bestselling author of Work Rules! and former Senior Vice President of People Operations at Google    </p>
<p>                    An inspiring guide from Dolly Chugh, an award-winning social psychologist at the New York University Stern School of Business, on how to confront difficult issues including sexism, racism, inequality, and injustice so that you can make the world (and yourself) better.    </p>
<p>                    Many of us believe in equality, diversity, and inclusion. But how do we stand up for those values in our turbulent world? The Person You Mean to Be is the smart, &#8220;semi-bold&#8221; person&#8217;s guide to fighting for what you believe in.    </p>
<p>                    Dolly reveals the surprising causes of inequality, grounded in the &#8220;psychology of good people&#8221;. Using her research findings in unconscious bias as well as work across psychology, sociology, economics, political science, and other disciplines, she offers practical tools to respectfully and effectively talk politics with family, to be a better colleague to people who don&#8217;t look like you, and to avoid being a well-intentioned barrier to equality. Being the person we mean to be starts with a look at ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    She argues that the only way to be on the right side of history is to be a good-ish- rather than good-person. Good-ish people are always growing. Second, she helps you find your &#8220;ordinary privilege&#8221;-the part of your everyday identity you take for granted, such as race for a white person, sexual orientation for a straight person, gender for a man, or education for a college graduate. This part of your identity may bring blind spots, but it is your best tool for influencing change. Third, Dolly introduces the psychological reasons that make it hard for us to see the bias in and around us. She leads you from willful ignorance to willful awareness. Finally, she guides you on how, when, and whom, to engage (and not engage) in your workplaces, homes, and communities. Her science-based approach is a method any of us can put to use in all parts of our life.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you are a long-time activist or new to the fight, you can start from where you are. Through the compelling stories Dolly shares and the surprising science she reports, Dolly guides each of us closer to being the person we mean to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-person-you-mean-to-be-how-good-people-fight-bias-dolly-chugh-foreword-by-laszlo-bock-abridged/">The Person You Mean to Be : How Good People Fight Bias &#8211; Dolly Chugh, Foreword by Laszlo Bock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What You Do Is Who You Are : How to Create Your Business Culture &#8211; Ben Horowitz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-you-do-is-who-you-are-how-to-create-your-business-culture-ben-horowitz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-you-do-is-who-you-are-how-to-create-your-business-culture-ben-horowitz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ben Horowitz, a leading venture capitalist, modern management expert, and New York Times bestselling author combines lessons both from history and modern organisational practice with practical and often surprising advice to help us build cultures that can weather both good and bad times. The times and circumstances in which people were raised often shape them [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-you-do-is-who-you-are-how-to-create-your-business-culture-ben-horowitz-abridged/">What You Do Is Who You Are : How to Create Your Business Culture &#8211; Ben Horowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ben Horowitz, a leading venture capitalist, modern management expert, and New York Times bestselling author combines lessons both from history and modern organisational practice with practical and often surprising advice to help us build cultures that can weather both good and bad times.    </p>
<p>                              The times and circumstances in which people were raised often shape them &#8211; yet a few leaders have managed to shape their times. In this follow-up to the bestselling business classic The Hard Thing About Hard Things, Ben Horowitz turns his attention to a question crucial to every organisation: How do you create and sustain the culture you want?     </p>
<p>                              This book is a journey through cultures ancient to modern, spotlighting models of leadership and culture-building from the samurai to prison gangs. Along the way, it answers fundamental questions: Who are we? How do people talk about us when we&#8217;re not around? How do we treat our customers? Can we be trusted?     </p>
<p>                              Because who you are is not the values you list on the wall. It&#8217;s not what you say in a company-wide meeting. It&#8217;s not your marketing campaign. It&#8217;s not even what you believe. Who you are is what you do. This book will help you do the things needed to become the kind of leader you want to be &#8211; and others want to follow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-you-do-is-who-you-are-how-to-create-your-business-culture-ben-horowitz-abridged/">What You Do Is Who You Are : How to Create Your Business Culture &#8211; Ben Horowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do the KIND Thing : Think Boundlessly, Work Purposefully, Live Passionately &#8211; Daniel Lubetzky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For the socially conscious, the intellectually curious, or the creative soul comes an inspiring, New York Times bestselling handbook for success in business, life, and the all-important task of building a more compassionate world&#8211;by the visionary founder and CEO of KIND Healthy Snacks. When Daniel Lubetzky started KIND Healthy Snacks in 2004, he aimed to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/">Do the KIND Thing : Think Boundlessly, Work Purposefully, Live Passionately &#8211; Daniel Lubetzky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For the socially conscious, the intellectually curious, or the creative soul comes an inspiring, New York Times bestselling handbook for success in business, life, and the all-important task of building a more compassionate world&#8211;by the visionary founder and CEO of KIND Healthy Snacks.    </p>
<p>                     When Daniel Lubetzky started KIND Healthy Snacks in 2004, he aimed to defy the conventional wisdom that snack bars could never be both tasty and healthy, convenient and wholesome. A decade later, the transformative power of the company&#8217;s &#8220;AND&#8221; philosophy has resulted in an astonishing record of achievement. KIND has become the fastest-growing purveyor of healthy snacks in the country. Meanwhile, the KIND Movement&#8211;the company&#8217;s social mission to make the world a little kinder&#8211;has sparked more than a million good deeds worldwide.  In Do the KIND Thing,  Lubetzky shares the revolutionary principles that have shaped KIND&#8217;s business model and led to its success, while offering an unfiltered and intensely personal look into the mind of a pioneering social entrepreneur. Inspired by his father, who survived the Holocaust thanks to the courageous kindness of strangers, Lubetzky began his career handselling a sun-dried tomato spread made collaboratively by Arabs and Jews in the war-torn Middle East. Despite early setbacks, he never lost his faith in his vision of a &#8220;not-only-for-profit&#8221; business&#8211;one that sold great products and helped to make the world a better place.  While other companies let circumstances force them into choosing between two seemingly incompatible options, people at KIND say &#8220;AND.&#8221; At its core, this idea is about challenging assumptions and false compromises. It is about not settling for less and being willing to take greater risks, often financial. It is about learning to think boundlessly and critically, and choosing what at first may be the tougher path for later, greater rewards. By using illuminating anecdotes from his own career, and celebrating some past failures through the lessons learned from them, Lubetzky outlines his core tenets for building a successful business and a thriving social enterprise. He explores the value of staying true to your brand, highlights the importance of transparency and communication in the workplace, and explains why good intentions alone won&#8217;t sell products.  Engaging and inspirational, Do the KIND Thing shows how the power of AND worked wonders for one company&#8211;and could empower the next generation of social entrepreneurs to improve their bottom line and change the world. Advance praise for Do the KIND Thing  &#8220;An enjoyable read . . . wise advice about matters from product development to people management.&#8221;&#8211;Financial Times &#8220;By sharing the ten tenets that helped KIND grow, Daniel Lubetzky has given entrepreneurs a road map to success that includes both passion and purpose.&#8221;&#8211;Arianna Huffington, president and editor in chief, Huffington Post Media Group  &#8220;Lubetzky uses the power of kindness to build purpose into his business and his community. He&#8217;s a role model for future leaders.&#8221;&#8211;Mehmet Oz, M.D., professor of surgery, Columbia University  &#8220;I&#8217;ve always been a fan of the KIND brand. This engaging and inspirational book shows how coupling a social mission with creativity can spark change and empower a generation.&#8221;&#8211;Bobbi Brown, founder and CCO, Bobbi Brown Cosmetics</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/">Do the KIND Thing : Think Boundlessly, Work Purposefully, Live Passionately &#8211; Daniel Lubetzky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Glass Closet : Why Coming Out is Good Business &#8211; John Browne (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-glass-closet-why-coming-out-is-good-business-john-browne-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay & Lesbian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay Studies (Gay Men)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-glass-closet-why-coming-out-is-good-business-john-browne-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I wish I had been brave enough to come out earlier in my tenure as CEO of BP. I regret it to this day. I know that if I had done so I would have made more of an impact for other gay men and women. With The Glass Closet, I hope to give some [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-glass-closet-why-coming-out-is-good-business-john-browne-abridged/">The Glass Closet : Why Coming Out is Good Business &#8211; John Browne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I wish I had been brave enough to come out earlier in my tenure as CEO of BP. I regret it to this day. I know that if I had done so I would have made more of an impact for other gay men and women. With The Glass Closet, I hope to give some of them the courage to make an impact of their own.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     Whether you&#8217;re lesbian, gay, transgender or straight, John Browne&#8217;s message is simple and clear, it&#8217;s better for you and it&#8217;s better for business when you bring your authentic self to work.    </p>
<p>                     Drawing on his personal experiences and the experience of other gay and lesbian business leaders, and by investigating the research and the social contexts, The Glass Closet strives to give courage and inspire the LGBT community that despite the risks involved, self-disclosure is best for employees and for the businesses that support them.    </p>
<p>                     Every CEO, every HR Manager, every team leader &#8211; anyone who is responsible for the culture and success of their business should read The Glass Closet. And for anyone fearful or lacking the confidence to bring their true self into work every day, this book was written for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-glass-closet-why-coming-out-is-good-business-john-browne-abridged/">The Glass Closet : Why Coming Out is Good Business &#8211; John Browne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It Doesn&#8217;t Have to Be Crazy at Work &#8211; Jason Fried, David Heinemeier Hansson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/it-doesnt-have-to-be-crazy-at-work-jason-fried-david-heinemeier-hansson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/it-doesnt-have-to-be-crazy-at-work-jason-fried-david-heinemeier-hansson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jason Fried and David Heinemeier Hansson, the authors of the New York Times bestseller Rework, are back with a manifesto to combat all your modern workplace worries and fears. It Doesn&#8217;t Have to Be Crazy at Work is a direct successor to Rework, the instant bestseller that showed readers a new path to working effectively. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-doesnt-have-to-be-crazy-at-work-jason-fried-david-heinemeier-hansson-abridged/">It Doesn&#8217;t Have to Be Crazy at Work &#8211; Jason Fried, David Heinemeier Hansson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jason Fried and David Heinemeier Hansson, the authors of the New York Times bestseller Rework, are back with a manifesto to combat all your modern workplace worries and fears.    </p>
<p>                              It Doesn&#8217;t Have to Be Crazy at Work is a direct successor to Rework, the instant bestseller that showed readers a new path to working effectively. Now Fried and Heinemeier Hansson have returned with a new strategy for the ideal company culture &#8211; what they call &#8220;the calm company&#8221;. It is a direct attack on the chaos, anxiety and stress that plagues millions of workplaces and billions of people working their day jobs.    </p>
<p>                              Working to breaking point with long hours, excessive workload, and a lack of sleep have become a badge of honour for many people these days, when it should be a mark of stupidity. This isn&#8217;t just a problem for large organisations; individuals, contractors and solopreneurs are burning themselves out in the very same way. As the authors reveal, the answer isn&#8217;t more hours. Rather, it&#8217;s less waste and fewer things that induce distraction, always-on anxiety and stress.    </p>
<p>                              It is time to stop celebrating crazy and start celebrating calm.    </p>
<p>                              Fried and Hansson have the proof to back up their argument. &#8220;Calm&#8221; has been the cornerstone of their company&#8217;s culture since Basecamp began twenty years ago. Destined to become the management guide for the next generation, It Doesn&#8217;t Have to Be Crazy at Work is a practical and inspiring distillation of their insights and experiences. It isn&#8217;t a book telling you what to do. It&#8217;s a book showing you what they&#8217;ve done-and how any manager or executive no matter the industry or size of the company, can do it too.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-doesnt-have-to-be-crazy-at-work-jason-fried-david-heinemeier-hansson-abridged/">It Doesn&#8217;t Have to Be Crazy at Work &#8211; Jason Fried, David Heinemeier Hansson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defence Strategy, Planning & Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Leadership is not a rank, it is a responsibility. Leadership is not about being in charge, it is about taking care of those in your charge. When we take care of our people, our people will take care of us. They will help see that our cause becomes a reality. In Leaders Eat Last, Simon [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/">Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Leadership is not a rank, it is a responsibility. Leadership is not about being in charge, it is about taking care of those in your charge.    </p>
<p>                    When we take care of our people, our people will take care of us. They will help see that our cause becomes a reality.    </p>
<p>                    In Leaders Eat Last, Simon Sinek, internationally bestselling author of Start With Why, investigates these great leaders from Marine Corps Officers, who don&#8217;t just sacrifice their place at the table but often their own comfort and even their lives for those in their care, to the heads of big business and government &#8211; each putting aside their own interests to protect their teams.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Simple and elegant, it shows us how leaders should lead&#8217; William Ury, co-author of Getting to Yes</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leaders-eat-last-why-some-teams-pull-together-and-others-dont-simon-sinek-abridged/">Leaders Eat Last : Why Some Teams Pull Together and Others Don&#8217;t &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Difference Makers &#8211; Dr Nicky Howe, Alicia Curtis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/difference-makers-dr-nicky-howe-alicia-curtis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Boards & Directors: Role & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Governance & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/difference-makers-dr-nicky-howe-alicia-curtis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Outstanding insight into how to effectively embrace diversity &#8230; a roadmap for creating better organisations, better companies and a better society.&#8217; &#8211; Rhys Williams, 2015 Young West Australian of the Year &#8216;&#8230;includes practical tools, checklists and activities for both the aspiring and experienced director.&#8217; &#8211; Angie Paskevicius, CEO, Holyoake &#8216;If you seriously want to make [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/difference-makers-dr-nicky-howe-alicia-curtis-abridged/">Difference Makers &#8211; Dr Nicky Howe, Alicia Curtis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Outstanding insight into how to effectively embrace diversity &#8230; a roadmap for creating better organisations, better companies and a better society.&#8217; &#8211; Rhys Williams, 2015 Young West Australian of the Year &#8216;&#8230;includes practical tools, checklists and activities for both the aspiring and experienced director.&#8217; &#8211; Angie Paskevicius, CEO, Holyoake &#8216;If you seriously want to make a difference &#8211; you must read Difference Makers.&#8217; &#8211; David Koutsoukis, founder of the Exceptional Teams Academy &#8216;I recommend this book to all those who believe we deserve better organisations.&#8217; &#8211; Rabia Siddique, international humanitarian, author and advocate &#8216;&#8230;a sound rationale highlighting the importance of diversity in achieving good governance &#8230; a nuanced and thoughtful resource designed to help meet the challenge.&#8217; &#8211; Professor David Gilchrist, director, Curtin University Dr Nicky Howe is a CEO and leadership and management expert, with a doctorate of business administration from the University of Western Australia, and postgraduate qualification in management from Flinders University. Nicky has a passion for building the capacity of individuals, organisations and communities. She is author of Better Relationships with Those You Lead, a handbook of practical skills and strategies for leaders and managers. Alicia Curtis is one of Western Australia&#8217;s most inspiring young social and business entrepreneurs, an award-winning speaker and leadership facilitator. Alicia established Alyceum in 2002 developing innovative transformational leadership programs. Alicia has a master&#8217;s degree in business leadership and was named one of the Australian Financial Review&#8217;s 100 Women of Influence in 2014. Together Nicky and Alicia founded the Engaging Young Leaders on Aged Care and Community Boards governance program, and as a consequence they were driven to share their findings and experiences in this fascinating book.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/difference-makers-dr-nicky-howe-alicia-curtis-abridged/">Difference Makers &#8211; Dr Nicky Howe, Alicia Curtis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Asking : How I learned to stop worrying and let people help &#8211; Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-asking-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-let-people-help-amanda-palmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History: From c 1960]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-asking-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-let-people-help-amanda-palmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>REDISCOVER THE FORGOTTEN ART OF ASKING IN THIS NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING BOOK &#8216;Amanda Palmer joyfully shows a generation how to change their lives&#8217; Caitlin Moran &#8216;To read Amanda Palmer&#8217;s remarkable memoir about asking and giving is to tumble headlong into her world&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert &#8216;The Art of Asking is a book about cultivating trust [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-asking-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-let-people-help-amanda-palmer-abridged/">The Art of Asking : How I learned to stop worrying and let people help &#8211; Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>REDISCOVER THE FORGOTTEN ART OF ASKING IN THIS NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING BOOK     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Amanda Palmer joyfully shows a generation how to change their lives&#8217; Caitlin Moran    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;To read Amanda Palmer&#8217;s remarkable memoir about asking and giving is to tumble headlong into her world&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The Art of Asking is a book about cultivating trust and getting as close as possible to love, vulnerability, and connection. Uncomfortably close. Dangerously close. Beautifully close&#8217; Brene Brown    </p>
<p>                    Imagine standing on a box in the middle of a busy city, dressed as a white-faced bride, and silently using your eyes to ask people for money. Or touring Europe in a punk cabaret band, and finding a place to sleep each night by reaching out to strangers on Twitter. For Amanda Palmer, actions like these have gone beyond satisfying her basic needs for food and shelter &#8211; they&#8217;ve taught her how to turn strangers into friends, build communities, and discover her own giving impulses. And because she had learned how to ask, she was able to go to the world to ask for the money to make a new album and tour with it, and to raise over a million dollars in a month.    </p>
<p>                    In the New York TImes bestseller The Art of Asking, Palmer expands upon her popular TED talk to reveal how ordinary people, those of us without thousands of Twitter followers and adoring fans, can use these same principles in our own lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-asking-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-and-let-people-help-amanda-palmer-abridged/">The Art of Asking : How I learned to stop worrying and let people help &#8211; Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Propaganda]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Does &#8216;fake news&#8217; really exist? Find out from the ultimate insider. After years of working as a respected journalist, Nick Davies, in this shocking expose, reveals what really goes on behind the scenes of this contentious industry. From a prestigious newspaper that allowed intelligence agencies to plant fiction in its columns, to the newsroom that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/">Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Does &#8216;fake news&#8217; really exist? Find out from the ultimate insider.    </p>
<p>                    After years of working as a respected journalist, Nick Davies, in this shocking expose, reveals what really goes on behind the scenes of this contentious industry.     </p>
<p>                    From a prestigious newspaper that allowed intelligence agencies to plant fiction in its columns, to the newsroom that routinely rejected stories due to racial bias, to the number of papers that accepted cash bribes. Gripping, thought-provoking and revelatory, this is an insider&#8217;s look at one of the most tainted professions.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Meticulous, fair-minded and utterly gripping&#8217; Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Powerful and timely&#8230;his analysis is fair, meticulously researched and fascinating&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/">Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hit Makers : How Things Become Popular &#8211; Derek Thompson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hit-makers-how-things-become-popular-derek-thompson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hit-makers-how-things-become-popular-derek-thompson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What makes a hit a hit? In Hit Makers, Atlantic Senior Editor Derek Thompson puts pop culture under the lens of science to answer the question that every business, every producer, every person looking to promote themselves and their work has asked. Drawing on ancient history and modern headlines &#8211; from vampire lore and Brahms&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hit-makers-how-things-become-popular-derek-thompson-abridged/">Hit Makers : How Things Become Popular &#8211; Derek Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What makes a hit a hit? In Hit Makers, Atlantic Senior Editor Derek Thompson puts pop  culture under the lens of science to answer the question that every  business, every producer, every person looking to promote themselves and  their work has asked.     </p>
<p>                     Drawing on ancient history and modern  headlines &#8211; from vampire lore and Brahms&#8217;s Lullaby to Instagram &#8211;  Thompson explores the economics and psychology of why certain things  become extraordinarily popular. With incisive analysis and captivating  storytelling, he reveals that, though blockbuster films, Internet memes  and number-one songs seem to have come out of nowhere, hits actually  have a story and operate by certain rules. People gravitate towards  familiar surprises: products that are bold and innovative, yet instantly  comprehensible.     </p>
<p>                    Whether he is uncovering the secrets of JFK  and Barack Obama&#8217;s speechwriters or analysing the unexpected reasons for  the success of Fifty Shades of Grey, Thompson goes beyond the  cultural phenomena that make the news by revealing the desires that make  us all human. While technology might change, he shows, our innate  preferences do not, and throughout history hits have held up a mirror to  ourselves.     </p>
<p>                     From the dawn of Impressionist art to the future of Snapchat, from small-scale Etsy entrepreneurs to the origin of Star Wars, Derek Thompson tells the fascinating story of how culture happens &#8211; and where genius lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hit-makers-how-things-become-popular-derek-thompson-abridged/">Hit Makers : How Things Become Popular &#8211; Derek Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Business Romantic : Fall back in love with your work and your life &#8211; Tim Leberecht (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-business-romantic-fall-back-in-love-with-your-work-and-your-life-tim-leberecht-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-business-romantic-fall-back-in-love-with-your-work-and-your-life-tim-leberecht-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Top 10 Motivational Books of 2015 &#8211; Inc.com Top 10 Creative Leadership Books of 2015 &#8211; Forbes Against the backdrop of eroding trust in capitalism, pervasive technology, big data, and the desire to quantify all of our behaviours, The Business Romantic makes a compelling case that we must meld the pursuit of success and achievement [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-business-romantic-fall-back-in-love-with-your-work-and-your-life-tim-leberecht-abridged/">The Business Romantic : Fall back in love with your work and your life &#8211; Tim Leberecht (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Top 10 Motivational Books of 2015 &#8211; Inc.com<br />
                    Top 10 Creative Leadership Books of 2015 &#8211; Forbes    </p>
<p>                    Against the backdrop of eroding trust in capitalism, pervasive technology, big data, and the desire to quantify all of our behaviours, The Business Romantic makes a compelling case that we must meld the pursuit of success and achievement with romance if we want to create an economy that serves our entire selves.    </p>
<p>                    A rising star in data analytics who is in love with the intrinsic beauty of spreadsheets; the mastermind behind a brand built on absence; an Argentinian couple who revolutionize shoelaces; the founder of a foodie-oriented start-up that creates intimate conversation spaces; a performance artist who offers fake corporate seminars for real professionals &#8211; these are some of the innovators readers will meet in this witty, deeply personal, and rousing journey through the world of Business Romanticism.    </p>
<p>                    The Business Romantic not only provides surprising insights into the emotional and social aspects of business but also presents &#8216;Rules of Enchantment&#8217; that will help both individuals and organisations construct more meaningful experiences for themselves and others.    </p>
<p>                    The Business Romantic offers a radically different view of the good life and outlines how to better meet one&#8217;s own desires as well as those of customers, employees, and society. It encourages readers to expect more from companies, to give more of themselves, and to fall back in love with their work and their lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-business-romantic-fall-back-in-love-with-your-work-and-your-life-tim-leberecht-abridged/">The Business Romantic : Fall back in love with your work and your life &#8211; Tim Leberecht (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4 Day Week : How the Flexible Work Revolution Can Increase Productivity, Profitability and Well-being, and Create a Sustainable Future &#8211; Andrew Barnes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE BUSINESS BOOK AWARDS 2021 In The 4 Day Week, entrepreneur and business innovator Andrew Barnes makes the case for the four-day work week as the answer to many of the ills of the 21st-century global economy. Barnes conducted an experiment in his own business, the New Zealand trust company Perpetual Guardian, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/">The 4 Day Week : How the Flexible Work Revolution Can Increase Productivity, Profitability and Well-being, and Create a Sustainable Future &#8211; Andrew Barnes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE BUSINESS BOOK AWARDS 2021    </p>
<p>                    In The 4 Day Week, entrepreneur and business innovator Andrew Barnes makes the case for the four-day work week as the answer to many of the ills of the 21st-century global economy.     </p>
<p>                     Barnes conducted an experiment in his own business, the New Zealand trust company Perpetual Guardian, and asked his staff to design a four-day week that would permit them to meet their existing productivity requirements on the same salary but with a 20% cut in work hours. The outcomes of this trial, which no business leader had previously attempted on these terms, were stunning. People were happier and healthier, more engaged in their personal lives, and more focused and productive in the office.    </p>
<p>                     The world of work has seen a dramatic shift in recent times: the former security and benefits associated with permanent employment are being displaced by the less stable gig economy. Barnes explains the dangers of a focus on flexibility at the expense of hard-won worker protections, and argues that with the four-day week, we can have the best of all worlds: optimal productivity, work-life balance, worker benefits and, at long last, a solution to pervasive economic inequities such as the gender pay gap and lack of diversity in business and governance.     </p>
<p>                     The 4 Day Week is a practical, how-to guide for business leaders and employees alike that is applicable to nearly every industry. Using qualitative and quantitative data from research gathered through the Perpetual Guardian trial and other sources by the University of Auckland and Auckland University of Technology, the book presents a step-by-step approach to preparing businesses for productivity-focused flexibility, from the necessary cultural conditions to the often complex legislative considerations.    </p>
<p>                     The story of Perpetual Guardian&#8217;s unprecedented work experiment has made headlines around the world and stormed social media, reaching a global audience in more than seventy countries. A mix of trenchant analysis, personal observation and actionable advice, The 4 Day Week is an essential guide for leaders and workers seeking to make a change for the better in their work world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/">The 4 Day Week : How the Flexible Work Revolution Can Increase Productivity, Profitability and Well-being, and Create a Sustainable Future &#8211; Andrew Barnes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smartest Guys in the Room : The Amazing Rise and Scandalous Fall of Enron &#8211; Peter Elkind, Bethany McLean (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Company Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy Industries & Utilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What went wrong with American business at the end of the 20th century? Until the spring of 2001, Enron epitomized the triumph of the New Economy. Feared by rivals, worshipped by investors, Enron seemingly could do no wrong. Its profits rose every year; its stock price surged ever upward; its leaders were hailed as visionaries. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/">The Smartest Guys in the Room : The Amazing Rise and Scandalous Fall of Enron &#8211; Peter Elkind, Bethany McLean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What went wrong with American business at the end of the 20th century?    </p>
<p>                    Until the spring of 2001, Enron epitomized the triumph of the New Economy. Feared by rivals, worshipped by investors, Enron seemingly could do no wrong. Its profits rose every year; its stock price surged ever upward; its leaders were hailed as visionaries.      </p>
<p>                    Then a young Fortune writer, Bethany McLean, wrote an article posing a simple question &#8211;  how, exactly, does Enron make its money?    </p>
<p>                    Within a year Enron was facing humiliation and bankruptcy, the largest in US history, which caused Americans to lose faith in a system that rewarded top insiders with millions of dollars, while small investors lost everything. It was revealed that Enron was a company whose business was an illusion, an illusion that Wall Street was willing to accept even though they knew what the real truth was.  This book &#8211; fully updated for the paperback &#8211; tells the extraordinary story of Enron&#8217;s fall.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/">The Smartest Guys in the Room : The Amazing Rise and Scandalous Fall of Enron &#8211; Peter Elkind, Bethany McLean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dip : The extraordinary benefits of knowing when to quit (and when to stick) &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-dip-the-extraordinary-benefits-of-knowing-when-to-quit-and-when-to-stick-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dip-the-extraordinary-benefits-of-knowing-when-to-quit-and-when-to-stick-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This iconic bestseller from the bestselling author of All Marketers Are Liars proves that winners are just the best quitters and &#8216;should be on every entrepreneur&#8217;s book list&#8217; (Entrepreneur.com) Every new project (or career or relationship) starts out exciting and fun. Then it gets harder and less fun, until it hits a low point &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dip-the-extraordinary-benefits-of-knowing-when-to-quit-and-when-to-stick-seth-godin-abridged/">The Dip : The extraordinary benefits of knowing when to quit (and when to stick) &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This iconic bestseller from the bestselling author of All Marketers Are Liars proves that winners are just the best quitters and &#8216;should be on every entrepreneur&#8217;s book list&#8217; (Entrepreneur.com)    </p>
<p>                    Every new project (or career or relationship) starts out exciting and fun. Then it gets harder and less fun, until it hits a low point &#8211; really hard, really not fun. At this point you might be in a Dip, which will get better if you keep pushing, or a Cul-de-Sac, which will never get better no matter how hard you try. The hard part is knowing the difference and acting on it.     </p>
<p>                    According to marketing guru and best-selling author Seth Godin, what sets successful entrepreneurs (and pop stars and weight lifters and car salesmen) apart from everyone else is their ability to give up on Cul-de-Sacs while staying motivated in Dips. Winners quit fast, quit often and quit without guilt &#8211; until they commit to beating the right Dip for the right reasons. You&#8217;ll never be number one at anything without picking your shots very carefully. The Dip is a short, entertaining book that helps you do just that. It will forever alter the way you think about success.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Smart, honest, and refreshingly free of self-help posturing, this primer on winning-through-quitting is at once motivational and comically indifferent. . . Godin&#8217;s truth-that &#8220;we fail when we get distracted by tasks we don&#8217;t have the guts to quit&#8221;-makes excellent sense of an often-difficult career move&#8217; (Publishers Weekly)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dip-the-extraordinary-benefits-of-knowing-when-to-quit-and-when-to-stick-seth-godin-abridged/">The Dip : The extraordinary benefits of knowing when to quit (and when to stick) &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anything You Want : 40 Lessons for a New Kind of Entrepreneur &#8211; Derek Sivers (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/anything-you-want-40-lessons-for-a-new-kind-of-entrepreneur-derek-sivers-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/anything-you-want-40-lessons-for-a-new-kind-of-entrepreneur-derek-sivers-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I love this book! If you want a true manifesto, a guidebook with clear signposts, and a fun ride you&#8217;ll return to again and again, you have it here in this book. I hope you enjoy it as much as I did&#8217; Tim Ferriss, author of The 4-Hour Workweek The iconic manifesto on lessons learned [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anything-you-want-40-lessons-for-a-new-kind-of-entrepreneur-derek-sivers-abridged/">Anything You Want : 40 Lessons for a New Kind of Entrepreneur &#8211; Derek Sivers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I love this book! If you want a true manifesto, a guidebook with clear signposts, and a fun ride you&#8217;ll return to again and again, you have it here in this book. I hope you enjoy it as much as I did&#8217; Tim Ferriss, author of The 4-Hour Workweek      </p>
<p>                    The iconic manifesto on lessons learned while becoming an entrepreneur    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;    </p>
<p>                    You don&#8217;t need a visionary master plan, loads of funding or a brilliant team to start a business.    </p>
<p>                    When Derek Sivers started CD Baby, he wasn&#8217;t planning on building a major business. He was a successful independent musician who just wanted to sell his CDs online. He started in 1998 by helping his friends sell their CDs too. In 2000, he hired his first employee. Eight years later, he sold CD Baby for $22 million.    </p>
<p>                    Sivers didn&#8217;t need a business plan and neither do you. You don&#8217;t need to think big; in fact, it&#8217;s better if you don&#8217;t. Anything You Want will inspire you to start with what you have, care about your customers more than yourself, and run your business like you don&#8217;t need the money.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Some of the best hours you&#8217;ll ever spend will be reading Derek Sivers&#8217;s new book&#8230;Anything You Want&#8217; Forbes</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anything-you-want-40-lessons-for-a-new-kind-of-entrepreneur-derek-sivers-abridged/">Anything You Want : 40 Lessons for a New Kind of Entrepreneur &#8211; Derek Sivers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Selling The Invisible : A Field Guide to Modern Marketing &#8211; Harry Beckwith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/selling-the-invisible-a-field-guide-to-modern-marketing-harry-beckwith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/selling-the-invisible-a-field-guide-to-modern-marketing-harry-beckwith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SELLING THE INVISIBLE is a succinct and often entertaining look at the unique characteristics of services and their prospects, and how any service, from a home-based consultancy to a multinational brokerage, can turn more prospects into clients and keep them. SELLING THE INVISIBLE covers service marketing from start to finish. Filled with wonderful insights and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selling-the-invisible-a-field-guide-to-modern-marketing-harry-beckwith-abridged/">Selling The Invisible : A Field Guide to Modern Marketing &#8211; Harry Beckwith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SELLING THE INVISIBLE is a succinct and often entertaining look at the unique characteristics of services and their prospects, and how any service, from a home-based consultancy to a multinational brokerage, can turn more prospects into clients and keep them. SELLING THE INVISIBLE covers service marketing from start to finish. Filled with wonderful insights and written in a roll-up-your-sleeves, jargon-free, accessible style, such as:    </p>
<p>                    Greatness May Get You Nowhere; Focus Groups Don&#8217;ts; The More You Say, the Less People Hear; Seeing the Forest Around the Falling Trees</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/selling-the-invisible-a-field-guide-to-modern-marketing-harry-beckwith-abridged/">Selling The Invisible : A Field Guide to Modern Marketing &#8211; Harry Beckwith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Developing the Leader Within You 2.0 &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/developing-the-leader-within-you-2-0-john-c-maxwell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/developing-the-leader-within-you-2-0-john-c-maxwell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to develop the influence, character, service and vision that it takes to be a leader in every aspect of your life. First released in 1993, John C. Maxwell&#8217;s now-classic work revolutionized the way leaders are made. By examining the differences between leadership styles, Maxwell outlines principles for inspiring, motivating, and influencing others from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/developing-the-leader-within-you-2-0-john-c-maxwell-abridged/">Developing the Leader Within You 2.0 &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to develop the influence, character, service and vision that it takes to be a leader in every aspect of your life.    </p>
<p>                    First released in 1993, John C. Maxwell&#8217;s now-classic work revolutionized the way leaders are made. By examining the differences between leadership styles, Maxwell outlines principles for inspiring, motivating, and influencing others from any type of leadership position&#8211;including as a business executive, a church leader, a teacher, or even a parent.    </p>
<p>                    In this thoroughly revised and updated edition, Maxwell includes two new chapters to include the leadership insights and practices he has learned in the decades since the first edition so that you&#8217;ll receive everything you need to take a significant step in your leadership journey.    </p>
<p>                    In Developing the Leader Within You 2.0, you will successfully learn and understand:    </p>
<p>                    Influence &#8211; using the 5 Levels of Leadership as a roadmap to influence others<br />
                    Character &#8211; embracing good ethics, practicing self-leadership, and valuing people<br />
                    Service &#8211; asking eight questions to develop into a leader who serves others daily<br />
                    Vision &#8211; including eight components when painting a vision for your people so they can experience it    </p>
<p>                    These foundational principles provides both new readers and longtime fans with the necessary wisdom to help any leader and organization succeed in fostering integrity, self-discipline, and effecting positive change.    </p>
<p>                    Developing the Leader Within You 2.0 will help you transform the way you think about leadership.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/developing-the-leader-within-you-2-0-john-c-maxwell-abridged/">Developing the Leader Within You 2.0 &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Successful People Think : Change Your Thinking, Change Your Life &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-successful-people-think-change-your-thinking-change-your-life-john-c-maxwell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-successful-people-think-change-your-thinking-change-your-life-john-c-maxwell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The perfect, compact read for today&#8217;s fast-paced world, How Successful People Think (derived from Maxwell&#8217;s previous book, Thinking for a Change) guides readers through the 11 secrets successful people know. Arranged in an easy-to-follow format, America&#8217;s leadership expert John C. Maxwell will teach readers how to expand their thinking and achieve their dreams. The 11 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-successful-people-think-change-your-thinking-change-your-life-john-c-maxwell-abridged/">How Successful People Think : Change Your Thinking, Change Your Life &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The perfect, compact read for today&#8217;s fast-paced world, How Successful People Think (derived from Maxwell&#8217;s previous book, Thinking for a Change) guides readers through the 11 secrets successful people know. Arranged in an easy-to-follow format, America&#8217;s leadership expert John C. Maxwell will teach readers how to expand their thinking and achieve their dreams. The 11 keys to successful thinking include: Big-Picture Thinking &#8211; seeing the world beyond your own needs and how that leads to great ideas Focused Thinking &#8211; removing mental clutter and distractions to realize your full potential Creative Thinking &#8211; thinking in unique ways and making breakthroughs Shared Thinking &#8211; working with others to compound results Reflective Thinking &#8211; looking at the past to gain a better understanding of the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-successful-people-think-change-your-thinking-change-your-life-john-c-maxwell-abridged/">How Successful People Think : Change Your Thinking, Change Your Life &#8211; John C. Maxwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Infinite Game : From the bestselling author of Start With Why &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-infinite-game-from-the-bestselling-author-of-start-with-why-simon-sinek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-infinite-game-from-the-bestselling-author-of-start-with-why-simon-sinek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER The New York Times-bestselling author of Start With Why, Leaders Eat Last, and Together Is Better offers a bold new approach to business strategy by asking one question: are you playing the finite game or the infinite game? In The Infinite Game, Sinek applies game theory to explore how great businesses [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-infinite-game-from-the-bestselling-author-of-start-with-why-simon-sinek-abridged/">The Infinite Game : From the bestselling author of Start With Why &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The New York Times-bestselling author of Start With Why, Leaders Eat Last, and Together Is Better offers a bold new approach to business strategy by asking one question: are you playing the finite game or the infinite game?     </p>
<p>                    In The Infinite Game, Sinek applies game theory to explore how great businesses achieve long-lasting success. He finds that building long-term value and healthy, enduring growth &#8211; that playing the infinite game &#8211; is the only thing that matters to your business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-infinite-game-from-the-bestselling-author-of-start-with-why-simon-sinek-abridged/">The Infinite Game : From the bestselling author of Start With Why &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Merchants of Doubt : How a Handful of Scientists Obscured the Truth on Issues from Tobacco Smoke to Global Warming &#8211; Erik M. Conway, Naomi Oreskes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/merchants-of-doubt-how-a-handful-of-scientists-obscured-the-truth-on-issues-from-tobacco-smoke-to-global-warming-erik-m-conway-naomi-oreskes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/merchants-of-doubt-how-a-handful-of-scientists-obscured-the-truth-on-issues-from-tobacco-smoke-to-global-warming-erik-m-conway-naomi-oreskes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. scientific community has long led the world in research on such areas as public health, environmental science, and issues affecting quality of life. Our scientists have produced landmark studies on the dangers of DDT, tobacco smoke, acid rain, and global warming. But at the same time, a small yet potent subset of this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/merchants-of-doubt-how-a-handful-of-scientists-obscured-the-truth-on-issues-from-tobacco-smoke-to-global-warming-erik-m-conway-naomi-oreskes-abridged/">Merchants of Doubt : How a Handful of Scientists Obscured the Truth on Issues from Tobacco Smoke to Global Warming &#8211; Erik M. Conway, Naomi Oreskes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. scientific community has long led the world in research on such areas as public health, environmental science, and issues affecting quality of life. Our scientists have produced landmark studies on the dangers of DDT, tobacco smoke, acid rain, and global warming. But at the same time, a small yet potent subset of this community leads the world in vehement denial of these dangers.    </p>
<p>                    Merchants of Doubt tells the story of how a loose-knit group of high-level scientists and scientific advisers, with deep connections in politics and industry, ran effective campaigns to mislead the public and deny well-established scientific knowledge over four decades. Remarkably, the same individuals surface repeatedly &#8211; some of the same figures who have claimed that the science of global warming is &#8220;not settled&#8221; denied the truth of studies linking smoking to lung cancer, coal smoke to acid rain, and CFCs to the ozone hole. &#8220;Doubt is our product,&#8221; wrote one tobacco executive. These &#8216;experts&#8217; supplied it.     </p>
<p>                    Naomi Oreskes and Erik M. Conway, historians of science, roll back the rug on this dark corner of the American scientific community, showing how ideology and corporate interests, aided by a too-compliant media, have skewed public understanding of some of the most pressing issues of our era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/merchants-of-doubt-how-a-handful-of-scientists-obscured-the-truth-on-issues-from-tobacco-smoke-to-global-warming-erik-m-conway-naomi-oreskes-abridged/">Merchants of Doubt : How a Handful of Scientists Obscured the Truth on Issues from Tobacco Smoke to Global Warming &#8211; Erik M. Conway, Naomi Oreskes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Common Good &#8211; Robert B. Reich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-common-good-robert-b-reich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-common-good-robert-b-reich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Robert B. Reich makes a powerful case for the expansion of America&#8217;s moral imagination. Rooting his argument in common sense and everyday reality, he demonstrates that a common good constitutes the very essence of any society or nation. Societies, he says, undergo virtuous cycles that reinforce the common good as well as vicious cycles that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-common-good-robert-b-reich-abridged/">The Common Good &#8211; Robert B. Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Robert B. Reich makes a powerful case for the expansion of America&#8217;s moral imagination. Rooting his argument in common sense and everyday reality, he demonstrates that a common good constitutes the very essence of any society or nation. Societies, he says, undergo virtuous cycles that reinforce the common good as well as vicious cycles that undermine it, one of which America has been experiencing for the past five decades. This process can and must be reversed. But first we need to weigh the moral obligations of citizenship and carefully consider how we relate to honor, shame, patriotism, truth, and the meaning of leadership.     </p>
<p>                     Powerful, urgent, and utterly vital, this is a heartfelt missive from one of our foremost political thinkers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-common-good-robert-b-reich-abridged/">The Common Good &#8211; Robert B. Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lying &#8211; Sam Harris, Edited by Annaka Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lying-sam-harris-edited-by-annaka-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lying-sam-harris-edited-by-annaka-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As it was in Anna Karenina, Madame Bovary, and Othello, so it is in life. Most forms of private vice and public evil are kindled and sustained by lies. Acts of adultery and other personal betrayals, financial fraud, government corruption&#8211;even murder and genocide&#8211;generally require an additional moral defect: a willingness to lie. In Lying, best-selling [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lying-sam-harris-edited-by-annaka-harris-abridged/">Lying &#8211; Sam Harris, Edited by Annaka Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As it was in Anna Karenina, Madame Bovary, and Othello, so it is in life. Most forms of private vice and public evil are kindled and sustained by lies. Acts of adultery and other personal betrayals, financial fraud, government corruption&#8211;even murder and genocide&#8211;generally require an additional moral defect: a willingness to lie.  In Lying, best-selling author and neuroscientist Sam Harris argues that we can radically simplify our lives and improve society by merely telling the truth in situations where others often lie. He focuses on &#8220;white&#8221; lies&#8211;those lies we tell for the purpose of sparing people discomfort&#8211;for these are the lies that most often tempt us. And they tend to be the only lies that good people tell while imagining that they are being good in the process.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lying-sam-harris-edited-by-annaka-harris-abridged/">Lying &#8211; Sam Harris, Edited by Annaka Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Two Birds in a Tree; Timeless Indian Wisdom for Business Leaders &#8211; Ram Nidumolu (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/two-birds-in-a-tree-timeless-indian-wisdom-for-business-leaders-ram-nidumolu-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/two-birds-in-a-tree-timeless-indian-wisdom-for-business-leaders-ram-nidumolu-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The health of business is inextricably linked with the health of humanity and nature. But our current approaches to leadership treat business as entirely separate&#8211;and the result has been recurring economic, environmental, and human crises. In this extraordinary book, Ram Nidumolu uses evocative parables and stories from the ancient Indian wisdom texts, the Upanishads, to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/two-birds-in-a-tree-timeless-indian-wisdom-for-business-leaders-ram-nidumolu-abridged/">Two Birds in a Tree; Timeless Indian Wisdom for Business Leaders &#8211; Ram Nidumolu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The health of business is inextricably linked with the health of humanity and nature. But our current approaches to leadership treat business as entirely separate&#8211;and the result has been recurring economic, environmental, and human crises.     </p>
<p>                     In this extraordinary book, Ram Nidumolu uses evocative parables and stories from the ancient Indian wisdom texts, the Upanishads, to introduce Being-centered leadership. This new kind of leadership is anchored in the concept of Being, the fundamental reality that underlies all phenomena. Being-centered leaders are guided by an innate sense of interconnection&#8211;the good of the whole becomes an integral part of their decisions and actions. Using the experiences of over twenty trailblazing CEOs, as well as those from his own life, Nidumolu describes a four-stage road map every aspiring leader can use to reconnect business to the wider world&#8211;to the benefit of all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/two-birds-in-a-tree-timeless-indian-wisdom-for-business-leaders-ram-nidumolu-abridged/">Two Birds in a Tree; Timeless Indian Wisdom for Business Leaders &#8211; Ram Nidumolu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conspiracy : A True Story of Power, Sex, and a Billionaire&#8217;s Secret Plot to Destroy a Media Empire &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2016, one of the giants of modern journalism fell: Gawker Media, infamous for saying what other outlets wouldn&#8217;t say, was sued for publishing Hulk Hogan&#8217;s sex tape, lost the case and went bust. After countless other lawsuits it seemed that Gawker had finally run out of luck. But luck had nothing to do with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Conspiracy : A True Story of Power, Sex, and a Billionaire&#8217;s Secret Plot to Destroy a Media Empire &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2016, one of the giants of modern journalism fell: Gawker Media, infamous for saying what other outlets wouldn&#8217;t say, was sued for publishing Hulk Hogan&#8217;s sex tape, lost the case and went bust. After countless other lawsuits it seemed that Gawker had finally run out of luck. But luck had nothing to do with it.     </p>
<p>                    Peter Thiel, PayPal founder and billionaire investor, had masterminded the whole thing. Still furious at an article that had outed him ten years previously, and increasingly disgusted at Gawker&#8217;s unscrupulous reporting methods, Thiel had spent nearly a decade meticulously plotting a conspiracy that would lead to the demise of Gawker and its founder, Nick Denton. After a multi-year proxy war through the Florida legal system, the settlement of $140million in favour of Hogan ended it.    </p>
<p>                    The verdict would stun the world and so would Peter&#8217;s ultimate unmasking as the man who had set it all in motion. Why had he done this? How had no one discovered it? What would this mean&#8211;for free speech? For privacy? For culture?    </p>
<p>                    In Holiday&#8217;s masterful telling of this nearly unbelievable conspiracy, informed by exclusive interviews with all the key players, this case transcends the narrative of how one billionaire took down a media empire or the current state of the free press. It&#8217;s a study in power, strategy, and one of the most wildly ambitious &#8211; and successful &#8211; secret plots in recent memory.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Conspiracy : A True Story of Power, Sex, and a Billionaire&#8217;s Secret Plot to Destroy a Media Empire &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Move Fast and Break Things : How Facebook, Google and Amazon Have Cornered Culture and Undermined Democracy &#8211; Jonathan Taplin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Network Security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Financial Times &#8216;Best Thing I Read This Year&#8217; LONGLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD Google. Amazon. Facebook. The modern world is defined by vast digital monopolies turning ever-larger profits. Those of us who consume the content that feeds them are farmed for the purposes of being sold ever [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/">Move Fast and Break Things : How Facebook, Google and Amazon Have Cornered Culture and Undermined Democracy &#8211; Jonathan Taplin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Financial Times &#8216;Best Thing I Read This Year&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    LONGLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD    </p>
<p>                    Google. Amazon. Facebook. The modern world is defined by vast digital monopolies turning ever-larger profits. Those of us who consume the content that feeds them are farmed for the purposes of being sold ever more products and advertising. Those that create the content &#8211; the artists, writers and musicians &#8211; are finding they can no longer survive in this unforgiving economic landscape.     </p>
<p>                     But it didn&#8217;t have to be this way.     </p>
<p>                     In Move Fast and Break Things, Jonathan Taplin offers a succinct and powerful history of how online life began to be shaped around the values of the entrepreneurs like Peter Thiel and Larry Page who founded these all-powerful companies. Their unprecedented growth came at the heavy cost of tolerating piracy of books, music and film, while at the same time promoting opaque business practices and subordinating the privacy of individual users to create the surveillance marketing monoculture in which we now live.    </p>
<p>                    It is the story of a massive reallocation of revenue in which $50 billion a year has moved from the creators and owners of content to the monopoly platforms. With this reallocation of money comes a shift in power. Google, Facebook and Amazon now enjoy political power on par with Big Oil and Big Pharma, which in part explains how such a tremendous shift in revenues from creators to platforms could have been achieved and why it has gone unchallenged for so long.    </p>
<p>                    And if you think that&#8217;s got nothing to do with you, their next move is to come after your jobs.     </p>
<p>                    Move Fast and Break Things is a call to arms, to say that is enough is enough and to demand that we do everything in our power to create a different future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/">Move Fast and Break Things : How Facebook, Google and Amazon Have Cornered Culture and Undermined Democracy &#8211; Jonathan Taplin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The No Asshole Rule : Building a Civilised Workplace and Surviving One That Isn&#8217;t &#8211; Robert Sutton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-no-asshole-rule-building-a-civilised-workplace-and-surviving-one-that-isnt-robert-sutton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-no-asshole-rule-building-a-civilised-workplace-and-surviving-one-that-isnt-robert-sutton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When the Harvard Business Review asked Robert Sutton for suggestions for its annual list of Breakthrough Ideas, he told them that the best business practice he knew of was &#8216;the no asshole rule&#8217;. Sutton&#8217;s piece became one of the most popular articles ever to appear in the HBR. Spurred on by the fear and despair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-no-asshole-rule-building-a-civilised-workplace-and-surviving-one-that-isnt-robert-sutton-abridged/">The No Asshole Rule : Building a Civilised Workplace and Surviving One That Isn&#8217;t &#8211; Robert Sutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When the Harvard Business Review asked Robert Sutton for suggestions for its annual list of Breakthrough Ideas, he told them that the best business practice he knew of was &#8216;the no asshole rule&#8217;. Sutton&#8217;s piece became one of the most popular articles ever to appear in the HBR. Spurred on by the fear and despair that people expressed, the tricks they used to survive with dignity in asshole-infested places, the revenge stories that made him laugh out loud and the other small wins that they celebrated against mean-spirited people, Sutton was persuaded to write THE NO ASSHOLE RULE.<br />
                    He believes passionately that civilised workplaces are not a naive dream, that they do exist, do bolster performance and that widespread contempt can be erased and replaced with mutual respect when a team or organisation is managed right. There is a huge temptation by executives and those in positions of authority to overlook this trait especially when exhibited by so-called producers, but Sutton shows how overall productivity suffers when the workplace is subjected to this kind of stress.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-no-asshole-rule-building-a-civilised-workplace-and-surviving-one-that-isnt-robert-sutton-abridged/">The No Asshole Rule : Building a Civilised Workplace and Surviving One That Isn&#8217;t &#8211; Robert Sutton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Slay In Your Lane : The Black Girl Bible &#8211; Yomi Adegoke, Elizabeth Uviebinene (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/slay-in-your-lane-the-black-girl-bible-yomi-adegoke-elizabeth-uviebinene-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/slay-in-your-lane-the-black-girl-bible-yomi-adegoke-elizabeth-uviebinene-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The long-awaited, inspirational guide to life for a generation of black British women inspired to make lemonade out of lemons, and find success in every area of their lives. &#8216;Inspirational&#8217; Stylist &#8216;Seismic&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;A comprehensive, inspirational tool book that gives voice to the next generation of young black British women&#8217; Vogue &#8216;Everyone should read [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/slay-in-your-lane-the-black-girl-bible-yomi-adegoke-elizabeth-uviebinene-abridged/">Slay In Your Lane : The Black Girl Bible &#8211; Yomi Adegoke, Elizabeth Uviebinene (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The long-awaited, inspirational guide to life for a generation of black British women inspired to make lemonade out of lemons, and find success in every area of their lives.    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Inspirational&#8217; Stylist    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Seismic&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;A comprehensive, inspirational tool book that gives voice to the next generation of young black British women&#8217; Vogue    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Everyone should read it&#8217; Sadiq Khan    </p>
<p>                              This honest and provocative book recognises and celebrates the strides black women have already made, while providing practical advice for those who want to do the same and forge a better, visible future.    </p>
<p>                              Illustrated with stories from best friends Elizabeth Uviebinene and Yomi Adegoke&#8217;s own lives, and using interviews with dozens of the most successful black women in Britain, Slay In Your Lane is essential reading for a generation of black women inspired to find success in every area of their lives.    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;A brilliant insight into being a black woman in Britain&#8217; Otegha Uwagba, author of Little Black Book</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/slay-in-your-lane-the-black-girl-bible-yomi-adegoke-elizabeth-uviebinene-abridged/">Slay In Your Lane : The Black Girl Bible &#8211; Yomi Adegoke, Elizabeth Uviebinene (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Building Social Business : The New Kind of Capitalism that Serves Humanity&#8217;s Most Pressing Needs &#8211; Muhammad Yunus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/building-social-business-the-new-kind-of-capitalism-that-serves-humanitys-most-pressing-needs-muhammad-yunus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-profitmaking Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/building-social-business-the-new-kind-of-capitalism-that-serves-humanitys-most-pressing-needs-muhammad-yunus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Muhammad Yunus, the practical visionary who pioneered microcredit and, with his Grameen Bank, won the 2006 Nobel Peace Prize, has developed a new dimension for capitalism which he calls &#8220;social business.&#8221; The social business model has been adopted by corporations, entrepreneurs, and social activists across the globe. Its goal is to create self-supporting, viable commercial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/building-social-business-the-new-kind-of-capitalism-that-serves-humanitys-most-pressing-needs-muhammad-yunus-abridged/">Building Social Business : The New Kind of Capitalism that Serves Humanity&#8217;s Most Pressing Needs &#8211; Muhammad Yunus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Muhammad Yunus, the practical visionary who pioneered microcredit and, with his Grameen Bank, won the 2006 Nobel Peace Prize, has developed a new dimension for capitalism which he calls &#8220;social business.&#8221; The social business model has been adopted by corporations, entrepreneurs, and social activists across the globe. Its goal is to create self-supporting, viable commercial enterprises that generate economic growth as they produce goods and services to fulfill human needs. In  Building Social Business , Yunus shows how social business can be put into practice and explains why it holds the potential to redeem the failed promise of free-market enterprise.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/building-social-business-the-new-kind-of-capitalism-that-serves-humanitys-most-pressing-needs-muhammad-yunus-abridged/">Building Social Business : The New Kind of Capitalism that Serves Humanity&#8217;s Most Pressing Needs &#8211; Muhammad Yunus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investing with Impact : Why Finance is a Force for Good &#8211; Jeremy Balkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Investing with Impact: Why Finance Is a Force for Good outlines the roadmap to reinvigorating a skeptical public and demoralized financial services industry by making the case that, contrary to popular misconception, finance is not the cause of the world&#8217;s problems; in fact, it can provide the solution. Author Jeremy Balkin presents the case that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/">Investing with Impact : Why Finance is a Force for Good &#8211; Jeremy Balkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investing with Impact: Why Finance Is a Force for Good outlines the roadmap to reinvigorating a skeptical public and demoralized financial services industry by making the case that, contrary to popular misconception, finance is not the cause of the world&#8217;s problems; in fact, it can provide the solution. Author Jeremy Balkin presents the case that the finance industry can improve the state of the world by positively influencing the allocation of capital.  Investing With Impact explains the methodology of Balkin&#8217;s 6 E Paradigm, opening the toolbox to this revolutionary framework for the first time. In so doing, Balkin expands the impact investment universe, enabling mainstream capital to flow where opportunities generate positive investment returns and have demonstrable social impact.  Described by the Huffington Post as the &#8220;Anti-Wolf of Wall Street,&#8221; Balkin is challenging the status quo on Wall Street by leading the intellectual debate embracing the $1 trillion frontier impact investment market opportunity. The book demonstrates conclusively that, if we can change the culture in finance, we can change the world for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/">Investing with Impact : Why Finance is a Force for Good &#8211; Jeremy Balkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good People : The Only Leadership Decision That Really Matters &#8211; Anthony Tjan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-people-the-only-leadership-decision-that-really-matters-anthony-tjan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-people-the-only-leadership-decision-that-really-matters-anthony-tjan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Good people are your organization&#8217;s most critical asset. But what does it really mean to be good? In this groundbreaking book, Anthony Tjan leads a movement to change the way we think about goodness, redefining it as a lifelong, proactive commitment that can be exercised, honed and taught. Packed with practical advice, Good People features [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-people-the-only-leadership-decision-that-really-matters-anthony-tjan-abridged/">Good People : The Only Leadership Decision That Really Matters &#8211; Anthony Tjan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Good people are your organization&#8217;s most critical asset. But what does it really mean to be good?    </p>
<p>                    In this groundbreaking book, Anthony Tjan leads a movement to change the way we think about goodness, redefining it as a lifelong, proactive commitment that can be exercised, honed and taught.    </p>
<p>                    Packed with practical advice, Good People features interviews with extraordinary innovators, executives, artists, academics, and role models from all walks of life, including Harvard Business School dean Nitin Nohria, Supreme Court justice Sonia Sotomayor and the late master jazz musician Clark Terry.    </p>
<p>                    Establishing a new language and framework you can use to evaluate, develop and lead with goodness, Anthony Tjan explains why choosing to work with good people is the only business decision that really matters.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An important book reminding us of the need for leadership to move beyond the individual to the culture of an organization&#8217; Dominic Barton, managing director of McKinsey &#038; Co</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-people-the-only-leadership-decision-that-really-matters-anthony-tjan-abridged/">Good People : The Only Leadership Decision That Really Matters &#8211; Anthony Tjan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Intelligent Disobedience: Doing Right When What You&#8217;re Told to Do Is Wrong &#8211; Ira Chaleff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/intelligent-disobedience-doing-right-when-what-youre-told-to-do-is-wrong-ira-chaleff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/intelligent-disobedience-doing-right-when-what-youre-told-to-do-is-wrong-ira-chaleff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When It&#8217;s Smart to Say No Nearly every week we read about a tragedy or scandal that could have been prevented if individuals had said no to ill-advised or illegitimate orders. In this timely book, Ira Chaleff explores when and how to disobey inappropriate orders, reduce unacceptable risk, and find better ways to achieve legitimate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/intelligent-disobedience-doing-right-when-what-youre-told-to-do-is-wrong-ira-chaleff-abridged/">Intelligent Disobedience: Doing Right When What You&#8217;re Told to Do Is Wrong &#8211; Ira Chaleff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When It&#8217;s Smart to Say No     </p>
<p>                     Nearly every week we read about a tragedy or scandal that could have been prevented if individuals had said no to ill-advised or illegitimate orders. In this timely book, Ira Chaleff explores when and how to disobey inappropriate orders, reduce unacceptable risk, and find better ways to achieve legitimate goals.     </p>
<p>                     The inspiration for the book, and its title, comes from the concept of intelligent disobedience used in guide dog training. Guide dogs must recognize and resist a command that would put their human and themselves at risk and identify safer options for achieving the goal. This is precisely what Chaleff helps humans do. Using both deeply disturbing and uplifting examples, as well as critical but largely forgotten research, he shows how to create a culture where, rather than &#8220;just following orders,&#8221; people hold themselves accountable to do the right thing, always.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/intelligent-disobedience-doing-right-when-what-youre-told-to-do-is-wrong-ira-chaleff-abridged/">Intelligent Disobedience: Doing Right When What You&#8217;re Told to Do Is Wrong &#8211; Ira Chaleff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conscious Business : How to Build Value Through Value &#8211; Fred Kofman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/conscious-business-how-to-build-value-through-value-fred-kofman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/conscious-business-how-to-build-value-through-value-fred-kofman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Consciousness is the main source of organizational greatness. Conscious business, explains Fred Kofman, means finding your passion and expressing your essential values through your work. A conscious business seeks to promote the intelligent pursuit of happiness in all its stakeholders. It produces sustainable, exceptional performance through the solidarity of its community and the dignity of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conscious-business-how-to-build-value-through-value-fred-kofman-abridged/">Conscious Business : How to Build Value Through Value &#8211; Fred Kofman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Consciousness is the main source of organizational greatness. Conscious business, explains Fred Kofman, means finding your passion and expressing your essential values through your work. A conscious business seeks to promote the intelligent pursuit of happiness in all its stakeholders. It produces sustainable, exceptional performance through the solidarity of its community and the dignity of each member.    </p>
<p>                    Conscious Business presents breakthrough techniques to help you achieve:    </p>
<p>                    Unconditional responsibility-how to become the main character of your life<br />
                    * Unflinching integrity-how to succeed beyond success<br />
                    * Authentic communication-how to speak your truth, and elicit others&#8217; truths<br />
                    * Impeccable commitments-how to coordinate actions with accountability<br />
                    * Right leadership-how being, rather than doing, is the ultimate source of excellence<br />
                    A conscious business fosters personal fulfillment in the individuals, mutual respect in the community, and success in the organization, teaches Fred Kofman. Conscious Business is the definitive resource for achieving what really matters in the workplace and beyond.    </p>
<p>                    Winner of the 2009 Nautilus Award</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conscious-business-how-to-build-value-through-value-fred-kofman-abridged/">Conscious Business : How to Build Value Through Value &#8211; Fred Kofman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tribes : We need you to lead us &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tribes-we-need-you-to-lead-us-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tribes-we-need-you-to-lead-us-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this fascinating book, Seth Godin argues that now, for the first time, everyone has an opportunity to start a movement &#8211; to bring together a tribe of like-minded people and do amazing things. There are tribes everywhere, all of them hungry for connection, meaning and change. And yet, too many people ignore the opportunity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tribes-we-need-you-to-lead-us-seth-godin-abridged/">Tribes : We need you to lead us &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this fascinating book, Seth Godin argues that now, for the first time, everyone has an opportunity to start a movement &#8211; to bring together a tribe of like-minded people and do amazing things. There are tribes everywhere, all of them hungry for connection, meaning and change. And yet, too many people ignore the opportunity to lead, because they are &#8220;sheepwalking&#8221; their way through their lives and work, too afraid to question whether their compliance is doing them (or their company) any good. This book is for those who don&#8217;t want to be sheep and instead have a desire to do fresh and exciting work. If you have a passion for what you want to do and the drive to make it happen, there is a tribe of fellow employees, or customers, or investors, or readers, just waiting for you to connect them with each other and lead them where they want to go.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tribes-we-need-you-to-lead-us-seth-godin-abridged/">Tribes : We need you to lead us &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Are the Nerds : The Birth and Tumultuous Life of REDDIT, the Internet&#8217;s Culture Laboratory &#8211; Christine Lagorio-Chafkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A gripping read&#8217; Adam Grant, bestselling author of Originals Reddit hails itself as &#8216;the front page of the Internet&#8217;. It&#8217;s the sixth most-visited website in the world &#8211; and yet, millions have no idea what it is. They should be paying attention. This definitive account of the birth and life of Reddit is perfect for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/">We Are the Nerds : The Birth and Tumultuous Life of REDDIT, the Internet&#8217;s Culture Laboratory &#8211; Christine Lagorio-Chafkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A gripping read&#8217; Adam Grant, bestselling author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    Reddit hails itself as &#8216;the front page of the Internet&#8217;. It&#8217;s the sixth most-visited website in the world &#8211; and yet, millions have no idea what it is. They should be paying attention.    </p>
<p>                    This definitive account of the birth and life of Reddit is perfect for readers of The Everything Store, Googled and The Facebook Effect.    </p>
<p>                    We Are the Nerds takes readers inside this captivating, maddening enterprise, whose army of obsessed users have been credited with everything from solving crimes and spurring millions in charitable donations to seeding alt-right fury and even landing Donald Trump in the White House. Reddit has become a mirror of the Internet itself: It has dark trenches, shiny memes, malicious trolls, and a heart-warming ability to connect people across cultures, oceans, and ideological divides.    </p>
<p>                    This is the gripping story of how Reddit&#8217;s founders, Steve Huffman and Alexis Ohanian, transformed themselves from student video-gamers into Silicon Valley millionaires as they turned their creation into an icon of the digital age. But the journey was often fraught. Reporting on Reddit for more than six years, conducting hundreds of interviews and gaining exclusive access to its founders, Christine Lagorio-Chafkin has written the definitive account of the birth and life of Reddit. Packed with revelatory details about its biggest triumphs and controversies, this inside look at Reddit includes fresh insights on the relationship between Huffman and Ohanian, staff turmoil, the tragic life of Aaron Swartz, and Reddit&#8217;s struggle to become profitable.    </p>
<p>                    In a time when we are increasingly concerned about privacy and manipulation on social platforms, We Are the Nerds reveals Reddit&#8217;s central role in the dissemination of culture and information in history&#8217;s first fully digital century. Rigorously reported and highly entertaining, We Are the Nerds explores how this unique platform has changed the way we all communicate today.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR THE BOOK:    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Incisive, witty and brilliantly written&#8217; &#8211; Emily Chang, bestselling author of Brotopia    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A triumph &#8211; a business book that reads like a page-turning novel&#8217; &#8211; James Ledbetter, author of One Nation Under Gold    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The best, grittiest, most accurate book yet about what it&#8217;s like to build a startup and a community from scratch&#8217; &#8211; John Zeratsky, bestselling author of Sprint and Make Time    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A gripping, entertaining book that is a must-read for every entrepreneur&#8217; &#8211; Daymond John, bestselling author of Rise and Grind    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Too many books on tech feel like they have been Googled together; Lagorio-Chafkin&#8217;s is rich in original reportage&#8217; &#8211; TLS</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/">We Are the Nerds : The Birth and Tumultuous Life of REDDIT, the Internet&#8217;s Culture Laboratory &#8211; Christine Lagorio-Chafkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nice Girls Don&#8217;t Get The Corner Office : Unconscious Mistakes Women Make That Sabotage Their Careers &#8211; Lois P. Frankel, PhD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/nice-girls-dont-get-the-corner-office-unconscious-mistakes-women-make-that-sabotage-their-careers-lois-p-frankel-phd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/nice-girls-dont-get-the-corner-office-unconscious-mistakes-women-make-that-sabotage-their-careers-lois-p-frankel-phd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller, which has become a must-have for women in business, is now revised and updated in celebration of its 10th anniversary. Internationally recognized executive coach Dr. Lois P. Frankel teacher women how to eliminate unconscious mistakes that could be holding them back, and gives invaluable coaching tips that can easily be [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nice-girls-dont-get-the-corner-office-unconscious-mistakes-women-make-that-sabotage-their-careers-lois-p-frankel-phd-abridged/">Nice Girls Don&#8217;t Get The Corner Office : Unconscious Mistakes Women Make That Sabotage Their Careers &#8211; Lois P. Frankel, PhD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller, which has become a must-have for women in business, is now revised and updated in celebration of its 10th anniversary.    </p>
<p>                    Internationally recognized executive coach Dr. Lois P. Frankel teacher women how to eliminate unconscious mistakes that could be holding them back, and gives invaluable coaching tips that can easily be incorporated into social and business skills. The results are career opportunities women never thought possible and the power and know-how to occupy the corner office! Stop making &#8220;nice girl&#8221; mistakes such as:<br />
                    -Mistake #13: Avoiding office politics<br />
                    -Mistake #21: Multi-tasking<br />
                    -Mistake #54: Failure to negotiate<br />
                    -Mistake #82: Asking permission<br />
                    -Mistake #100: Smiling inappropriately.     </p>
<p>                    These and other behaviors are why NICE GIRLS DON&#8217;T GET THE CORNER OFFICE.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nice-girls-dont-get-the-corner-office-unconscious-mistakes-women-make-that-sabotage-their-careers-lois-p-frankel-phd-abridged/">Nice Girls Don&#8217;t Get The Corner Office : Unconscious Mistakes Women Make That Sabotage Their Careers &#8211; Lois P. Frankel, PhD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Business of Good : Social Entrepreneurship and the New Bottom Line &#8211; Jason Haber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-business-of-good-social-entrepreneurship-and-the-new-bottom-line-jason-haber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-profitmaking Organizations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-business-of-good-social-entrepreneurship-and-the-new-bottom-line-jason-haber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Business of Good narrates the story behind social entrepreneurship as told by the individuals compelled to create a change in the world&#8211;not just another business. Serial and social entrepreneur Jason Haber intertwines case studies and anecdotes that show how social entrepreneurship is creating jobs, growing the economy, and ultimately changing the world. From Main [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-business-of-good-social-entrepreneurship-and-the-new-bottom-line-jason-haber-abridged/">The Business of Good : Social Entrepreneurship and the New Bottom Line &#8211; Jason Haber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Business of Good narrates the story behind social entrepreneurship as told by the individuals compelled to create a change in the world&#8211;not just another business. Serial and social entrepreneur Jason Haber intertwines case studies and anecdotes that show how social entrepreneurship is creating jobs, growing the economy, and ultimately changing the world.  From Main Street to Wall Street, today&#8217;s social entrepreneurs are rebooting capitalism, challenging the charity industrial complex, and disrupting business models. Haber envelops the reader in the foundation of social entrepreneurship, from Benjamin Franklin to what he calls The Great Convergence, the turn-of-the-millennium zeitgeist shift which provided the fuel for social entrepreneurship&#8217;s surge to the forefront of business.  Haber shares the stories of inspiring young people that are disrupting established norms and changing the world. This is a must read book for Millennials, business executives, nonprofits, doers, and dreamers&#8211;The Business of Good brings a much-needed fresh and innovative look at social entrepreneurship.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-business-of-good-social-entrepreneurship-and-the-new-bottom-line-jason-haber-abridged/">The Business of Good : Social Entrepreneurship and the New Bottom Line &#8211; Jason Haber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smarter Screen : What Your Business Can Learn from the Way Consumers Think Online &#8211; Shlomo Benartzi, Jonah Lehrer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The typical office worker now spends the majority of their waking hours staring at a screen. In the 21st century, every business is a digital business, which is why it&#8217;s so critical to understand how we think and behave online. Acclaimed behavioural economist Shlomo Benartzi has teamed up with science writer Jonah Lehrer to reveal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/">The Smarter Screen : What Your Business Can Learn from the Way Consumers Think Online &#8211; Shlomo Benartzi, Jonah Lehrer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The typical office worker now spends the majority of their waking hours staring at a screen. In the 21st century, every business is a digital business, which is why it&#8217;s so critical to understand how we think and behave online.    </p>
<p>                    Acclaimed behavioural economist Shlomo Benartzi has teamed up with science writer Jonah Lehrer to reveal a toolkit of cues and nudges for the digital age. Using provocative case-studies and engaging reader exercises, Benartzi shows how businesses can update their nudges to help consumers make better decisions on screens. Up-to-the-minute research will help optimise your business&#8217;s online presence, from designing a webshop that helps your customers find what they are looking for, to laying out your website so that it both attracts and holds attention.    </p>
<p>                    This book will help you transform the challenges of the digital world into powerful new opportunities that will drive your success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/">The Smarter Screen : What Your Business Can Learn from the Way Consumers Think Online &#8211; Shlomo Benartzi, Jonah Lehrer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutionary Groups & Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. To manage the risks and spread the benefits, we have to act now, and in the interest of stakeholders everywhere&#8217; Andrew McAfee, Co-Founder, MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy, MIT, USA    </p>
<p>                    We are on the brink of the Fourth Industrial Revolution. And this one will be unlike any other in human history.    </p>
<p>                    Characterized by new technologies fusing the physical, digital and biological worlds, the Fourth Industrial Revolution will impact all disciplines, economies and industries &#8211; and it will do so at an unprecedented rate. World Economic Forum data predicts that by 2025 we will see: commercial use of nanomaterials 200 times stronger than steel and a million times thinner than human hair; the first transplant of a 3D-printed liver; 10% of all cars on US roads being driverless; and much more besides.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Industrial Revolution, Schwab outlines the key technologies driving this revolution, discusses the major impacts on governments, businesses, civil society and individuals, and offers bold ideas for what can be done to shape a better future for all.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The technologies of the Fourth Industrial Revolution are extraordinary. Leadership has to be equally extraordinary to manage the complexities of systemic change&#8217; Eric Schmidt, Technical Advisor, Alphabet, USA</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Truth : 13 Reasons To Question Everything You Are Told &#8211; Hector Macdonald (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/truth-13-reasons-to-question-everything-you-are-told-hector-macdonald-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/truth-13-reasons-to-question-everything-you-are-told-hector-macdonald-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>_________________ &#8216;Macdonald zeros in on the slipperiness of factuality, offering an array of case studies from the worlds of history, commerce and &#8211; of course &#8211; politics.&#8217; New York Times True or false? It&#8217;s rarely that simple. There is always more than one truth in every story. Eating meat is nutritious but it&#8217;s also damaging [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/truth-13-reasons-to-question-everything-you-are-told-hector-macdonald-abridged/">Truth : 13 Reasons To Question Everything You Are Told &#8211; Hector Macdonald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>_________________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Macdonald zeros in on the slipperiness of factuality, offering an array of case studies from the worlds of history, commerce and &#8211; of course &#8211; politics.&#8217; New York Times     </p>
<p>                    True or false?  It&#8217;s rarely that simple.    </p>
<p>                    There is always more than one truth in every story.  Eating meat is nutritious but it&#8217;s also damaging to the environment.  The Internet disseminates knowledge but it also spreads hatred.  As communicators, we select the truths that are most useful to our agenda.    </p>
<p>                    We can select truths constructively to inspire nations, encourage children, and drive progressive change.  Or we can select truths that give a false impression of reality, misleading people without actually lying.  Others can do the same, motivating or deceiving us with the truth.      </p>
<p>                    In Truth, communications strategy expert Hector Macdonald explores how truth is used and abused in politics, business, the media and everyday life.   Combining great storytelling with practical takeaways and a litany of fascinating, funny and insightful case studies, Truth is a chilling and engaging read about how profoundly our mindsets and actions are influenced by the truths that those around us choose to tell.    </p>
<p>                    For fans of Factfulness, A Field Guide to Lies and Statistics and The Art of Thinking Clearly, a fascinating dive into the many ways in which &#8216;competing truths&#8217; shape our opinions, behaviours and beliefs.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/truth-13-reasons-to-question-everything-you-are-told-hector-macdonald-abridged/">Truth : 13 Reasons To Question Everything You Are Told &#8211; Hector Macdonald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Linchpin : Are You Indispensable? How to drive your career and create a remarkable future &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/linchpin-are-you-indispensable-how-to-drive-your-career-and-create-a-remarkable-future-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/linchpin-are-you-indispensable-how-to-drive-your-career-and-create-a-remarkable-future-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this compelling, accessible and purpose-filled book bestselling business author Seth Godin shows how you have the potential to make a big difference-and make yourself indispensable in the process-wherever you are. Why are some people easily outsourced, downsized, or freelanced into obscurity, while others have their pick of opportunities? In his most powerful book yet, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/linchpin-are-you-indispensable-how-to-drive-your-career-and-create-a-remarkable-future-seth-godin-abridged/">Linchpin : Are You Indispensable? How to drive your career and create a remarkable future &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this compelling, accessible and purpose-filled book bestselling business author Seth Godin shows how you have the potential to make a big difference-and make yourself indispensable in the process-wherever you are.    </p>
<p>                    Why are some people easily outsourced, downsized, or freelanced into obscurity, while others have their pick of opportunities? In his most powerful book yet, Seth Godin argues that it&#8217;s more essential than ever to become indispensable &#8211; to become a linchpin. Linchpins are the essential building blocks of great organizations: they invent, lead (regardless of title), connect others, make things happen, and create order out of chaos. They love their work and pour their best selves into it and turn each day into a kind of art &#8211; and, in today&#8217;s world, they get the best jobs and the most freedom.    </p>
<p>                    Godin shows that the key to being indispensable is overcoming the fears that hold most of us back. If you have you ever found a shortcut that others missed, seen a new way to resolve a conflict, or made a connection with someone others couldn&#8217;t reach, then you have what it takes to become indispensable. It&#8217;s time to stop complying with the system and draw your own map.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/linchpin-are-you-indispensable-how-to-drive-your-career-and-create-a-remarkable-future-seth-godin-abridged/">Linchpin : Are You Indispensable? How to drive your career and create a remarkable future &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Outward Mindset &#8211; Arbinger Institute (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-outward-mindset-arbinger-institute-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-outward-mindset-arbinger-institute-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The new edition of an international bestseller helps individuals and organizations shift to a new mindset that will improve performance, spark collaboration, accelerate innovation, and make your life and the lives of everyone around you better. Without even being aware of it, many of us operate from an inward mindset, a single-minded focus on our [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-outward-mindset-arbinger-institute-abridged/">The Outward Mindset &#8211; Arbinger Institute (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The new edition of an international bestseller helps individuals and organizations shift to a new mindset that will improve performance, spark collaboration, accelerate innovation, and make your life and the lives of everyone around you better.     </p>
<p>                     Without even being aware of it, many of us operate from an inward mindset, a single-minded focus on our own goals and objectives. This book points out the many ways, some quite subtle and deceptive, that this mindset invites tension and conflict. But incredible things happen when people switch to an outward mindset. They intuitively understand what coworkers, colleagues, family, and friends need to be successful and happy. Their organizations thrive, and astonishingly, by focusing on others they become happier and more successful themselves! This new mindset brings about deep and far-reaching changes.     </p>
<p>                     The Outward Mindset presents compelling true stories to illustrate the gaps that individuals and organizations typically experience between their actual inward mindsets and their needed outward mindsets. And it provides simple yet profound guidance and tools to help bridge this mindset gap. This new edition includes a new preface, updated case studies, and new material covering Arbinger&#8217;s latest research on mindsets. In the long run, changing negative behavior without changing one&#8217;s mindset doesn&#8217;t last&#8211;the old behaviors always reassert themselves. But changing the mindset that causes the behavior changes everything.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-outward-mindset-arbinger-institute-abridged/">The Outward Mindset &#8211; Arbinger Institute (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everybody Matters : The Extraordinary Power of Caring for Your People Like Family &#8211; Bob Chapman, Raj Sisodia (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everybody-matters-the-extraordinary-power-of-caring-for-your-people-like-family-bob-chapman-raj-sisodia-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everybody-matters-the-extraordinary-power-of-caring-for-your-people-like-family-bob-chapman-raj-sisodia-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re ready for a new way of doing business, this is the book for you&#8217; Daniel H. Pink, author of To Sell Is Human and Drive &#8216;Bob Chapman is on a mission to change the way businesses treat their employees&#8217; Inc.magazine Do you want to boost the morale, loyalty, creativity and performance of your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-matters-the-extraordinary-power-of-caring-for-your-people-like-family-bob-chapman-raj-sisodia-abridged/">Everybody Matters : The Extraordinary Power of Caring for Your People Like Family &#8211; Bob Chapman, Raj Sisodia (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re ready for a new way of doing business, this is the book for you&#8217; Daniel H. Pink, author of To Sell Is Human and Drive    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Bob Chapman is on a mission to change the way businesses treat their employees&#8217; Inc.magazine     </p>
<p>                    Do you want to boost the morale, loyalty, creativity and performance of your employees?     </p>
<p>                    In Everybody Matters, CEO Bob Chapman and bestselling author Raj Sisodia challenge traditional thinking about how to run a business and show you how to lead your company so that everyone feels valued.      </p>
<p>                     As CEO of Barry-Wehmiller, Bob Chapman has pioneered a dramatically different approach to leadership that has created a high performing and happy culture. At Barry-Wehmiller, every single person matters, just like in a family. That&#8217;s not a cliche; it&#8217;s the bedrock of the company&#8217;s success.    </p>
<p>                     In Everybody Matters, Chapman shows how any organization can stop viewing its employees are simply func tions, to be moved around, &#8216;managed&#8217; with carrots and sticks, or discarded at will. By doing so, disengaged workers begin to share their gifts and talents toward a shared future. Uninspired workers stop feeling that their jobs have no meaning. And everyone stops counting the minutes until it&#8217;s time to go home.    </p>
<p>                     Everybody Matters provides clear steps to transform your own workplace, whether you lead two or two hundred thousand people.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-matters-the-extraordinary-power-of-caring-for-your-people-like-family-bob-chapman-raj-sisodia-abridged/">Everybody Matters : The Extraordinary Power of Caring for Your People Like Family &#8211; Bob Chapman, Raj Sisodia (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
