<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Elections &amp; Referenda Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/elections-referenda/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/elections-referenda/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Elections &amp; Referenda Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/elections-referenda/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</title>
		<link>/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019 Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump. The 2016 election was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019</p>
<p>                    Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump.</p>
<p>                    The 2016 election was a watershed for the United States. But, as Tim Alberta explains in American Carnage, to understand Trump&#8217;s victory is to view him not as the creator of this era of polarization and bruising partisanship, but rather as its most manifest consequence.</p>
<p>                    American Carnage is the story of a president&#8217;s rise based on a country&#8217;s evolution and a party&#8217;s collapse. As George W. Bush left office with record-low approval ratings and Barack Obama led a Democratic takeover of Washington, Republicans faced a moment of reckoning: They had no vision, no generation of new leaders, and no energy in the party&#8217;s base. Yet Obama&#8217;s forceful pursuit of his progressive agenda, coupled with the nation&#8217;s rapidly changing cultural and demographic landscape, lit a fire under the right, returning Republicans to power and inviting a bloody struggle for the party&#8217;s identity in the post-Bush era. The factions that emerged-one led by absolutists like Jim Jordan and Ted Cruz, the other led by pragmatists like John Boehner and Mitch McConnell-engaged in a series of devastating internecine clashes and attempted coups for control. With the GOP&#8217;s internal fissures rendering it legislatively impotent, and that impotence fueling a growing resentment toward the political class and its institutions, the stage was set for an outsider to crash the party. When Trump descended a gilded escalator to announce his run in the summer of 2015, the candidate had met the moment.</p>
<p>                    Only by viewing Trump as the culmination of a decade-long civil war inside the Republican Party-and of the parallel sense of cultural, socioeconomic, and technological disruption during that period-can we appreciate how he won the White House and consider the fundamental questions at the center of America&#8217;s current turmoil. How did a party obsessed with the national debt vote for trillion-dollar deficits and record-setting spending increases? How did the party of compassionate conservatism become the party of Muslim bans and walls? How did the party of family values elect a thrice-divorced philanderer? And, most important, how long can such a party survive?</p>
<p>                     Loaded with exclusive reporting and based off hundreds of interviews-including with key players such as President Trump, Paul Ryan, Ted Cruz, John Boehner, Mitch McConnell, Jim DeMint, and Reince Priebus, and many others-American Carnage takes us behind the scenes of this tumultuous period as we&#8217;ve never seen it before and establishes Tim Alberta as the premier chronicler of this political era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Revolt : Inside the Populist Coalition Reshaping American Politics &#8211; Salena Zito</title>
		<link>/the-great-revolt-inside-the-populist-coalition-reshaping-american-politics-salena-zito/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-revolt-inside-the-populist-coalition-reshaping-american-politics-salena-zito/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A CNN political analyst and a Republican strategist reframe the discussion of the &#8220;Trump voter&#8221; to answer the question, What&#8217;s next? NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY FOREIGN AFFAIRS &#8211; &#8220;Unlike most retellings of the 2016 election, The Great Revolt provides a cohesive, non-wild-eyed argument about where the Republican Party could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-revolt-inside-the-populist-coalition-reshaping-american-politics-salena-zito/">The Great Revolt : Inside the Populist Coalition Reshaping American Politics &#8211; Salena Zito</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A CNN political analyst and a Republican strategist reframe the discussion of the &#8220;Trump voter&#8221; to answer the question, What&#8217;s next?</p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY FOREIGN AFFAIRS &#8211; &#8220;Unlike most retellings of the 2016 election, The Great Revolt provides a cohesive, non-wild-eyed argument about where the Republican Party could be headed.&#8221;&#8211;The Atlantic </p>
<p>                    Political experts were wrong about the 2016 election and they continue to blow it, predicting the coming demise of the president without pausing to consider the durability of the winds that swept him into office. </p>
<p>                    Salena Zito and Brad Todd have traveled over 27,000 miles of country roads to interview more than three hundred Trump voters in ten swing counties. What emerges is a portrait of a group of citizens who span job descriptions, income brackets, education levels, and party allegiances, united by their desire to be part of a movement larger than themselves. They want to put pragmatism before ideology and localism before globalism, and demand the respect they deserve from Washington. </p>
<p>                    The 2016 election signaled a realignment in American politics that will outlast any one president. Zito and Todd reframe the discussion of the &#8220;Trump voter&#8221; to answer the question, What&#8217;s next?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-revolt-inside-the-populist-coalition-reshaping-american-politics-salena-zito/">The Great Revolt : Inside the Populist Coalition Reshaping American Politics &#8211; Salena Zito</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dark Money : how a secretive group of billionaires is trying to buy political control in the US &#8211; Jane Mayer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A LITHUB BOOK OF THE DECADE. The US is one of the largest democracies in the world &#8211; or is it? America is experiencing an age of profound economic inequality. Employee protections have been decimated, and state welfare is virtually non-existent, while hedge fund billionaires are grossly under-taxed and big businesses make astounding profits at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/">Dark Money : how a secretive group of billionaires is trying to buy political control in the US &#8211; Jane Mayer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A LITHUB BOOK OF THE DECADE.    </p>
<p>                    The US is one of the largest democracies in the world &#8211; or is it?    </p>
<p>                    America is experiencing an age of profound economic inequality. Employee protections have been decimated, and state welfare is virtually non-existent, while hedge fund billionaires are grossly under-taxed and big businesses make astounding profits at the expense of the environment and of their workers.    </p>
<p>                    How did this come about, and who were the driving forces behind it?    </p>
<p>                    In this powerful and meticulously researched work of investigative journalism, New Yorker staff writer Jane Mayer exposes the network of billionaires trying to buy the US electoral system &#8211; and succeeding. Led by libertarian industrialists the Koch brothers, they believe that taxes are a form of tyranny and that government oversight of business is an assault on freedom. Together, they have spent hundreds of millions of dollars influencing politicians and voters, and hijacking American democracy for their own ends.    </p>
<p>                    Dark Money brilliantly illuminates a shady corner of US politics. It is essential reading for anybody interested in the future of democracy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/">Dark Money : how a secretive group of billionaires is trying to buy political control in the US &#8211; Jane Mayer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fight to Vote &#8211; Michael Waldman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fight-to-vote-michael-waldman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fight-to-vote-michael-waldman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Praised by the late John Lewis, this is the seminal book about the long and ongoing struggle to win voting rights for all citizens by the president of The Brennan Center, the leading organization on voter rights and election security, now newly revised to describe today&#8217;s intense fights over voting. As Rep. Lewis said, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fight-to-vote-michael-waldman-abridged/">The Fight to Vote &#8211; Michael Waldman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Praised by the late John Lewis, this is the seminal book about the long and ongoing struggle to win voting rights for all citizens by the president of The Brennan Center, the leading organization on voter rights and election security, now newly revised to describe today&#8217;s intense fights over voting.     </p>
<p>                    As Rep. Lewis said, and recent events in state legislatures across the country demonstrate, the struggle for the right to vote is not over. In this &#8220;important and powerful&#8221; (Linda Greenhouse, former New York Times Supreme Court correspondent) book Michael Waldman describes the long struggle to extend the right to vote to all Americans. From the writing of the Constitution, and at every step along the way, as disenfranchised Americans sought this right, others have fought to stop them. Waldman traces this history from the Founders&#8217; debates to today&#8217;s many restrictions: gerrymandering; voter ID laws; the flood of dark money released by conservative organizations; and the concerted effort in many state legislatures after the 2020 election to enact new limitations on voting.     </p>
<p>                    Despite the pandemic, the 2020 election had the highest turnout since 1900. In this updated edition, Waldman describes the nationwide effort that made this possible. He offers new insights into how Donald Trump&#8217;s false claims of fraud&#8211;&#8220;the Big Lie&#8221;&#8211;led to the January 6 insurrection and the fights over voting laws that followed one of the most dramatic chapters in the story of American democracy.     </p>
<p>                    As Waldman shows, this fight, sometimes vicious, has always been at the center of American politics because it determines the outcome of the struggle for power. The Fight to Vote is &#8220;an engaging, concise history&#8230;offering many useful reforms that advocates on both sides of the aisle should consider&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fight-to-vote-michael-waldman-abridged/">The Fight to Vote &#8211; Michael Waldman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Myth of the Rational Voter : Why Democracies Choose Bad Policies &#8211; New Edition &#8211; Bryan Caplan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-myth-of-the-rational-voter-why-democracies-choose-bad-policies-new-edition-bryan-caplan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-myth-of-the-rational-voter-why-democracies-choose-bad-policies-new-edition-bryan-caplan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The greatest obstacle to sound economic policy is not entrenched special interests or rampant lobbying, but the popular misconceptions, irrational beliefs, and personal biases held by ordinary voters. This is economist Bryan Caplan&#8217;s sobering assessment in this provocative and eye-opening book. Caplan argues that voters continually elect politicians who either share their biases or else [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myth-of-the-rational-voter-why-democracies-choose-bad-policies-new-edition-bryan-caplan-abridged/">The Myth of the Rational Voter : Why Democracies Choose Bad Policies &#8211; New Edition &#8211; Bryan Caplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The greatest obstacle to sound economic policy is not entrenched special interests or rampant lobbying, but the popular misconceptions, irrational beliefs, and personal biases held by ordinary voters. This is economist Bryan Caplan&#8217;s sobering assessment in this provocative and eye-opening book. Caplan argues that voters continually elect politicians who either share their biases or else pretend to, resulting in bad policies winning again and again by popular demand. Boldly calling into question our most basic assumptions about American politics, Caplan contends that democracy fails precisely because it does what voters want. Through an analysis of Americans&#8217; voting behavior and opinions on a range of economic issues, he makes the convincing case that noneconomists suffer from four prevailing biases: they underestimate the wisdom of the market mechanism, distrust foreigners, undervalue the benefits of conserving labor, and pessimistically believe the economy is going from bad to worse.<br />
                    Caplan lays out several bold ways to make democratic government work better&#8211;for example, urging economic educators to focus on correcting popular misconceptions and recommending that democracies do less and let markets take up the slack. The Myth of the Rational Voter takes an unflinching look at how people who vote under the influence of false beliefs ultimately end up with government that delivers lousy results. With the upcoming presidential election season drawing nearer, this thought-provoking book is sure to spark a long-overdue reappraisal of our elective system.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myth-of-the-rational-voter-why-democracies-choose-bad-policies-new-edition-bryan-caplan-abridged/">The Myth of the Rational Voter : Why Democracies Choose Bad Policies &#8211; New Edition &#8211; Bryan Caplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chasing Hillary : On the Trail of the First Woman President Who Wasn&#8217;T &#8211; Amy Chozick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chasing-hillary-on-the-trail-of-the-first-woman-president-who-wasnt-amy-chozick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chasing-hillary-on-the-trail-of-the-first-woman-president-who-wasnt-amy-chozick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hillary Clinton dominated Amy Chozick&#8217;s life for more than a decade. Here, she tells the inside story of Clinton&#8217;s pursuit of the US presidency in a campaign book like no other. &#8216;A breathtaking, page-turning masterpiece&#8217; Mary Karr A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER Amy Chozick&#8217;s assignments, covering Clinton&#8217;s imploding 2008 campaign and then her front-row seat [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chasing-hillary-on-the-trail-of-the-first-woman-president-who-wasnt-amy-chozick-abridged/">Chasing Hillary : On the Trail of the First Woman President Who Wasn&#8217;T &#8211; Amy Chozick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hillary Clinton dominated Amy Chozick&#8217;s life for more than a decade. Here, she tells the inside story of Clinton&#8217;s pursuit of the US presidency in a campaign book like no other.    </p>
<p>                              &#8216;A breathtaking, page-turning masterpiece&#8217; Mary Karr<br />
                              A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                              Amy Chozick&#8217;s assignments, covering Clinton&#8217;s imploding 2008 campaign and then her front-row seat to the 2016 election on &#8216;The Hillary Beat,&#8217; set off a years-long journey in which the formative years of Chozick&#8217;s life became, both personally and professionally, intrinsically intertwined with Clinton&#8217;s presidential ambitions. As Clinton tried, and twice failed, to shatter &#8216;that highest, hardest glass ceiling,&#8217; Chozick was trying, with various fits and starts, to scale the highest echelons of American journalism.    </p>
<p>                              In this rollicking, hilarious narrative, Chozick takes us through the high- and low-lights of the most noxious and dramatic presidential election in history. Chozick&#8217;s candour and clear-eyed perspective &#8211; from her seat on the Hillary bus and reporting from inside the campaign&#8217;s headquarters to her run-ins with Donald J. Trump &#8211; provide fresh intrigue and insights into the story we think we all know.    </p>
<p>                              But Chasing Hillary is also the unusually personal and moving memoir of how Chozick came to understand Clinton not as a political animal, but as a complete, complex person, full of contradictions and forged in the crucible of many earlier battles. In the process, Chozick develops an intimate understanding of what drives Clinton, how she accomplished what no woman had before, and why she ultimately failed.    </p>
<p>                              The results also make Chozick question everything she&#8217;d worked so hard for in the first place. Political journalism had failed. The elite world Chozick had tried for years to fit in with had been rebuffed. The less qualified, bombastic man had triumphed (as they always seem to do), and Clinton had retreated to the woods, finally showing the real person Chozick had spent years hoping to see. Illuminating, poignant, laugh-out-loud funny, Chasing Hillary is a campaign book unlike any other that reads like a fast-moving political novel.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chasing-hillary-on-the-trail-of-the-first-woman-president-who-wasnt-amy-chozick-abridged/">Chasing Hillary : On the Trail of the First Woman President Who Wasn&#8217;T &#8211; Amy Chozick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Connection is a story of political skullduggery unprecedented in American history. It weaves together tales of international intrigue, cyber espionage, and superpower rivalry. After US-Russia relations soured, as Vladimir Putin moved to reassert Russian strength on the global stage, Moscow trained its best hackers on US political targets and exploited Julian Assange and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/">Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Connection is a story of political skullduggery unprecedented in American history. It weaves together tales of international intrigue, cyber espionage, and superpower rivalry. After US-Russia relations soured, as Vladimir Putin moved to reassert Russian strength on the global stage, Moscow trained its best hackers on US political targets and exploited Julian Assange and Wikileaks to disseminate information that could affect the 2016 election.     </p>
<p>                    The Russians were wildly successful and the great break-in of 2016 was no &#8220;third rate burglary.&#8221; It was far more sophisticated and sinister &#8212; a brazen act of political espionage designed to interfere with American democracy, and at the end of the day, Trump, the candidate with business ties to Russia, won. And millions of Americans were left wondering, what the hell happened?    </p>
<p>                    This story of high-tech spying and multiple political feuds will be told against the backdrop of Donald Trump and his strange relationship with Putin, and his inner circle of advisers with profitable ties to Russia, most notably Michael Flynn and Paul Manafort.    </p>
<p>                    The Russian Connection will chronicle and examine all these bizarre events and relationships, explain the stakes, and seek to answer one of the biggest questions in American politics: How and why did a foreign government infiltrate the country&#8217;s political process and implant its tentacles in Washington?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/">Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Senator Bernie Sanders explains where he comes from. He describes in detail how, after cutting his teeth in the Civil Rights movement, Sanders helped build an extraordinary grassroots political movement in Vermont, making it possible for him to become the first independent elected to the U.S. House of Representatives in forty years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/">Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Senator Bernie Sanders explains where he comes from. He describes in detail how, after cutting his teeth in the Civil Rights movement, Sanders helped build an extraordinary grassroots political movement in Vermont, making it possible for him to become the first independent elected to the U.S. House of Representatives in forty years and now the longest-serving independent in U.S. political history. An extensive afterword by The Nation&#8217;s National Affairs correspondent John Nichols continues the story with Sanders&#8217;s entrance into the Senate, the drama of the 2016 Democratic Primary, his ongoing resistance to Trump, and the thrilling launch of his 2020 bid for the White House. A new foreword by Nina Turner, former president of Our Revolution and co-chair of the Sanders for President campaign, provides a rare glimpse of Bernie as a person. Outsider in the White House tells the story of a passionate and principled political life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/">Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>IAN BREMMER WAS NAMED LINKEDIN&#8217;S #1 TOP INFLUENCER in 2017 &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; &#8216;Required reading to help repair a world in pieces and build a world at peace&#8217; &#8211; Antonio Guterres, United Nations Secretary General &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; &#8216;Ian Bremmer is provocative, controversial, and always intelligent about the state of the world, which he knows so well&#8217; &#8211; Christine [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IAN BREMMER WAS NAMED LINKEDIN&#8217;S #1 TOP INFLUENCER in 2017    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Required reading to help repair a world in pieces and build a world at peace&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Antonio Guterres, United Nations Secretary General     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ian Bremmer is provocative, controversial, and always intelligent about the state of the world, which he knows so well&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Christine Lagarde, Managing Director of the International Monetary Fund     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    From Brexit, to Donald Trump, to extremist parties in Europe and the developing world, populism has dominated recent headlines.     </p>
<p>                    But what explains the rise of leaders who stoke nationalist anger in their countries, from Le Pen to Erdogan? How long will the populist wave last? Who will be the winners and losers in this climate, and how can we defend the values of democracy, free trade and international cooperation?     </p>
<p>                    No one is better suited to explore these questions than Ian Bremmer, the CEO of the Eurasia Group and acclaimed Time magazine columnist. Analysing the social, economic and technological forces fuelling this new wave of populism, Bremmer explains why we&#8217;re witnessing a rejection of the democratic, global, cosmopolitan trends of the late 20th century. Us vs. Them is a definitive guide to navigating the shifting political landscape, for businesses looking to weather and survive the populist storm.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Global politics is a jungle today. Thank goodness Ian Bremmer can be your guide&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; David Miliband, president and CEO of the International Rescue Committee    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A masterful analysis of why global crashed and populism soared&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Adam Grant, author of Give and Take, and Originals and Option B with Sheryl Sandberg</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stronger Together &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, Tim Kaine (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For more than a year, Hillary Clinton has laid out an ambitious agenda to improve the lives of the American people and make the country stronger and safer. Stronger Together presents that agenda in full, relating stories from the American people and outlining the Clinton/Kaine campaign&#8217;s plans on everything from apprenticeships to the Zika virus, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/">Stronger Together &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, Tim Kaine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For more than a year, Hillary Clinton has laid out an ambitious agenda to improve the lives of the American people and make the country stronger and safer. Stronger Together presents that agenda in full, relating stories from the American people and outlining the Clinton/Kaine campaign&#8217;s plans on everything from apprenticeships to the Zika virus, including:<br />
                     -Building an economy that works for everyone.<br />
                     -Making investment in good-paying jobs, including infrastructure, manufacturing, clean energy and small business.<br />
                     -Making debt-free college a reality and tackling the student debt crisis.<br />
                     -A course of action to defeat global terrorist networks and support allies.<br />
                     -Breaking down the barriers that hold Americans back by reforming a broken immigration system, ending mass incarceration, protecting voting rights, and fixing the campaign finance system.<br />
                     -Putting families first through universal, affordable health care; paid family and medical leave, and affordable child care.<br />
                        Stronger Together offers specific solutions and a bold vision for building a more perfect union.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/">Stronger Together &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, Tim Kaine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crime in Progress : The Secret History of the Trump-Russia Investigation &#8211; Glenn Simpson, Peter Fritsch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crime-in-progress-the-secret-history-of-the-trump-russia-investigation-glenn-simpson-peter-fritsch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Investigation & Detection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Campaigning & Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crime-in-progress-the-secret-history-of-the-trump-russia-investigation-glenn-simpson-peter-fritsch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** The never-before-told inside story of the Steele Dossier and the Trump-Russia investigation &#8216;The best procedural yet written about the discovery of Trump&#8217;s Russia ties&#8217; New York Times In the autumn of 2015, the founders of the Washington-based intelligence firm Fusion GPS, Glenn Simpson and Peter Fritsch, were hired by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crime-in-progress-the-secret-history-of-the-trump-russia-investigation-glenn-simpson-peter-fritsch-abridged/">Crime in Progress : The Secret History of the Trump-Russia Investigation &#8211; Glenn Simpson, Peter Fritsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**<br />
                    The never-before-told inside story of the Steele Dossier and the Trump-Russia investigation    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The best procedural yet written about the discovery of Trump&#8217;s Russia ties&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                    In the autumn of 2015, the founders of the Washington-based intelligence firm Fusion GPS, Glenn Simpson and Peter Fritsch, were hired by a republican client to look into the records of Donald Trump. What began as a march through a mind-boggling trove of lawsuits and sketchy overseas projects soon took a darker turn, as they became the first to uncover Trump&#8217;s disturbing ties to the Kremlin and the crimes that since have plagued his presidency.     </p>
<p>                     To help them decipher this alarming evidence, they engaged the services of an old acquaintance, the former British MI6 agent and Russia expert Christopher Steele. Steele would produce the notorious dossier which disclosed that the Trump team was deeply compromised by a hostile foreign power bent on disrupting the West and influencing the US presidential election.    </p>
<p>                     In Crime in Progress, the authors break their silence for the first time, chronicling their high-stakes investigation and their desperate efforts to warn both the American and British governments, the FBI and the media, to little avail &#8211; and no matter the costs. Yet when the dossier finally exploded onto the world stage after a leak, a ten-person research firm above a Starbucks in Washington was thrust into the centre of the biggest news story on the planet &#8211; a story that would lead to the Mueller report and disrupt Trump&#8217;s secret planned rapprochement with Putin&#8217;s Russia that could have re-ordered the western alliance. After four years on his trail, the authors&#8217; inescapable conclusion is that Trump is an asset of the Russian government, whether he knows it or not.     </p>
<p>                     A real-life political thriller with the makings of a modern classic, Crime in Progress is the definitive story of the pursuit of the truth about Trump and one of the greatest betrayals in American history.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;ve read all the books on this subject &#8211; this is the one you want to read . . . I feel fairly steeped in this matter and I learned something on every page&#8217; Rachel Maddow, MSNBC     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;You don&#8217;t need to read John le Carre or Tom Clancy to find espionage thrills in Washington these days, turn over any stone in the Beltway&#8217;s secret world and you&#8217;ll observe the seething mass of conspiracy and subterfuge beneath . . . Take Glenn Simpson and Peter Fritsch, who have become central characters in a quite terrifying international spy thriller&#8217; Josh Glancy, Sunday Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crime-in-progress-the-secret-history-of-the-trump-russia-investigation-glenn-simpson-peter-fritsch-abridged/">Crime in Progress : The Secret History of the Trump-Russia Investigation &#8211; Glenn Simpson, Peter Fritsch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everybody Lies : The New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Seth Stephens-Davidowitz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Analysis: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AN ECONOMIST BOOK OF THE YEAR A NEW STATESMAN BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8216;This book is about a whole new way of studying the mind &#8230; Endlessly fascinating&#8217; Steven Pinker &#8216;A whirlwind tour of the modern human psyche&#8217; Economist Everybody lies, to friends, lovers, doctors, pollsters &#8211; and to themselves. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/">Everybody Lies : The New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Seth Stephens-Davidowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    AN ECONOMIST BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    A NEW STATESMAN BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book is about a whole new way of studying the mind &#8230; Endlessly fascinating&#8217; Steven Pinker    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A whirlwind tour of the modern human psyche&#8217; Economist    </p>
<p>                    Everybody lies, to friends, lovers, doctors, pollsters &#8211; and to themselves. In Internet searches, however, people confess the truth.    </p>
<p>                    Insightful, funny and always surprising, Everybody Lies explores how this huge collection of data, unprecedented in human history, could just be the most important ever collected. It offers astonishing insights into the human psyche, revealing the biases deeply embedded within us, the questions we&#8217;re afraid to ask that might be essential to our well-being, and the information we can use to change our culture for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/">Everybody Lies : The New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Seth Stephens-Davidowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Short History of Brexit : From Brentry to Backstop &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Rourke (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EU & European Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crisp, clear and quietly devastating&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Excellent, authoritative, highly readable&#8217; Irish Times A succinct, expert guide to how we got to Brexit After all the debates, manoeuvrings, recriminations and exaltations, Brexit is upon us. But, as Kevin O&#8217;Rourke writes, Brexit did not emerge out of nowhere: it is the culmination of events that have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/">A Short History of Brexit : From Brentry to Backstop &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Rourke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crisp, clear and quietly devastating&#8217; Guardian<br />
                    &#8216;Excellent, authoritative, highly readable&#8217; Irish Times    </p>
<p>                    A succinct, expert guide to how we got to Brexit    </p>
<p>                    After all the debates, manoeuvrings, recriminations and exaltations,  Brexit is upon us. But, as Kevin O&#8217;Rourke writes, Brexit did not emerge  out of nowhere: it is the culmination of events  that have been under  way for decades and have historical roots stretching back well beyond  that. Brexit has a history.    </p>
<p>                    O&#8217;Rourke, one of the leading economic  historians of his generation, explains not only how British attitudes  to Europe have evolved, but also how the EU&#8217;s history explains why it  operates as it does today &#8211; and how that history has shaped the ways in  which it has responded to Brexit. Why are the economics, the politics  and the history so tightly woven together? Crucially, he also explains  why the question of the Irish border is not just one of customs and  trade, but for the EU goes to the heart of what it is about.  The way in  which British, Irish and European histories continue to interact with  each other will shape the future of Brexit &#8211; and of the continent.    </p>
<p>                    Calm and lucid, A Short History of Brexit  rises above the usual fray of discussions to provide fresh perspectives  and understanding of the most momentous political and economic change  in Britain and the EU for decades.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/">A Short History of Brexit : From Brentry to Backstop &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Rourke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Read the inspiring Sunday Times bestselling memoir from the first woman, and woman of colour, to serve as Vice President of the United States. &#8216;A life story that genuinely entrances&#8217; Los Angeles Times The daughter of immigrants and civil rights activists, Vice President Kamala Harris was raised in a California community that cared deeply about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/">The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read the inspiring Sunday Times bestselling memoir from the first woman, and woman of colour, to serve as Vice President of the United States.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A life story that genuinely entrances&#8217; Los Angeles Times    </p>
<p>                    The daughter of immigrants and civil rights activists, Vice President Kamala Harris was raised in a California community that cared deeply about social justice. As she rose to prominence as a political leader, her experiences would become her guiding light as she grappled with an array of complex issues and learned to bring a voice to the voiceless.    </p>
<p>                    Now, in The Truths We Hold, Harris reckons with the big challenges we face together. Drawing on the hard-won wisdom and insight from her own career and the work of those who have most inspired her, she communicates a vision of shared struggle, shared purpose, and shared values as we confront the great work of our day.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Personal integrity shines through every page&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truths-we-hold-an-american-journey-kamala-harris-abridged/">The Truths We Hold : An American Journey &#8211; Kamala Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Prime Ministers We Never Had : Success and Failure from Butler to Corbyn &#8211; Steve Richards (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-prime-ministers-we-never-had-success-and-failure-from-butler-to-corbyn-steve-richards-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-prime-ministers-we-never-had-success-and-failure-from-butler-to-corbyn-steve-richards-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BOOK OF THE YEAR, The Times, Guardian and Prospect Was Harold Wilson a bigger figure than Denis Healey? Was John Major more &#8216;prime ministerial&#8217; than Michael Heseltine? Would David Miliband have become prime minister if it were not for his brother Ed? Would Ed have become prime minister if it were not for David? How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-prime-ministers-we-never-had-success-and-failure-from-butler-to-corbyn-steve-richards-abridged/">The Prime Ministers We Never Had : Success and Failure from Butler to Corbyn &#8211; Steve Richards (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BOOK OF THE YEAR, The Times, Guardian and Prospect    </p>
<p>                    Was Harold Wilson a bigger figure than Denis Healey? Was John Major more &#8216;prime ministerial&#8217; than Michael Heseltine? Would David Miliband have become prime minister if it were not for his brother Ed? Would Ed have become prime minister if it were not for David? How close did Jeremy Corbyn come to being prime minister?     </p>
<p>                    In this piercing and original study, journalist and commentator Steve Richards looks at eleven prime ministers we never had, examining what made each of these illustrious figures unique and why they failed to make the final leap to the very top. Combining astute insights into the demands of leadership with compelling historical analysis, this fascinating exploration of failure and success sheds new light on some of the most compelling characters in British public life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-prime-ministers-we-never-had-success-and-failure-from-butler-to-corbyn-steve-richards-abridged/">The Prime Ministers We Never Had : Success and Failure from Butler to Corbyn &#8211; Steve Richards (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Language Intelligence : Lessons on persuasion from Jesus, Shakespeare, Lincoln, and Lady Gaga &#8211; Joseph J Romm (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/language-intelligence-lessons-on-persuasion-from-jesus-shakespeare-lincoln-and-lady-gaga-joseph-j-romm-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/language-intelligence-lessons-on-persuasion-from-jesus-shakespeare-lincoln-and-lady-gaga-joseph-j-romm-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Romm, one of Rolling Stone magazine&#8217;s top &#8220;100 Agents of Change,&#8221; has focused his talents on helping us all to increase our Language Intelligence and to better understand the art of persuasion. Romm demonstrates that you don&#8217;t have to be an expert to vastly improve your ability to communicate. He has pulled together the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/language-intelligence-lessons-on-persuasion-from-jesus-shakespeare-lincoln-and-lady-gaga-joseph-j-romm-abridged/">Language Intelligence : Lessons on persuasion from Jesus, Shakespeare, Lincoln, and Lady Gaga &#8211; Joseph J Romm (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Romm, one of Rolling Stone magazine&#8217;s top &#8220;100 Agents of Change,&#8221; has focused his talents on helping us all to increase our Language Intelligence and to better understand the art of persuasion.     </p>
<p>                     Romm demonstrates that you don&#8217;t have to be an expert to vastly improve your ability to communicate. He has pulled together the secrets of the greatest communicators in history to show how you can apply these tools to your writing, speaking, blogging &#8211; even your Tweeting. The book also looks at the language intelligence of President Obama and Governor Romney.     </p>
<p>                     Nothing could be more relevant in 2012 as Americans prepare to make vital choices in the upcoming elections. Language Intelligence not only will prepare you to be a much more memorable and persuasive communicator, it will also help you to understand the tricks of the trade used &#8212; and misused &#8212; by candidates on the stump.     </p>
<p>                     With a few easily digestible and memorable concepts, Language Intelligence also offers readers an indispensible roadmap for today&#8217;s political and pop culture landscape. &#8220;For anyone who seeks to understand why Lady Gaga&#8217;s music has become a global phenomena or how to avoid &#8216;Etch-a-Sketch&#8217; moments, this book is for you,&#8221; said Romm.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/language-intelligence-lessons-on-persuasion-from-jesus-shakespeare-lincoln-and-lady-gaga-joseph-j-romm-abridged/">Language Intelligence : Lessons on persuasion from Jesus, Shakespeare, Lincoln, and Lady Gaga &#8211; Joseph J Romm (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Strangers In Their Own Land : Anger and Mourning on the American Right &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/strangers-in-their-own-land-anger-and-mourning-on-the-american-right-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/strangers-in-their-own-land-anger-and-mourning-on-the-american-right-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Strangers in Their Own Land, the renowned sociologist Arlie Hochschild embarks on a thought-provoking journey from her liberal hometown of Berkeley, California, deep into Louisiana bayou country &#8211; a stronghold of the conservative right. As she gets to know people who strongly oppose many of the ideas she famously champions, Hochschild nevertheless finds common [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strangers-in-their-own-land-anger-and-mourning-on-the-american-right-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">Strangers In Their Own Land : Anger and Mourning on the American Right &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Strangers in Their Own Land, the renowned sociologist Arlie Hochschild embarks on a thought-provoking journey from her liberal hometown of Berkeley, California, deep into Louisiana bayou country &#8211; a stronghold of the conservative right. As she gets to know people who strongly oppose many of the ideas she famously champions, Hochschild nevertheless finds common ground and quickly warms to the people she meets, people whose concerns are actually ones that all Americans share: the desire for community, the embrace of family, and hopes for their children.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strangers-in-their-own-land-anger-and-mourning-on-the-american-right-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">Strangers In Their Own Land : Anger and Mourning on the American Right &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shattered : Inside Hillary Clinton&#8217;s Doomed Campaign &#8211; Jonathan Allen, Amie Parnes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/shattered-inside-hillary-clintons-doomed-campaign-jonathan-allen-amie-parnes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/shattered-inside-hillary-clintons-doomed-campaign-jonathan-allen-amie-parnes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER It was never supposed to be this close. And of course she was supposed to win. How Hillary Clinton lost the 2016 election to Donald Trump is the riveting story of a sure thing gone off the rails. For every Comey revelation or hindsight acknowledgment about the electorate, no explanation [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shattered-inside-hillary-clintons-doomed-campaign-jonathan-allen-amie-parnes-abridged/">Shattered : Inside Hillary Clinton&#8217;s Doomed Campaign &#8211; Jonathan Allen, Amie Parnes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER It was never supposed to be this close. And of course she was supposed to win. How Hillary Clinton lost the 2016 election to Donald Trump is the riveting story of a sure thing gone off the rails. For every Comey revelation or hindsight acknowledgment about the electorate, no explanation of defeat can begin with anything other than the core problem of Hillary&#8217;s campaign&#8211;the candidate herself. Through deep access to insiders from the top to the bottom of the campaign, political writers Jonathan Allen and Amie Parnes have reconstructed the key decisions and unseized opportunities, the well-intentioned misfires and the hidden thorns that turned a winnable contest into a devastating loss. Drawing on the authors&#8217; deep knowledge of Hillary from their previous book, the acclaimed biography HRC, Shattered offers an object lesson in how Hillary herself made victory an uphill battle, how her difficulty articulating a vision irreparably hobbled her impact with voters, and how the campaign failed to internalize the lessons of populist fury from the hard-fought primary against Bernie Sanders. Moving blow-by-blow from the campaign&#8217;s difficult birth through the bewildering terror of election night, Shattered tells an unforgettable story with urgent lessons both political and personal, filled with revelations that will change the way readers understand just what happened to America on November 8, 2016.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shattered-inside-hillary-clintons-doomed-campaign-jonathan-allen-amie-parnes-abridged/">Shattered : Inside Hillary Clinton&#8217;s Doomed Campaign &#8211; Jonathan Allen, Amie Parnes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Happened &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-happened-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-happened-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times Number One Bestseller &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; &#8211; Financial Times &#8216;A sporadically absorbing, pleasingly vengeful and often darkly funny account of one woman&#8217;s bid for presidential history.&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;Her new book is more gossipy, it is meaner, more entertaining and more wrong-headed than anything she or her speechwriters have written before.&#8217; Observer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-happened-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/">What Happened &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times Number One Bestseller    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; &#8211; Financial Times<br />
                     &#8216;A sporadically absorbing, pleasingly vengeful and often darkly funny account of one woman&#8217;s bid for presidential history.&#8217; Sunday Times<br />
                     &#8216;Her new book is more gossipy, it is meaner, more entertaining and more wrong-headed than anything she or her speechwriters have written before.&#8217; Observer<br />
                     &#8216;What Happened is highly entertaining. It is spirited, well-written and informative.&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;In the past, for reasons I try to explain, I&#8217;ve often felt I had to be careful in public, like I was up on a wire without a net. Now I&#8217;m letting my guard down.&#8217; &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, from the introduction of What Happened    </p>
<p>                     For the first time, Hillary Rodham Clinton reveals what she was thinking and feeling during one of the most controversial and unpredictable presidential elections in history. Now free from the constraints of running, Hillary takes you inside the intense personal experience of becoming the first woman nominated for president by a major party in an election marked by rage, sexism, exhilarating highs and infuriating lows, stranger-than-fiction twists, Russian interference and an opponent who broke all the rules. This is her most personal memoir yet.    </p>
<p>                     In these pages, she describes what it was like to run against Donald Trump, the mistakes she made, how she has coped with a shocking and devastating loss, and how she found the strength to pick herself back up afterwards. With humour and candour, she tells readers what it took to get back on her feet &#8211; the rituals, relationships and reading that got her through, and what the experience has taught her about life. She speaks about the challenges of being a strong woman in the public eye, the criticism over her voice, age and appearance, and the double standard confronting women in politics.     </p>
<p>                     She lays out how the 2016 election was marked by an unprecedented assault on democracy by a foreign adversary. By analysing the evidence and connecting the dots, Hillary shows just how dangerous the forces are that shaped the outcome, and why Americans need to understand them to protect their values and democracy in the future.    </p>
<p>                     The election of 2016 was unprecedented and historic. What Happened is the story of that campaign and its aftermath &#8211; both a deeply intimate account and a cautionary tale.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-happened-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/">What Happened &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the 2018 Waterstones Book of the Year Winner at the 2018 Parliamentary Book Awards Longlisted for the Orwell Prize, 2019 ____________ &#8220;A really good book&#8230; Well-structured and well-written.&#8221; Observer &#8220;Well written and incisive.&#8221; The Times &#8220;Vital and compelling.&#8221; New Statesman In an era when politicians are responsible for the Brexit logjam and embroiled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/">Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the 2018 Waterstones Book of the Year<br />
                    Winner at the 2018 Parliamentary Book Awards<br />
                    Longlisted for the Orwell Prize, 2019<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A really good book&#8230;  Well-structured and well-written.&#8221; Observer<br />
                    &#8220;Well written and incisive.&#8221; The Times<br />
                    &#8220;Vital and compelling.&#8221; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    In an era when politicians are responsible for the Brexit logjam and embroiled in sexual-harassment and expenses scandals, it&#8217;s no wonder we&#8217;ve lost our faith in government. Every year, they introduce new legislation that doesn&#8217;t do what it sets out to achieve &#8211; often with terrible financial and human costs. But, with some notable exceptions, they are decent, hard-working people, doing a hugely difficult and demanding job. In this searching examination of our political class, award-winning journalist Isabel Hardman investigates the strange and demanding world of Westminster, and asks why we end up with representatives we no longer trust &#8211; and how might faith be restored.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/">Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019 Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump. The 2016 election was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019    </p>
<p>                    Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump.    </p>
<p>                    The 2016 election was a watershed for the United States. But, as Tim Alberta explains in American Carnage, to understand Trump&#8217;s victory is to view him not as the creator of this era of polarization and bruising partisanship, but rather as its most manifest consequence.    </p>
<p>                    American Carnage is the story of a president&#8217;s rise based on a country&#8217;s evolution and a party&#8217;s collapse. As George W. Bush left office with record-low approval ratings and Barack Obama led a Democratic takeover of Washington, Republicans faced a moment of reckoning: They had no vision, no generation of new leaders, and no energy in the party&#8217;s base. Yet Obama&#8217;s forceful pursuit of his progressive agenda, coupled with the nation&#8217;s rapidly changing cultural and demographic landscape, lit a fire under the right, returning Republicans to power and inviting a bloody struggle for the party&#8217;s identity in the post-Bush era. The factions that emerged-one led by absolutists like Jim Jordan and Ted Cruz, the other led by pragmatists like John Boehner and Mitch McConnell-engaged in a series of devastating internecine clashes and attempted coups for control. With the GOP&#8217;s internal fissures rendering it legislatively impotent, and that impotence fueling a growing resentment toward the political class and its institutions, the stage was set for an outsider to crash the party. When Trump descended a gilded escalator to announce his run in the summer of 2015, the candidate had met the moment.    </p>
<p>                    Only by viewing Trump as the culmination of a decade-long civil war inside the Republican Party-and of the parallel sense of cultural, socioeconomic, and technological disruption during that period-can we appreciate how he won the White House and consider the fundamental questions at the center of America&#8217;s current turmoil. How did a party obsessed with the national debt vote for trillion-dollar deficits and record-setting spending increases? How did the party of compassionate conservatism become the party of Muslim bans and walls? How did the party of family values elect a thrice-divorced philanderer? And, most important, how long can such a party survive?    </p>
<p>                     Loaded with exclusive reporting and based off hundreds of interviews-including with key players such as President Trump, Paul Ryan, Ted Cruz, John Boehner, Mitch McConnell, Jim DeMint, and Reince Priebus, and many others-American Carnage takes us behind the scenes of this tumultuous period as we&#8217;ve never seen it before and establishes Tim Alberta as the premier chronicler of this political era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>For the Record &#8211; David Cameron (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/for-the-record-david-cameron-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Administration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Opinion & Polls]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/for-the-record-david-cameron-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The political memoir of the decade&#8217; Sunday Times The referendum on Britain&#8217;s membership of the EU is one of the most controversial political events of our times. For the first time, the man who called that vote talks about the decision and its origins, as well as giving a candid account of his time at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/for-the-record-david-cameron-abridged/">For the Record &#8211; David Cameron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The political memoir of the decade&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                                The referendum on Britain&#8217;s membership of the EU is one of the most controversial political events of our times. For the first time, the man who called that vote talks about the decision and its origins, as well as giving a candid account of his time at the top of British politics.    </p>
<p>                              David Cameron was Conservative Party leader during the largest financial crash in living memory. The Arab Spring and the Eurozone crisis both started during his first year as prime minister. The backdrop to his time in office included the advent of ISIS, surging migration and a rapidly changing EU.    </p>
<p>                              Here he talks about how he confronted those challenges, from modernising a party that had suffered three successive electoral defeats to forming the first coalition government for seventy years. He sets out how he helped turn around Britain&#8217;s economy, implementing a modern, compassionate agenda that included education and welfare reform, the legalisation of gay marriage, the referendum on Scottish independence and world-leading environmental policies.    </p>
<p>                              David Cameron is searingly honest about the key players from his time in politics. And he is frank about himself &#8211; the things he got right and the things he got wrong. He opens up about family life too, including the tragic loss of his eldest son.    </p>
<p>                              We learn why he kept Britain&#8217;s promise on overseas aid spending and what it was like to commit British troops to conflicts in Libya, Iraq and Syria. He sets out how he won the first outright Conservative majority in nearly a quarter of a century, and describes the events leading up to the EU referendum, the renegotiation, the campaign &#8211; and his thoughts on it all today.    </p>
<p>                              It is the most compelling record yet of what it&#8217;s like to lead in modern times and to live behind the most famous door in the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/for-the-record-david-cameron-abridged/">For the Record &#8211; David Cameron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
