<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Carving &amp; Modelling, Moulding &amp; Casting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/carving-modelling-moulding-casting/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/carving-modelling-moulding-casting/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Carving &amp; Modelling, Moulding &amp; Casting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/carving-modelling-moulding-casting/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Art Of Candle Making Business Startup : How to Start, Run &#038; Grow a Million Dollar Success From Home! &#8211; Suzanne Carpenter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/art-of-candle-making-business-startup-how-to-start-run-grow-a-million-dollar-success-from-home-suzanne-carpenter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Carving & Modelling, Moulding & Casting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/art-of-candle-making-business-startup-how-to-start-run-grow-a-million-dollar-success-from-home-suzanne-carpenter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Art Of Candle Making Business Startup How to Start, Run &#038; Grow a Million Dollar Success From Home! In this book, I don&#8217;t tell you how to make beautiful candles in few steps and then give you a few recipes to try, so you can start your own Candle making business. You can find that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/art-of-candle-making-business-startup-how-to-start-run-grow-a-million-dollar-success-from-home-suzanne-carpenter-abridged/">Art Of Candle Making Business Startup : How to Start, Run &#038; Grow a Million Dollar Success From Home! &#8211; Suzanne Carpenter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Art Of Candle Making Business Startup<br />
                    How to Start, Run &#038; Grow a Million Dollar Success From Home!    </p>
<p>                    In this book, I don&#8217;t tell you how to make beautiful candles in few steps and then give you a few recipes to try, so you can start your own Candle making business. You can find that information anywhere, don&#8217;t have to buy my book to learn that. Wait! Oh! I did that in this book. I did explain how to make Beautiful Candles, I also did give you a few simple recipes too. But I hope that is not why you bought this book.    </p>
<p>                    In this book my goal is to explain to you in simple terms how to CREATE great natural and organic candles and not just MAKE any candles, there is a difference. You will get to see and understand that difference when you understand each ingredients and how they interact and react with each other.    </p>
<p>                     You will not have a great business if you are just making carbon copy of few candles of other people which your customers can go buy from any local stores. What will make you unique is when you create a blend or two of your own and people start liking your creation. That is when you can hit the home run in business.    </p>
<p>                    Imagine growing your candle company into a local, regional and ultimately a national brand, where your candles will be sold at every Whole food, Body, Bath and Beyond, Home Goods and many other great retailers.     </p>
<p>                    This is a two part book. In the first part I show you how to get started with candle making, I show you every steps you need to take to make your first batch of candle. Then I show you how to test your creation and how to figure out what works and what does not.    </p>
<p>                    On the second part of the book, I teach you everything you need to know about turning your new found passion into a successful business. In my last book, &#8220;Soap Making Business Start Up&#8221; I shared how I grew that business from 0 to a six figure business and then sold it for a good profit. If you have read that book than you know dream are not just dreams, they can become a reality with some dedication, focus and hard work. I think you may find it inspiring that an average housewife like myself was able to build the business and then was able to sell it for a good profit.    </p>
<p>                    In the First Part I will Show You:     </p>
<p>                    What Candle Making Equipment and tools you will needWhat and how to get Raw MaterialsHow to get Started for very little MoneyHow to Scent a Candle ProperlyWhat makes a candle Natural and Organic?How to Make Soy, Beeswax and Many other Natural CandlesHow to be Creative with Candle makingHow to Color your Candles with natural color7 Steps to Making Great CandlesAll the Candle Making methods Step by StepCandle Making Safety Rules to FollowBest &#038; Easiest Candle Making Projects to Start with    </p>
<p>                    In the Second Part I Will Show You:     </p>
<p>                    How to get started, Step by StepHow to Start from Home and Save MoneyHow to Find and Develop a Niche for your Candle BusinessThe New Market Trends in the Candle IndustryHow to Price your Candles for Sale6 Must Do&#8217;s in Candle Business5 Mistakes to Avoid at all CostHow to Calculate Profit Margin of your BusinessHow and Where to Market and Sell your Handmade candlesHow to Promote your Business both On and OfflineHow to Price and Sell to WholesalersHow to Grow your Homemade Candle Business    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to a beautiful and colorful world of Candle making Business. Where else can you have fun and make money at the same time? Enjoy this wonderful journey, I know I have.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/art-of-candle-making-business-startup-how-to-start-run-grow-a-million-dollar-success-from-home-suzanne-carpenter-abridged/">Art Of Candle Making Business Startup : How to Start, Run &#038; Grow a Million Dollar Success From Home! &#8211; Suzanne Carpenter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
