<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Employee-ownership &amp; Co-operatives Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/employee-ownership-co-operatives/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/employee-ownership-co-operatives/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Employee-ownership &amp; Co-operatives Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/employee-ownership-co-operatives/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Learn or Die : Using Science to Build a Leading-Edge Learning Organization &#8211; Edward D. Hess (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/learn-or-die-using-science-to-build-a-leading-edge-learning-organization-edward-d-hess-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/learn-or-die-using-science-to-build-a-leading-edge-learning-organization-edward-d-hess-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>To compete with today&#8217;s increasing globalization and rapidly evolving technologies, individuals and organizations must take their ability to learn-the foundation for continuous improvement, operational excellence, and innovation-to a much higher level. In Learn or Die, Edward D. Hess combines recent advances in neuroscience, psychology, behavioral economics, and education with key research on high-performance businesses to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-or-die-using-science-to-build-a-leading-edge-learning-organization-edward-d-hess-abridged/">Learn or Die : Using Science to Build a Leading-Edge Learning Organization &#8211; Edward D. Hess (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To compete with today&#8217;s increasing globalization and rapidly evolving technologies, individuals and organizations must take their ability to learn-the foundation for continuous improvement, operational excellence, and innovation-to a much higher level. In Learn or Die, Edward D. Hess combines recent advances in neuroscience, psychology, behavioral economics, and education with key research on high-performance businesses to create an actionable blueprint for becoming a leading-edge learning organization. Learn or Die examines the process of learning from an individual and an organizational standpoint. From an individual perspective, the book discusses the cognitive, emotional, motivational, attitudinal, and behavioral factors that promote better learning. Organizationally, Learn or Die focuses on the kinds of structures, culture, leadership, employee learning behaviors, and human resource policies that are necessary to create an environment that enables critical and innovative thinking, learning conversations, and collaboration.<br />
                    The volume also provides strategies to mitigate the reality that humans can be reflexive, lazy thinkers who seek confirmation of what they believe to be true and affirmation of their self-image. Exemplar learning organizations discussed include the secretive Bridgewater Associates, LP; Intuit, Inc.; United Parcel Service (UPS); W. L. Gore &#038; Associates; and IDEO.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-or-die-using-science-to-build-a-leading-edge-learning-organization-edward-d-hess-abridged/">Learn or Die : Using Science to Build a Leading-Edge Learning Organization &#8211; Edward D. Hess (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Most Important Thing Illuminated : Uncommon Sense for the Thoughtful Investor &#8211; Howard Marks, Foreword by Bruce Greenwald (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Howard Marks&#8217;s The Most Important Thing distilled the investing insight of his celebrated client memos into a single volume and, for the first time, made his time-tested philosophy available to general readers. In this edition, Marks&#8217;s wisdom is joined by the comments, insights, and counterpoints of four renowned investors and investment educators: Christopher C. Davis [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/">The Most Important Thing Illuminated : Uncommon Sense for the Thoughtful Investor &#8211; Howard Marks, Foreword by Bruce Greenwald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Howard Marks&#8217;s The Most Important Thing distilled the investing insight of his celebrated client memos into a single volume and, for the first time, made his time-tested philosophy available to general readers. In this edition, Marks&#8217;s wisdom is joined by the comments, insights, and counterpoints of four renowned investors and investment educators: Christopher C. Davis (Davis Funds), Joel Greenblatt (Gotham Capital), Paul Johnson (Nicusa Capital), and Seth A. Klarman (Baupost Group). These experts lend insight into such concepts as &#8220;second-level thinking,&#8221; the price/value relationship, patient opportunism, and defensive investing. Marks also adds his own annotations, expanding on his book&#8217;s original themes and issues. A new chapter addresses the importance of reasonable expectations, and a foreword by Bruce C. Greenwald, called &#8220;a guru to Wall Street&#8217;s gurus&#8221; by the New York Times, speaks on value investing, productivity, and the economics of information.  ***  Howard Marks, the chairman and cofounder of Oaktree Capital Management, is renowned for his insightful assessments of market opportunity and risk.<br />
                    After four decades spent ascending to the top of the investment management profession, he is today sought out by the world&#8217;s leading value investors, and his client memos brim with insightful commentary and a time-tested, fundamental philosophy. Now for the first time, all readers can benefit from Marks&#8217;s wisdom, concentrated into a single volume that speaks to both the amateur and seasoned investor.  Informed by a lifetime of experience and study, The Most Important Thing explains the keys to successful investment and the pitfalls that can destroy capital or ruin a career. Utilizing passages from his memos to illustrate his ideas, Marks teaches by example, detailing the development of an investment philosophy that fully acknowledges the complexities of investing and the perils of the financial world. Brilliantly applying insight to today&#8217;s volatile markets, Marks offers a volume that is part memoir, part creed, with a number of broad takeaways.  Marks expounds on such concepts as &#8220;second-level thinking,&#8221; the price/value relationship, patient opportunism, and defensive investing.<br />
                    Frankly and honestly assessing his own decisions&#8211;and occasional missteps&#8211;he provides valuable lessons for critical thinking, risk assessment, and investment strategy. Encouraging investors to be &#8220;contrarian,&#8221; Marks wisely judges market cycles and achieves returns through aggressive yet measured action. Which element is the most essential? Successful investing requires thoughtful attention to many separate aspects, and each of Marks&#8217;s subjects proves to be the most important thing.  &#8220;This is that rarity, a useful book.&#8221;&#8211;Warren Buffett</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/">The Most Important Thing Illuminated : Uncommon Sense for the Thoughtful Investor &#8211; Howard Marks, Foreword by Bruce Greenwald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Berkshire Beyond Buffett : The Enduring Value of Values &#8211; Lawrence A. Cunningham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Governance & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Berkshire Hathaway, the $300 billion conglomerate that Warren Buffett built, is among the world&#8217;s largest and most famous corporations. Yet, for all its power and celebrity, few people understand Berkshire, and many assume it cannot survive without Buffett. This book proves them wrong. In a comprehensive portrait of the corporate culture that unites Berkshire&#8217;s subsidiaries, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/">Berkshire Beyond Buffett : The Enduring Value of Values &#8211; Lawrence A. Cunningham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Berkshire Hathaway, the $300 billion conglomerate that Warren Buffett built, is among the world&#8217;s largest and most famous corporations. Yet, for all its power and celebrity, few people understand Berkshire, and many assume it cannot survive without Buffett. This book proves them wrong. In a comprehensive portrait of the corporate culture that unites Berkshire&#8217;s subsidiaries, Lawrence A. Cunningham unearths the traits that assure the conglomerate&#8217;s continued prosperity. Riveting stories of each subsidiary&#8217;s origins, triumphs, and journey to Berkshire reveal how managers generate economic value from intangibles like thrift, integrity, entrepreneurship, autonomy, and a sense of permanence. Rich with lessons for those wishing to profit from the Berkshire model, this engaging book is a valuable read for entrepreneurs, business owners, managers, family business members, and investors, and it is an important resource for scholars of corporate stewardship. General readers will enjoy learning how an iconoclastic businessman transformed a struggling textile company into a corporate legacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/">Berkshire Beyond Buffett : The Enduring Value of Values &#8211; Lawrence A. Cunningham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commodities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jim Paul&#8217;s meteoric rise took him from a small town in Northern Kentucky to governor of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, yet he lost it all-his fortune, his reputation, and his job-in one fatal attack of excessive economic hubris. In this honest, frank analysis, Paul and Brendan Moynihan revisit the events that led to Paul&#8217;s disastrous [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/">What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jim Paul&#8217;s meteoric rise took him from a small town in Northern Kentucky to governor of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, yet he lost it all-his fortune, his reputation, and his job-in one fatal attack of excessive economic hubris. In this honest, frank analysis, Paul and Brendan Moynihan revisit the events that led to Paul&#8217;s disastrous decision and examine the psychological factors behind bad financial practices in several economic sectors.  This book-winner of a 2014 Axiom Business Book award gold medal-begins with the unbroken string of successes that helped Paul achieve a jet-setting lifestyle and land a key spot with the Chicago Mercantile Exchange. It then describes the circumstances leading up to Paul&#8217;s $1.6 million loss and the essential lessons he learned from it-primarily that, although there are as many ways to make money in the markets as there are people participating in them, all losses come from the same few sources. Investors lose money in the markets either because of errors in their analysis or because of psychological barriers preventing the application of analysis.<br />
                    While all analytical methods have some validity and make allowances for instances in which they do not work, psychological factors can keep an investor in a losing position, causing him to abandon one method for another in order to rationalize the decisions already made. Paul and Moynihan&#8217;s cautionary tale includes strategies for avoiding loss tied to a simple framework for understanding, accepting, and dodging the dangers of investing, trading, and speculating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/">What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
