<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sociology &amp; Anthropology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/sociology-anthropology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/sociology-anthropology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Sociology &amp; Anthropology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/sociology-anthropology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Half The Sky : How to Change the World &#8211; Nicholas D. Kristof, Sheryl WuDunn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/half-the-sky-how-to-change-the-world-nicholas-d-kristof-sheryl-wudunn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/half-the-sky-how-to-change-the-world-nicholas-d-kristof-sheryl-wudunn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pulitzer Prize-winning reporting team, husband and wife Nicholas D. Kristof and Sheryl WuDunn, take us on a journey through Africa and Asia to meet an extraordinary array of exceptional women struggling against terrible circumstances. More girls have been killed in the last fifty years, precisely because they are girls, than men were killed in all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/half-the-sky-how-to-change-the-world-nicholas-d-kristof-sheryl-wudunn-abridged/">Half The Sky : How to Change the World &#8211; Nicholas D. Kristof, Sheryl WuDunn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pulitzer Prize-winning reporting team, husband and wife Nicholas D. Kristof and Sheryl WuDunn, take us on a journey through Africa and Asia to meet an extraordinary array of exceptional women struggling against terrible circumstances. More girls have been killed in the last fifty years, precisely because they are girls, than men were killed in all the wars of the twentieth century combined. More girls are killed in this routine &#8216;gendercide&#8217; in any one decade than people were slaughtered in all the genocides of the twentieth century.     </p>
<p>                    In the nineteenth century, the central moral challenge was slavery. In the twentieth, it was totalitarianism. In the twenty-first, Kristof and WuDunn demonstrate, it will be the struggle for gender equality in the developing world. Fierce, moral, pragmatic, full of amazing stories of courage and inspiration, HALF THE SKY is essential reading for every global citizen.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/half-the-sky-how-to-change-the-world-nicholas-d-kristof-sheryl-wudunn-abridged/">Half The Sky : How to Change the World &#8211; Nicholas D. Kristof, Sheryl WuDunn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Silo Effect : Why Every Organisation Needs to Disrupt Itself to Survive &#8211; Gillian Tett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-silo-effect-why-every-organisation-needs-to-disrupt-itself-to-survive-gillian-tett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-silo-effect-why-every-organisation-needs-to-disrupt-itself-to-survive-gillian-tett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ever since civilised society began, we have felt the need to classify, categorise and specialise. It can make things more efficient, and help give the leaders of any organisation a sense of confidence that they have the right people focusing on the right tasks. But it can also be catastrophic, leading to tunnel vision and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-silo-effect-why-every-organisation-needs-to-disrupt-itself-to-survive-gillian-tett-abridged/">The Silo Effect : Why Every Organisation Needs to Disrupt Itself to Survive &#8211; Gillian Tett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ever  since civilised society began, we have felt the need to classify,  categorise and specialise. It can make things more efficient, and help  give the leaders of any organisation a sense of confidence that they  have the right people focusing on the right tasks. But it can also be  catastrophic, leading to tunnel vision and tribalism. Most importantly  it can create a structural fog, with the full picture of where an  organisation is heading hidden from view. It is incredibly widespread:  the chances are these &#8216;silos&#8217; are rife in any organisation or  profession, whether your business, or your local school or hospital.    </p>
<p>                    Across  industries and cultures, as this brilliant and penetrating book shows,  silos have the power to collapse companies and destabilise financial  markets, yet they still dominate the workplace. They blind and confuse  us, often making modern institutions act in risky, silly and damaging  ways.    </p>
<p>                    Gillian Tett has spent years covering financial markets and  business, but she&#8217;s also a trained anthropologist, having completed a  doctorate at Cambridge University and conducted field work in Tibet and  Tajikistan. She&#8217;s no stranger to questioning the assumptions and  practices of a culture. Those in question &#8211; financial trading desks,  urban police forces, surgical teams within medical clinics, software  debuggers and consumer product engineers &#8211; have practices and rituals as  ordered and intricate as those of any far-flung tribe.    </p>
<p>                    In The Silo Effect,  she uses an anthropological lens to explore how individuals, teams and  whole organisations often work in silos of thought, process and product.  With examples drawn from a range of fascinating areas &#8211; the New York  Fire Department and Facebook to the Bank of England and Sony &#8211; these  narratives illustrate not just how foolishly people can behave when they  are mastered by silos but also how the brightest institutions and  individuals can master them. The Silo Effect is a sharp,  visionary and inspiring work with the insight, prescriptions and power  to remove our organisational blinders and transform the way we think for  the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-silo-effect-why-every-organisation-needs-to-disrupt-itself-to-survive-gillian-tett-abridged/">The Silo Effect : Why Every Organisation Needs to Disrupt Itself to Survive &#8211; Gillian Tett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are men literally born to cheat? Does monogamy actually serve women&#8217;s interests? These are among the questions that have made The Moral Animal one of the most provocative science books in recent years. Wright unveils the genetic strategies behind everything from our sexual preferences to our office politics&#8211;as well as their implications for our moral [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/">The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are men literally born to cheat? Does monogamy actually serve women&#8217;s interests? These are among the questions that have made The Moral Animal one of the most provocative science books in recent years. Wright unveils the genetic strategies behind everything from our sexual preferences to our office politics&#8211;as well as their implications for our moral codes and public policies. Illustrations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/">The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Immigrants : Your Country Needs Them &#8211; Philippe Legrain (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/immigrants-your-country-needs-them-philippe-legrain-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Migration, Immigration & Emigration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/immigrants-your-country-needs-them-philippe-legrain-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Immigration divides our globalising world like no other issue. We are swamped by bogus asylum-seekers and infiltrated by terrorists, our jobs stolen, our benefit system abused, our way of life destroyed &#8211; or so we are told. Philippe Legrain, author of the critically acclaimed OPEN WORLD, has written the first book that looks beyond the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/immigrants-your-country-needs-them-philippe-legrain-abridged/">Immigrants : Your Country Needs Them &#8211; Philippe Legrain (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Immigration divides our globalising world like no other issue. We are swamped by bogus asylum-seekers and infiltrated by terrorists, our jobs stolen, our benefit system abused, our way of life destroyed &#8211; or so we are told. Philippe Legrain, author of the critically acclaimed OPEN WORLD, has written the first book that looks beyond the headlines. Why are ever-rising numbers of people from poor countries arriving in Europe, North America and Australasia? Can we keep them out? Should we even be trying? Combining compelling first-hand reporting from around the world, incisive socio-economic analysis and a broad understanding of what is at stake politically and culturally, IMMIGRANTS is a passionate, but lucid book. In our open world, more people will inevitably move across borders, Legrain says &#8211; and we should generally welcome them. They do the jobs we can&#8217;t or won&#8217;t do &#8211; and their diversity enriches us all. Left and right; free-marketeers and campaigners for global justice; enlightened patriots &#8211; all should rally behind the cause of freer migration, because They need Us and We need Them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/immigrants-your-country-needs-them-philippe-legrain-abridged/">Immigrants : Your Country Needs Them &#8211; Philippe Legrain (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Danes are the happiest people in the world, and pay the highest taxes. &#8216;Neutral&#8217; Sweden is one of the biggest arms manufacturers in the world. Finns have the largest per capita gun ownership after the US and Yemen. 54 per cent of Icelanders believe in elves. Norway is the richest country on earth. 5 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/">The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Danes are the happiest people in the world, and pay the highest taxes.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Neutral&#8217; Sweden is one of the biggest arms manufacturers in the world.    </p>
<p>                    Finns have the largest per capita gun ownership after the US and Yemen.    </p>
<p>                    54 per cent of Icelanders believe in elves.    </p>
<p>                    Norway is the richest country on earth.    </p>
<p>                    5 per cent of Danish men have had sex with an animal.    </p>
<p>                    Michael Booth has lived among the Scandinavians, on and off, for over ten years, perplexed by their many strange paradoxes and character traits and equally bemused by the unquestioning enthusiasm for all things Nordic and hygge that has engulfed the rest of the world.     </p>
<p>                    He leaves his adopted home of Denmark and embarks on a journey through all five of the Nordic countries to discover who these curious tribes are, the secrets of their success and, most intriguing of all, what they think of each other. Along the way a more nuanced, often darker picture emerges of a region plagued by taboos, characterised by suffocating parochialism and populated by extremists of various shades.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The next Bill Bryson.&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                    Winner of the Best Narrative Travel Book Award from the British Guild of Travel Writers</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-almost-nearly-perfect-people-behind-the-myth-of-the-scandinavian-utopia-michael-booth-abridged/">The Almost Nearly Perfect People : Behind the Myth of the Scandinavian Utopia &#8211; Michael Booth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Southern Theory : Social Science And The Global Dynamics Of Knowledge &#8211; Raewyn W. Connell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/southern-theory-social-science-and-the-global-dynamics-of-knowledge-raewyn-w-connell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/southern-theory-social-science-and-the-global-dynamics-of-knowledge-raewyn-w-connell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Southern Theory Raewyn Connell presents the case for a new &#8216;world social science&#8217; &#8211; one that is inclusive of many voices &#8211; by arguing for a more democratic global recognition of social theory from societies outside the dominant European and North American metropole. Intellectual production of the majority &#8216;southern&#8217; world does in fact include [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/southern-theory-social-science-and-the-global-dynamics-of-knowledge-raewyn-w-connell-abridged/">Southern Theory : Social Science And The Global Dynamics Of Knowledge &#8211; Raewyn W. Connell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Southern Theory Raewyn Connell presents the case for a new &#8216;world social science&#8217; &#8211; one that is inclusive of many voices &#8211; by arguing for a more democratic global recognition of social theory from societies outside the dominant European and North American metropole. Intellectual production of the majority &#8216;southern&#8217; world does in fact include theory, though its contribution is often marginalised and intellectually discredited by the metropole. Connell shows how social theory about the modern world from peripheral societies is equal in intellectual rigour and is often of greater political relevance to our changing world. Beginning with an examination of the hidden assumptions of modern general theory, Southern Theory looks to the &#8216;southern&#8217; social experience and the theories that have emerged from Australia, Indigenous peoples, Latin America, India, Africa, Islam and other post-colonial societies, as sources of important and vital contributions to world social science.<br />
                    These myriad theories offer valuable perspectives so crucial to the application of social theory in the contemporary world, having the power to transform the influence of the metropolitan hegemony on social thought by mutual regard and interaction. Southern Theory is a major new work in social theory, drawing on anthropology, history, psychology, philosophy, economics and cultural studies, with wide-ranging implications for the social sciences in the 21st century.  Visit  www.raewynconnell.net</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/southern-theory-social-science-and-the-global-dynamics-of-knowledge-raewyn-w-connell-abridged/">Southern Theory : Social Science And The Global Dynamics Of Knowledge &#8211; Raewyn W. Connell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
