<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Religious &amp; Spiritual Fiction Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/religious-spiritual-fiction/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/religious-spiritual-fiction/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Religious &amp; Spiritual Fiction Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/religious-spiritual-fiction/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Exodus : A Novel of Israel &#8211; Leon Uris</title>
		<link>/exodus-a-novel-of-israel-leon-uris/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bible Readings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious & Spiritual Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Selections & Meditations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/exodus-a-novel-of-israel-leon-uris/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Passionate summary of the inhuman treatment of the Jewish people in Europe, of the exodus in the nineteenth and twentieth centuries to Palestine, and of the triumphant founding of the new Israel.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Exodus is an international publishing phenomenon&#8211;the towering novel of the twentieth century&#8217;s most dramatic geopolitical event. Leon Uris magnificently portrays [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/exodus-a-novel-of-israel-leon-uris/">Exodus : A Novel of Israel &#8211; Leon Uris</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Passionate summary of the inhuman treatment of the Jewish people in Europe, of the exodus in the nineteenth and twentieth centuries to Palestine, and of the triumphant founding of the new Israel.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times     </p>
<p>                    Exodus is an international publishing phenomenon&#8211;the towering novel of the twentieth century&#8217;s most dramatic geopolitical event. Leon Uris magnificently portrays the birth of a new nation in the midst of enemies&#8211;the beginning of an earthshaking struggle for power. Here is the tale that swept the world with its fury: the story of an American nurse, an Israeli freedom fighter caught up in a glorious, heartbreaking, triumphant era. Here is Exodus&#8211;one of the great bestselling novels of all time.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/exodus-a-novel-of-israel-leon-uris/">Exodus : A Novel of Israel &#8211; Leon Uris</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Red Tent &#8211; Anita Diamant, Read by Carol Bilger</title>
		<link>/the-red-tent-anita-diamant-read-by-carol-bilger/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious & Spiritual Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-red-tent-anita-diamant-read-by-carol-bilger/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Deeply affecting, The Red Tent combines rich storytelling with a valuable contribution in modern fiction: a new perspective of female life in biblical society. It is a vast and stirring work described as what the Bible might have been had it been written by Gods daughters instead of sons. Far beyond the traditional women-of-the-Bible sagas [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-red-tent-anita-diamant-read-by-carol-bilger/">The Red Tent &#8211; Anita Diamant, Read by Carol Bilger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Deeply affecting, The Red Tent combines rich storytelling with a valuable contribution in modern fiction: a new perspective of female life in biblical society. It is a vast and stirring work described as what the Bible might have been had it been written by Gods daughters instead of sons. Far beyond the traditional women-of-the-Bible sagas in both impact and vigor, The Red Tent is based upon a mention in Genesis of Jacobs only female offspringâhis daughter, Dinah. Author Anita Diamant, in the voice of Dinah, gives an insiders look at the details of womens lives in biblical times and a chronicle of their earthy stories and long-ignored histories. The red tent of the title is the place where women were sequestered during their cycles of birthing, menses, and illness. It is here that Dinah hears the whispered stories of her four mothersâJacobs wives Leah, Rachel, Zilpah, and Bilhahâand tells their tales to us in remarkable and thought-provoking oratories. Familiar passages from the Bible take on new life as Dinah fills in what the Bible has left outâthe lives of women. Dinah tells us of her initiation into the religious and sexual practices of the tribe; Jacobs courtship with Rachel and Leah; the ancient world of caravans, farmers, midwives, and slaves; her ill-fated sojourn in the city of Sechem; her years in Canaan; and her half-brother Josephs rise in Egypt. Skillfully interweaving biblical tales with characters of her own invention, the author re-creates the life of Dinah providing an illuminating portrait of a courageous woman and the life she might have lived. A new view of the panorama of life in biblical times emerges from the female perspective, and the red tent itself becomes a symbol of womanly strength, love, and wisdom.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-red-tent-anita-diamant-read-by-carol-bilger/">The Red Tent &#8211; Anita Diamant, Read by Carol Bilger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Greatest Salesman in the World &#8211; Og Mandino (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-og-mandino-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Christian Testimony & Popular Inspirational Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious & Spiritual Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-og-mandino-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The runaway bestseller with more than four million copies in print! You too can change your life with the priceless wisdom of ten ancient scrolls handed down for thousands of years. &#8220;Every sales manager should read The Greatest Salesman in the World. It is a book to keep at the bedside, or on the living [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-og-mandino-abridged/">The Greatest Salesman in the World &#8211; Og Mandino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The runaway bestseller with more than four million copies in print! You too can change your life with the priceless wisdom of ten ancient scrolls handed down for thousands of years.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Every sales manager should read The Greatest Salesman in the World. It is a book to keep at the bedside, or on the living room table&#8211;a book to dip into as needed, to browse in now and then, to enjoy in small stimulating portions. It is a book for the hours and for the years, a book to turn to over and over again, as to a friend, a book of moral, spiritual and ethical guidance, an unfailing source of comfort and inspiration.&#8221;&#8211;Lester J. Bradshaw, Jr., Former Dean, Dale Carnegie Institute of Effective Speaking &#038; Human Relations     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I have read almost every book that has ever been written on salesmanship, but I think Og Mandino has captured all of them in The Greatest Salesman in the World. No one who follows these principles will ever fail as a salesman, and no one will ever be truly great without them; but, the author has done more than present the principles&#8211;he has woven them into the fabric of one of the most fascinating stories I have ever read.&#8221;&#8211;Paul J. Meyer, President of Success Motivation Institute, Inc.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I was overwhelmed by The Greatest Salesman in the World. It is, without doubt, the greatest and the most touching story I have ever read. It is so good that there are two musts that I would attach to it: First, you must not lay it down until you have finished it; and secondly, every individual who sells anything, and that includes us all, must read it.&#8221;&#8211;Robert B. Hensley, President, Life Insurance Co. of Kentucky</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-og-mandino-abridged/">The Greatest Salesman in the World &#8211; Og Mandino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
