<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Economic Growth Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/economic-growth/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/economic-growth/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Economic Growth Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/economic-growth/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why our democracies need urgent reform, before it&#8217;s too late A generation after the fall of the Berlin Wall, the world is once again on the edge of chaos. Demonstrations have broken out from Belgium to Brazil led by angry citizens demanding a greater say in their political and economic future, better education, heathcare and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/">Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why our democracies need urgent reform, before it&#8217;s too late    </p>
<p>                    A generation after the fall of the Berlin Wall, the world is once again on the edge of chaos. Demonstrations have broken out from Belgium to Brazil led by angry citizens demanding a greater say in their political and economic future, better education, heathcare and living standards. The bottom line of this outrage is the same; people are demanding their governments do more to improve their lives faster, something which policymakers are unable to deliver under conditions of anaemic growth. Rising income inequality and a stagnant economy are threats to both the developed and the developing world, and leaders can no longer afford to ignore this gathering storm.    </p>
<p>                    In Edge of Chaos, Dambisa Moyo sets out the new political and economic challenges facing the world, and the specific, radical solutions needed to resolve these issues and reignite global growth. Dambisa enumerates the four headwinds of demographics, inequality, commodity scarcity and technological innovation that are driving social and economic unrest, and argues for a fundamental retooling of democratic capitalism to address current problems and deliver better outcomes in the future. In the twenty-first century, a crisis in one country can quickly become our own, and fragile economies produce a fragile international community. Edge of Chaos is a warning for advanced and emerging nations alike: we must reverse the dramatic erosion in growth, or face the consequences of a fragmented and unstable global future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/">Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rocket: Eight Lessons to Secure Infinite Growth &#8211; Michael Silverstein, Dylan Bolden, Rune Jacobsen, Rohan Sajdeh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rocket-eight-lessons-to-secure-infinite-growth-michael-silverstein-dylan-bolden-rune-jacobsen-rohan-sajdeh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rocket-eight-lessons-to-secure-infinite-growth-michael-silverstein-dylan-bolden-rune-jacobsen-rohan-sajdeh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Make profits soar by converting casual consumers into apostles Rocket showcases the stories of sixteen entrepreneurs. It draws out the lessons that you can apply Monday morning in your business. Authentic and specific Boston Consulting Group case studies about the rocketeers/inventors who created brand legacies. For everyone who wants a business to grow faster than [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rocket-eight-lessons-to-secure-infinite-growth-michael-silverstein-dylan-bolden-rune-jacobsen-rohan-sajdeh-abridged/">Rocket: Eight Lessons to Secure Infinite Growth &#8211; Michael Silverstein, Dylan Bolden, Rune Jacobsen, Rohan Sajdeh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Make profits soar by converting casual consumers into apostles    </p>
<p>                    Rocket showcases the stories of sixteen entrepreneurs. It draws out the lessons that you can apply Monday morning in your business. Authentic and specific Boston Consulting Group case studies about the rocketeers/inventors who created brand legacies.    </p>
<p>                    For everyone who wants a business to grow faster than a competitor-this motivating book gives you a step-by-step approach to growth, share gain, and higher profits.    </p>
<p>                    Michael Silverstein  is a senior partner and managing director of the consumer practice at BCG.    </p>
<p>                    Dylan Bolden  is a senior partner and managing director at BCG.    </p>
<p>                    Rune Jacobsen  is a senior partner and managing director at BCG    </p>
<p>                    Rohan Sajdeh  is a senior partner and managing director at BCG.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rocket-eight-lessons-to-secure-infinite-growth-michael-silverstein-dylan-bolden-rune-jacobsen-rohan-sajdeh-abridged/">Rocket: Eight Lessons to Secure Infinite Growth &#8211; Michael Silverstein, Dylan Bolden, Rune Jacobsen, Rohan Sajdeh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smartest Places on Earth : Why Rustbelts Are the Emerging Hotspots of Global Innovation &#8211; Antoine van Agtmael, Fred Bakker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smartest-places-on-earth-why-rustbelts-are-the-emerging-hotspots-of-global-innovation-antoine-van-agtmael-fred-bakker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smartest-places-on-earth-why-rustbelts-are-the-emerging-hotspots-of-global-innovation-antoine-van-agtmael-fred-bakker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Antoine van Agtmael coined the term &#8220;emerging markets&#8221; and built a career and a multibillion-dollar investing firm centered on these surging economies that would, over time, supplant the West as engines of wealth and prosperity. The trend held for decades, but a few years ago van Agtmael and Alfred Bakker, a renowned European journalist, began [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-places-on-earth-why-rustbelts-are-the-emerging-hotspots-of-global-innovation-antoine-van-agtmael-fred-bakker-abridged/">The Smartest Places on Earth : Why Rustbelts Are the Emerging Hotspots of Global Innovation &#8211; Antoine van Agtmael, Fred Bakker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Antoine van Agtmael coined the term &#8220;emerging markets&#8221; and built a career and a multibillion-dollar investing firm centered on these surging economies that would, over time, supplant the West as engines of wealth and prosperity. The trend held for decades, but a few years ago van Agtmael and Alfred Bakker, a renowned European journalist, began seeing signs that the tide might be turning. For example, during a visit to an enormously successful chip company in Taiwan, the company&#8217;s leaders told them that their American competitors were now eating their lunch. And Taiwan was not the only place giving them this message.    </p>
<p>                    Thus began a remarkable two-year journey to reassess the conventional wisdom that the United States and Europe are yesterday&#8217;s story and to determine whether there something profound is happening that points the way to the creation of the next economy.     </p>
<p>                    In The Smartest Places on Earth, van Agtmael and Bakker present a truly hopeful and inspiring investigation into the emerging sources of a new era of competitiveness for America and Europe that are coming from unlikely places&#8211;those cities and areas once known as &#8220;rustbelts&#8221; that have, from an economic perspective, been written off. Take Akron, Ohio, whose economy for decades was dependent on industries such as tire manufacturing, a product now made cheaply elsewhere. In Akron and other such communities, a combination of forces&#8211;including visionary thinkers, government initiatives, start-ups making real products, and even big corporations&#8211;have succeeded in creating what van Agtmael and Bakker call a &#8220;brainbelt.&#8221; These brainbelts depend on a collaborative work style that is unique to the societies and culture of America and Europe, since they involve levels of trust and freedom of thinking that can&#8217;t be replicated elsewhere. They are producing products and technologies that are transforming industries such as vehicles and transportation, farming and food production, medical devices and health care.    </p>
<p>                    For several decades, American and European industry focused on cost by outsourcing production to those emerging markets that can make things cheaper. The tide has now turned toward being smart, as van Agtmael and Bakker report, and the next emerging market, may, in fact, be the West.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-places-on-earth-why-rustbelts-are-the-emerging-hotspots-of-global-innovation-antoine-van-agtmael-fred-bakker-abridged/">The Smartest Places on Earth : Why Rustbelts Are the Emerging Hotspots of Global Innovation &#8211; Antoine van Agtmael, Fred Bakker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Information Grows : The Evolution of Order, from Atoms to Economies &#8211; Cesar Hidalgo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-information-grows-the-evolution-of-order-from-atoms-to-economies-cesar-hidalgo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-information-grows-the-evolution-of-order-from-atoms-to-economies-cesar-hidalgo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Why Information Grows, rising star Cesar Hidalgo offers a radical interpretation of global economics What is economic growth? And why, historically, has it occurred in only a few places? Previous efforts to answer these questions have focused on institutions, geography, finances, and psychology. But MIT professor Cesar Hidalgo argues that in order to fully [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-information-grows-the-evolution-of-order-from-atoms-to-economies-cesar-hidalgo-abridged/">Why Information Grows : The Evolution of Order, from Atoms to Economies &#8211; Cesar Hidalgo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Why Information Grows, rising star Cesar Hidalgo offers a radical interpretation of global economics    </p>
<p>                    What is economic growth? And why, historically, has it occurred in only a few places? Previous efforts to answer these questions have focused on institutions, geography, finances, and psychology. But MIT professor Cesar Hidalgo argues that in order to fully grasp the nature of economic growth we need to transcend the social sciences and turn to the science of information, networks and complexity. The growth of economies, he explains, is deeply connected with the growth of order &#8211; or information.    </p>
<p>                    At first glance, the universe seems hostile to order. Thermodynamics dictates that over time, order will disappear. But thermodynamics also has loopholes that promote the growth of information in pockets. Our cities are such pockets where information grows, but they are not all the same. For every Silicon Valley, Tokyo, and London, there are dozens of places with underdeveloped economies. Why does the US economy outstrip Brazil&#8217;s, and Brazil&#8217;s that of Chad? Why did the technology corridor along Boston&#8217;s Route 128 languish while Silicon Valley blossomed? In each case, the key is how people, companies, and the networks they form process information &#8211; it is all about their knowledge, knowhow and imagination. As Hidalgo compellingly shows, economies are made of networks of people and society is a collective computer. The problem of economic development is in fact the problem of making these networks more powerful.    </p>
<p>                    A radical new interpretation of global economics, Why Information Grows overturns traditional assumptions about the development of economies and the origins of wealth and takes a crucial step toward making economics less the dismal science and more the insightful one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-information-grows-the-evolution-of-order-from-atoms-to-economies-cesar-hidalgo-abridged/">Why Information Grows : The Evolution of Order, from Atoms to Economies &#8211; Cesar Hidalgo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
