<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Miscellaneous Items Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/miscellaneous-items/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/miscellaneous-items/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Miscellaneous Items Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/miscellaneous-items/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Full Dark, No Stars : featuring 1922, now a Netflix film &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/full-dark-no-stars-featuring-1922-now-a-netflix-film-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Short Story Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/full-dark-no-stars-featuring-1922-now-a-netflix-film-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is it possible to fully know anyone? Even those we love the most? What tips someone over the edge to commit a crime? For a Nebraska farmer, the turning point comes when his wife threatens to sell off the family homestead. A cozy mystery writer plots a savage revenge after a brutal encounter with a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/full-dark-no-stars-featuring-1922-now-a-netflix-film-stephen-king/">Full Dark, No Stars : featuring 1922, now a Netflix film &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is it possible to fully know anyone? Even those we love the most? What tips someone over the edge to commit a crime?</p>
<p>                    For a Nebraska farmer, the turning point comes when his wife threatens to sell off the family homestead.</p>
<p>                    A cozy mystery writer plots a savage revenge after a brutal encounter with a stranger.</p>
<p>                    Dave Streeter gets the chance to cure himself from illness &#8211; if he agrees to impose misery on an old rival.</p>
<p>                    And Darcy Anderson discovers a box containing her husband&#8217;s dark and terrifying secrets &#8211; he&#8217;s not the man who keeps his nails short and collects coins.  And now he&#8217;s heading home . . .</p>
<p>                    Like DIFFERENT SEASONS and FOUR PAST MIDNIGHT, which generated such enduring hit films as The Shawshank Redemption and Stand by Me, FULL DARK, NO STARS proves Stephen King a master of the long story form.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/full-dark-no-stars-featuring-1922-now-a-netflix-film-stephen-king/">Full Dark, No Stars : featuring 1922, now a Netflix film &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>2019 &#8211; 2020 Academic Planner : Nineteen 06: An 18-Month Weekly Calendar for Kappa Alpha Phi Frats &#8211; July 2019 &#8211; December 2020 &#8211; P4 Publishing</title>
		<link>/2019-2020-academic-planner-nineteen-06-an-18-month-weekly-calendar-for-kappa-alpha-phi-frats-july-2019-december-2020-p4-publishing/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stationery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/2019-2020-academic-planner-nineteen-06-an-18-month-weekly-calendar-for-kappa-alpha-phi-frats-july-2019-december-2020-p4-publishing/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Use This Paperback Planner To Keep Track of All Your Important Dates, Priorities, and Obligations This planner is perfect to help you remember all your personal meetings, appointments and kids&#8217; practices, rehearsals, games, or performances. Make sure you never miss another appointment. The Cover &#8211; The cover is a sturdy paperback book with a glossy [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2019-2020-academic-planner-nineteen-06-an-18-month-weekly-calendar-for-kappa-alpha-phi-frats-july-2019-december-2020-p4-publishing/">2019 &#8211; 2020 Academic Planner : Nineteen 06: An 18-Month Weekly Calendar for Kappa Alpha Phi Frats &#8211; July 2019 &#8211; December 2020 &#8211; P4 Publishing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Use This Paperback Planner To Keep Track of All Your Important Dates, Priorities, and Obligations</p>
<p>                    This planner is perfect to help you remember all your personal meetings, appointments and kids&#8217; practices, rehearsals, games, or performances. Make sure you never miss another appointment. </p>
<p>                    The Cover &#8211; The cover is a sturdy paperback book with a glossy finish. The binding is the same as a standard paperback book. (The notebook may need to be pressed open to lie flat.)</p>
<p>                    Size Dimensions &#8211; 8.5&#8243; x 11&#8243; </p>
<p>                    The Interior &#8211; The interior of the planner holds 80 pages. </p>
<p>                    This planner is ideal for anyone with a busy schedule. It makes a great gift for birthdays, Christmas, or any other holiday.</p>
<p>                    Now that you&#8217;ve got all the details on this 2019 &#8211; 2020 academic planner, click the buy button to get your copy today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/2019-2020-academic-planner-nineteen-06-an-18-month-weekly-calendar-for-kappa-alpha-phi-frats-july-2019-december-2020-p4-publishing/">2019 &#8211; 2020 Academic Planner : Nineteen 06: An 18-Month Weekly Calendar for Kappa Alpha Phi Frats &#8211; July 2019 &#8211; December 2020 &#8211; P4 Publishing</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Isc Economics &#8216;road to Board&#8217; : A Compendium of Notes (Class 12, Series-1 Microeconomics).From a successful University of Manchester (QS-27, 2020) Economics&#8217; Applicant &#8211; Anand Kumar</title>
		<link>/isc-economics-road-to-board-a-compendium-of-notes-class-12-series-1-microeconomics-from-a-successful-university-of-manchester-qs-27-2020-economics-applicant-anand-kumar/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stationery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/isc-economics-road-to-board-a-compendium-of-notes-class-12-series-1-microeconomics-from-a-successful-university-of-manchester-qs-27-2020-economics-applicant-anand-kumar/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When I was in my class 12th, I chose economics as a subject. It&#8217;s a beautiful subject with intricate concepts and I thoroughly loved it. But there was a problem. I had to read through 569 pages of the book to understand the concepts. But only about 100 of those pages were relevant. So I [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/isc-economics-road-to-board-a-compendium-of-notes-class-12-series-1-microeconomics-from-a-successful-university-of-manchester-qs-27-2020-economics-applicant-anand-kumar/">Isc Economics &#8216;road to Board&#8217; : A Compendium of Notes (Class 12, Series-1 Microeconomics).From a successful University of Manchester (QS-27, 2020) Economics&#8217; Applicant &#8211; Anand Kumar</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When I was in my class 12th, I chose economics as a subject. It&#8217;s a beautiful subject with intricate concepts and I thoroughly loved it. But there was a problem. I had to read through 569 pages of the book to understand the concepts. But only about 100 of those pages were relevant. So I made notes of these concepts for exam purpose.After the exams, these notes lay gathering dust on my shelf. And when I got selected in University of Manchester for Economics, I realised how much knowledge lays buried in our shelves and how much time it will take another student to make the same notes. Why not form it in a book for ready reference of all those students who are taking the #isc board this year?Presenting to you all #theeconomicsguide_roadtoboard which is a compendium of ready made notes of microeconomics for class 12th. No need to shift through hundreds of pages of filler material. No need to spend hours to make notes from the book. All of this is ready for you at this link.It&#8217;s time to study smart and spend your worthy time more productively. Do share with your friends and family who are giving the board exams.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/isc-economics-road-to-board-a-compendium-of-notes-class-12-series-1-microeconomics-from-a-successful-university-of-manchester-qs-27-2020-economics-applicant-anand-kumar/">Isc Economics &#8216;road to Board&#8217; : A Compendium of Notes (Class 12, Series-1 Microeconomics).From a successful University of Manchester (QS-27, 2020) Economics&#8217; Applicant &#8211; Anand Kumar</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deliver Me From Evil : A Sadistic Foster Mother, A Childhood Torn Apart &#8211; Alloma Gilbert</title>
		<link>/deliver-me-from-evil-a-sadistic-foster-mother-a-childhood-torn-apart-alloma-gilbert/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deliver-me-from-evil-a-sadistic-foster-mother-a-childhood-torn-apart-alloma-gilbert/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When I was a little girl I believed what I was told over and over again: that I was evil, that I deserved to be tortured because I was the Devil&#8217;s child . . .&#8217; In April 2007 foster-mother Eunice Spry was sentenced to fourteen years in prison for her sadistic abuse of the children [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deliver-me-from-evil-a-sadistic-foster-mother-a-childhood-torn-apart-alloma-gilbert/">Deliver Me From Evil : A Sadistic Foster Mother, A Childhood Torn Apart &#8211; Alloma Gilbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When I was a little girl I believed what I was told over and over again: that I was evil, that I deserved to be tortured because I was the Devil&#8217;s child . . .&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     In April 2007 foster-mother Eunice Spry was sentenced to fourteen years in prison for her sadistic abuse of the children in her care. The details of her cruelty were so sickening they shocked the country. Alloma Gilbert was one of Spry&#8217;s young victims, sent to live with her at the age of six and left at her mercy for eleven brutal years.    </p>
<p>                     Eunice used her own twisted religious beliefs as an excuse for punishing her foster children. When she took them to live on an isolated farmhouse, the abuse escalated to terrifying levels &#8211; a stick was thrust down Alloma&#8217;s throat so often it was stained red with blood, she was starved for over a year and survived only by secretly eating pigswill, and the vicious beatings were relentless. At the age of seventeen she finally escaped but, alone in the outside world, she fell prey to abusive men. It was the birth of her baby daughter that saved her, that finally taught her what love really is. Written with powerful honesty,  Deliver Me From Evil is a moving and inspiring story of survival.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deliver-me-from-evil-a-sadistic-foster-mother-a-childhood-torn-apart-alloma-gilbert/">Deliver Me From Evil : A Sadistic Foster Mother, A Childhood Torn Apart &#8211; Alloma Gilbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>THE ENTREPRENEURIAL BIBLE TO VENTURE CAPITAL: Inside Secrets from the Leaders in the Startup Game &#8211; Andrew Romans (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-entrepreneurial-bible-to-venture-capital-inside-secrets-from-the-leaders-in-the-startup-game-andrew-romans-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-entrepreneurial-bible-to-venture-capital-inside-secrets-from-the-leaders-in-the-startup-game-andrew-romans-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>40 leading venture capitalists come together to teach entrepreneurs how to succeed with their startupThe Entrepreneurial Bible to Venture Capital is packed with invaluable advice about how to raise angel and venture capital funding, how to build value in a startup, and how to exit a company with maximum value for both founders and investors. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-entrepreneurial-bible-to-venture-capital-inside-secrets-from-the-leaders-in-the-startup-game-andrew-romans-abridged/">THE ENTREPRENEURIAL BIBLE TO VENTURE CAPITAL: Inside Secrets from the Leaders in the Startup Game &#8211; Andrew Romans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>40 leading venture capitalists come together to teach entrepreneurs how to succeed with their startupThe Entrepreneurial Bible to Venture Capital is packed with invaluable advice about how to raise angel and venture capital funding, how to build value in a startup, and how to exit a company with maximum value for both founders and investors. It guides entrepreneurs through every step in an entrepreneurial venture from the legalities of raising initial capital to knowing when to change tactics.    </p>
<p>                    Andrew Romans is the co-founder and general partner of Rubicon Venture Capital, a venture capital fund that invests in privately held technology companies and enables its investors to co-invest along side the fund on a deal-by-deal basis via innovative sidecar funds right up to IPO or M&#038;A exit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-entrepreneurial-bible-to-venture-capital-inside-secrets-from-the-leaders-in-the-startup-game-andrew-romans-abridged/">THE ENTREPRENEURIAL BIBLE TO VENTURE CAPITAL: Inside Secrets from the Leaders in the Startup Game &#8211; Andrew Romans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Execution Factor: The One Skill that Drives Success &#8211; Kim Perell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-execution-factor-the-one-skill-that-drives-success-kim-perell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-execution-factor-the-one-skill-that-drives-success-kim-perell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn the best-kept secret of the world&#8217;s most successful entrepreneurs: EXECUTION! Kim Perell made headlines for her amazing transformative story of a startup entrepreneur to an internationally renowned CEO and prominent angel investor. From her modest beginnings at her kitchen table, she went from broke to multi-millionaire in just a few short years. Today, she [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-execution-factor-the-one-skill-that-drives-success-kim-perell-abridged/">The Execution Factor: The One Skill that Drives Success &#8211; Kim Perell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn the best-kept secret of the world&#8217;s most successful entrepreneurs: EXECUTION!<br />
                    Kim Perell made headlines for her amazing transformative story of a startup entrepreneur to an internationally renowned CEO and prominent angel investor.  From her modest beginnings at her kitchen table, she went from broke to multi-millionaire in just a few short years.  Today, she has investments in over 70 startups many of which have been sold to some of the largest Fortune 500 companies.  Now, in The Execution Factor, she offers indispensable wisdom as she shares her personal journey and proven program for achieving success.<br />
                    The Execution Factor offers a straightforward approach to success &#8211; deliberately designed in a way that anyone can master. Perell flips the notion on its head that success is all about having a great idea, an advanced degree or a high IQ.  Because people around the world have achieved their dreams without any of those things.  Perell believes the ability to execute is the difference between success and failure.<br />
                    **Perell is so confident that committing to mastering these 5 traits of execution will lead to your success, that she is putting all of her book royalties into an Execution Fund to help others turn their dreams into reality.  The Execution Fund is a seed stage fund that will invest a minimum of $1 million into execution-led companies, providing early financing to entrepreneurs and connecting them with an extensive network of industry experts.**<br />
                    The Execution Factor is for anyone looking to transform themselves from a &#8220;dreamer&#8221; to a &#8220;doer&#8221; and will make you feel like you have a success coach by your side. Perell teaches her unique 5 traits of execution: vision, passion, action, resilience, and relationships.  By the time you&#8217;ve completed the book you will have a have a blueprint to achieve your dreams in business and in life. Don&#8217;t settle for ordinary when you can have extraordinary.   Master execution and change your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-execution-factor-the-one-skill-that-drives-success-kim-perell-abridged/">The Execution Factor: The One Skill that Drives Success &#8211; Kim Perell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Widgets: The 12 New Rules for Managing Your Employees as if They&#8217;re Real People &#8211; Rodd Wagner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/widgets-the-12-new-rules-for-managing-your-employees-as-if-theyre-real-people-rodd-wagner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/widgets-the-12-new-rules-for-managing-your-employees-as-if-theyre-real-people-rodd-wagner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling author Rodd Wagner tackles one of the most destructive problems facing organizations today-the breakdown of the relationship between employees and the organizations they work for &#8220;Your people are not your greatest asset. They&#8217;re not yours, and they&#8217;re not assets.&#8221; With this declaration, one of the leading authorities on employee performance rolls [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/widgets-the-12-new-rules-for-managing-your-employees-as-if-theyre-real-people-rodd-wagner-abridged/">Widgets: The 12 New Rules for Managing Your Employees as if They&#8217;re Real People &#8211; Rodd Wagner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling author Rodd Wagner tackles one of the most destructive problems facing organizations today-the breakdown of the relationship between employees and the organizations they work for    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Your people are not your greatest asset. They&#8217;re not yours, and they&#8217;re not assets.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    With this declaration, one of the leading authorities on employee performance rolls up his sleeves against the weasel words, contradictions, bad habits, and intrusions that reduce people to &#8220;human resources.&#8221; To &#8220;FTEs.&#8221; To &#8220;human capital.&#8221; To flesh-and-blood widgets.    </p>
<p>                    Armed with empirical evidence from the provocative studies he leads around the globe, Wagner guides you through the new realities of what it takes to get the highest levels of intensity from people in a more mercenary, skeptical, and wired work world. He explains how elements such as individualization, fearlessness, transparency, recognition, and coolness are reciprocated with loyalty, productivity, innovation, and&#8211;inescapably&#8211;corporate reputation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/widgets-the-12-new-rules-for-managing-your-employees-as-if-theyre-real-people-rodd-wagner-abridged/">Widgets: The 12 New Rules for Managing Your Employees as if They&#8217;re Real People &#8211; Rodd Wagner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SPIN Selling &#8211; Neil Rackham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/spin-selling-neil-rackham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/spin-selling-neil-rackham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The international bestseller that revolutionized high-end selling! Written by Neil Rackham, former president and founder of Huthwaite corporation, SPIN Selling is essential reading for anyone involved in selling or managing a sales force. Unquestionably the best-documented account of sales success ever collected and the result of the Huthwaite corporation&#8217;s massive 12-year, $1-million dollar research into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spin-selling-neil-rackham-abridged/">SPIN Selling &#8211; Neil Rackham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The international bestseller that revolutionized high-end selling!    </p>
<p>                    Written by Neil Rackham, former president and founder of Huthwaite corporation, SPIN Selling is essential reading for anyone involved in selling or managing a sales force. Unquestionably the best-documented account of sales success ever collected and the result of the Huthwaite corporation&#8217;s massive 12-year, $1-million dollar research into effective sales performance, this groundbreaking resource details the revolutionary SPIN (Situation, Problem, Implication, Need-payoff) strategy.    </p>
<p>                     In SPIN Selling, Rackham, who has advised leading companies such as IBM and Honeywell delivers the first book to specifically examine selling high-value product and services. By following the simple, practical, and easy-to-apply techniques of SPIN, readers will be able to dramatically increase their sales volume from major accounts. Rackham answers key questions such as &#8220;What makes success in major sales&#8221; and  &#8220;Why do techniques like closing work in small sales but fail in larger ones?&#8221;    </p>
<p>                      You will learn why traditional sales methods which were developed for small consumer sales, just won&#8217;t work for large sales and why conventional selling methods are doomed to fail in major sales. Packed with real-world examples, illuminating graphics, and informative case studies &#8211; and backed by hard research data &#8211; SPIN Selling is the million-dollar key to understanding and producing record-breaking high-end sales performance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spin-selling-neil-rackham-abridged/">SPIN Selling &#8211; Neil Rackham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge    </p>
<p>                    With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. This clear, concise, and accessible guide from two industry insiders shows you how to navigate this brave new blockchain world-and how to invest in these emerging assets to secure your financial future.    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets gives you all the tools you need:    </p>
<p>                    * An actionable framework for investigating and valuing cryptoassets     </p>
<p>                    * Portfolio management techniques to maximize returns while managing risk    </p>
<p>                    * Historical context and tips to navigate inevitable bubbles and manias    </p>
<p>                    * Practical guides to exchanges, wallets, capital market vehicles, and ICOs    </p>
<p>                    * Predictions on how blockchain technology may disrupt current portfolios    </p>
<p>                    In addition to offering smart investment strategies, this authoritative resource will help you understand how these assets were created, how they work, and how they are evolving amid the blockchain revolution. The authors define a clear and original cryptoasset taxonomy, composed of cryptocurrencies, cryptocommodities, and cryptotokens, with insights into how each subset is blending technology and markets. You&#8217;ll find a variety of methods to invest in these assets, whether through global exchanges that trade 24/7 or initial cryptoasset offerings (ICOs). By sequentially building on the concepts of each prior chapter, the book will provide you with a full understanding of the cryptoasset economy and the opportunities that await the innovative investor .    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets represent the future of money and markets. This book is your guide to that future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Visual Storytelling: How to Use Visuals, Videos, and Social Media to Market Your Brand &#8211; Ekaterina Walter, Jessica Gioglio (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Attention is the new commodity. Visual Storytelling is the new currency. Human brain processes visuals 60,000x faster than text.Web posts with visuals drive up to 180% more engagement than those without.Viewers spend 100% more time on web pages with videos. Filled with full-color images and thought-provoking examples from leading companies, The Power of Visual Storytelling [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/">The Power of Visual Storytelling: How to Use Visuals, Videos, and Social Media to Market Your Brand &#8211; Ekaterina Walter, Jessica Gioglio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Attention is the new commodity. Visual Storytelling is the new currency.    </p>
<p>                    Human brain processes visuals 60,000x faster than text.Web posts with visuals drive up to 180% more engagement than those without.Viewers spend 100% more time on web pages with videos.<br />
                    Filled with full-color images and thought-provoking examples from leading companies, The Power of Visual Storytelling explains how to grow your business and strengthen your brand by leveraging photos, videos, infographics, presentations, and other rich media. The book delivers a powerful road map for getting started, while inspiring new levels of creativity within organizations of all types and sizes.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book is not only a complete overview of [visual storytelling] but, most importantly, the key to doing it right, a total Right Hook!&#8221;<br />
                    -Gary Vaynerchuk, New York Times bestselling author of Crush It! and Jab, Jab, Jab, Right Hook    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A valuable guide to understanding how to develop powerful marketing programs using the art of visual storytelling.&#8221;<br />
                    -Guy Kawasaki, author of APE: Author, Publisher, Entrepreneur and former chief evangelist of Apple    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The Power of Visual Storytelling is the new marketing bible!&#8221;<br />
                    -Nancy Bhagat, Vice President, Global Marketing Strategy and Campaigns, Intel    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If a picture is worth a thousand words, The Power of Visual Storytelling is worth a million.&#8221;<br />
                    -Scott Monty, Global Digital &#038; Multimedia Communications for Ford Motor Company</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/">The Power of Visual Storytelling: How to Use Visuals, Videos, and Social Media to Market Your Brand &#8211; Ekaterina Walter, Jessica Gioglio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Epic Content Marketing: How to Tell a Different Story, Break through the Clutter, and Win More Customers by Marketing Less &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of FORTUNE Magazine&#8217;s Top 5 Business Book Must-Reads How do you cut through the noise, commotion, and bad information that is right now cluttering up your customers&#8217; digital space? EPIC CONTENT MARKETINGOne of the world&#8217;s leading experts on content marketing, Joe Pulizzi explains how to attract prospects and customers by creating information and content [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Epic Content Marketing: How to Tell a Different Story, Break through the Clutter, and Win More Customers by Marketing Less &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of FORTUNE Magazine&#8217;s Top 5 Business Book Must-Reads How do you cut through the noise, commotion, and bad information that is right now cluttering up your customers&#8217; digital space?    </p>
<p>                    EPIC CONTENT MARKETINGOne of the world&#8217;s leading experts on content marketing, Joe Pulizzi explains how to attract prospects and customers by creating information and content they actually want to engage with. No longer can we interrupt our customers with mediocre content and sales messages they don&#8217;t care about.    </p>
<p>                    Epic Content Marketing takes you step-by-stepthrough the process of developing stories that inform and entertain and compel customers to act&#8211;without actually telling them to. Epic content, distributed to the right person at the right time, is the way to truly capture the hearts and minds of customers. It&#8217;s how to position your business as a trusted expert in its industry. It&#8217;s what customers share and talk about.    </p>
<p>                    Once we hook customers with epic content, they reward us by sending our sales through the roof.    </p>
<p>                    Epic Content Marketing provides everything youneed to:    </p>
<p>                    Determine what your content niche should be to attract and retain customersDiscover and develop your content marketing mission statementSet up a process for creating and curating epic contentLearn how to leverage social and e-mail channels to create&#8211;and grow&#8211;your audienceMeasure the performance of your content&#8211;and increase your content marketing budget    </p>
<p>                    With in-depth case studies of how John Deere, LEGO, Coca-Cola, and other leading corporations are using content to drive epic sales, this groundbreaking guide gives you all the tools to start creating and disseminating content that leads directly to greater profits and growth.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re the CMO of a Fortune 500, a digital marketer, or an entrepreneur, Epic Content Marketing gives you the tools you need to vanquish the competition. Start your epic journey now!    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR EPIC CONTENT MARKETING&#8221;From the man who invented content marketing. Listen to this guy. He really understands the new world of marketing. The concepts in Epic Content Marketing are usable all over the world&#8211;instantly usable and useful for any business.&#8221; &#8212; Don Schultz, the &#8220;father of integrated marketing,&#8221; Professor Emeritus at Northwestern University&#8217;s Medill School of Journalism, and author of 13 books    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Joe Pulizzi&#8217;s ideas are so consistently . . . well, epic (!) that they really don&#8217;t need any endorsement by anyone. But here&#8217;s mine anyway: You don&#8217;t need MORE content. You need the right kind of content,strategically applied. For those organizations struggling to create a content marketing program that drives results, Joe delivers. Again.&#8221; &#8212; Ann Handley, coauthor of Content Rules and Chief Content Officer, MarketingProfs    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;As Joe shows us in his wonderful Epic Content Marketing, you must unlearn interrupting people with your nonsense. Instead, publish the valuable content they want to consume and are eager to share.&#8221; &#8212; David Meerman Scott, marketing strategist and bestselling author ofThe New Rules of Marketing and PR    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This is a brilliant canter through the rapid and ever-changing world of content marketing. Joe has managed to capture the right blend of art and science as he plots the major trends impacting all marketers right now.&#8221; &#8212; Jonathan Mildenhall, VP, Global Advertising Strategy and Creative Excellence, Coca-Cola Company    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You could say that Joe Pulizzi wrote the book on content marketing, but now it&#8217;s more than just a saying.It&#8217;s what you&#8217;re holding in your hands. If you truly want to be successful at content marketing, Pulizzi is one of the few who can show you the way.&#8221; &#8212; Mitch Joel, President, Twist Image, and author of Six Pixels of Separation and CTRL ALT Delete    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Joe Pulizzi may know more about content marketing than any person alive. He proves it in these pages.&#8221; &#8212; Jay Baer, New York Times bestselling author of Youtility: Why Smart Marketing is About Help Not Hype    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The future of successful brand building, and especially the art of solidifying the emotional connection between people and brands, will require expertise in Content Marketing. Epic Content Marketing gives all the details practitioners need without overcomplicating.&#8221; &#8212; Professor JoAnn Sciarrino, Knight Chair, Digital Advertising and Marketing, UNC Chapel Hill    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Joe Pulizzi is the godfather of our burgeoning profession of Content Marketing. He lays out the objectives, principles, and core strategies of our field in a way that&#8217;s easy-to-understand, inspiring, and entertaining. If your company doesn&#8217;t yet realize that it&#8217;s a media company, with all the challenges and advantages that implies, you&#8217;re missing the most powerful way to connect with your customers.&#8221; &#8212; Julie Fleischer, Director, Media &#038; Consumer Engagement, Kraft Foods</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Epic Content Marketing: How to Tell a Different Story, Break through the Clutter, and Win More Customers by Marketing Less &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated for the post-COVID economy! The proven low-risk, cost-effective way to launch a successful business Today&#8217;s markets are getting more and more dynamic, and customers are increasingly fickle. Meanwhile the COVID-driven economic crash has made mitigating financial risk more important than ever. From one of today&#8217;s leading experts in content marketing, Content Inc. is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated for the post-COVID economy! The proven low-risk, cost-effective way to launch a successful business     </p>
<p>                    Today&#8217;s markets are getting more and more dynamic, and customers are increasingly fickle. Meanwhile the COVID-driven economic crash has made mitigating financial risk more important than ever.    </p>
<p>                    From one of today&#8217;s leading experts in content marketing, Content Inc. is the go-to guide to building a solid small-business by establishing a loyal audience before you sell any products or services. In these pages, Joe Pulizzi provides a lower-risk, better way to build a successful business by re-engineering the process that so often leads to failure: You&#8217;ll learn how to develop valuable content, build an audience around that content-and then create a product for that audience. Content Inc. walks you through the entire process, showing how to    </p>
<p>                    Identify the intersection of your expertise and your future customer&#8217;s needs<br />
                    Determine how to &#8220;tilt&#8221; your sweet spot to find a place where little or no competition exists<br />
                    Establish your number-one channel for disseminating content (blog, podcast, YouTube, etc.)<br />
                    Use social-media and SEO to convert one-time visitors into long-term subscribers<br />
                    Grow your business by expanding into multiple delivery channels<br />
                    Monetize your product or service for ultimate business success<br />
                    Understand how to sell your content asset for millions or build the business into a large enterprise    </p>
<p>                    This fully updated edition includes new and enhanced coverage of platforms like TikTok, SnapChat, and Instagram, a new section about the exit strategy for the model, more practical how-tos, and current examples of companies that have successfully implemented these strategies.      </p>
<p>                    Apply the methods laid out for you in Content Inc., and before you know it, you&#8217;ll be running your own profitable, scalable business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Vindication of the Rights of Woman (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Mary Wollstonecraft (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Discover Wollstonecraft&#8217;s classic feminist text in an abridged, digestible form. WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY ZOE WILLIAMS The term feminism did not yet exist when Mary Wollstonecraft wrote this book, but it was the first great piece of feminist writing. In these pages you will find the essence of her argument &#8211; for the education of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/">A Vindication of the Rights of Woman (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Mary Wollstonecraft (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Discover Wollstonecraft&#8217;s classic feminist text in an abridged, digestible form.    </p>
<p>                    WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY ZOE WILLIAMS     </p>
<p>                    The term feminism did not yet exist when Mary Wollstonecraft wrote this book, but it was the first great piece of feminist writing. In these pages you will find the essence of her argument &#8211; for the education of women and for an increased female contribution to society. Her work made the first ripples of what would later become the tidal wave of the women&#8217;s rights movement. Rationalist but revolutionary, Wollstonecraft changed the world for women.    </p>
<p>                    Vintage Feminism: classic feminist texts in short form</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/">A Vindication of the Rights of Woman (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Mary Wollstonecraft (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happier: Can you learn to be Happy? (UK Paperback) &#8211; Tal Ben-Shahar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happier-can-you-learn-to-be-happy-uk-paperback-tal-ben-shahar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happier-can-you-learn-to-be-happy-uk-paperback-tal-ben-shahar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Can You Learn to Be Happy? &#8220;There are few self-help books more resolutley down to earth than Happier&#8230;Ben Shahar provides straightforward guidelines for integrating habits of gratitude and accepting negative emotions into daily life&#8221; Observer, January 2012YES . . . according to the teacher of Harvard University&#8217;s most popular and life-changing course. One out of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happier-can-you-learn-to-be-happy-uk-paperback-tal-ben-shahar-abridged/">Happier: Can you learn to be Happy? (UK Paperback) &#8211; Tal Ben-Shahar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Can You Learn to Be Happy? &#8220;There are few self-help books more resolutley down to earth than Happier&#8230;Ben Shahar provides straightforward guidelines for integrating habits of gratitude and accepting negative emotions into daily life&#8221; Observer, January 2012YES . . . according to the teacher of Harvard University&#8217;s most popular and life-changing course. One out of every five Harvard students has lined up to hear Tal Ben-Shahar&#8217;s insightful and inspiring lectures on that ever-elusive state: HAPPINESS. HOW?<br />
                    Grounded in the revolutionary &#8220;positive psychology&#8221; movement, Ben-Shahar ingeniously combines scientific studies, scholarly research, self-help advice, and spiritual enlightenment. He weaves them together into a set of principles that you can apply to your daily life. Once you open your heart and mind to Happier &#8216;s thoughts, you will feel more fulfilled, more connected . . . and, yes, HAPPIER. &#8220;This fine book shimmers with a rare brand of good sense that is imbedded in scientific knowledge about how to increase happiness. It is easy to see how this is the backbone of the most popular course at Harvard today.&#8221; &#8211; Martin E. P. Seligman, author of Authentic Happiness This paperback edition contains a preview chapter of Tal Ben-Shahar&#8217;s &#8216;The Pursuit of Perfect&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happier-can-you-learn-to-be-happy-uk-paperback-tal-ben-shahar-abridged/">Happier: Can you learn to be Happy? (UK Paperback) &#8211; Tal Ben-Shahar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Story Of Sushi : An Unlikely Story of Raw Fish and Rice &#8211; Trevor Corson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-story-of-sushi-an-unlikely-story-of-raw-fish-and-rice-trevor-corson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cooking With Fish & Seafood]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Aquatic Creatures]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-story-of-sushi-an-unlikely-story-of-raw-fish-and-rice-trevor-corson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Editor&#8217;s Choice Everything you never knew about sushi&#8211; its surprising origins, the colorful lives of its chefs, and the bizarre behavior of the creatures that compose it Trevor Corson takes us behind the scenes at America&#8217;s first sushi-chef training academy, as eager novices strive to master the elusive art of cooking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-sushi-an-unlikely-story-of-raw-fish-and-rice-trevor-corson-abridged/">The Story Of Sushi : An Unlikely Story of Raw Fish and Rice &#8211; Trevor Corson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Editor&#8217;s Choice    </p>
<p>                    Everything you never knew about sushi&#8211; its surprising origins, the colorful lives of its chefs, and the bizarre behavior of the creatures that compose it    </p>
<p>                    Trevor Corson takes us behind the scenes at America&#8217;s first sushi-chef training academy, as eager novices strive to master the elusive art of cooking without cooking. He delves into the biology and natural history of the edible creatures of the sea, and tells the fascinating story of an Indo-Chinese meal reinvented in nineteenth-century Tokyo as a cheap fast food. He reveals the pioneers who brought sushi to the United States and explores how this unlikely meal is exploding into the American heartland just as the long-term future of sushi may be unraveling.    </p>
<p>                    The Story of Sushi is at once a compelling tale of human determination and a delectable smorgasbord of surprising food science, intrepid reporting, and provocative cultural history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-sushi-an-unlikely-story-of-raw-fish-and-rice-trevor-corson-abridged/">The Story Of Sushi : An Unlikely Story of Raw Fish and Rice &#8211; Trevor Corson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pitch Anything: An Innovative Method for Presenting, Persuading, and Winning the Deal &#8211; Oren Klaff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/pitch-anything-an-innovative-method-for-presenting-persuading-and-winning-the-deal-oren-klaff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pitch-anything-an-innovative-method-for-presenting-persuading-and-winning-the-deal-oren-klaff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gold Medal Winner&#8211;Tops Sales World&#8217;s Best Sales and Marketing Book &#8220;Fast, fun and immensely practical.&#8221; -JOE SULLIVAN, Founder, Flextronics &#8220;Move over Neil Strauss and game theory. Pitch Anything reveals the next big thing in social dynamics: game for business.&#8221; -JOSH WHITFORD, Founder, Echelon Media &#8220;What do supermodels and venture capitalists have in common?They hear hundreds [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pitch-anything-an-innovative-method-for-presenting-persuading-and-winning-the-deal-oren-klaff-abridged/">Pitch Anything: An Innovative Method for Presenting, Persuading, and Winning the Deal &#8211; Oren Klaff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gold Medal Winner&#8211;Tops Sales World&#8217;s Best Sales and Marketing Book    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Fast, fun and immensely practical.&#8221;<br />
                    -JOE SULLIVAN, Founder, Flextronics    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Move over Neil Strauss and game theory. Pitch Anything reveals the next big thing in social dynamics: game for business.&#8221;<br />
                    -JOSH WHITFORD, Founder, Echelon Media    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;What do supermodels and venture capitalists have in common?They hear hundreds of pitches a year. Pitch Anything makes sure you get the nod (or wink) you deserve.&#8221;<br />
                    -RALPH CRAM, Investor    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Pitch Anything offers a new method that will differentiate you from the rest of the pack.&#8221;<br />
                    -JASON JONES, Senior Vice President, Jones Lang LaSalle    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If you want to pitch a product, raise money, or close a deal, read Pitch Anything and put its principles to work.&#8221;<br />
                    -STEVEN WALDMAN, Principal and Founder, Spectrum Capital    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Pitch Anything opened my eyes to what I had been missing in my presentations and business interactions.&#8221;<br />
                    -LOUIE UCCIFERRI, President, Regent Capital Group    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I use Oren&#8217;s unique strategies to sell deals, raise money, and handle tough situations.&#8221;<br />
                    -TAYLOR GARRETT, Vice President, White Cap    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A counter-intuitive method that works.&#8221;<br />
                    -JAY GOYAL, CEO, SumOpti    </p>
<p>                    About the Book:    </p>
<p>                    When it comes to delivering a pitch, Oren Klaff has unparalleled credentials. Over the past 13 years, he has used his one-of-a- kind method to raise more than $400 million-and now, for the fi rst time, he describes his formula to help you deliver a winning pitch in any business situation.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re selling ideas to investors, pitching a client for new business, or even negotiating for a higher salary, Pitch Anything will transform the way you position your ideas.    </p>
<p>                    According to Klaff, creating and presenting a great pitch isn&#8217;t an art-it&#8217;s a simple science. Applying the latest findings in the field of neuroeconomics, while sharing eye-opening stories of his method in action, Klaff describes how the brain makes decisions and responds to pitches. With this information, you&#8217;ll remain in complete control of every stage of the pitch process.    </p>
<p>                    Pitch Anything introduces the exclusive STRONG method of pitching, which can be put to use immediately:    </p>
<p>                    Setting the Frame<br />
                    Telling the Story<br />
                    Revealing the Intrigue<br />
                    Offering the Prize<br />
                    Nailing the Hookpoint<br />
                    Getting a Decision    </p>
<p>                    One truly great pitch can improve your career, make you a lot of money-and even change your life. Success is dependent on the method you use, not how hard you try. &#8220;Better method, more money,&#8221; Klaff says. &#8220;Much better method, much more money.&#8221; Klaff is the best in the business because his method is much better than anyone else&#8217;s. And now it&#8217;s yours.    </p>
<p>                    Apply the tactics and strategies outlined inPitch Anything to engage and persuade your audience-and you&#8217;ll have more funding and support than you ever thought possible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pitch-anything-an-innovative-method-for-presenting-persuading-and-winning-the-deal-oren-klaff-abridged/">Pitch Anything: An Innovative Method for Presenting, Persuading, and Winning the Deal &#8211; Oren Klaff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for staying top of mind with your audience-from Inc.com&#8217;s #1 content marketing company What do all successful businesses have in common? They&#8217;re the first name that comes to mind when people think about their particular market. How do companies achieve this? By developing habits and strategies that focus on building meaningful relationships and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/">Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for staying top of mind with your audience-from Inc.com&#8217;s #1 content marketing company     </p>
<p>                    What do all successful businesses have in common? They&#8217;re the first name that comes to mind when people think about their particular market. How do companies achieve this? By developing habits and strategies that focus on building meaningful relationships and delivering value consistently, day in and day out.    </p>
<p>                    In Top of Mind, the cofounder of a leading content marketing company shows you how to create business opportunities by occupying the space at the top of your audience&#8217;s minds-and keeping it there. This groundbreaking book explains how consumer needs and expectations have changed and what this shift means for readers interested in building a brand-whether you&#8217;re a leader in marketing engaging potential customers, a VP of sales bringing in new business, or a director of HR who&#8217;s recruiting the best talent in the industry. It provides effective ways to establish trust and foster connections; maintain transparency and consistency; identify and clearly communicate the &#8220;why&#8221; behind the message; and create processes to make that message part of a brand&#8217;s DNA.     </p>
<p>                    Maintaining a prominent spot in your audience&#8217;s minds will increase the likelihood that the moment they need to make a choice, you&#8217;ll be the first one they call.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/">Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Psychobabble : Exploding the myths of the self-help generation &#8211; Stephen Dr. Briers (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/psychobabble-exploding-the-myths-of-the-self-help-generation-stephen-dr-briers-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/psychobabble-exploding-the-myths-of-the-self-help-generation-stephen-dr-briers-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exposing the self-help myths that make us all more miserable. This is what your psychologist would really tell you-if he thought you could handle it! This is the kick up the backside the self-help genre needs: an intelligent, provocative and thought-provoking expose of the modern myths that we&#8217;re told make us happier, but in reality [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/psychobabble-exploding-the-myths-of-the-self-help-generation-stephen-dr-briers-abridged/">Psychobabble : Exploding the myths of the self-help generation &#8211; Stephen Dr. Briers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exposing the self-help myths that make us all more miserable. This is what your psychologist would really tell you-if he thought you could handle it!    </p>
<p>                     This is the kick up the backside the self-help genre needs: an intelligent, provocative and thought-provoking expose of the modern myths that we&#8217;re told make us happier, but in reality screw us up.     </p>
<p>                     Clinical psychologist, Dr Stephen Briers shines a light into the dark corners of self-help and explodes the myths, false hopes, quack philosophies and unrealistic expectations it routinely advocates. It is a refreshing antidote to the `same old same old&#8217; approaches, offering a radical re-think of the way we approach problems in our lives, offering empowering new perspectives and expert advice on avoiding the biggest life traps. Dr Briers questions the perceived wisdom, shakes up the status quo, and encourages us to think again.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/psychobabble-exploding-the-myths-of-the-self-help-generation-stephen-dr-briers-abridged/">Psychobabble : Exploding the myths of the self-help generation &#8211; Stephen Dr. Briers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Millionaire Real Estate Agent &#8211; Gary Keller, Dave Jenks, Jay Papasan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-millionaire-real-estate-agent-gary-keller-dave-jenks-jay-papasan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[English Language: Reading & Writing Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-millionaire-real-estate-agent-gary-keller-dave-jenks-jay-papasan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Take your real estate career to the highest level! &#8216;Gary Keller knows the beauty of a simple path to a spectacular goal! Whether you are just getting started or a veteran in the business, &#8220;The Millionaire Real Estate Agent&#8221; is the step-by-step handbook for seeking excellence in your profession and in your life&#8217; &#8211; Mark [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-millionaire-real-estate-agent-gary-keller-dave-jenks-jay-papasan-abridged/">The Millionaire Real Estate Agent &#8211; Gary Keller, Dave Jenks, Jay Papasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Take your real estate career to the highest level! &#8216;Gary Keller knows the beauty of a simple path to a spectacular goal! Whether you are just getting started or a veteran in the business, &#8220;The Millionaire Real Estate Agent&#8221; is the step-by-step handbook for seeking excellence in your profession and in your life&#8217; &#8211; Mark Victor Hansen, co-creator, number 1 &#8220;New York Times&#8221; best-selling series &#8220;Chicken Soup for the Soul&#8221;, co-author, &#8220;The One Minute Manager&#8221;. &#8216;This book presents a new paradigm for real estate and should be required reading for real estate professionals everywhere&#8217; &#8211; Robert T. Kiyosaki, &#8220;New York Times&#8221;, best-selling author of &#8220;Rich Dad, Poor Dad&#8221;. &#8216;In &#8220;The Millionaire Real Estate Agent&#8221;, Gary Keller&#8217;s positive influence on the careers of so many agents is encapsulated for all to enjoy and utilize&#8217; &#8211; Howard Brinton, Founder and CEO, Star Power Systems, Inc. &#8216;Gary Keller understands that to become a real millionaire, it starts with a change in your thinking. You must treat your business like a business with a focus on long-term profitability&#8217; &#8211; Brian Buffini, President and Founder, Providence Systems, Inc.Anyone who wants to turn their real estate practice into a highly successful business must understand the fundamental models that drive the best real estate agents in the industry.<br />
                    In &#8220;The Millionaire Real Estate Agent&#8221; these models are revealed and explained. This book represents the culmination of decades of real estate experience, research, and consulting, with case studies from some of the top millionaire agents in the U.S. In this revolutionary handbook you&#8217;ll learn: three key concepts that drive mega-agent production. It provides essential economic, budgetary, organizational, and lead generation models that are the foundations of any high-achiever&#8217;s business.The distinguishing characteristic of &#8220;Millionaire Real Estate Agents&#8221; &#8211; the way they think! How you can get on the real estate career path to &#8216;earn a million,&#8217; &#8216;net a million,&#8217; and then &#8216;receive a million&#8217; dollars in annual income. &#8220;The Millionaire Real Estate Agent&#8221; is not about quick fixes. It is about the innovative application of proven business techniques to the real estate industry. Isn&#8217;t it about time you put your career on the path to becoming a &#8220;Millionaire Real Estate Agent&#8221;.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-millionaire-real-estate-agent-gary-keller-dave-jenks-jay-papasan-abridged/">The Millionaire Real Estate Agent &#8211; Gary Keller, Dave Jenks, Jay Papasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Be a Power Connector: The 5+50+100 Rule for Turning Your Business Network into Profits &#8211; Judy Robinett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Create a personal &#8220;power grid&#8221; of influence to spark professional and personal success&#8221;Other people have the answers, deals, money, access, power, and influence you need to get what you want in this world. To achieve any goal, you need other people to help you do it.&#8221; &#8212; JUDY ROBINETT As anyone in business knows, strategic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/">How to Be a Power Connector: The 5+50+100 Rule for Turning Your Business Network into Profits &#8211; Judy Robinett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Create a personal &#8220;power grid&#8221; of influence to spark professional and personal success&#8221;Other people have the answers, deals, money, access, power, and influence you need to get what you want in this world. To achieve any goal, you need other people to help you do it.&#8221; &#8212; JUDY ROBINETT    </p>
<p>                    As anyone in business knows, strategic planning iscritical to achieving long-term success. In How to Be a Power Connector, super-networker Judy Robinett argues that strategic relationship planning should be your top priority.    </p>
<p>                    When you combine your specific skills and talents with a clear, workable path for creating and managing your relationships, nothing will stop you from meeting your goals. With high-value connections, you&#8217;ll tap into a dynamic &#8220;power grid&#8221; of influence guaranteed to accelerate your personal and professional success.    </p>
<p>                    Robinett uses her decades of experience connecting the world&#8217;s highest achievers with one another to help you build high-value relationships. She reveals all the secrets of her trade, including proven ways to:    </p>
<p>                    Find and enter the best network &#8220;ecosystem&#8221; to meet your goalsReach even the most unreachable people quickly and effectivelyGet anyone&#8217;s contact information within 30 secondsCreate a &#8220;3-D connection&#8221; that adds value to multiple people at the same timeAccess key infl uencers through industry and community eventsSubtly seed conversation with information about interests and needsUse social media to your best advantage    </p>
<p>                    Robinett has based her methods on solid researchproving that social groups begin to break up when they become larger than 150 people, and that 50 members is the optimal size for group communication. As such, she has developed what she calls the &#8220;5+50+100&#8243; method: contact your top 5 connections daily, your Key 50 weekly, and your Vital 100 monthly. this is your power grid, and it will work wonders for your career.    </p>
<p>                    Nothing will stop you when you learn How to Be aPower Connector.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR HOW TO BE A POWER CONNECTOR:&#8221;Unlike many books in this genre, this one is written by a woman who has lived it.. . . Judy Robinett offers guidance on how to form authentic relationships thatbring mutual benefits.&#8221; &#8212; ADAM GRANT, Wharton professor and New York Times bestselling author of Give and Take    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;How to Be a Power Connector is like an MBA in networking: an advanced course in finding and developing quality relationships with the people who can make the biggest difference in your professional success.&#8221; &#8212; IVAN MISNER, founder and chairman of BNI    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Talk about power! Follow Judy Robinett&#8217;s logical, straightforward, and helpfully detailed advice, and you can be a &#8216;Power Connector&#8217; yourself! Great ideas, wellpresented, with no &#8216;wasted space&#8217; in her argument!&#8221; &#8212; DON PEPPERS, coauthor of Extreme Trust: Honesty as a Competitive Advantage    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Absolutely brilliant. A step-by-step guide to building a network that will be both invaluable to you and just as valuable to those whose lives you will now have theopportunity to touch. I can&#8217;t imagine a more powerful book for one who truly desires to be a Power Connector.&#8221; &#8212; BOB BURG, coauthor of The Go-Giver and author of Adversaries into Allies    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;In the C-Suite or in your personal life everything comes down to the quality of your relationships. Judy&#8217;s book helps you attract and maintain the relationships that will get you what you want most. Be a super connector now!&#8221; &#8212; JEFFREY HAYZLETT, TV host and bestselling author of Running the Gauntlet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/">How to Be a Power Connector: The 5+50+100 Rule for Turning Your Business Network into Profits &#8211; Judy Robinett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemba Kaizen: A Commonsense Approach to a Continuous Improvement Strategy, Second Edition &#8211; Masaaki Imai (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/gemba-kaizen-a-commonsense-approach-to-a-continuous-improvement-strategy-second-edition-masaaki-imai-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Quality Control]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance (QA) & Total Quality Management (TQM)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/gemba-kaizen-a-commonsense-approach-to-a-continuous-improvement-strategy-second-edition-masaaki-imai-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Publisher&#8217;s Note: Products purchased from Third Party sellers are not guaranteed by the publisher for quality, authenticity, or access to any online entitlements included with the product. The definitive, fully up-to-date guide to continuous improvement in the workplace&#8221;An updated version of a classic book that shares a wealth of new healthcare examples and case studies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gemba-kaizen-a-commonsense-approach-to-a-continuous-improvement-strategy-second-edition-masaaki-imai-abridged/">Gemba Kaizen: A Commonsense Approach to a Continuous Improvement Strategy, Second Edition &#8211; Masaaki Imai (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Publisher&#8217;s Note: Products purchased from Third Party sellers are not guaranteed by the publisher for quality,   authenticity, or access to any online entitlements included with the product.    </p>
<p>                    The definitive, fully up-to-date guide to continuous improvement in the workplace&#8221;An updated version of a classic book that shares a wealth of new healthcare examples and case studies from around the world. The methods in this book will help you improve quality and safety, reduce waiting times, and improve the long-term financial position of your organization. Highly recommended!&#8221; &#8211;Mark Graban, author of Lean Hospitals and coauthor of Healthcare Kaizen    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Every business faces the iron triangle of quality, cost, and delivery. Conventional thinking claims you cannot have all three. Not only does Mr. Imai turn that thinking on its head, but he shows you exactly how to do it.&#8221; &#8212; Matthew E. May, author of The Elegant Solution and The Laws of Subtraction    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Masaaki Imai has done it again. The second edition of his famous book not only describes all the tools necessary for any type of business to implement a lean strategy but also includes a large number of excellent case studies.&#8221; &#8212; Art Byrne, author of The Lean Turnaround    </p>
<p>                    Written by Masaaki Imai, pioneer of modern business operational excellence and founder of the Kaizen Institute, Gemba Kaizen, Second Edition is an in-depth revision of this renowned, bestselling work. The book reveals how to implement cost-effective, incremental improvements in your most critical business processes. Global case studies from a wide range of industries demonstrate how gemba kaizen has been successfully used to:    </p>
<p>                    Maximize capacity and reduce inventory at Unga Limited, one of Kenya&#8217;s largest flour-milling operations<br />
                    Change the IT culture at Achmea, a large European insurance firm<br />
                    Exceed customer expectations at Walt Disney World in the United States<br />
                    Improve quality at Inoue Hospital in Japan<br />
                    Transform retail processes at Sonae MC, Portugal&#8217;s largest employer<br />
                    Practice daily kaizen at Tork Ledervin, a weaving plant in Brazil<br />
                    Stamp out muda at Sunclipse, an industrial packaging distributor in the United States<br />
                    Manage quality improvement by total workforce involvement at Xuji Group Corporation, an electrical manufacturer in China<br />
                    Implement gemba kaizen at many other companies worldwide    </p>
<p>                    To thrive in today&#8217;s competitive global economy, organizations need to operate more effectively and profitably than ever before. Developing problem solvers, increasing productivity, improving quality, and reducing waste are essential success factors. Proven strategies for achieving these goals are included in this pioneering guide.    </p>
<p>                    This comprehensive resource offers detailed coverage of important gemba kaizen topics, including:    </p>
<p>                    Quality, cost, and delivery in the gemba<br />
                    The five steps of workplace organization<br />
                    Identifying and eliminating muda&#8211;any non-value-adding activity<br />
                    Visual management<br />
                    Supervisors&#8217; roles in the lean workplace<br />
                    Gemba managers&#8217; roles and accountability in sustaining high performance<br />
                    Just-in-time and total flow management<br />
                    The CEO&#8217;s role in leading a kaizen culture    </p>
<p>                    The methods presented in Gemba Kaizen, Second Edition reveal that when management focuses on implementing kaizen (incremental, continuous improvement) in the gemba (the worksite) unique opportunities can be discovered for increasing the success and profitability of any organization.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gemba-kaizen-a-commonsense-approach-to-a-continuous-improvement-strategy-second-edition-masaaki-imai-abridged/">Gemba Kaizen: A Commonsense Approach to a Continuous Improvement Strategy, Second Edition &#8211; Masaaki Imai (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Evergreen: Cultivate the Enduring Customer Loyalty That Keeps Your Business Thriving &#8211; Noah Fleming (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/evergreen-cultivate-the-enduring-customer-loyalty-that-keeps-your-business-thriving-noah-fleming-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/evergreen-cultivate-the-enduring-customer-loyalty-that-keeps-your-business-thriving-noah-fleming-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Loyal customers are the beating heart of every great business. So why do so many companies act like adrenalin junkies, chasing after new customers at the expense of creating deeper, more profitable relationships with the ones they already have?Evergreen exposes the mad pursuit for what it is: a brief spike in metrics and an ongoing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/evergreen-cultivate-the-enduring-customer-loyalty-that-keeps-your-business-thriving-noah-fleming-abridged/">Evergreen: Cultivate the Enduring Customer Loyalty That Keeps Your Business Thriving &#8211; Noah Fleming (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Loyal customers are the beating heart of every great business. So why do so many companies act like adrenalin junkies, chasing after new customers at the expense of creating deeper, more profitable relationships with the ones they already have?Evergreen exposes the mad pursuit for what it is: a brief spike in metrics and an ongoing revenue drain, as one-time customers fail to return. A better solution is to shift resources from attracting new customers to engaging the base &#8211; the path to stable growth, season after season. The book&#8217;s entertaining stories and action steps reveal how anyone can:    </p>
<p>                    Cultivate the 3Cs of evergreen companies: character, community, and contentBuild loyalty programs that turn satisfied customers into enthusiastic advocatesNurture profitable customers while pruning those who sap time and moneyInject authenticity into social media communicationsInvert the expectations gap that can drive customers away<br />
                    From Internet startups and mom-and-pop businesses to multinational giants, strong companies are rooted in customer retention. Evergreen helps anyone merge high-tech tools with the personal touch to forge lasting bonds and steady profits.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/evergreen-cultivate-the-enduring-customer-loyalty-that-keeps-your-business-thriving-noah-fleming-abridged/">Evergreen: Cultivate the Enduring Customer Loyalty That Keeps Your Business Thriving &#8211; Noah Fleming (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 11 Laws of Likability: Relationship Networking Because People Do Business with People They Like &#8211; Michelle Tillis Lederman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-11-laws-of-likability-relationship-networking-because-people-do-business-with-people-they-like-michelle-tillis-lederman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Secretarial, Clerical & Office Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-11-laws-of-likability-relationship-networking-because-people-do-business-with-people-they-like-michelle-tillis-lederman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We all know that networking is important, and that forming relationships with others is a vital part of success. But sometimes it seems like networking removes all emotions from the equation and focuses only on immediate goals&#8230;whereas the kind of relationships that have true staying power, give us joy, and support us in the long [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-11-laws-of-likability-relationship-networking-because-people-do-business-with-people-they-like-michelle-tillis-lederman-abridged/">The 11 Laws of Likability: Relationship Networking Because People Do Business with People They Like &#8211; Michelle Tillis Lederman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We all know that networking is important, and that forming relationships with others is a vital part of success. But sometimes it seems like networking removes all emotions from the equation and focuses only on immediate goals&#8230;whereas the kind of relationships that have true staying power, give us joy, and support us in the long run are founded on simply liking each other.     </p>
<p>                      This book, featuring activities, self-assessment quizzes, and real-life anecdotes from professional and social settings, shows readers how to identify what&#8217;s likable in themselves and create honest, authentic interactions that become &#8220;wins&#8221; for all parties involved. Readers will discover how to:     </p>
<p>                      * Start conversations and keep them going with ease     </p>
<p>                      * Convert acquaintances into friends     </p>
<p>                      * Uncover people&#8217;s preferences and tweak their own personal style to enable engaging, reciprocal interactions     </p>
<p>                      * Create follow-up and stay in others&#8217; minds long after the initial meeting     </p>
<p>                      The worst thing we can do when trying to establish a personal bond with someone is to come across as manipulative or self-serving. Authentic connections go much deeper-and feel much easier-than trying to hit self-imposed business card collection quotas. This book presents a new paradigm that shows how even the most networking-averse can network&#8230;and like it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-11-laws-of-likability-relationship-networking-because-people-do-business-with-people-they-like-michelle-tillis-lederman-abridged/">The 11 Laws of Likability: Relationship Networking Because People Do Business with People They Like &#8211; Michelle Tillis Lederman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition: Turn Your Dreams into a Licensing Goldmine While Letting Others Do the Work &#8211; Stephen Key (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inventions & Inventors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With must-have updates, a new edition of the bestselling method that shows how anyone can turn their one simple idea into millions &#8211; without lifting a finger! Stephen Key is an award-winning inventor who has licensed more than 20 product ideas. In 2011, he shared the secrets to his success in the bestselling book One [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/">One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition: Turn Your Dreams into a Licensing Goldmine While Letting Others Do the Work &#8211; Stephen Key (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With must-have updates, a new edition of the bestselling method that shows how anyone can turn their one simple idea into millions &#8211; without lifting a finger!    </p>
<p>                     Stephen Key is an award-winning inventor who has licensed more than 20 product ideas. In 2011, he shared the secrets to his success in the bestselling book One Simple Idea. Since that time, many changes have occurred in the entrepreneurial world.    </p>
<p>                    One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition has been revised and updated to reflect current trends and practices in the industry. In addition to teaching readers how to turn their ideas into marketable products that companies will want to license, Key expands upon his cutting-edge product development, sales, and negotiation strategies, making note of the new opportunities and technologies available to creative people today. The book also features real-life success stories from people who have used the author&#8217;s strategies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/one-simple-idea-revised-and-expanded-edition-turn-your-dreams-into-a-licensing-goldmine-while-letting-others-do-the-work-stephen-key-abridged/">One Simple Idea, Revised and Expanded Edition: Turn Your Dreams into a Licensing Goldmine While Letting Others Do the Work &#8211; Stephen Key (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mind Gym &#8211; Gary Mack, David Casstevens (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mind-gym-gary-mack-david-casstevens-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[American Football]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Baseball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basketball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Combat Sports & Self-defence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football (Soccer, Association Football)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Golf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gymnastics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ice-skating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Multidiscipline Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olympic Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming & Diving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tennis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Track & Field Sports, Athletics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Volleyball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wrestling]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mind-gym-gary-mack-david-casstevens-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Mind Gym &#8220;Believing in yourself is paramount to success for any athlete. Gary&#8217;s lessons and David&#8217;s writing provide examples of the importance of the mental game.&#8221; &#8211;Ben Crenshaw, two-time Masters champion and former Ryder Cup captain &#8220;Mind Gym hits a home run. If you want to build mental muscle for the major leagues, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mind-gym-gary-mack-david-casstevens-abridged/">Mind Gym &#8211; Gary Mack, David Casstevens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Mind Gym    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Believing in yourself is paramount to success for any athlete. Gary&#8217;s lessons and David&#8217;s writing provide examples of the importance of the mental game.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Ben Crenshaw, two-time Masters champion and former Ryder Cup captain    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Mind Gym hits a home run. If you want to build mental muscle for the major leagues, read this book.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Ken Griffey Jr., Major League Baseball MVP    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I read Mind Gym on my way to the Sydney Olympics and really got a lot out of it. Gary has important lessons to teach, and you&#8217;ll find the exercises fun and beneficial.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Jason Kidd, NBA All-Star and Olympic gold-medal winner    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I love the book Mind Gym.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Madison Kocian, 2016 U.S. Women&#8217;s Gymnastics Team, 2015 Uneven Bars World Champion, as told to Us Weekly    </p>
<p>                    In Mind Gym, noted sports psychology consultant Gary Mack explains how your mind influences your performance on the field or on the court as much as your physical skill does, if not more so. Through forty accessible lessons and inspirational anecdotes from prominent athletes&#8211;many of whom he has worked with&#8211;you will learn the same techniques and exercises Mack uses to help elite athletes build mental &#8220;muscle.&#8221; Mind Gym will give you the &#8220;head edge&#8221; over the competition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mind-gym-gary-mack-david-casstevens-abridged/">Mind Gym &#8211; Gary Mack, David Casstevens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription: A Disruptive Solution for Health Care &#8211; Clayton Christensen, Jerome Grossman, Jason Hwang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Administration & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking prescription for health care reform&#8211;from a legendaryleader in innovation . . . Our health care system is in critical condition. Each year, fewer Americans can afford it, fewer businesses can provide it, and fewer government programs can promise it for future generations. We need a cure, and we need it now. Harvard Business [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/">The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription: A Disruptive Solution for Health Care &#8211; Clayton Christensen, Jerome Grossman, Jason Hwang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking prescription for health care reform&#8211;from a legendaryleader in innovation . . .    </p>
<p>                    Our health care system is in critical condition. Each year, fewer Americans can afford it, fewer businesses can provide it, and fewer government programs can promise it for future generations.    </p>
<p>                    We need a cure, and we need it now.    </p>
<p>                    Harvard Business School&#8217;s Clayton M. Christensen-whose bestselling The Innovator&#8217;s Dilemma revolutionized the business world-presents The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription, a comprehensive analysis of the strategies that will improvehealth care and make it affordable.    </p>
<p>                    Christensen applies the principles of disruptive innovation to the broken health care system with two pioneers in the field-Dr. Jerome Grossman and Dr. Jason Hwang. Together, they examine arange of symptoms and offer proven solutions.    </p>
<p>                    YOU&#8217;LL DISCOVER HOW    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Precision medicine&#8221; reduces costs and makes good on the promise of personalized careDisruptive business models improve quality, accessibility, and affordability by changing the way hospitals and doctors workPatient networks enable better treatment of chronic diseasesEmployers can change the roles they play in health care to compete effectively in the era of globalizationInsurance and regulatory reforms stimulate disruption in health care</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/">The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription: A Disruptive Solution for Health Care &#8211; Clayton Christensen, Jerome Grossman, Jason Hwang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reach Out: The Simple Strategy You Need to Expand Your Network and Increase Your Influence &#8211; Molly Beck (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reach-out-the-simple-strategy-you-need-to-expand-your-network-and-increase-your-influence-molly-beck-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reach-out-the-simple-strategy-you-need-to-expand-your-network-and-increase-your-influence-molly-beck-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical guide to building valuable career connections-through tools you already have and people you already know Success in life is more than having goals and skills. You need connections. And to get connections, you need to Reach Out-fearlessly, strategically, and every day of the work week. For many, this is a daunting and confusing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reach-out-the-simple-strategy-you-need-to-expand-your-network-and-increase-your-influence-molly-beck-abridged/">Reach Out: The Simple Strategy You Need to Expand Your Network and Increase Your Influence &#8211; Molly Beck (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical guide to building valuable career connections-through tools you already have and people you already know     </p>
<p>                    Success in life is more than having goals and skills. You need connections. And to get connections, you need to Reach Out-fearlessly, strategically, and every day of the work week.     </p>
<p>                    For many, this is a daunting and confusing task.     </p>
<p>                    Reach Out shows readers how to use social media and simple digital tools to begin building and expanding the number of people they know. Author Molly Beck explains how to:    </p>
<p>                    *Establish and strengthen your digital presence     </p>
<p>                    *Develop career goals that Reaching Out can help you obtain     </p>
<p>                    *Think strategically about who you have already met, who you could strengthen a relationship with, and who your current connections know    </p>
<p>                    *Determine who to Reach Out to and push past common networking fears to do it    </p>
<p>                    * Apply step-by-step instructions on how to craft email and social media messages to those you want to connect with    </p>
<p>                    *Optimize your efforts by managing both your time and your inbox     </p>
<p>                    The book features personal stories on networking from some of today&#8217;s top thought leaders. Studies, statistics, and real world examples illustrate the key concepts of Reaching Out. Whether you&#8217;re just starting out, changing jobs, or well-established and just eager to know more people, Reaching Out will help you turn career dreams into professional success by helping you connect with others who can put you on the fast track.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reach-out-the-simple-strategy-you-need-to-expand-your-network-and-increase-your-influence-molly-beck-abridged/">Reach Out: The Simple Strategy You Need to Expand Your Network and Increase Your Influence &#8211; Molly Beck (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Take Care of Your Customers&#8211;or Someone Else Will!Legendary ServiceGreat customer service is a concept organizations love to be known for. Yet most people consider the service they receive to be average, at best. Successful companies make the connection between legendary customer service and athriving business&#8211;they recognize that the way employees treat customers is directly related [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/">Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Take Care of Your Customers&#8211;or Someone Else Will!Legendary ServiceGreat customer service is a concept organizations love to be known for. Yet most people consider the service they receive to be average, at best. Successful companies make the connection between legendary customer service and athriving business&#8211;they recognize that the way employees treat customers is directly related to the way managers treat employees.    </p>
<p>                    Kelsey Young is an optimistic but disillusioned sales associate working her way through college. Her world opens up when one of her professors challenges her to create a culture of service at her workplace by putting the five components of Legendary Service into practice. AlthoughFerguson&#8217;s, the store where Kelsey works, certainly isn&#8217;t known for service excellence, Kelsey believes she can make a positive difference. She quickly learns that culture change isn&#8217;t easy&#8211;and that her role as a frontline employee is more significant than she ever could have imagined.    </p>
<p>                    In characteristic Blanchard style, Legendary Service: The Key Is to Care is a quick and entertainingread for people at all organizational levels in every industry. When applied, its lessons will have a profound impact on the service experience your customers will receive. Whether a CEO or a part-time employee, every person can make a difference&#8211;and customer service iseveryone&#8217;s job.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR LEGENDARY SERVICE:&#8221;Read this book and establish a service culture in your organization.&#8221; &#8212; Horst Schulze, Chairman/CEO, Capella Hotel Group    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Legendary Service has great learnings for people at all organizational levels: for executives and managers, the value of a service culture; and for frontlinestaff, the reality that they are the face of the company and can make a difference. Legendary service&#8211;it&#8217;s everyone, always.&#8221; &#8212; Mark King, CEO and President, TaylorMade Golf    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Everything I know about service I learned from my career at Hilton Hotels, Marriott International, The Walt Disney Company, and Ken Blanchard. The One Minute Manager dramatically changed my thinking 32 years ago. LegendaryService will teach the next generation how to deliver sensational service. Buy it, study it, implement it.&#8221; &#8212; Lee Cockerell, Executive Vice President, Walt Disney World (Retired &#038; Inspired), and author of Creating Magic and The Customer Rules    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Kathy Cuff and Vicki Halsey have created a fantastic customer service model called ICARE. When you add their voices to that of the master storyteller KenBlanchard, you have a masterpiece entitled Legendary Service. It is a must-read for everyone who, like me, has a passion for service.&#8221; &#8212; Colleen Barrett, President Emeritus, Southwest Airlines, and coauthor of Lead with LUV    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Ken Blanchard has done it again and delivered the right book at the right time. Legendary Service provides the essentials of hospitality and servant leadership in a way that everyone can adopt&#8211;right now&#8211;today!&#8221; &#8212; John Caparella, President and COO,The Venetian, The Palazzo, and Sands Expo    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Ken, Kathy, and Vicki show us how to change everyday service events into memorable experiences. Their book is a must-read for anyone unwilling to acceptmediocrity.&#8221; &#8212; Leonardo Inghilleri, coauthor ofExceptional Service, Exceptional Profit</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/legendary-service-the-key-is-to-care-ken-blanchard-victoria-halsey-kathy-cuff-abridged/">Legendary Service: The Key is to Care &#8211; Ken Blanchard, Victoria Halsey, Kathy Cuff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Million Dollar Consulting: The Professional&#8217;s Guide to Growing a Practice, Fifth Edition &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Build a thriving consultancy with the updated edition of this classic bestseller Having inspired generations of consultants and entrepreneurs around the world, the &#8220;Rock Star of Consulting&#8221; Alan Weiss returns with a revised and completely updated edition of his authoritative guide to consulting success. Weiss provides his time-tested model on creating a flourishing consulting business, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/">Million Dollar Consulting: The Professional&#8217;s Guide to Growing a Practice, Fifth Edition &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Build a thriving consultancy with the updated edition of this classic bestseller    </p>
<p>                    Having inspired generations of consultants and entrepreneurs around the world, the &#8220;Rock Star of Consulting&#8221; Alan Weiss returns with a revised and completely updated edition of his authoritative guide to consulting success.      </p>
<p>                    Weiss provides his time-tested model on creating a flourishing consulting business, while incorporating and focusing on the many dynamic changes in solo and boutique consulting, coaching, and entrepreneurship. In addition to guidance on raising capital, attracting clients, and creating a marketing plan, he also gives brand new step-by-step advice on:    </p>
<p>                    * Harnessing today&#8217;s global opportunities<br />
                    * Developing brands across markets<br />
                    * Creating and licensing intellectual property<br />
                    * Avoiding the pitfalls of social media<br />
                    * Landing unsolicited referrals through counterintuitive methods<br />
                    * Managing and organizing your time wisely<br />
                    * Succeeding in the face of continuing turbulence    </p>
<p>                    Find out why this book has been the classic go-to for consultants for nearly twenty-five years, and learn how to grow your business into a $1 million-per-year firm today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/million-dollar-consulting-the-professionals-guide-to-growing-a-practice-fifth-edition-alan-weiss-abridged/">Million Dollar Consulting: The Professional&#8217;s Guide to Growing a Practice, Fifth Edition &#8211; Alan Weiss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
