<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Evolution Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/evolution/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/evolution/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Evolution Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/evolution/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Genome : The Autobiography of a Species in 23 Chapters &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anatomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Ridley leaps from chromosome to chromosome in a handy summation of our ever increasing understanding of the roles that genes play in disease, behavior, sexual differences, and even intelligence. . . . . He addresses not only the ethical quandaries faced by contemporary scientists but the reductionist danger in equating inheritability with inevitability.&#8221; &#8212; The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/">Genome : The Autobiography of a Species in 23 Chapters &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Ridley leaps from chromosome to chromosome in a handy summation of our ever increasing understanding of the roles that genes play in disease, behavior, sexual differences, and even intelligence. . . . . He addresses not only the ethical quandaries faced by contemporary scientists but the reductionist danger in equating inheritability with inevitability.&#8221; &#8212; The New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    The genome&#8217;s been mapped. But what does it mean? Matt Ridley&#8217;s Genome is the book that explains it all: what it is, how it works, and what it portends for the future    </p>
<p>                    Arguably the most significant scientific discovery of the new century, the mapping of the twenty-three pairs of chromosomes that make up the human genome raises almost as many questions as it answers. Questions that will profoundly impact the way we think about disease, about longevity, and about free will. Questions that will affect the rest of your life.    </p>
<p>                    Genome offers extraordinary insight into the ramifications of this incredible breakthrough. By picking one newly discovered gene from each pair of chromosomes and telling its story, Matt Ridley recounts the history of our species and its ancestors from the dawn of life to the brink of future medicine. From Huntington&#8217;s disease to cancer, from the applications of gene therapy to the horrors of eugenics, Ridley probes the scientific, philosophical, and moral issues arising as a result of the mapping of the genome. It will help you understand what this scientific milestone means for you, for your children, and for humankind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/">Genome : The Autobiography of a Species in 23 Chapters &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Third Chimpanzee : The Evolution and Future of the Human Animal &#8211; Jared M Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-third-chimpanzee-the-evolution-and-future-of-the-human-animal-jared-m-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-third-chimpanzee-the-evolution-and-future-of-the-human-animal-jared-m-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Wonderful&#8230;.Jared Diamond conducts his fascinating study of our behavior and origins with a naturalist&#8217;s eye and a philosopher&#8217;s cunning.&#8221; &#8211;Diane Ackerman, author of A Natural History of the Senses In this fascinating, provocative, passionate, funny, endlessly entertaining work, renowned Pulitzer Prize-winning author and scientist Jared Diamond, author of Gun, Germs, and Steel, explores how the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-chimpanzee-the-evolution-and-future-of-the-human-animal-jared-m-diamond-abridged/">The Third Chimpanzee : The Evolution and Future of the Human Animal &#8211; Jared M Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Wonderful&#8230;.Jared Diamond conducts his fascinating study of our behavior and origins with a naturalist&#8217;s eye and a philosopher&#8217;s cunning.&#8221; &#8211;Diane Ackerman, author of A Natural History of the Senses    </p>
<p>                    In this fascinating, provocative, passionate, funny, endlessly entertaining work, renowned Pulitzer Prize-winning author and scientist Jared Diamond, author of Gun, Germs, and Steel, explores how the extraordinary human animal, in a remarkably short time, developed the capacity to rule the world . . . and the means to irrevocably destroy it.     </p>
<p>                    We human beings share 98 percent of our genes with chimpanzees. Yet humans are the dominant species on the planet&#8211;having founded civilizations and religions, developed intricate and diverse forms of communication, learned science, built cities, and created breathtaking works of art&#8211;while chimps remain animals concerned primarily with the basic necessities of survival. What is it about that two percent difference in DNA that has created such a divergence between evolutionary cousins?     </p>
<p>                    The Third Chimpanzee is a tour de force, an iconoclastic, compelling, sometimes alarming look at the unique and marvelous creature that is the human animal.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-chimpanzee-the-evolution-and-future-of-the-human-animal-jared-m-diamond-abridged/">The Third Chimpanzee : The Evolution and Future of the Human Animal &#8211; Jared M Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marine Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oceanography (seas)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Aquatic Creatures]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BBC R4 Book of the Week &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Fascinating and often delightful&#8217; The Times What if intelligent life on Earth evolved not once, but twice? The octopus is the closest we will come to meeting an intelligent alien. What can we learn from the encounter? In Other Minds, Peter Godfrey-Smith, a distinguished philosopher of science [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/">Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BBC R4 Book of the Week<br />
                              &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian<br />
                              &#8216;Fascinating and often delightful&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                                What if intelligent life on Earth evolved not once, but twice? The octopus is the closest we will come to meeting an intelligent alien. What can we learn from the encounter?    </p>
<p>                              In Other Minds, Peter Godfrey-Smith, a distinguished philosopher of science and a skilled scuba diver, tells a bold new story of how nature became aware of itself &#8211; a story that largely occurs in the ocean, where animals first appeared.    </p>
<p>                              Tracking the mind&#8217;s fitful development from unruly clumps of seaborne cells to the first evolved nervous systems in ancient relatives of jellyfish, he explores the incredible evolutionary journey of the cephalopods, which began as inconspicuous molluscs who would later abandon their shells to rise above the ocean floor, searching for prey and acquiring the greater intelligence needed to do so &#8211; a journey completely independent from the route that mammals and birds would later take.    </p>
<p>                              But what kind of intelligence do cephalopods possess? How did the octopus, a solitary creature with little social life, become so smart? What is it like to have eight tentacles that are so packed with neurons that they virtually &#8216;think for themselves&#8217;? By tracing the question of inner life back to its roots and comparing human beings with our most remarkable animal relatives, Godfrey-Smith casts crucial new light on the octopus mind &#8211; and on our own.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/">Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Selfish Gene, Richard Dawkins crystallized the gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution developed by W.D. Hamilton and others. The book provoked widespread and heated debate. Written in part as a response, The Extended Phenotype gave a deeper clarification of the central concept of the gene as the unit of selection; but it did much [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Selfish Gene, Richard Dawkins crystallized  the gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution developed by W.D. Hamilton and others. The book provoked widespread and heated debate. Written in part as a response, The Extended Phenotype gave a deeper clarification of the central concept of the gene as the unit of selection; but it did much more besides. In it, Dawkins extended the gene&#8217;s eye view to argue that the genes that sit within an organism have an<br />
                    influence that reaches out beyond the visible traits in that body &#8211; the phenotype &#8211; to the wider environment, which can include other individuals. So, for instance, the genes of the beaver drive it to gather twigs to produce the substantial physical structure of a dam; and the genes of the cuckoo chick produce effects that<br />
                    manipulate the behaviour of the host bird, making it nurture the intruder as one of its own. This notion of the extended phenotype has proved to be highly influential in the way we understand evolution and the natural world. It represents a key scientific contribution to evolutionary biology, and it continues to play an important role in research in the life sciences.    </p>
<p>                    The Extended Phenotype is a conceptually deep book that forms important reading for biologists and students. But Dawkins&#8217; clear exposition is accessible to all who are prepared to put in a little effort.    </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-extended-phenotype-the-long-reach-of-the-gene-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Extended Phenotype : The Long Reach of the Gene &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Storytelling Animal : How Stories Make Us Human &#8211; Instructor Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-storytelling-animal-how-stories-make-us-human-instructor-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-storytelling-animal-how-stories-make-us-human-instructor-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this delightful and original book, Jonathan Gottschall offers the first unified theory of storytelling. Drawing on neuroscience and evolutionary biology, The Storytelling Animal explores what stories reveal about human nature, how we process information, and think about the world. Humans live in landscapes of make-believe. We spin fantasies. We devour novels, films, and plays. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-storytelling-animal-how-stories-make-us-human-instructor-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/">The Storytelling Animal : How Stories Make Us Human &#8211; Instructor Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this delightful and original book, Jonathan Gottschall offers the first unified theory of storytelling. Drawing on neuroscience and evolutionary biology, The Storytelling Animal explores what stories reveal about human nature, how we process information, and think about the world.<br />
                    Humans live in landscapes of make-believe. We spin fantasies. We devour novels, films, and plays. Even sporting events and criminal trials unfold as narratives. Gottschall argues that stories help us navigate life&#8217;s complex social problems &#8212; just as flight simulators prepare pilots for difficult situations. Storytelling has evolved, like other behaviors, to ensure our survival. Gottschall tells us what it means to be a storytelling animal and explains how stories can change the world for the better.<br />
                    We know we are master shapers of story. The Storytelling Animal finally reveals how stories shape us.<br />
                    A NYTimes.com Editor&#8217;s Choice<br />
                    A Los Angeles Times Book Prizes Finalist<br />
                    &#8220;A jaunty, insightful new book . . . [that] draws from disparate corners of history and science to celebrate our compulsion to storify everything around us.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-storytelling-animal-how-stories-make-us-human-instructor-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/">The Storytelling Animal : How Stories Make Us Human &#8211; Instructor Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dazzled and Deceived : Mimicry and Camouflage &#8211; Peter Forbes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dazzled-and-deceived-mimicry-and-camouflage-peter-forbes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biodiversity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Developmental Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology & Animal Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dazzled-and-deceived-mimicry-and-camouflage-peter-forbes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The remarkable story of how mimicry is used by some of the most extraordinary creatures in the world Nature has perfected the art of deception. Thousands of creatures all over the world-including butterflies, moths, fish, birds, insects and snakes-have honed and practiced camouflage over hundreds of millions of years. Imitating other animals or their surroundings, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dazzled-and-deceived-mimicry-and-camouflage-peter-forbes-abridged/">Dazzled and Deceived : Mimicry and Camouflage &#8211; Peter Forbes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The remarkable story of how mimicry is used by some of the most extraordinary creatures in the world    </p>
<p>                     Nature has perfected the art of deception. Thousands of creatures all over the world-including butterflies, moths, fish, birds, insects and snakes-have honed and practiced camouflage over hundreds of millions of years. Imitating other animals or their surroundings, nature&#8217;s fakers use mimicry to protect themselves, to attract and repel, to bluff and warn, to forage, and to hide. The advantages of mimicry are obvious-but how does &#8220;blind&#8221; nature do it? And how has humanity learned to profit from nature&#8217;s ploys?    </p>
<p>                    Dazzled and Deceived tells the unique and fascinating story of mimicry and camouflage in science, art, warfare, and the natural world. Discovered in the 1850s by the young English naturalists Henry Walter Bates and Alfred Russel Wallace in the Amazonian rainforest, the phenomenon of mimicry was seized upon as the first independent validation of Darwin&#8217;s theory of natural selection. But mimicry and camouflage also created a huge impact outside the laboratory walls. Peter Forbes&#8217;s cultural history links mimicry and camouflage to art, literature, military tactics, and medical cures across the twentieth century, and charts its intricate involvement with the perennial dispute between evolution and creationism.    </p>
<p>                    As Dazzled and Deceived unravels the concept of mimicry, Forbes introduces colorful stories and a dazzling cast of characters-Roosevelt, Picasso, Nabokov, Churchill, and Darwin himself, to name a few-whom its mystery influenced and enthralled. Illuminating and lively, Dazzled and Deceived sheds new light on the greatest quest: to understand the processes of life at its deepest level.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dazzled-and-deceived-mimicry-and-camouflage-peter-forbes-abridged/">Dazzled and Deceived : Mimicry and Camouflage &#8211; Peter Forbes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Oxygen has had extraordinary effects on life. Three hundred million years ago, in Carboniferous times, dragonflies grew as big as seagulls, with wingspans of nearly a metre. Researchers claim they could have flown only if the air had contained more oxygen than today &#8211; probably as much as 35 per cent. Giant spiders, tree-ferns, marine [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/">Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Oxygen has had extraordinary effects on life.     </p>
<p>                    Three hundred million years ago, in Carboniferous times, dragonflies grew as big as seagulls, with wingspans of<br />
                    nearly a metre. Researchers claim they could have flown only if the air had contained more oxygen than today &#8211;<br />
                    probably as much as 35 per cent. Giant spiders, tree-ferns, marine rock formations and fossil charcoals<br />
                    all tell the same story. High oxygen levels may also explain the global firestorm that contributed to the<br />
                    demise of the dinosaurs after the asteroid impact.    </p>
<p>                    The strange and profound effects that oxygen has had on the evolution of life pose a riddle, which this book<br />
                    sets out to answer. Oxygen is a toxic gas. Divers breathing pure oxygen at depth suffer from convulsions<br />
                    and lung injury. Fruit flies raised at twice normal atmospheric levels of oxygen live half as long as their<br />
                    siblings. Reactive forms of oxygen, known as free radicals, are thought to cause ageing in people. Yet if<br />
                    atmospheric oxygen reached 35 per cent in the Carboniferous, why did it promote exuberant growth,<br />
                    instead of rapid ageing and death?    </p>
<p>                    Oxygen takes the reader on an enthralling journey, as gripping as a thriller, as it unravels the unexpected<br />
                    ways in which oxygen spurred the evolution of life and death. The book explains far more than the size of<br />
                    ancient insects: it shows how oxygen underpins the origin of biological complexity, the birth of photosynthesis, the sudden evolution of animals, the need for two sexes, the accelerated ageing of cloned animals like Dolly the sheep, and the surprisingly long lives of bats and birds.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on this grand evolutionary canvas, Oxygen offers fresh perspectives on our own lives and deaths,<br />
                    explaining modern killer diseases, why we age, and what we can do about it. Advancing revelatory new ideas,<br />
                    following chains of evidence, the book ranges through many disciplines, from environmental sciences to<br />
                    molecular medicine. The result is a captivating vision of contemporary science and a humane synthesis of our<br />
                    place in nature. This remarkable book might just redefine the way we think about the world.    </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oxygen-the-molecule-that-made-the-world-nick-lane-abridged/">Oxygen : The molecule that made the world &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanistic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Why do human beings behave as they do? &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**    </p>
<p>                    Why do human beings behave as they do?     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm    </p>
<p>                     We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of our nature destined to win out over the other?    </p>
<p>                     Every act of human behaviour has multiple layers of causation, spiralling back seconds, minutes, hours, days, months, years, even centuries, right back to the dawn of time and the origins of our species.     </p>
<p>                     In the epic sweep of history, how does our biology affect the arc of war and peace, justice and persecution? How have our brains evolved alongside our cultures?    </p>
<p>                     This is the exhilarating story of human morality and the science underpinning the biggest question of all: what makes us human?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the best scientist-writers of our time&#8217; Oliver Sacks</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Go Wild : Free Your Body and Mind from the Afflictions of Civilization &#8211; Dr. John J. Ratey, Richard Manning (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/go-wild-free-your-body-and-mind-from-the-afflictions-of-civilization-dr-john-j-ratey-richard-manning-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/go-wild-free-your-body-and-mind-from-the-afflictions-of-civilization-dr-john-j-ratey-richard-manning-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The scientific evidence behind why we should maintain a lifestyle more like that of our ancestors to restore our health and well-being. In GO WILD, Harvard Medical School professor John Ratey, MD, and journalist Richard Manning reveal that although civilization has rapidly evolved, our bodies stopped changing long ago&#8211;creating a disconnect between how we live [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/go-wild-free-your-body-and-mind-from-the-afflictions-of-civilization-dr-john-j-ratey-richard-manning-abridged/">Go Wild : Free Your Body and Mind from the Afflictions of Civilization &#8211; Dr. John J. Ratey, Richard Manning (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The scientific evidence behind why we should maintain a lifestyle more like that of our ancestors to restore our health and well-being.     </p>
<p>                    In GO WILD, Harvard Medical School professor John Ratey, MD, and journalist Richard Manning reveal that although civilization has rapidly evolved, our bodies stopped changing long ago&#8211;creating a disconnect between how we live and what is best for us. This disconnect affects every area of our lives, from our energy levels to our relationships to our general health. Only by using ancient evolutionary instructions to navigate modern life can we realize our true potential in everything including strength, health and well-being, intelligence, happiness, and more. The book addresses modern diseases (from diabetes to cancer to addiction); the problems of the modern diet; exercise; sleep; mindfulness and relationships; and much more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/go-wild-free-your-body-and-mind-from-the-afflictions-of-civilization-dr-john-j-ratey-richard-manning-abridged/">Go Wild : Free Your Body and Mind from the Afflictions of Civilization &#8211; Dr. John J. Ratey, Richard Manning (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Power, Sex, Suicide : Mitochondria and the meaning of life &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/power-sex-suicide-mitochondria-and-the-meaning-of-life-nick-lane-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/power-sex-suicide-mitochondria-and-the-meaning-of-life-nick-lane-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mitochondria are tiny structures located inside our cells that carry out the essential task of producing energy for the cell. They are found in all complex living things, and in that sense, they are fundamental for driving complex life on the planet. But there is much more to them than that. Mitochondria have their own [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/power-sex-suicide-mitochondria-and-the-meaning-of-life-nick-lane-abridged/">Power, Sex, Suicide : Mitochondria and the meaning of life &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mitochondria are tiny structures located inside our cells that carry out the essential task of producing energy for the cell. They are found in all complex living things, and in that sense, they are fundamental for driving complex life on the planet. But there is much more to them than that.     </p>
<p>                    Mitochondria have their own DNA, with their own small collection of genes, separate from those in the cell nucleus. It is thought that they were once bacteria living independent lives. Their enslavement within the larger cell was a turning point in the evolution of life, enabling the development of complex organisms and, closely related, the origin of two sexes. Unlike the DNA in the nucleus, mitochondrial DNA is passed down exclusively (or almost exclusively) via the female line. That&#8217;s why it<br />
                    has been used by some researchers to trace human ancestry daughter-to-mother, to &#8216;Mitochondrial Eve&#8217;. Mitochondria give us important information about our evolutionary history. And that&#8217;s not all. Mitochondrial genes mutate much faster than those in the nucleus because of the free radicals produced<br />
                    in their energy-generating role. This high mutation rate lies behind our ageing and certain congenital diseases. The latest research suggests that mitochondria play a key role in degenerative diseases such as cancer, through their involvement in precipitating cell suicide.     </p>
<p>                    Mitochondria, then, are pivotal in power, sex, and suicide. In this fascinating and thought-provoking book, Nick Lane brings together the latest research findings in this exciting field to show how our growing understanding of mitochondria is shedding light on how complex life evolved, why sex arose (why don&#8217;t we just bud?), and why we age and die. This understanding is of fundamental importance, both in understanding how we and all other complex life came to be, but also in order to be able to<br />
                    control our own illnesses, and delay our degeneration and death.     </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/power-sex-suicide-mitochondria-and-the-meaning-of-life-nick-lane-abridged/">Power, Sex, Suicide : Mitochondria and the meaning of life &#8211; Nick Lane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Picture : On the Origins of Life, Meaning, and the Universe Itself &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrophysics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Brian Cox, Mail on Sunday Books of the Year Where are we? Who are we? Do our beliefs, hopes and dreams hold any significance out there in the void? Can human purpose and meaning ever fit into a scientific worldview? Award-winning author Sean Carroll brings his extraordinary intellect to bear on the realms [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Big Picture : On the Origins of Life, Meaning, and the Universe Itself &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Brian Cox, Mail on Sunday Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Where are we? Who are we? Do our beliefs, hopes and dreams hold any significance out there in the void? Can human purpose and meaning ever fit into a scientific worldview?    </p>
<p>                    Award-winning author Sean Carroll brings his extraordinary intellect to bear on the realms of knowledge, the laws of nature and the most profound questions about life, death and our place in it all.    </p>
<p>                    From Darwin and Einstein to the origins of life, consciousness and the universe itself, Carroll combines cosmos-sprawling science and profound thought in a quest to explain our world. Destined to sit alongside the works of our greatest thinkers, The Big Picture demonstrates that while our lives may be forever dwarfed by the immensity of the universe, they can be redeemed by our capacity to comprehend it and give it meaning.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Big Picture : On the Origins of Life, Meaning, and the Universe Itself &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmosapiens : Human Evolution from the Origin of the Universe &#8211; John Hands (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Daily Telegraph and TLS Book of the Year &#8216;An audacious tour of all that science can teach us&#8217; Edward O. Wilson Specialist scientific fields are developing at incredibly swift speeds, but what can they really tell us about how the universe began and how humans evolved to play such a dominant role on Earth? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/">Cosmosapiens : Human Evolution from the Origin of the Universe &#8211; John Hands (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Daily Telegraph and TLS Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An audacious tour of all that science can teach us&#8217; Edward O. Wilson    </p>
<p>                    Specialist scientific fields are developing at incredibly swift speeds, but what can they really tell us about how the universe began and how humans evolved to play such a dominant role on Earth? John Hands&#8217;s extraordinarily ambitious quest brings together our scientific knowledge and evaluates the theories and evidence about the origin and evolution of matter, life, consciousness, and humankind.    </p>
<p>                    Cosmosapiens provides the most comprehensive account yet of current ideas such as cosmic inflation, dark energy, the selfish gene, and neurogenetic determinism. In clear and accessible language, Hands differentiates the firmly established from the speculative and examines the claims of various fields such as string theory to approach a unified theory of everything. In doing so he challenges the orthodox consensus in those branches of cosmology, biology, and neuroscience that have ossified into dogma. His striking analysis reveals underlying patterns of cooperation, complexification, and convergence that lead to the unique emergence in humans of a self-reflective consciousness that enables us to determine our future evolution. This groundbreaking book is destined to become a classic of scientific thinking.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/">Cosmosapiens : Human Evolution from the Origin of the Universe &#8211; John Hands (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Story of the Human Body : Evolution, Health and Disease &#8211; Daniel Lieberman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-story-of-the-human-body-evolution-health-and-disease-daniel-lieberman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Palaeontology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-story-of-the-human-body-evolution-health-and-disease-daniel-lieberman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Story of the Human Body, Daniel Lieberman, Professor of human evolutionary biology at Harvard, shows how we need to change our world to fit our hunter-gatherer bodies This ground-breaking book of popular science explores how the way we use our bodies is all wrong. From an evolutionary perspective, if normal is defined as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-the-human-body-evolution-health-and-disease-daniel-lieberman-abridged/">The Story of the Human Body : Evolution, Health and Disease &#8211; Daniel Lieberman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Story of the Human Body, Daniel Lieberman, Professor of human evolutionary biology at Harvard, shows how we need to change our world to fit our hunter-gatherer bodies    </p>
<p>                    This ground-breaking book of popular science explores how the way we use our bodies is all wrong. From an evolutionary perspective, if normal is defined as what most people have done for millions of years, then it&#8217;s normal to walk and run 9 -15 kilometres a day to hunt and gather fresh food which is high in fibre, low in sugar, and barely processed. It&#8217;s also normal to spend much of your time nursing, napping, making stone tools, and gossiping with a small band of people.     </p>
<p>                    Our 21st-century lifestyles, argues Daniel Lieberman, are out of synch with our stone-age bodies. Never have we been so healthy and long-lived &#8211; but never, too, have we been so prone to a slew of problems that were, until recently, rare or unknown, from asthma, to diabetes, to &#8211; scariest of all &#8211; overpopulation.    </p>
<p>                    The Story of the Human Body asks how our bodies got to be the way they are, and considers how that evolutionary history &#8211; both ancient and recent &#8211; can help us evaluate how we use our bodies. How is the present-day state of the human body related to the past? And what is the human body&#8217;s future?<br />
                    &#8216;Monumental. The Story of the Human Body, by one of our leading experts, takes us on an epic voyage&#8217; &#8211; Neil Shubin, author of Your Inner Fish    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Riveting, enlightening, and more than a little frightening&#8217; &#8211; Christopher McDougall, author of Born to Run    </p>
<p>                    Daniel Lieberman is the Chair of the Department of Human Evolutionary Biology at Harvard and a leader in the field. He has written nearly 100 articles, many appearing in the journals Nature and Science, and his cover story on barefoot running in Nature was picked up by major media the world over. His research and discoveries have been highlighted in newspapers and magazines, including The New York Times, Boston Globe, Discover, and National Geographic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-the-human-body-evolution-health-and-disease-daniel-lieberman-abridged/">The Story of the Human Body : Evolution, Health and Disease &#8211; Daniel Lieberman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As we approach a great turning point in history when technology is poised to redefine what it means to be human, The Fourth Age offers fascinating insight into AI, robotics, and their extraordinary implications for our species. &#8220;If you only read just one book about the AI revolution, make it this one&#8221; (John Mackey, cofounder [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/">The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As we approach a great turning point in history when technology is poised to redefine what it means to be human, The Fourth Age offers fascinating insight into AI, robotics, and their extraordinary implications for our species. &#8220;If you only read just one book about the AI revolution, make it this one&#8221; (John Mackey, cofounder and CEO, Whole Foods Market).     </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Age, Byron Reese makes the case that technology has reshaped humanity just three times in history: 100,000 years ago, we harnessed fire, which led to language; 10,000 years ago, we developed agriculture, which led to cities and warfare; 5,000 years ago, we invented the wheel and writing, which lead to the nation state.    </p>
<p>                    We are now on the doorstep of a fourth change brought about by two technologies: AI and robotics. &#8220;Timely, highly informative, and certainly optimistic&#8221; (Booklist), The Fourth Age provides an essential background on how we got to this point, and how-rather than what-we should think about the topics we&#8217;ll soon all be facing: machine consciousness, automation, changes in employment, creative computers, radical life extension, artificial life, AI ethics, the future of warfare, superintelligence, and the implications of extreme prosperity.    </p>
<p>                    By asking questions like &#8220;Are you a machine?&#8221; and &#8220;Could a computer feel anything?&#8221;, Reese leads you through a discussion along the cutting edge in robotics and AI, and provides a framework by which we can all understand, discuss, and act on the issues of the Fourth Age and how they&#8217;ll transform humanity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/">The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are men literally born to cheat? Does monogamy actually serve women&#8217;s interests? These are among the questions that have made The Moral Animal one of the most provocative science books in recent years. Wright unveils the genetic strategies behind everything from our sexual preferences to our office politics&#8211;as well as their implications for our moral [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/">The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are men literally born to cheat? Does monogamy actually serve women&#8217;s interests? These are among the questions that have made The Moral Animal one of the most provocative science books in recent years. Wright unveils the genetic strategies behind everything from our sexual preferences to our office politics&#8211;as well as their implications for our moral codes and public policies. Illustrations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/">The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology: Mammals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans. Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests? By studying [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans.      </p>
<p>                    Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests?     </p>
<p>                    By studying social behaviors in animals, such as bonding, the herd instinct, the forming of trusting alliances, expressions of consolation, and conflict resolution, Frans de Waal demonstrates that animals-and humans-are preprogrammed to reach out. He has found that chimpanzees care for mates that are wounded by leopards, elephants offer reassuring rumbles to youngsters in distress, and dolphins support sick companions near the water&#8217;s surface to prevent them from drowning. From day one humans have innate sensitivities to faces, bodies, and voices; we&#8217;ve been designed to feel for one another.     </p>
<p>                    De Waal&#8217;s theory runs counter to the assumption that humans are inherently selfish, which can be seen in the fields of politics, law, and finance. But he cites the public&#8217;s outrage at the U.S. government&#8217;s lack of empathy in the wake of Hurricane Katrina as a significant shift in perspective-one that helped Barack Obama become elected and ushered in what perhaps could become an Age of Empathy. Through a better understanding of empathy&#8217;s survival value in evolution, de Waal suggests, we can work together toward a more just society based on a more generous and accurate view of human nature.     </p>
<p>                    Written in layman&#8217;s prose with a wealth of anecdotes, wry humor, and incisive intelligence, The Age of Empathy is essential reading for our embattled times.     </p>
<p>                    An important and timely message about the biological roots of human kindness.&#8211;Desmond Morris, author of The Naked Ape</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good Reasons for Bad Feelings : Insights from the Frontier of Evolutionary Psychiatry &#8211; Randolph M. Nesse (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-reasons-for-bad-feelings-insights-from-the-frontier-of-evolutionary-psychiatry-randolph-m-nesse-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Developmental Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-reasons-for-bad-feelings-insights-from-the-frontier-of-evolutionary-psychiatry-randolph-m-nesse-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new approach to mental disorder. Randolph Nesse&#8217;s insightful book suggests that conditions such as anxiety and depression have a clear evolutionary purpose &#8230; This intriguing book turns some age-old questions about the human condition upside down&#8217; Tim Adams, Observer One of the world&#8217;s most respected psychiatrists provides a much-needed new evolutionary framework for making [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-reasons-for-bad-feelings-insights-from-the-frontier-of-evolutionary-psychiatry-randolph-m-nesse-abridged/">Good Reasons for Bad Feelings : Insights from the Frontier of Evolutionary Psychiatry &#8211; Randolph M. Nesse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new approach to mental disorder. Randolph Nesse&#8217;s insightful book  suggests that conditions such as anxiety and depression have a clear  evolutionary purpose &#8230; This intriguing book turns some age-old  questions about the human condition upside down&#8217; Tim Adams, Observer    </p>
<p>                    One of the world&#8217;s most respected psychiatrists provides a much-needed new evolutionary framework for making sense of mental illness    </p>
<p>                    With his classic book Why We Get Sick, Randolph Nesse established the field of evolutionary medicine. Now he returns with a book that transforms our understanding of mental disorders by exploring a fundamentally new question. Instead of asking why certain people suffer from mental illness, Nesse asks why natural selection has left us with fragile minds at all.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on revealing stories from his own clinical practice and insights from evolutionary biology, Nesse shows how negative emotions are useful in certain situations, yet can become excessive. Anxiety protects us from harm in the face of danger, but false alarms are inevitable. Low mood prevents us from wasting effort in pursuit of unreachable goals, but it often escalates into pathological depression. Other mental disorders, such as addiction and anorexia, result from the mismatch between modern environments and our ancient human past. Taken together, these insights and many more help to explain the pervasiveness of human suffering, and show us new paths for relieving it.    </p>
<p>                    Good Reasons for Bad Feelings will fascinate anyone who wonders how our minds can be so powerful, yet so fragile, and how love and goodness came to exist in organisms shaped to maximize Darwinian fitness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-reasons-for-bad-feelings-insights-from-the-frontier-of-evolutionary-psychiatry-randolph-m-nesse-abridged/">Good Reasons for Bad Feelings : Insights from the Frontier of Evolutionary Psychiatry &#8211; Randolph M. Nesse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Survival of the Prettiest : The Science of Beauty &#8211; Nancy Etcoff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/survival-of-the-prettiest-the-science-of-beauty-nancy-etcoff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmetics, Hair & Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/survival-of-the-prettiest-the-science-of-beauty-nancy-etcoff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A provocative and thoroughly researched inquiry into what we find beautiful and why, skewering the myth that the pursuit of beauty is a learned behavior. In Survival of the Prettiest, Nancy Etcoff, a faculty member at Harvard Medical School and a practicing psychologist at Massachusetts General Hospital, argues that beauty is neither a cultural construction, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/survival-of-the-prettiest-the-science-of-beauty-nancy-etcoff-abridged/">Survival of the Prettiest : The Science of Beauty &#8211; Nancy Etcoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A provocative and thoroughly researched inquiry into what we find beautiful and why, skewering the myth that the pursuit of beauty is a learned behavior.     </p>
<p>                     In Survival of the Prettiest, Nancy Etcoff, a faculty member at Harvard Medical School and a practicing psychologist at Massachusetts General Hospital, argues that beauty is neither a cultural construction, an invention of the fashion industry, nor a backlash against feminism&#8211;it&#8217;s in our biology.     </p>
<p>                     Beauty, she explains, is an essential and ineradicable part of human nature that is revered and ferociously pursued in nearly every civilization&#8211;and for good reason. Those features to which we are most attracted are often signals of fertility and fecundity. When seen in the context of a Darwinian struggle for survival, our sometimes extreme attempts to attain beauty&#8211;both to become beautiful ourselves and to acquire an attractive partner&#8211;suddenly become much more understandable. Moreover, if we understand how the desire for beauty is innate, then we can begin to work in our own interests, and not just the interests of our genetic tendencies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/survival-of-the-prettiest-the-science-of-beauty-nancy-etcoff-abridged/">Survival of the Prettiest : The Science of Beauty &#8211; Nancy Etcoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Tangled Tree : A Radical New History of Life &#8211; David Quammen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the National Book Award for Nonfiction and A New York Times Notable Book of 2018. Our understanding of the &#8216;tree of life&#8217;, with powerful implications for human genetics, human health and our own human nature, has recently completely changed. This book is about a new method of telling the story of life on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/">The Tangled Tree : A Radical New History of Life &#8211; David Quammen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the National Book Award for Nonfiction and A New York Times Notable Book of 2018.    </p>
<p>                              Our understanding of the &#8216;tree of life&#8217;, with powerful implications for human genetics, human health and our own human nature, has recently completely changed.    </p>
<p>                              This book is about a new method of telling the story of life on earth &#8211; through molecular phylogenetics. It involves a fairly simple method &#8211; the reading of the deep history of life by looking at the variation in protein molecules found in living organisms. For instance, we now know that roughly eight per cent of the human genome arrived not through traditional inheritance from directly ancestral forms, but sideways by viral infection.    </p>
<p>                              In The Tangled Tree, acclaimed science writer David Quammen chronicles these discoveries through the lives of the researchers who made them &#8211; such as Carl Woese, the most important little-known biologist of the twentieth century; Lynn Margulis, the notorious maverick whose wild ideas about &#8216;mosaic&#8217; creatures proved to be true; and Tsutomu Wantanabe, who discovered that the scourge of antibiotic-resistant bacteria is a direct result of horizontal gene transfer, bringing the deep study of genome histories to bear on a global crisis in public health.    </p>
<p>                              Quammen explains how molecular studies of evolution have brought startling recognitions about the tangled tree of life &#8211; including where we humans fit into it. Thanks to new technologies, we now have the ability to alter even our genetic composition &#8211; through sideways insertions, as nature has long been doing. The Tangled Tree is a brilliant exploration of our transformed understanding of evolution and of life&#8217;s history itself.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tangled-tree-a-radical-new-history-of-life-david-quammen-abridged/">The Tangled Tree : A Radical New History of Life &#8211; David Quammen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeological Methodology & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The past few years have seen a revolution in our ability to map whole genome DNA from ancient humans. With the ancient DNA revolution, combined with rapid genome mapping of present human populations, has come remarkable insights into our past. This important new data has clarified and added to our knowledge from archaeology and anthropology, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/">Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past few years have seen a revolution in our ability to map whole genome DNA from ancient humans. With the ancient DNA revolution, combined with rapid genome mapping of present human populations, has come remarkable insights into our past. This important new data has clarified and added to our knowledge from archaeology and anthropology, helped resolve long-existing controversies, challenged long-held views, and thrown up some remarkable surprises.    </p>
<p>                    The emerging picture is one of many waves of ancient human migrations, so that all populations existing today are mixes of ancient ones, as well as in many cases carrying a genetic component from Neanderthals, and, in some populations, Denisovans. David Reich, whose team has been at the forefront of these discoveries, explains what the genetics is telling us about ourselves and our complex and often surprising ancestry. Gone are old ideas of any kind of racial &#8216;purity&#8217;, or even deep and ancient<br />
                    divides between peoples. Instead, we are finding a rich variety of mixtures. Reich describes the cutting-edge findings from the past few years, and also considers the sensitivities involved in tracing ancestry, with science sometimes jostling with politics and tradition. He brings an important wider<br />
                    message: that we should celebrate our rich diversity, and recognize that every one of us is the result of a long history of migration and intermixing of ancient peoples, which we carry as ghosts in our DNA.    </p>
<p>                    What will we discover next?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/">Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Red Queen : Sex and the Evolution of Human Nature &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-red-queen-sex-and-the-evolution-of-human-nature-matt-ridley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-red-queen-sex-and-the-evolution-of-human-nature-matt-ridley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A terrific book, witty and lucid, and brimming with provocative conjectures.&#8221; (Wall Street Journal) from the author of the acclaimed New York Times bestseller Genome Brilliantly written, The Red Queen compels us to rethink everything from the persistence of sexism to the endurance of romantic love. Referring to Lewis Carroll&#8217;s Red Queen from Through the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-red-queen-sex-and-the-evolution-of-human-nature-matt-ridley-abridged/">The Red Queen : Sex and the Evolution of Human Nature &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A terrific book, witty and lucid, and brimming with provocative conjectures.&#8221; (Wall Street Journal) from the author of the acclaimed New York Times bestseller Genome    </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly written, The Red Queen compels us to rethink everything from the persistence of sexism to the endurance of romantic love.    </p>
<p>                    Referring to Lewis Carroll&#8217;s Red Queen from Through the Looking-Glass, a character who has to keep running to stay in the same place, Matt Ridley demonstrates why sex is humanity&#8217;s best strategy for outwitting its constantly mutating internal predators. The Red Queen answers dozens of other riddles of human nature and culture&#8211;including why men propose marriage, the method behind our maddening notions of beauty, and the disquieting fact that a woman is more likely to conceive a child by an adulterous lover than by her husband. The Red Queen offers an extraordinary new way of interpreting the human condition and how it has evolved.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-red-queen-sex-and-the-evolution-of-human-nature-matt-ridley-abridged/">The Red Queen : Sex and the Evolution of Human Nature &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene<br />
                    Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the future of our species for fans of Homo Deus and The Gene.<br />
                    After 3.8 billion years humankind is about to start evolving by new rules&#8230;<br />
                    From leading geopolitical expert and technology futurist Jamie Metzl comes a groundbreaking exploration of the many ways genetic-engineering is shaking the core foundations of our lives-sex, war, love, and death.<br />
                    At the dawn of the genetics revolution, our DNA is becoming as readable, writable, and hackable as our information technology. But as humanity starts retooling our own genetic code, the choices we make today will be the difference between realizing breathtaking advances in human well-being and descending into a dangerous and potentially deadly genetic arms race.<br />
                    Enter the laboratories where scientists are turning science fiction into reality. Look towards a future where our deepest beliefs, morals, religions, and politics are challenged like never before and the very essence of what it means to be human is at play. When we can engineer our future children, massively extend our lifespans, build life from scratch, and recreate the plant and animal world, should we?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The million copy international bestseller, critically acclaimed and translated into over 25 languages. As influential today as when it was first published, The Selfish Gene has become a classic exposition of evolutionary thought. Professor Dawkins articulates a gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution &#8211; a view giving centre stage to these persistent units of information, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The million copy international bestseller, critically acclaimed and translated into over 25 languages.    </p>
<p>                    As influential today as when it was first published, The Selfish Gene  has become a classic exposition of evolutionary thought. Professor Dawkins articulates a gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution &#8211; a view giving centre stage to these persistent units of information, and in which organisms can be seen as vehicles for their replication. This imaginative, powerful, and stylistically brilliant work not only brought the insights of Neo-Darwinism to a wide audience, but galvanized the biology<br />
                    community, generating much debate and stimulating whole new areas of research. Forty years later, its insights remain as relevant today as on the day it was published.     </p>
<p>                    This 40th anniversary edition includes a new epilogue from the author discussing the continuing relevance of these ideas in evolutionary biology today, as well as the original prefaces and foreword, and extracts from early reviews.     </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Makes Us Human? &#8211; Edited byCharles Pasternak (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-makes-us-human-edited-by-charles-pasternak-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance, C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-makes-us-human-edited-by-charles-pasternak-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In What Makes us Human? some of the world&#8217;s most brilliant thinkers answer this perennial puzzle. Is it our imagination or our knack for cooking? Is it because we are social, scientific, or spiritual? Exploring the true nature of human nature, What Makes us Human? sheds new light on how and why our ancestors produced [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-makes-us-human-edited-by-charles-pasternak-abridged/">What Makes Us Human? &#8211; Edited byCharles Pasternak (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In What Makes us Human? some of the world&#8217;s    </p>
<p>                    most brilliant thinkers answer this perennial    </p>
<p>                    puzzle. Is it our imagination or our knack for    </p>
<p>                    cooking? Is it because we are social, scientific,    </p>
<p>                    or spiritual? Exploring the true nature of human    </p>
<p>                    nature, What Makes us Human? sheds new    </p>
<p>                    light on how and why our ancestors produced    </p>
<p>                    such clever, talented, and unlikely progeny.    </p>
<p>                    With contributions by Susan Blackmore, Robin    </p>
<p>                    Dunbar, Stephen Oppenheimer, Ian Tattersall, and    </p>
<p>                    more.For all to enjoy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-makes-us-human-edited-by-charles-pasternak-abridged/">What Makes Us Human? &#8211; Edited byCharles Pasternak (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs : The Untold Story of a Lost World &#8211; Steve Brusatte (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dinosaurs & The Prehistoric World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Palaeontology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Times Science Book of the Year. A Sunday Times Bestseller. 66 million years ago the dinosaurs were wiped from the face of the earth. Today, Dr. Steve Brusatte, one of the leading scientists of a new generation of dinosaur hunters, armed with cutting edge technology, is piecing together the complete story of how the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/">The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs : The Untold Story of a Lost World &#8211; Steve Brusatte (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Times Science Book of the Year.<br />
                    A Sunday Times Bestseller.    </p>
<p>                    66 million years ago the dinosaurs were wiped from the face of the earth. Today, Dr. Steve Brusatte, one of the leading scientists of a new generation of dinosaur hunters, armed with cutting edge technology, is piecing together the complete story of how the dinosaurs ruled the earth for 150 million years.    </p>
<p>                    The world of the dinosaurs has fascinated on book and screen for decades &#8211; from early science fiction classics like The Lost World, to Godzilla terrorizing the streets of Tokyo, and the monsters of Jurassic Park. But what if we got it wrong? In The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs, top dinosaur expert Brusatte, tells the real story of how dinosaurs rose to dominate the planet. Using the fossil clues that have been gathered using state of the art technology, Brusatte follows these magnificent creatures from their beginnings in the Early Triassic period, through the Jurassic period to their final days in the Cretaceous and the legacy that they left behind.    </p>
<p>                    Along the way, Brusatte introduces us to modern day dinosaur hunters and gives an insight into what it&#8217;s like to be a paleontologist. The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs is full of thrilling accounts of some of his personal discoveries, including primitive human-sized tyrannosaurs, monstrous carnivores even larger than T. rex, and feathered raptor dinosaurs preserved in lava from China.     </p>
<p>                    At a time when Homo sapiens has existed for less than 200,000 years and we are already talking about planetary extinction, The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs is a timely reminder of what humans can learn from the magnificent creatures who ruled the earth before us.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thrilling . . . the best book on the subject written for the general reader since the 1980s.&#8217; &#8211;  The Sunday Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/">The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs : The Untold Story of a Lost World &#8211; Steve Brusatte (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control  chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On the Origin of Species : By Means of Natural Selection &#8211; Charles Darwin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-the-origin-of-species-by-means-of-natural-selection-charles-darwin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-the-origin-of-species-by-means-of-natural-selection-charles-darwin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Origin is one of the most important books ever published, and a knowledge of it should be a part of the intellectual equipment of every educated person. . . . The book will endure in future ages so long as a knowledge of science persists among mankind. &#8212; Nature It took Charles Darwin more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-the-origin-of-species-by-means-of-natural-selection-charles-darwin-abridged/">On the Origin of Species : By Means of Natural Selection &#8211; Charles Darwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Origin is one of the most important books ever published, and a knowledge of it should be a part of the intellectual equipment of every educated person. . . . The book will endure in future ages so long as a knowledge of science persists among mankind. &#8212; Nature<br />
                    It took Charles Darwin more than twenty years to publish this book, in part because he realized that it would ignite a firestorm of controversy. On the Origin of Species first appeared in 1859, and it remains a continuing source of conflict to this day. Even among those who reject its ideas, however, the work&#8217;s impact is undeniable. In science, philosophy, and theology, this is a book that changed the world.<br />
                    In addition to its status as the focus of a dramatic turning point in scientific thought, On the Origin of Species stands as a remarkably readable study. Carefully reasoned and well-documented in its arguments, the work offers coherent views of natural selection, adaptation, the struggle for existence, survival of the fittest, and other concepts that form the foundation of modern evolutionary theory. This volume is a reprint of the critically acclaimed first edition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-the-origin-of-species-by-means-of-natural-selection-charles-darwin-abridged/">On the Origin of Species : By Means of Natural Selection &#8211; Charles Darwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A specialist on social insects writes about the origins and implications of our own vast social organisation, and the ways in which our ethnic and national distinctions mirror those of other animals. In this paradigm-shattering book, biologist Mark W. Moffett draws on findings in psychology, sociology and anthropology to explain the social adaptations that bind [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/">The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A specialist on social insects writes about the origins and implications of our own vast social organisation, and the ways in which our ethnic and national distinctions mirror those of other animals.     </p>
<p>                    In this paradigm-shattering book, biologist Mark W. Moffett draws on findings in psychology, sociology and anthropology to explain the social adaptations that bind societies. He explores how the tension between identity and anonymity defines how societies develop, function, and fail. In the vein of Guns, Germs, and Steel and Sapiens, The Human Swarm reveals how mankind created sprawling civilizations of unrivalled complexity &#8211; and what it will take to sustain them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/">The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blueprint : The Evolutionary Origins of a Good Society &#8211; Nicholas A. Christakis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blueprint-the-evolutionary-origins-of-a-good-society-nicholas-a-christakis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blueprint-the-evolutionary-origins-of-a-good-society-nicholas-a-christakis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For too long, scientists have focused on the dark side of our biological heritage: our capacity for aggression, cruelty, prejudice, and self-interest. But natural selection has given us a suite of beneficial social features, including our capacity for love, friendship, cooperation, and learning. Beneath all our inventions &#8212; our tools, farms, machines, cities, nations &#8212; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blueprint-the-evolutionary-origins-of-a-good-society-nicholas-a-christakis-abridged/">Blueprint : The Evolutionary Origins of a Good Society &#8211; Nicholas A. Christakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For too long, scientists have focused on the dark side of our biological heritage: our capacity for aggression, cruelty, prejudice, and self-interest. But natural selection has given us a suite of beneficial social features, including our capacity for love, friendship, cooperation, and learning. Beneath all our inventions &#8212; our tools, farms, machines, cities, nations &#8212; we carry with us innate proclivities to make a good society.     </p>
<p>                    In Blueprint, Nicholas A. Christakis introduces the compelling idea that our genes affect not only our bodies and behaviors, but also the ways in which we make societies, ones that are surprisingly similar worldwide. With many vivid examples &#8212; including diverse historical and contemporary cultures, communities formed in the wake of shipwrecks, commune dwellers seeking utopia, online groups thrown together by design or involving artificially intelligent bots, and even the tender and complex social arrangements of elephants and dolphins that so resemble our own &#8212; Christakis shows that, despite a human history replete with violence, we cannot escape our social blueprint for goodness.     </p>
<p>                    In a world of increasing political and economic polarization, it&#8217;s tempting to ignore the positive role of our evolutionary past. But by exploring the ancient roots of goodness in civilization, Blueprint shows that our genes have shaped societies for our welfare and that, in a feedback loop stretching back many thousands of years, societies have shaped, and are still shaping, our genes today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blueprint-the-evolutionary-origins-of-a-good-society-nicholas-a-christakis-abridged/">Blueprint : The Evolutionary Origins of a Good Society &#8211; Nicholas A. Christakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Feathers : The Evolution of a Natural Miracle &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/feathers-the-evolution-of-a-natural-miracle-thor-hanson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Birds (ornithology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dinosaurs & The Prehistoric World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Birds & Birdwatching]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/feathers-the-evolution-of-a-natural-miracle-thor-hanson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Feathers are an evolutionary marvel: aerodynamic, insulating, beguiling. They date back more than 100 million years. Yet their story has never been fully told. In Feathers , biologist Thor Hanson details a sweeping natural history, as feathers have been used to fly, protect, attract, and adorn through time and place. Applying the research of paleontologists, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feathers-the-evolution-of-a-natural-miracle-thor-hanson-abridged/">Feathers : The Evolution of a Natural Miracle &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Feathers are an evolutionary marvel: aerodynamic, insulating, beguiling. They date back more than 100 million years. Yet their story has never been fully told. In  Feathers , biologist Thor Hanson details a sweeping natural history, as feathers have been used to fly, protect, attract, and adorn through time and place. Applying the research of paleontologists, ornithologists, biologists, engineers, and even art historians, Hanson asks: What are feathers? How did they evolve? What do they mean to us? Engineers call feathers the most efficient insulating material ever discovered, and they are at the root of biology&#8217;s most enduring debate. They silence the flight of owls and keep penguins dry below the ice. They have decorated queens, jesters, and priests. And they have inked documents from the Constitution to the novels of Jane Austen.  Feathers  is a captivating and beautiful exploration of this most enchanting object.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feathers-the-evolution-of-a-natural-miracle-thor-hanson-abridged/">Feathers : The Evolution of a Natural Miracle &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life : A Psychologist Investigates How Evolution, Cognition, and Complexity are Revolutionizing Our View of Human Nature &#8211; Douglas Kenrick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sex-murder-and-the-meaning-of-life-a-psychologist-investigates-how-evolution-cognition-and-complexity-are-revolutionizing-our-view-of-human-nature-douglas-kenrick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sex-murder-and-the-meaning-of-life-a-psychologist-investigates-how-evolution-cognition-and-complexity-are-revolutionizing-our-view-of-human-nature-douglas-kenrick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#038;ldquoKenrick writes like a dream.&#8221;- Robert Sapolsky, Professor of Biology and Neurology, Stanford University author of A Primate&#8217;s Memoir and Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers What do sex and murder have to do with the meaning of life? Everything. In Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life , social psychologist Douglas Kenrick exposes the selfish [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-murder-and-the-meaning-of-life-a-psychologist-investigates-how-evolution-cognition-and-complexity-are-revolutionizing-our-view-of-human-nature-douglas-kenrick-abridged/">Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life : A Psychologist Investigates How Evolution, Cognition, and Complexity are Revolutionizing Our View of Human Nature &#8211; Douglas Kenrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#038;ldquoKenrick writes like a dream.&#8221;- Robert Sapolsky, Professor of Biology and Neurology, Stanford University author of  A Primate&#8217;s Memoir  and  Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers  What do sex and murder have to do with the meaning of life? Everything. In  Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life , social psychologist Douglas Kenrick exposes the selfish animalistic underside of human nature, and shows how it is intimately connected to our greatest and most selfless achievements. Masterfully integrating cognitive science, evolutionary psychology, and complexity theory, this intriguing book paints a comprehensive picture of the principles that govern our lives. As Kenrick divulges, beneath our civilized veneer, human beings are a lot like howling hyenas and barking baboons, with heads full of homicidal tendencies and sexual fantasies. But, in his view, many ingrained, apparently irrational behaviours- such as inclinations to one-night stands, racial prejudices, and conspicuous consumption- ultimately manifest what he calls&#8221;Deep Rationality.&#8221;  Although our heads are full of simple selfish biases that evolved to help our ancestors survive, modern human beings are anything but simple and selfish cavemen. Kenrick argues that simple and selfish mental mechanisms we inherited from our ancestors ultimately give rise to the multifaceted social lives that we humans lead today, and to the most positive features of humanity, including generosity, artistic creativity, love, and familial bonds. And out of those simple mechanisms emerge all the complexities of society, including international conflicts and global economic markets. By exploring the nuance of social psychology and the surprising results of his own research, Kenrick offers a detailed picture of what makes us caring, creative, and complex- that is, fully human.   Illuminated with stories from Kenrick&#8217;s own colourful experiences &#8211;  from his criminally inclined shantytown Irish relatives, his own multiple high school expulsions, broken marriages, and homicidal fantasies, to his eventual success as an evolutionary psychologist and loving father of two boys separated by 26 years &#8211;  this book is an exploration of our mental biases and failures, and our mind&#8217;s great successes. Idiosyncratic, controversial, and fascinating,  Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life  uncovers the pitfalls and promise of our biological inheritance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-murder-and-the-meaning-of-life-a-psychologist-investigates-how-evolution-cognition-and-complexity-are-revolutionizing-our-view-of-human-nature-douglas-kenrick-abridged/">Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life : A Psychologist Investigates How Evolution, Cognition, and Complexity are Revolutionizing Our View of Human Nature &#8211; Douglas Kenrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
