<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Literary Reference Works Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/literary-reference-works/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/literary-reference-works/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Literary Reference Works Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/literary-reference-works/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>On Writing : A Memoir of the Craft: Twentieth Anniversary Edition with Contributions from Joe Hill and Owen King &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/on-writing-a-memoir-of-the-craft-twentieth-anniversary-edition-with-contributions-from-joe-hill-and-owen-king-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Novelists & Prose Writers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-writing-a-memoir-of-the-craft-twentieth-anniversary-edition-with-contributions-from-joe-hill-and-owen-king-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Twentieth Anniversary Edition with Contributions from Joe Hill and Owen King Immensely helpful and illuminating to any aspiring writer, this special edition of Stephen King&#8217;s critically lauded, million-copy bestseller shares the experiences, habits, and convictions that have shaped him and his work. Part memoir, part masterclass by one of the bestselling authors of all time, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-writing-a-memoir-of-the-craft-twentieth-anniversary-edition-with-contributions-from-joe-hill-and-owen-king-stephen-king/">On Writing : A Memoir of the Craft: Twentieth Anniversary Edition with Contributions from Joe Hill and Owen King &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Twentieth Anniversary Edition with Contributions from Joe Hill and Owen King </p>
<p>                    Immensely helpful and illuminating to any aspiring writer, this special edition of Stephen King&#8217;s critically lauded, million-copy bestseller shares the experiences, habits, and convictions that have shaped him and his work.</p>
<p>                     Part memoir, part masterclass by one of the bestselling authors of all time, this superb volume is a revealing and practical view of the writer&#8217;s craft, comprising the basic tools of the trade every writer must have. </p>
<p>                    King&#8217;s advice is grounded in his vivid memories from childhood through his emergence as a writer, from his struggling early career to his widely reported, near-fatal accident in 1999 &#8211; and how the inextricable link between writing and living spurred his recovery. </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly structured, friendly and inspiring, On Writing will empower and entertain everyone who reads it &#8211; fans, writers, and anyone who loves a great story well told.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-writing-a-memoir-of-the-craft-twentieth-anniversary-edition-with-contributions-from-joe-hill-and-owen-king-stephen-king/">On Writing : A Memoir of the Craft: Twentieth Anniversary Edition with Contributions from Joe Hill and Owen King &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sense of Style : The Thinking Person&#8217;s Guide to Writing in the 21st Century &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sense-of-style-the-thinking-persons-guide-to-writing-in-the-21st-century-steven-pinker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Grammar, Syntax]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psycholinguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sense-of-style-the-thinking-persons-guide-to-writing-in-the-21st-century-steven-pinker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steven Pinker, the bestselling author of The Language Instinct, deploys his gift for explaining big ideas in The Sense of Style &#8211; an entertaining writing guide for the 21st century What is the secret of good prose? Does writing well even matter in an age of instant communication? Should we care? In this funny, thoughtful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sense-of-style-the-thinking-persons-guide-to-writing-in-the-21st-century-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Sense of Style : The Thinking Person&#8217;s Guide to Writing in the 21st Century &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steven Pinker, the bestselling author of The Language Instinct, deploys his gift for explaining big ideas in The Sense of Style &#8211; an entertaining writing guide for the 21st century    </p>
<p>                    What is the secret of good prose? Does writing well even matter in an age of instant communication? Should we care? In this funny, thoughtful book about the modern art of writing, Steven Pinker shows us why we all need a sense of style.    </p>
<p>                    More than ever before, the currency of our social and cultural lives is the written word, from Twitter and texting to blogs, e-readers and old-fashioned books. But most style guides fail to prepare people for the challenges of writing in the 21st century, portraying it as a minefield of grievous errors rather than a form of pleasurable mastery. They fail to deal with an inescapable fact about language: it changes over time, adapted by millions of writers and speakers to their needs. Confusing changes in the world with moral decline, every generation believes the kids today are degrading society and taking language with it. A guide for the new millennium, writes Steven Pinker, has to be different.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the latest research in linguistics and cognitive science, Steven Pinker replaces the recycled dogma of previous style guides with reason and evidence. This thinking person&#8217;s guide to good writing shows why style still matters: in communicating effectively, in enhancing the spread of ideas, in earning a reader&#8217;s trust and, not least, in adding beauty to the world. Eye-opening, mind-expanding and cheerful, The Sense of Style shows that good style is part of what it means to be human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sense-of-style-the-thinking-persons-guide-to-writing-in-the-21st-century-steven-pinker-abridged/">The Sense of Style : The Thinking Person&#8217;s Guide to Writing in the 21st Century &#8211; Steven Pinker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mythology : Timeless Tales of Gods and Heroes, 75th Anniversary Illustrated Edition &#8211; Edith Hamilton, Illustrated by Jim Tierney (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mythology-timeless-tales-of-gods-and-heroes-75th-anniversary-illustrated-edition-edith-hamilton-illustrated-by-jim-tierney-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ancient Religions & Mythologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Folklore, Myths & Legends]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Classical, Early & Medieval]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Traditional]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mythology-timeless-tales-of-gods-and-heroes-75th-anniversary-illustrated-edition-edith-hamilton-illustrated-by-jim-tierney-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since its original publication by Little, Brown and Company in 1942, Edith Hamilton&#8217;s Mythology has sold millions of copies throughout the word and established itself as a perennial bestseller in its various available formats: hardcover, trade paperback, mass market paperback, and e-book. For 75 years readers have chosen this book above all others to discover [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mythology-timeless-tales-of-gods-and-heroes-75th-anniversary-illustrated-edition-edith-hamilton-illustrated-by-jim-tierney-abridged/">Mythology : Timeless Tales of Gods and Heroes, 75th Anniversary Illustrated Edition &#8211; Edith Hamilton, Illustrated by Jim Tierney (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since its original publication by Little, Brown and Company in 1942, Edith Hamilton&#8217;s Mythology has sold millions of copies throughout the word and established itself as a perennial bestseller in its various available formats: hardcover, trade paperback, mass market paperback, and e-book. For 75 years readers have chosen this book above all others to discover the thrilling, enchanting, and fascinating world of Western mythology-from Odysseus&#8217;s adventure-filled journey to the Norse god Odin&#8217;s effort to postpone the final day of doom. This exciting new deluxe, large-format hardcover edition, published in celebration of the book&#8217;s 75th anniversary, will be beautifully packages and fully-illustrated throughout with all-new, specially commissioned four-color art, making it a true collector&#8217;s item.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mythology-timeless-tales-of-gods-and-heroes-75th-anniversary-illustrated-edition-edith-hamilton-illustrated-by-jim-tierney-abridged/">Mythology : Timeless Tales of Gods and Heroes, 75th Anniversary Illustrated Edition &#8211; Edith Hamilton, Illustrated by Jim Tierney (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Read Literature Like a Professor Revised Edition : A Lively and Entertaining Guide to Reading Between the Lines &#8211; Thomas C Foster (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-read-literature-like-a-professor-revised-edition-a-lively-and-entertaining-guide-to-reading-between-the-lines-thomas-c-foster-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry & Drama]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-read-literature-like-a-professor-revised-edition-a-lively-and-entertaining-guide-to-reading-between-the-lines-thomas-c-foster-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A thoroughly revised and updated edition of Thomas C. Foster&#8217;s classic guide-a lively and entertaining introduction to literature and literary basics, including symbols, themes and contexts, that shows you how to make your everyday reading experience more rewarding and enjoyable. While many books can be enjoyed for their basic stories, there are often deeper literary [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-read-literature-like-a-professor-revised-edition-a-lively-and-entertaining-guide-to-reading-between-the-lines-thomas-c-foster-abridged/">How to Read Literature Like a Professor Revised Edition : A Lively and Entertaining Guide to Reading Between the Lines &#8211; Thomas C Foster (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A thoroughly revised and updated edition of Thomas C. Foster&#8217;s classic guide-a lively and entertaining introduction to literature and literary basics, including symbols, themes and contexts, that shows you how to make your everyday reading experience more rewarding and enjoyable.  While many books can be enjoyed for their basic stories, there are often deeper literary meanings interwoven in these texts. How to Read Literature Like a Professor helps us to discover those hidden truths by looking at literature with the eyes-and the literary codes-of the ultimate professional reader, the college professor.  What does it mean when a literary hero is traveling along a dusty road? When he hands a drink to his companion? When he&#8217;s drenched in a sudden rain shower?  Ranging from major themes to literary models, narrative devices and form, Thomas C. Foster provides us with a broad overview of literature-a world where a road leads to a quest, a shared meal may signify a communion, and rain, whether cleansing or destructive, is never just a shower-and shows us how to make our reading experience more enriching, satisfying, and fun.<br />
                    This revised edition includes new chapters, a new preface and epilogue, and incorporates updated teaching points that Foster has developed over the past decade.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-read-literature-like-a-professor-revised-edition-a-lively-and-entertaining-guide-to-reading-between-the-lines-thomas-c-foster-abridged/">How to Read Literature Like a Professor Revised Edition : A Lively and Entertaining Guide to Reading Between the Lines &#8211; Thomas C Foster (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
