<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Adventure Holidays Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/adventure-holidays/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/adventure-holidays/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Adventure Holidays Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/adventure-holidays/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Into Thin Air : A Personal Account of the Mt. Everest Disaster &#8211; Jon Krakauer</title>
		<link>/into-thin-air-a-personal-account-of-the-mt-everest-disaster-jon-krakauer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Climbing & Mountaineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Endurance & Survival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories Of Heroism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/into-thin-air-a-personal-account-of-the-mt-everest-disaster-jon-krakauer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; A harrowing tale of the perils of high-altitude climbing, a story of bad luck and worse judgment and of heartbreaking heroism. &#8211;PEOPLE A bank of clouds was assembling on the not-so-distant horizon, but journalist-mountaineer Jon Krakauer, standing on the summit of Mt. Everest, saw nothing that suggested that a murderous storm [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/into-thin-air-a-personal-account-of-the-mt-everest-disaster-jon-krakauer/">Into Thin Air : A Personal Account of the Mt. Everest Disaster &#8211; Jon Krakauer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; A harrowing tale of the perils of high-altitude climbing, a story of bad luck and worse judgment and of heartbreaking heroism. &#8211;PEOPLE  </p>
<p>                    A bank of clouds was assembling on the not-so-distant horizon, but journalist-mountaineer Jon Krakauer, standing on the summit of Mt. Everest, saw nothing that suggested that a murderous storm was bearing down. He was wrong. The storm, which claimed five lives and left countless more&#8211;including Krakauer&#8217;s&#8211;in guilt-ridden disarray, would also provide the impetus for Into Thin Air, Krakauer&#8217;s epic account of the May 1996 disaster. </p>
<p>                    By writing Into Thin Air, Krakauer may have hoped to exorcise some of his own demons and lay to rest some of the painful questions that still surround the event. He takes great pains to provide a balanced picture of the people and events he witnessed and gives due credit to the tireless and dedicated Sherpas. He also avoids blasting easy targets such as Sandy Pittman, the wealthy socialite who brought an espresso maker along on the expedition. Krakauer&#8217;s highly personal inquiry into the catastrophe provides a great deal of insight into what went wrong. But for Krakauer himself, further interviews and investigations only lead him to the conclusion that his perceived failures were directly responsible for a fellow climber&#8217;s death. Clearly, Krakauer remains haunted by the disaster, and although he relates a number of incidents in which he acted selflessly and even heroically, he seems unable to view those instances objectively. In the end, despite his evenhanded and even generous assessment of others&#8217; actions, he reserves a full measure of vitriol for himself. </p>
<p>                    This updated trade paperback edition of Into Thin Air includes an extensive new postscript that sheds fascinating light on the acrimonious debate that flared between Krakauer and Everest guide Anatoli Boukreev in the wake of the tragedy. I have no doubt that Boukreev&#8217;s intentions were good on summit day, writes Krakauer in the postscript, dated August 1999. What disturbs me, though, was Boukreev&#8217;s refusal to acknowledge the possibility that he made even a single poor decision. Never did he indicate that perhaps it wasn&#8217;t the best choice to climb without gas or go down ahead of his clients. As usual, Krakauer supports his points with dogged research and a good dose of humility. But rather than continue the heated discourse that has raged since Into Thin Air&#8217;s denouncement of guide Boukreev, Krakauer&#8217;s tone is conciliatory; he points most of his criticism at G. Weston De Walt, who coauthored The Climb, Boukreev&#8217;s version of events. And in a touching conclusion, Krakauer recounts his last conversation with the late Boukreev, in which the two weathered climbers agreed to disagree about certain points. Krakauer had great hopes to patch things up with Boukreev, but the Russian later died in an avalanche on another Himalayan peak, Annapurna I. </p>
<p>                    In 1999, Krakauer received an Academy Award in Literature from the American Academy of Arts and Letters&#8211;a prestigious prize intended to honor writers of exceptional accomplishment. According to the Academy&#8217;s citation, Krakauer combines the tenacity and courage of the finest tradition of investigative journalism with the stylish subtlety and profound insight of the born writer. His account of an ascent of Mount Everest has led to a general reevaluation of climbing and of the commercialization of what was once a romantic, solitary sport; while his account of the life and death of Christopher McCandless, who died of starvation after challenging the Alaskan wilderness, delves even more deeply and disturbingly into the fascination of nature and the devastating effects of its lure on a young and curious mind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/into-thin-air-a-personal-account-of-the-mt-everest-disaster-jon-krakauer/">Into Thin Air : A Personal Account of the Mt. Everest Disaster &#8211; Jon Krakauer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tips & Advice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Maps & Atlases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a new foreword by Tim Ferriss &#8211; &#8220;Vagabonding easily remains in my top-10 list of life-changing books. Why? Because one incredible trip, especially a long-term trip, can change your life forever. And Vagabonding teaches you how to travel (and think), not just for one trip, but for the rest of your life.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Ferriss, from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a new foreword by Tim Ferriss &#8211; &#8220;Vagabonding easily remains in my top-10 list of life-changing books. Why? Because one incredible trip, especially a long-term trip, can change your life forever. And Vagabonding teaches you how to travel (and think), not just for one trip, but for the rest of your life.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Ferriss, from the foreword     </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s nothing like vagabonding: taking time off from your normal life&#8211;from six weeks to four months to two years&#8211;to discover and experience the world on your own terms. In this one-of-a-kind handbook, veteran travel writer Rolf Potts explains how anyone armed with an independent spirit can achieve the dream of extended overseas travel. Now completely revised and updated, Vagabonding is an accessible and inspiring guide to     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; financing your travel time<br />
                     &#8211; determining your destination<br />
                     &#8211; adjusting to life on the road<br />
                     &#8211; working and volunteering overseas<br />
                     &#8211; handling travel adversity<br />
                     &#8211; re-assimilating back into ordinary life     </p>
<p>                     Praise for Vagabonding    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A crucial reference for any budget wanderer.&#8221;&#8211;Time    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The book is a meditation on the joys of hitting the road. . . . It&#8217;s also a primer for those with a case of pent-up wanderlust seeking to live the dream.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I couldn&#8217;t put this book down. It&#8217;s a whole different ethic of travel. . . . [Potts&#8217;s] practical advice might just convince you to enjoy that open-ended trip of a lifetime.&#8221;&#8211;Rick Steves     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Potts wants us to wander, to explore, to embrace the unknown, and, finally, to take our own damn time about it. I think this is the most sensible book of travel-related advice ever written.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Cahill, founding editor of Outside</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
