<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Production &amp; Quality Control Management Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/production-quality-control-management/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/production-quality-control-management/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Production &amp; Quality Control Management Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/production-quality-control-management/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Reinventing the Product : How to Transform your Business and Create Value in the Digital Age &#8211; Eric Schaeffer, David Sovie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reinventing-the-product-how-to-transform-your-business-and-create-value-in-the-digital-age-eric-schaeffer-david-sovie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reinventing-the-product-how-to-transform-your-business-and-create-value-in-the-digital-age-eric-schaeffer-david-sovie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Create the personalized and compelling experiences that today&#8217;s customers expect by harnessing AI and digital technologies to create smart connected products, with this cutting-edge guide from senior leaders at Accenture. Digital technology is both friend and foe: highly disruptive, yet it cannot be ignored. As traditional products transform into smart connected products faster than ever [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reinventing-the-product-how-to-transform-your-business-and-create-value-in-the-digital-age-eric-schaeffer-david-sovie-abridged/">Reinventing the Product : How to Transform your Business and Create Value in the Digital Age &#8211; Eric Schaeffer, David Sovie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Create the personalized and compelling experiences that today&#8217;s customers expect by harnessing AI and digital technologies to create smart connected products, with this cutting-edge guide from senior leaders at Accenture.      </p>
<p>                    Digital technology is both friend and foe: highly disruptive, yet it cannot be ignored. As traditional products transform into smart connected products faster than ever before, companies that fail to make use of it now put themselves in the firing line for disintermediation or even eradication.     </p>
<p>                    However, digital technology is also the biggest opportunity for product-making businesses to create the next generation of goods in the marketplace. In Reinventing the Product, Eric Schaeffer and David Sovie, both Senior Managing Directors at Accenture, show how this reinvention is made possible, to deliver truly intelligent, and often even autonomous, products.     </p>
<p>                    Reinventing the Product makes the case for companies to rethink their product strategy, innovation and engineering processes, including:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; How to harness the opportunities of AI and digital technologies, such as IoT sensors, blockchain, advanced analytics, cloud and edge computing<br />
                    &#8211; Practical advice on transforming their entire culture to build the future of successful &#8216;living products&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Features case studies from global organizations such as Faurecia, Signify, Symmons and Haier and interviews with thought leaders from top companies including Amazon, ABB, Tesla, Samsung and Google    </p>
<p>                    This book provides the only advice any product-making company needs as it embarks on, or accelerates, its digitization journey.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reinventing-the-product-how-to-transform-your-business-and-create-value-in-the-digital-age-eric-schaeffer-david-sovie-abridged/">Reinventing the Product : How to Transform your Business and Create Value in the Digital Age &#8211; Eric Schaeffer, David Sovie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Traction: Get a Grip on Your Business : Get a Grip on Your Business &#8211; Gino Wickman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/traction-get-a-grip-on-your-business-get-a-grip-on-your-business-gino-wickman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/traction-get-a-grip-on-your-business-get-a-grip-on-your-business-gino-wickman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you have a grip on your business, or does your business have a grip on you? All entrepreneurs and business leaders face similar frustrations&#8211;personnel conflict, profit woes, and inadequate growth. Decisions never seem to get made, or, once made, fail to be properly implemented. But there is a solution. It&#8217;s not complicated or theoretical.The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/traction-get-a-grip-on-your-business-get-a-grip-on-your-business-gino-wickman-abridged/">Traction: Get a Grip on Your Business : Get a Grip on Your Business &#8211; Gino Wickman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you have a grip on your business, or does your business have a grip on you? All entrepreneurs and business leaders face similar frustrations&#8211;personnel conflict, profit woes, and inadequate growth. Decisions never seem to get made, or, once made, fail to be properly implemented. But there is a solution. It&#8217;s not complicated or theoretical.The Entrepreneurial Operating System(R) is a practical method for achieving the business success you have always envisioned. More than 2,000 companies have discovered what EOS can do. In Traction, you&#8217;ll learn the secrets of strengthening the six key components of your business. You&#8217;ll discover simple yet powerful ways to run your company that will give you and your leadership team more focus, more growth, and more enjoyment. Successful companies are applying Traction every day to run profitable, frustration-free businesses&#8211;and you can too. For an illustrative, real-world lesson on how to apply Traction to your business, check out its companion book, Get A Grip.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/traction-get-a-grip-on-your-business-get-a-grip-on-your-business-gino-wickman-abridged/">Traction: Get a Grip on Your Business : Get a Grip on Your Business &#8211; Gino Wickman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thinking in New Boxes : A New Paradigm for Business Creativity &#8211; Luc De Brabandere, Alan Iny (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thinking-in-new-boxes-a-new-paradigm-for-business-creativity-luc-de-brabandere-alan-iny-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thinking-in-new-boxes-a-new-paradigm-for-business-creativity-luc-de-brabandere-alan-iny-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When BIC, manufacturer of disposable ballpoint pens, wanted to grow, it looked for an idea beyond introducing new sizes and ink colors. Someone suggested lighters. LIGHTERS? With an idea that seemed crazy at first, that bright executive, instead of seeing BIC as a pen company&#8211;a business in the PEN &#8220;box&#8221;&#8211;figured out that there was growth [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinking-in-new-boxes-a-new-paradigm-for-business-creativity-luc-de-brabandere-alan-iny-abridged/">Thinking in New Boxes : A New Paradigm for Business Creativity &#8211; Luc De Brabandere, Alan Iny (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When BIC, manufacturer of disposable ballpoint pens, wanted to grow, it looked for an idea beyond introducing new sizes and ink colors. Someone suggested lighters.     </p>
<p>                     LIGHTERS?     </p>
<p>                     With an idea that seemed crazy at first, that bright executive, instead of seeing BIC as a pen company&#8211;a business in the PEN &#8220;box&#8221;&#8211;figured out that there was growth to be found in the DISPOSABLE &#8220;box.&#8221; And he was right. Now there are disposable BIC lighters, razors, even phones. The company opened its door to a host of opportunities.     </p>
<p>                     IT INVENTED A NEW BOX.     </p>
<p>                     Your business can, too. And simply thinking &#8220;out of the box&#8221; is not the answer. True ingenuity needs structure, hard analysis, and bold brainstorming. It needs to start     </p>
<p>                     THINKING IN NEW BOXES    </p>
<p>                     &#8211;a revolutionary process for sustainable creativity from two strategic innovation experts from The Boston Consulting Group (BCG).     </p>
<p>                     To make sense of the world, we all rely on assumptions, on models&#8211;on what Luc de Brabandere and Alan Iny call &#8220;boxes.&#8221; If we are unaware of our boxes, they can blind us to risks and opportunities.     </p>
<p>                     This innovative book challenges everything you thought you knew about business creativity by breaking creativity down into five steps:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Doubt everything. Challenge your current perspectives.<br />
                     &#8211; Probe the possible. Explore options around you.<br />
                     &#8211; Diverge. Generate many new and exciting ideas, even if they seem absurd.<br />
                     &#8211; Converge. Evaluate and select the ideas that will drive breakthrough results.<br />
                     &#8211; Reevaluate. Relentlessly. No idea is a good idea forever. And did we mention Reevaluate? Relentlessly.     </p>
<p>                     Creativity is paramount if you are to thrive in a time of accelerating change. Replete with practical and potent creativity tools, and featuring fascinating case studies from BIC to Ford to Trader Joe&#8217;s, Thinking in New Boxes will help you and your company overcome missed opportunities and stay ahead of the curve.     </p>
<p>                     This book isn&#8217;t a simpleminded checklist. This is Thinking in New Boxes.     </p>
<p>                     And it will be fun. (We promise.)     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Thinking in New Boxes     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Excellent . . . While focusing on business creativity, the principles in this book apply anywhere change is needed and will be of interest to anyone seeking to reinvent herself.&#8221;&#8211;Blogcritics     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Thinking in New Boxes is a five-step guide that leverages the authors&#8217; deep understanding of human nature to enable readers to overcome their limitations and both imagine and create their own futures. This book is a must-read for people living and working in today&#8217;s competitive environment.&#8221;&#8211;Ray O. Johnson, Ph.D., chief technology officer, Lockheed Martin     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Thinking In New Boxes discusses what I believe to be one of the fundamental shifts all companies/brands need to be thinking about: how to think creatively, in order to innovate and differentiate our brands. We need to thrive and lead in a world of accelerating change and this book challenges us to even greater creativity in our thinking. One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in a long time.&#8221;&#8211;Jennifer Fox, CEO, Fairmont Hotels &#038; Resorts     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;As impressive as teaching new tricks to old dogs, Thinking in New Boxes is both inspirational and practical&#8211;a comprehensive, step-by-step guide to sharpening one&#8217;s wits in order to harness creativity in the workplace.&#8221;&#8211;Peter Gelb, general manager, Metropolitan Opera</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinking-in-new-boxes-a-new-paradigm-for-business-creativity-luc-de-brabandere-alan-iny-abridged/">Thinking in New Boxes : A New Paradigm for Business Creativity &#8211; Luc De Brabandere, Alan Iny (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fit for Growth : A Guide to Strategic Cost Cutting, Restructuring, and Renewal &#8211; Vinay Couto, John Plansky, Deniz Caglar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fit-for-growth-a-guide-to-strategic-cost-cutting-restructuring-and-renewal-vinay-couto-john-plansky-deniz-caglar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fit-for-growth-a-guide-to-strategic-cost-cutting-restructuring-and-renewal-vinay-couto-john-plansky-deniz-caglar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical approach to business transformation Fit for Growth* is a unique approach to business transformation that explicitly connects growth strategy with cost management and organization restructuring. Drawing on 70-plus years of strategy consulting experience and in-depth research, the experts at PwC s Strategy&#038; lay out a winning framework that helps CEOs and senior executives [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fit-for-growth-a-guide-to-strategic-cost-cutting-restructuring-and-renewal-vinay-couto-john-plansky-deniz-caglar-abridged/">Fit for Growth : A Guide to Strategic Cost Cutting, Restructuring, and Renewal &#8211; Vinay Couto, John Plansky, Deniz Caglar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical approach to business transformation Fit for Growth* is a unique approach to business transformation that explicitly connects growth strategy with cost management and organization restructuring. Drawing on 70-plus years of strategy consulting experience and in-depth research, the experts at PwC s Strategy&#038; lay out a winning framework that helps CEOs and senior executives transform their organizations for sustainable, profitable growth. This approach gives structure to strategy while promoting lasting change. Examples from Strategy&#038; s hundreds of clients illustrate successful transformation on the ground, and illuminate how senior and middle managers are able to take ownership and even thrive during difficult periods of transition. Throughout the Fit for Growth process, the focus is on maintaining consistent high-value performance while enabling fundamental change. Strategy&#038; has helped major clients around the globe achieve significant and sustained results with its research-backed approach to restructuring and cost reduction.<br />
                    This book provides practical guidance for leveraging that expertise to make the choices that allow companies to: * Achieve growth while reducing costs * Manage transformation and transition productively * Create lasting competitive advantage * Deliver reliable, high-value performance Sustainable success is founded on efficiency and high performance. Companies are always looking to do more with less, but their efforts often work against them in the long run. Total business transformation requires total buy-in, and it entails a series of decisions that must not be made lightly. The Fit for Growth approach provides a clear strategy and practical framework for growth-oriented change, with expert guidance on getting it right.  * Fit for Growth is a registered service mark of PwC Strategy&#038; Inc. in the United States</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fit-for-growth-a-guide-to-strategic-cost-cutting-restructuring-and-renewal-vinay-couto-john-plansky-deniz-caglar-abridged/">Fit for Growth : A Guide to Strategic Cost Cutting, Restructuring, and Renewal &#8211; Vinay Couto, John Plansky, Deniz Caglar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gemba Kaizen: A Commonsense Approach to a Continuous Improvement Strategy, Second Edition &#8211; Masaaki Imai (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/gemba-kaizen-a-commonsense-approach-to-a-continuous-improvement-strategy-second-edition-masaaki-imai-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Quality Control]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quality Assurance (QA) & Total Quality Management (TQM)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/gemba-kaizen-a-commonsense-approach-to-a-continuous-improvement-strategy-second-edition-masaaki-imai-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Publisher&#8217;s Note: Products purchased from Third Party sellers are not guaranteed by the publisher for quality, authenticity, or access to any online entitlements included with the product. The definitive, fully up-to-date guide to continuous improvement in the workplace&#8221;An updated version of a classic book that shares a wealth of new healthcare examples and case studies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gemba-kaizen-a-commonsense-approach-to-a-continuous-improvement-strategy-second-edition-masaaki-imai-abridged/">Gemba Kaizen: A Commonsense Approach to a Continuous Improvement Strategy, Second Edition &#8211; Masaaki Imai (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Publisher&#8217;s Note: Products purchased from Third Party sellers are not guaranteed by the publisher for quality,   authenticity, or access to any online entitlements included with the product.    </p>
<p>                    The definitive, fully up-to-date guide to continuous improvement in the workplace&#8221;An updated version of a classic book that shares a wealth of new healthcare examples and case studies from around the world. The methods in this book will help you improve quality and safety, reduce waiting times, and improve the long-term financial position of your organization. Highly recommended!&#8221; &#8211;Mark Graban, author of Lean Hospitals and coauthor of Healthcare Kaizen    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Every business faces the iron triangle of quality, cost, and delivery. Conventional thinking claims you cannot have all three. Not only does Mr. Imai turn that thinking on its head, but he shows you exactly how to do it.&#8221; &#8212; Matthew E. May, author of The Elegant Solution and The Laws of Subtraction    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Masaaki Imai has done it again. The second edition of his famous book not only describes all the tools necessary for any type of business to implement a lean strategy but also includes a large number of excellent case studies.&#8221; &#8212; Art Byrne, author of The Lean Turnaround    </p>
<p>                    Written by Masaaki Imai, pioneer of modern business operational excellence and founder of the Kaizen Institute, Gemba Kaizen, Second Edition is an in-depth revision of this renowned, bestselling work. The book reveals how to implement cost-effective, incremental improvements in your most critical business processes. Global case studies from a wide range of industries demonstrate how gemba kaizen has been successfully used to:    </p>
<p>                    Maximize capacity and reduce inventory at Unga Limited, one of Kenya&#8217;s largest flour-milling operations<br />
                    Change the IT culture at Achmea, a large European insurance firm<br />
                    Exceed customer expectations at Walt Disney World in the United States<br />
                    Improve quality at Inoue Hospital in Japan<br />
                    Transform retail processes at Sonae MC, Portugal&#8217;s largest employer<br />
                    Practice daily kaizen at Tork Ledervin, a weaving plant in Brazil<br />
                    Stamp out muda at Sunclipse, an industrial packaging distributor in the United States<br />
                    Manage quality improvement by total workforce involvement at Xuji Group Corporation, an electrical manufacturer in China<br />
                    Implement gemba kaizen at many other companies worldwide    </p>
<p>                    To thrive in today&#8217;s competitive global economy, organizations need to operate more effectively and profitably than ever before. Developing problem solvers, increasing productivity, improving quality, and reducing waste are essential success factors. Proven strategies for achieving these goals are included in this pioneering guide.    </p>
<p>                    This comprehensive resource offers detailed coverage of important gemba kaizen topics, including:    </p>
<p>                    Quality, cost, and delivery in the gemba<br />
                    The five steps of workplace organization<br />
                    Identifying and eliminating muda&#8211;any non-value-adding activity<br />
                    Visual management<br />
                    Supervisors&#8217; roles in the lean workplace<br />
                    Gemba managers&#8217; roles and accountability in sustaining high performance<br />
                    Just-in-time and total flow management<br />
                    The CEO&#8217;s role in leading a kaizen culture    </p>
<p>                    The methods presented in Gemba Kaizen, Second Edition reveal that when management focuses on implementing kaizen (incremental, continuous improvement) in the gemba (the worksite) unique opportunities can be discovered for increasing the success and profitability of any organization.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gemba-kaizen-a-commonsense-approach-to-a-continuous-improvement-strategy-second-edition-masaaki-imai-abridged/">Gemba Kaizen: A Commonsense Approach to a Continuous Improvement Strategy, Second Edition &#8211; Masaaki Imai (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ultimate Sales Machine &#8211; Chet Holmes, Notes by Jay Conrad Levinson, Foreword by Michael Gerber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A classic.-Jay Conrad Levinson, author of Guerrilla Marketing Now in paperback, the bestselling business playbook that introduced a simple framework for turbocharging any organization. What if you could create the finest, most profitable and best-run version of your business without wasting precious dollars on a thousand different strategies? Legendary sales expert Chet Holmes says you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/">Ultimate Sales Machine &#8211; Chet Holmes, Notes by Jay Conrad Levinson, Foreword by Michael Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A classic.-Jay Conrad Levinson, author of Guerrilla Marketing     </p>
<p>                    Now in paperback, the bestselling business playbook that introduced a simple framework for turbocharging any organization.     </p>
<p>                     What if you could create the finest, most profitable and best-run version of your business without wasting precious dollars on a thousand different strategies? Legendary sales expert Chet Holmes says you can. All you need is to focus on twelve key areas of improvement&#8211;and practice them over and over with pigheaded discipline.     </p>
<p>                     The Ultimate Sales Machine is essential reading for anyone who wants to transform their organization into a high-performing, moneymaking force. By spending just an hour per week on crucial aspects of your business&#8211;from sales and marketing to management and hiring&#8211;you can systematically improve how your business operates. With practical tools, real-life examples, and proven strategies presented in Holmes&#8217; signature tell-it-like-it-is style, this book will show you how to:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Teach your team to work smarter, not harder<br />
                     &#8211; Get more bang from your marketing for less<br />
                     &#8211; Perfect every sales interaction by working on sales, not just in sales<br />
                     &#8211; Land your dream clients     </p>
<p>                    For every CEO, manager, and business owner who wants to take their organization to the next level, The Ultimate Sales Machine will put you and your company on the path to success&#8211;and help you stay there!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/">Ultimate Sales Machine &#8211; Chet Holmes, Notes by Jay Conrad Levinson, Foreword by Michael Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Numbers Rule Your World: The Hidden Influence of Probabilities and Statistics on Everything You Do &#8211; Kaiser Fung (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/numbers-rule-your-world-the-hidden-influence-of-probabilities-and-statistics-on-everything-you-do-kaiser-fung-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/numbers-rule-your-world-the-hidden-influence-of-probabilities-and-statistics-on-everything-you-do-kaiser-fung-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WHAT ARE THE ODDS YOU&#8217;LL WIN THE LOTTERY? How long will your kids wait in line at Disney World?Who decides that &#8220;standardized tests&#8221; are fair?Why do highway engineers build slow-moving ramps?What does it mean, statistically, to be an &#8220;Average Joe&#8221;?NUMBERS RULE YOUR WORLD In the popular tradition of eye-opening bestsellers like Freakonomics, The Tipping Point, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/numbers-rule-your-world-the-hidden-influence-of-probabilities-and-statistics-on-everything-you-do-kaiser-fung-abridged/">Numbers Rule Your World: The Hidden Influence of Probabilities and Statistics on Everything You Do &#8211; Kaiser Fung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WHAT ARE THE ODDS YOU&#8217;LL WIN THE LOTTERY?<br />
                    How long will your kids wait in line at Disney World?Who decides that &#8220;standardized tests&#8221; are fair?Why do highway engineers build slow-moving ramps?What does it mean, statistically, to be an &#8220;Average Joe&#8221;?NUMBERS RULE YOUR WORLD<br />
                    In the popular tradition of eye-opening bestsellers like Freakonomics, The Tipping Point, and Super Crunchers, this fascinating book from renowned statistician and blogger Kaiser Fung takes you inside the hidden world of facts and figures that affect you every day, in every way. These are the statistics that rule your life, your job, your commute, your vacation, your food, your health, your money, and your success. This is how engineers calculate your quality of living, how corporations determine your needs, and how politicians estimate your opinions. These are the numbers you never think about-even though they play a crucial role in every single aspect of your life.What you learn may surprise you, amuse you, or even enrage you. But there&#8217;s one thing you won&#8217;t be able to deny: Numbers Rule Your World&#8230;&#8221;An easy read with a big benefit.&#8221;<br />
                    -Fareed Zakaria, CNN    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;For those who have anxiety about how organization data-mining is impacting their world,  Kaiser Fung pulls back the curtain to reveal the good and the bad of predictive analytics.&#8221;<br />
                    -Ian Ayres,Yale professor and author of Super Crunchers:  Why Thinking By Numbers is the New Way to Be Smart<br />
                     &#8220;A book that engages us with stories that a journalist would write, the compelling stories behind the stories as illuminated by the numbers, and the dynamics that the numbers reveal.&#8221;<br />
                    -John Sall, Executive Vice President, SAS Institute  &#8220;Little did I suspect, when I picked up Kaiser Fung&#8217;s book, that I would become so entranced by it &#8211; an illuminating and accessible exploration of the power of statistical analysis for those of us who have no prior training in a field that he explores so ably.&#8221;<br />
                    -Peter Clarke, author of  Keynes: The Rise, Fall, and Return of the 20th Century&#8217;s Most Influential Economist    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A tremendous book. . . . If you want to understand how to use statistics, how to think with numbers and yet to do this without getting lost in equations, if you&#8217;ve been looking for the book to unlock the door to logical thinking about problems, well, you will be pleased to know that you are holding that book in your hands.&#8221;<br />
                    -Daniel Finkelstein, Executive Editor, The Times of London&#8221;I thoroughly enjoyed this accessible book and enthusiastically recommendit to anyone looking to understand and appreciate the role of statistics and dataanalysis in solving problems and in creating a better world.&#8221;<br />
                     -Michael Sherman, Texas A&#038;M University, American Statistician</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/numbers-rule-your-world-the-hidden-influence-of-probabilities-and-statistics-on-everything-you-do-kaiser-fung-abridged/">Numbers Rule Your World: The Hidden Influence of Probabilities and Statistics on Everything You Do &#8211; Kaiser Fung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
