<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>History Of Medicine Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/history-of-medicine/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/history-of-medicine/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>History Of Medicine Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/history-of-medicine/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Tale of the Dueling Neurosurgeons : The History of the Human Brain as Revealed by True Stories of Trauma, Madness, and Recovery &#8211; Sam Kean (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-tale-of-the-dueling-neurosurgeons-the-history-of-the-human-brain-as-revealed-by-true-stories-of-trauma-madness-and-recovery-sam-kean-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tale-of-the-dueling-neurosurgeons-the-history-of-the-human-brain-as-revealed-by-true-stories-of-trauma-madness-and-recovery-sam-kean-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The author of the bestseller The Disappearing Spoon reveals the secret inner workings of the brain through strange but true stories. Early studies of the human brain used a simple method: wait for misfortune to strike &#8212; strokes, seizures, infectious diseases, horrendous accidents &#8212; and see how victims coped. In many cases their survival was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tale-of-the-dueling-neurosurgeons-the-history-of-the-human-brain-as-revealed-by-true-stories-of-trauma-madness-and-recovery-sam-kean-abridged/">The Tale of the Dueling Neurosurgeons : The History of the Human Brain as Revealed by True Stories of Trauma, Madness, and Recovery &#8211; Sam Kean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author of the bestseller The Disappearing Spoon reveals the secret inner workings of the brain through strange but true stories.      </p>
<p>                     Early studies of the human brain used a simple method: wait for misfortune to strike &#8212; strokes, seizures, infectious diseases, horrendous accidents &#8212; and see how victims coped. In many cases their survival was miraculous, if puzzling. Observers were amazed by the transformations that took place when different parts of the brain were destroyed, altering victims&#8217; personalities. Parents suddenly couldn&#8217;t recognize their own children. Pillars of the community became pathological liars. Some people couldn&#8217;t speak but could still sing.     </p>
<p>                     In The Tale of the Dueling Neurosurgeons, Sam Kean travels through time with stories of neurological curiosities: phantom limbs, Siamese twin brains, viruses that eat patients&#8217; memories, blind people who see through their tongues. He weaves these narratives together with prose that makes the pages fly by, to create a story of discovery that reaches back to the 1500s and the high-profile jousting accident that inspired this book&#8217;s title.     </p>
<p>                     With the lucid, masterful explanations and razor-sharp wit his fans have come to expect, Kean explores the brain&#8217;s secret passageways and recounts the forgotten tales of the ordinary people whose struggles, resilience, and deep humanity made neuroscience possible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tale-of-the-dueling-neurosurgeons-the-history-of-the-human-brain-as-revealed-by-true-stories-of-trauma-madness-and-recovery-sam-kean-abridged/">The Tale of the Dueling Neurosurgeons : The History of the Human Brain as Revealed by True Stories of Trauma, Madness, and Recovery &#8211; Sam Kean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Age of Anxiety &#8211; Scott Stossel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/my-age-of-anxiety-scott-stossel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-age-of-anxiety-scott-stossel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER and SHORTLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME BOOK PRIZE 2015 As recently as thirty-five years ago, anxiety did not exist as a diagnostic category. Today, it is the most common form of officially classified mental illness. Scott Stossel gracefully guides us across the terrain of an affliction that is pervasive yet too [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-age-of-anxiety-scott-stossel-abridged/">My Age of Anxiety &#8211; Scott Stossel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER and SHORTLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME BOOK PRIZE 2015     </p>
<p>                    As recently as thirty-five years ago, anxiety did not exist as a diagnostic category. Today, it is the most common form of officially classified mental illness. Scott Stossel gracefully guides us across the terrain of an affliction that is pervasive yet too often misunderstood.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his own long-standing battle with anxiety, Stossel presents an astonishing history, at once intimate and authoritative, of the efforts to understand the condition from medical, cultural, philosophical and experiential perspectives. He ranges from the earliest medical reports of Galen and Hippocrates, through later observations by Robert Burton and Soren Kierkegaard, to the investigations by great nineteenth-century scientists, such as Charles Darwin, William James and Sigmund Freud, as they began to explore its sources and causes, to the latest research by neuroscientists and geneticists. Stossel reports on famous individuals who struggled with anxiety, as well as the afflicted generations of his own family. His portrait of anxiety reveals not only the emotion&#8217;s myriad manifestations and the anguish it produces, but also the countless psychotherapies, medications and other (often outlandish) treatments that have been developed to counteract it. Stossel vividly depicts anxiety&#8217;s human toll &#8211; its crippling impact, its devastating power to paralyse &#8211; while at the same time exploring how those who suffer from it find ways to manage and control it.    </p>
<p>                    My Age of Anxiety is learned and empathetic, humorous and inspirational, offering the reader great insight into the biological, cultural and environmental factors that contribute to the affliction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-age-of-anxiety-scott-stossel-abridged/">My Age of Anxiety &#8211; Scott Stossel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Madness in Civilization : A Cultural History of Insanity from the Bible to Freud, from the Madhouse to Modern Medicine &#8211; Andrew Scull (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/madness-in-civilization-a-cultural-history-of-insanity-from-the-bible-to-freud-from-the-madhouse-to-modern-medicine-andrew-scull-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/madness-in-civilization-a-cultural-history-of-insanity-from-the-bible-to-freud-from-the-madhouse-to-modern-medicine-andrew-scull-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This ambitious volume, worldwide in scope and ranging from antiquity to the present, examines the human encounter with Unreason in all its manifestations, the challenges it poses to society and our responses to it. In twelve chapters organized chronologically from the Bible to Freud, from exorcism to mesmerism, from Bedlam to Victorian asylums, from the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/madness-in-civilization-a-cultural-history-of-insanity-from-the-bible-to-freud-from-the-madhouse-to-modern-medicine-andrew-scull-abridged/">Madness in Civilization : A Cultural History of Insanity from the Bible to Freud, from the Madhouse to Modern Medicine &#8211; Andrew Scull (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This ambitious volume, worldwide in scope and ranging from antiquity to the present, examines the human encounter with Unreason in all its manifestations, the challenges it poses to society and our responses to it. In twelve chapters organized chronologically from the Bible to Freud, from exorcism to mesmerism, from Bedlam to Victorian asylums, from the theory of humours to modern pharmacology, Andrew Scull writes compellingly about madness, its meanings, its consequences and our attempts to understand and treat it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/madness-in-civilization-a-cultural-history-of-insanity-from-the-bible-to-freud-from-the-madhouse-to-modern-medicine-andrew-scull-abridged/">Madness in Civilization : A Cultural History of Insanity from the Bible to Freud, from the Madhouse to Modern Medicine &#8211; Andrew Scull (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get Well Soon : History&#8217;s Worst Plagues and the Heroes Who Fought Them &#8211; Jennifer Wright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/get-well-soon-historys-worst-plagues-and-the-heroes-who-fought-them-jennifer-wright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/get-well-soon-historys-worst-plagues-and-the-heroes-who-fought-them-jennifer-wright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 1518, in a small town in France, Frau Troffea began dancing and didn&#8217;t stop. She danced herself to her death six days later, and soon thirty-four more villagers joined her. Then more. In a month more than 400 people had died from the mysterious dancing plague. In late-nineteenth-century England an eccentric gentleman founded the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-well-soon-historys-worst-plagues-and-the-heroes-who-fought-them-jennifer-wright-abridged/">Get Well Soon : History&#8217;s Worst Plagues and the Heroes Who Fought Them &#8211; Jennifer Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 1518, in a small town in France, Frau Troffea began dancing and didn&#8217;t stop. She danced herself to her death six days later, and soon thirty-four more villagers joined her. Then more. In a month more than 400 people had died from the mysterious dancing plague. In late-nineteenth-century England an eccentric gentleman founded the No Nose Club in his gracious townhome&#8211;a social club for those who had lost their noses, and other body parts, to the plague of syphilis for which there was then no cure. And in turn-of-the-century New York, an Irish cook caused two lethal outbreaks of typhoid fever, a case that transformed her into the notorious Typhoid Mary and led to historic medical breakthroughs. Throughout time, humans have been terrified and fascinated by the plagues they&#8217;ve suffered from. Get Well Soon delivers the gruesome, morbid details of some of the worst plagues in human history, as well as stories of the heroic figures who fought to ease their suffering. With her signature mix of in-depth research and upbeat storytelling, and not a little dark humour, Jennifer Wright explores history&#8217;s most gripping and deadly outbreaks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-well-soon-historys-worst-plagues-and-the-heroes-who-fought-them-jennifer-wright-abridged/">Get Well Soon : History&#8217;s Worst Plagues and the Heroes Who Fought Them &#8211; Jennifer Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epidemiology & Medical Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than three hundred infectious diseases have emerged or reemerged in new territory during the past fifty years, and ninety percent of epidemiologists expect that one of them will cause a disruptive, deadly pandemic sometime in the next two generations. To reveal how that might happen, Sonia Shah tracks each stage of cholera&#8217;s dramatic journey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/">Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than three hundred infectious diseases have emerged or reemerged in new territory during the past fifty years, and ninety percent of epidemiologists expect that one of them will cause a disruptive, deadly pandemic sometime in the next two generations. To reveal how that might happen, Sonia Shah tracks each stage of cholera&#8217;s dramatic journey from harmless microbe to world-changing pandemic, from its 1817 emergence in the South Asian hinterlands to its rapid dispersal across the nineteenth-century world and its latest beachhead in Haiti. She reports on the pathogens following in cholera&#8217;s footsteps, from the MRSA bacterium that besieges her own family to the never-before-seen killers emerging from China&#8217;s wet markets, the surgical wards of New Delhi, the slums of Port-au-Prince, and the suburban backyards of the East Coast. A deep-dive into the convoluted science, strange politics, and checkered history of one of the world&#8217;s deadliest diseases, Pandemic reveals what the next epidemic might look like&#8211;and what we can do to prevent it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/">Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Body : A Guide for Occupants &#8211; THE SUNDAY TIMES NO.1 BESTSELLER &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-body-a-guide-for-occupants-the-sunday-times-no-1-bestseller-bill-bryson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-body-a-guide-for-occupants-the-sunday-times-no-1-bestseller-bill-bryson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; SUNDAY TIMES SCIENCE BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019 _______ &#8216;A directory of wonders.&#8217; &#8211; The Guardian &#8216;Jaw-dropping.&#8217; &#8211; The Times &#8216;Classic, wry, gleeful Bryson&#8230;an entertaining and absolutely fact-rammed book.&#8217; &#8211; The Sunday Times &#8216;It is a feat of narrative skill to bake so many facts into an entertaining [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-body-a-guide-for-occupants-the-sunday-times-no-1-bestseller-bill-bryson-abridged/">The Body : A Guide for Occupants &#8211; THE SUNDAY TIMES NO.1 BESTSELLER &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; SUNDAY TIMES SCIENCE BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A directory of wonders.&#8217; &#8211; The Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Jaw-dropping.&#8217; &#8211; The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Classic, wry, gleeful Bryson&#8230;an entertaining and absolutely fact-rammed book.&#8217; &#8211; The Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is a feat of narrative skill to bake so many facts into an entertaining and nutritious book.&#8217; &#8211; The Daily Telegraph<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We spend our whole lives in one body and yet most of us have practically no idea how it works and what goes on inside it. The idea of the book is simply to try to understand the extraordinary contraption that is us.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Bill Bryson sets off to explore the human body, how it functions and its remarkable ability to heal itself. Full of extraordinary facts and astonishing stories The Body: A Guide for Occupants is a brilliant, often very funny attempt to understand the miracle of our physical and neurological make up.     </p>
<p>                    A wonderful successor to A Short History of Nearly Everything, this new book is an instant classic. It will  have you marvelling at the form you occupy, and celebrating the genius of your existence, time and time again.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;What I learned is that we are infinitely more complex and wondrous, and often more mysterious, than I had ever suspected. There really is no story more amazing than the story of us.&#8217; Bill Bryson</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-body-a-guide-for-occupants-the-sunday-times-no-1-bestseller-bill-bryson-abridged/">The Body : A Guide for Occupants &#8211; THE SUNDAY TIMES NO.1 BESTSELLER &#8211; Bill Bryson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mosquito : A Human History of Our Deadliest Predator &#8211; Timothy C. Winegard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-mosquito-a-human-history-of-our-deadliest-predator-timothy-c-winegard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Butterflies, Other Insects & Spiders]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mosquito-a-human-history-of-our-deadliest-predator-timothy-c-winegard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**The instant New York Times bestseller** *An international bestseller* &#8220;Hugely impressive, a major work.&#8221;&#8211;NPR A pioneering and groundbreaking work of narrative nonfiction that offers a dramatic new perspective on the history of humankind, showing how through millennia, the mosquito has been the single most powerful force in determining humanity&#8217;s fate. Why was gin and tonic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mosquito-a-human-history-of-our-deadliest-predator-timothy-c-winegard-abridged/">The Mosquito : A Human History of Our Deadliest Predator &#8211; Timothy C. Winegard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**The instant New York Times bestseller**<br />
                    *An international bestseller*     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Hugely impressive, a major work.&#8221;&#8211;NPR    </p>
<p>                    A pioneering and groundbreaking work of narrative nonfiction that offers a dramatic new perspective on the history of humankind, showing how through millennia, the mosquito has been the single most powerful force in determining humanity&#8217;s fate.     </p>
<p>                     Why was gin and tonic the cocktail of choice for British colonists in India and Africa? What does Starbucks have to thank for its global domination? What has protected the lives of popes for millennia? Why did Scotland surrender its sovereignty to England? What was George Washington&#8217;s secret weapon during the American Revolution?     </p>
<p>                     The answer to all these questions, and many more, is the mosquito.     </p>
<p>                     Across our planet since the dawn of humankind, this nefarious pest, roughly the size and weight of a grape seed, has been at the frontlines of history as the grim reaper, the harvester of human populations, and the ultimate agent of historical change. As the mosquito transformed the landscapes of civilization, humans were unwittingly required to respond to its piercing impact and universal projection of power.     </p>
<p>                     The mosquito has determined the fates of empires and nations, razed and crippled economies, and decided the outcome of pivotal wars, killing nearly half of humanity along the way. She (only females bite) has dispatched an estimated 52 billion people from a total of 108 billion throughout our relatively brief existence. As the greatest purveyor of extermination we have ever known, she has played a greater role in shaping our human story than any other living thing with which we share our global village.     </p>
<p>                     Imagine for a moment a world without deadly mosquitoes, or any mosquitoes, for that matter? Our history and the world we know, or think we know, would be completely unrecognizable.     </p>
<p>                     Driven by surprising insights and fast-paced storytelling, The Mosquito is the extraordinary untold story of the mosquito&#8217;s reign through human history and her indelible impact on our modern world order.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mosquito-a-human-history-of-our-deadliest-predator-timothy-c-winegard-abridged/">The Mosquito : A Human History of Our Deadliest Predator &#8211; Timothy C. Winegard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks &#8211; Rebecca Skloot (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bio-ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Ethics & Professional Conduct]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Her name was Henrietta Lacks, but scientists know her as HeLa. Born a poor black tobacco farmer, her cancer cells &#8211; taken without her knowledge &#8211; became a multimillion-dollar industry and one of the most important tools in medicine. Yet Henrietta&#8217;s family did not learn of her &#8216;immortality&#8217; until more than twenty years after her [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/">The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks &#8211; Rebecca Skloot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Her name was Henrietta Lacks, but scientists know her as HeLa. Born a poor black tobacco farmer, her cancer cells &#8211; taken without her knowledge &#8211; became a multimillion-dollar industry and one of the most important tools in medicine. Yet Henrietta&#8217;s family did not learn of her &#8216;immortality&#8217; until more than twenty years after her death, with devastating consequences . . .     </p>
<p>                    Rebecca Skloot&#8217;s fascinating account is the story of the life, and afterlife, of one woman who changed the medical world forever. Balancing the beauty and drama of scientific discovery with dark questions about who owns the stuff our bodies are made of, The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks is an extraordinary journey in search of the soul and story of a real woman, whose cells live on today in all four corners of the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/">The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks &#8211; Rebecca Skloot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shrinks : The Untold Story of Psychiatry &#8211; Dr Jeffrey A Lieberman, With Ogi Ogas (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/shrinks-the-untold-story-of-psychiatry-dr-jeffrey-a-lieberman-with-ogi-ogas-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/shrinks-the-untold-story-of-psychiatry-dr-jeffrey-a-lieberman-with-ogi-ogas-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The inspiration for the PBS series Mysterious of Mental Illness, Shrinks brilliantly tells the &#8220;astonishing&#8221; story of psychiatry&#8217;s origins, demise, and redemption (Siddhartha Mukherjee). Psychiatry has come a long way since the days of chaining &#8220;lunatics&#8221; in cold cells and parading them as freakish marvels before a gaping public. But, as Jeffrey Lieberman, MD, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shrinks-the-untold-story-of-psychiatry-dr-jeffrey-a-lieberman-with-ogi-ogas-abridged/">Shrinks : The Untold Story of Psychiatry &#8211; Dr Jeffrey A Lieberman, With Ogi Ogas (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The inspiration for the PBS series Mysterious of Mental Illness, Shrinks brilliantly tells the &#8220;astonishing&#8221; story of psychiatry&#8217;s origins, demise, and redemption (Siddhartha Mukherjee).      </p>
<p>                    Psychiatry has come a long way since the days of chaining &#8220;lunatics&#8221; in cold cells and parading them as freakish marvels before a gaping public.     </p>
<p>                    But, as Jeffrey Lieberman, MD, the former president of the American Psychiatric Association, reveals in his extraordinary and eye-opening book, the path to legitimacy for &#8220;the black sheep of medicine&#8221; has been anything but smooth.     </p>
<p>                    In Shrinks, Dr. Lieberman traces the field from its birth as a mystic pseudo-science through its adolescence as a cult of &#8220;shrinks&#8221; to its late blooming maturity &#8212; beginning after World War II &#8212; as a science-driven profession that saves lives. With fascinating case studies and portraits of the luminaries of the field &#8212; from Sigmund Freud to Eric Kandel &#8212; Shrinks is a gripping and illuminating read, and an urgent call-to-arms to dispel the stigma of mental illnesses by treating them as diseases rather than unfortunate states of mind.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A lucid popular history&#8230;At once skeptical and triumphalist. It shows just how far psychiatry has come.&#8221; &#8211;Julia M. Klein, Boston Globe</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shrinks-the-untold-story-of-psychiatry-dr-jeffrey-a-lieberman-with-ogi-ogas-abridged/">Shrinks : The Untold Story of Psychiatry &#8211; Dr Jeffrey A Lieberman, With Ogi Ogas (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heart: A History : Shortlisted for the Wellcome Book Prize 2019 &#8211; Sandeep Jauhar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diaries, Letters & Journals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geographical Discovery & Exploration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transplant Surgery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories: Discovery / Historical / Scientific]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jauhar weaves his own personal and family story into his history of the heart&#8230;very effectively&#8230; This gives a certain dramatic tension to the book, as it tells the fascinating and rather wonderful history of cardiology.&#8217; -Henry Marsh, New Statesman A Mail on Sunday Book of the Year The heart lies at the centre of life. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/">Heart: A History : Shortlisted for the Wellcome Book Prize 2019 &#8211; Sandeep Jauhar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jauhar weaves his own personal and family story into his history of the heart&#8230;very effectively&#8230; This gives a certain dramatic tension to the book, as it tells the fascinating and rather wonderful history of cardiology.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    -Henry Marsh, New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    A Mail on Sunday Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    The heart lies at the centre of life. For cardiologist Sandeep Jauhar it is an obsession.    </p>
<p>                    In this fascinating history he interweaves gripping scenes from the operating theatre with the moving tale of his family&#8217;s history of heart problems &#8211; from the death of his grandfather to the ominous signs of how he himself might die.    </p>
<p>                    Jauhar looks at the pioneers who risked patients&#8217; lives and their own careers, and confronts the limits of medical technology, arguing that how we live is more important than any device or drug we may invent. Heart is the all-encompassing story of the engine of life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heart-a-history-shortlisted-for-the-wellcome-book-prize-2019-sandeep-jauhar-abridged/">Heart: A History : Shortlisted for the Wellcome Book Prize 2019 &#8211; Sandeep Jauhar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Hour of Eugenics&#8221; : Race, Gender, and Nation in Latin America &#8211; Nancy Leys Stepan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-hour-of-eugenics-race-gender-and-nation-in-latin-america-nancy-leys-stepan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-hour-of-eugenics-race-gender-and-nation-in-latin-america-nancy-leys-stepan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Eugenics was a term coined in 1883 to name the scientific and social theory which advocated &#8220;race improvement&#8221; through selective human breeding. In Europe and the United States the eugenics movement found many supporters before it was finally discredited by its association with the racist ideology of Nazi Germany. Examining for the first time how [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hour-of-eugenics-race-gender-and-nation-in-latin-america-nancy-leys-stepan-abridged/">The Hour of Eugenics&#8221; : Race, Gender, and Nation in Latin America &#8211; Nancy Leys Stepan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Eugenics was a term coined in 1883 to name the scientific and social theory which advocated &#8220;race improvement&#8221; through selective human breeding. In Europe and the United States the eugenics movement found many supporters before it was finally discredited by its association with the racist ideology of Nazi Germany. Examining for the first time how eugenics was taken up by scientists and social reformers in Latin America, Nancy Leys Stepan compares the eugenics movements in Mexico, Brazil, and Argentina with the more familiar cases of Britain, the United States, and Germany.In this highly original account, Stepan sheds new light on the role of science in reformulating issues of race, gender, reproduction, and public health in an era when the focus on national identity was particularly intense. Drawing upon a rich body of evidence concerning the technical publications and professional meetings of Latin American eugenicists, she examines how they adapted eugenic principles to local contexts between the world wars. Stepan shows that Latin American eugenicists diverged considerably from their counterparts in Europe and the United States in their ideological approach and their interpretations of key texts concerning heredity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hour-of-eugenics-race-gender-and-nation-in-latin-america-nancy-leys-stepan-abridged/">The Hour of Eugenics&#8221; : Race, Gender, and Nation in Latin America &#8211; Nancy Leys Stepan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In a Different Key : The Story of Autism &#8211; John Donvan, Caren Zucker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-a-different-key-the-story-of-autism-john-donvan-caren-zucker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-a-different-key-the-story-of-autism-john-donvan-caren-zucker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A magnificent opus &#8230; extraordinary, spellbinding &#8230; this book does what no other on autism has done&#8217; Ann Bauer, Washington Post *Pulitzer finalist 2017* The stunning history of autism as it has been discovered and felt by parents, children and doctors Nearly seventy-five years ago, Donald Triplett of Forest, Mississippi became the first child diagnosed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-a-different-key-the-story-of-autism-john-donvan-caren-zucker-abridged/">In a Different Key : The Story of Autism &#8211; John Donvan, Caren Zucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A magnificent opus &#8230; extraordinary, spellbinding &#8230; this book does what no other on autism has done&#8217; Ann Bauer, Washington Post    </p>
<p>                    *Pulitzer finalist 2017*    </p>
<p>                    The stunning history of autism as it has been discovered and felt by parents, children and doctors    </p>
<p>                    Nearly seventy-five years ago, Donald Triplett of Forest, Mississippi became the first child diagnosed with autism. In a Different Key tells the extraordinary story of the world his diagnosis created &#8211; a riveting human drama that takes us across continents and through some of the great social movements of the twentieth century.    </p>
<p>                    The history of autism is, above all, the story of families fighting for a place in the world for their children. It is the story of women like Ruth Sullivan, who rebelled against a medical establishment that blamed &#8220;refrigerator mothers&#8221; for causing autism, of fathers who pushed scientists to dig harder for treatments, of parents who forced schools to accept their children. But many others played starring roles too: doctors like Leo Kanner, who pioneered our understanding of autism, scientists who sparred over how to treat autism, and those with autism, like Temple Grandin and Ari Ne&#8217;eman, who explained their inner worlds and championed a philosophy of &#8216;neurodiversity&#8217;.     </p>
<p>                    This is also a story of fierce controversy: from the question of whether there is truly an autism &#8216;epidemic&#8217;, and whether vaccines played a part in it, to scandals involving &#8216;facilitated communication&#8217;, one of many treatments that have proved to be blind alleys. And there are dark turns too: we learn about experimenters feeding LSD to children with autism, or shocking them with electricity to change their behaviour; and the authors reveal, for the first time, that Hans Asperger, discoverer of the syndrome named after him, may have cooperated with the Nazis in sending disabled children to their deaths.    </p>
<p>                    By turns intimate and panoramic, In a Different Key takes us on a journey from an era when families were shamed and children were condemned to institutions, to one in which parents and people with autism push not simply for inclusion, but for a new understanding of autism: as difference rather than disability.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-a-different-key-the-story-of-autism-john-donvan-caren-zucker-abridged/">In a Different Key : The Story of Autism &#8211; John Donvan, Caren Zucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Immunity &#8211; William E. Paul (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A leading figure in immunology takes readers inside the remarkably powerful human immune system. Winner of the CHOICE Outstanding Academic Title of the Choice ACRL The immune system has incredible power to protect us from the ravages of infection. Boosted by vaccines, it can protect us from diseases such as measles. However, the power of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/">Immunity &#8211; William E. Paul (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A leading figure in immunology takes readers inside the remarkably powerful human immune system.    </p>
<p>                    Winner of the CHOICE Outstanding Academic Title of the Choice ACRL    </p>
<p>                    The immune system has incredible power to protect us from the ravages of infection. Boosted by vaccines, it can protect us from diseases such as measles. However, the power of the immune system is a double-edged sword: an overactive immune system can wreak havoc, destroying normal tissue and causing diseases such as type I diabetes, rheumatoid arthritis, and multiple sclerosis. The consequences of an impaired immune system, on the other hand, are all too evident in the agonies of AIDS.    </p>
<p>                    Packed with illustrations, stories from Dr. William E. Paul&#8217;s distinguished career, and fascinating accounts of scientific discovery, Immunity presents the three laws of the human immune system-universality, tolerance, and appropriateness-and explains how the system both protects and harms us. From the tale of how smallpox was overcome and the lessons of the Ebola epidemic to the hope that the immune system can be used to treat or prevent cancer, Dr. Paul argues that we must take advantage of cutting-edge technologies and promising new tools in immunological research.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/">Immunity &#8211; William E. Paul (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
