<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Memory Improvement &amp; Thinking Techniques Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/memory-improvement-thinking-techniques/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/memory-improvement-thinking-techniques/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Memory Improvement &amp; Thinking Techniques Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/memory-improvement-thinking-techniques/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Limitless : Upgrade Your Brain, Learn Anything Faster, and Unlock Your Exceptional Life &#8211; Jim Kwik</title>
		<link>/limitless-upgrade-your-brain-learn-anything-faster-and-unlock-your-exceptional-life-jim-kwik/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/limitless-upgrade-your-brain-learn-anything-faster-and-unlock-your-exceptional-life-jim-kwik/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For the last 25 years, Jim Kwik has helped everyone from celebrities to CEOs to students improve their memory, increase their decision-making skills, learn to speed-read and unleash their superbrains. In Limitless, readers will learn Jim&#8217;s revolutionary strategies and shortcuts to break free from their perceived limitations. They&#8217;ll learn how to supercharge their brains with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/limitless-upgrade-your-brain-learn-anything-faster-and-unlock-your-exceptional-life-jim-kwik/">Limitless : Upgrade Your Brain, Learn Anything Faster, and Unlock Your Exceptional Life &#8211; Jim Kwik</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For the last 25 years, Jim Kwik has helped everyone from celebrities to CEOs to students improve their memory, increase their decision-making skills, learn to speed-read and unleash their superbrains.    </p>
<p>                    In Limitless, readers will learn Jim&#8217;s revolutionary strategies and shortcuts to break free from their perceived limitations. They&#8217;ll learn how to supercharge their brains with simple, actionable tools to sharpen the mind, enhance focus and fast-track their fullest potential.    </p>
<p>                    The book is organized into four sections: Mindset, Motivation, Meta-Learning and Mission. Readers will discover the myths they&#8217;ve been told about their IQ, abilities and skillset; understand why learning matters; learn core habits and steps to becoming limitless; and explore how they can serve the world. They&#8217;ll also learn how to conquer the four supervillains: Distraction, Digital Dementia, Digital Deluge and Depression.    </p>
<p>                    Believing that you are limited is holding you back from achieving your biggest dreams. But we all have superpowers inside of us, and the key to activating those superpowers is unlimiting yourself.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/limitless-upgrade-your-brain-learn-anything-faster-and-unlock-your-exceptional-life-jim-kwik/">Limitless : Upgrade Your Brain, Learn Anything Faster, and Unlock Your Exceptional Life &#8211; Jim Kwik</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do the Work : Overcome Resistance and Get Out of Your Own Way &#8211; Steven Pressfield, Foreword by Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-the-work-overcome-resistance-and-get-out-of-your-own-way-steven-pressfield-foreword-by-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing Skills]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-the-work-overcome-resistance-and-get-out-of-your-own-way-steven-pressfield-foreword-by-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;There is an enemy. There is an intelligent, active, malign force working against us. Step one is to recognize this. This recognition alone is enormously powerful. It saved my life, and it will save yours.&#8221; &#8212; Steven Pressfield Could you be getting in your way of producing great work? Have you started a project but [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-the-work-overcome-resistance-and-get-out-of-your-own-way-steven-pressfield-foreword-by-seth-godin-abridged/">Do the Work : Overcome Resistance and Get Out of Your Own Way &#8211; Steven Pressfield, Foreword by Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;There is an enemy. There is an intelligent, active, malign force working against us. Step one is to recognize this. This recognition alone is enormously powerful. It saved my life, and it will save yours.&#8221; &#8212; Steven Pressfield Could you be getting in your way of producing great work? Have you started a project but never finished? Would you like to do work that matters, but don&#8217;t know where to start?The answer is Do the Work, a manifesto by bestselling author Steven Pressfield, that will show you that it&#8217;s not about better ideas, it&#8217;s about actually doing the work. Do the Work is a weapon against Resistance &#8211; a tool that will help you take action and successfully ship projects out the door. Picking up where The War of Art and Turning Pro left off, Do The Work takes the reader from the start to the finish of any long-form project-novel, screenplay, album, software piece, you name it. Do The Work identifies the predictable Resistance Points along the way and walks you through each of them. No, you are not crazy. No, you are not alone. No, you are not the first person to &#8220;hit the wall&#8221; in Act Two. Do The Work charts the territory. It&#8217;s the stage-by-stage road map for taking your project from Page One to THE END.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-the-work-overcome-resistance-and-get-out-of-your-own-way-steven-pressfield-foreword-by-seth-godin-abridged/">Do the Work : Overcome Resistance and Get Out of Your Own Way &#8211; Steven Pressfield, Foreword by Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The War of Art : Break Through the Blocks and Win Your Inner Creative Battles &#8211; Steven Pressfield (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-war-of-art-break-through-the-blocks-and-win-your-inner-creative-battles-steven-pressfield-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-war-of-art-break-through-the-blocks-and-win-your-inner-creative-battles-steven-pressfield-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A succinct, engaging, and practical guide for succeeding in any creative sphere, The War of Art is nothing less than Sun-Tzu for the soul. What keeps so many of us from doing what we long to do? Why is there a naysayer within? How can we avoid the roadblocks of any creative endeavor-be it starting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-of-art-break-through-the-blocks-and-win-your-inner-creative-battles-steven-pressfield-abridged/">The War of Art : Break Through the Blocks and Win Your Inner Creative Battles &#8211; Steven Pressfield (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A succinct, engaging, and practical guide for succeeding in any creative sphere, The War of Art is nothing less than Sun-Tzu for the soul.    </p>
<p>                     What keeps so many of us from doing what we long to do?    </p>
<p>                    Why is there a naysayer within? How can we avoid the roadblocks of any creative endeavor-be it starting up a dream business venture, writing a novel, or painting a masterpiece?    </p>
<p>                    Bestselling novelist Steven Pressfield identifies the enemy that every one of us must face, outlines a battle plan to conquer this internal foe, then pinpoints just how to achieve the greatest success.    </p>
<p>                    The War of Art emphasizes the resolve needed to recognize and overcome the obstacles of ambition and then effectively shows how to reach the highest level of creative discipline.    </p>
<p>                    Think of it as tough love . . . for yourself.    </p>
<p>                    Whether an artist, writer or business person, this simple, personal, and no-nonsense book will inspire you to seize the potential of your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-of-art-break-through-the-blocks-and-win-your-inner-creative-battles-steven-pressfield-abridged/">The War of Art : Break Through the Blocks and Win Your Inner Creative Battles &#8211; Steven Pressfield (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Designing Your Life : For Fans of Atomic Habits &#8211; Bill Burnett, Dave Evans (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/designing-your-life-for-fans-of-atomic-habits-bill-burnett-dave-evans-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/designing-your-life-for-fans-of-atomic-habits-bill-burnett-dave-evans-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Change your life in 2021 with the simple, scientifically proven method that has already worked for thousands of people. &#8216;Life has questions. They have answers&#8217; New York Times At last, a book that shows you how to build &#8211; design &#8211; a life you can thrive in, at any age or stage. A well-designed life [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/designing-your-life-for-fans-of-atomic-habits-bill-burnett-dave-evans-abridged/">Designing Your Life : For Fans of Atomic Habits &#8211; Bill Burnett, Dave Evans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Change your life in 2021 with the simple, scientifically proven method that has already worked for thousands of people.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Life has questions. They have answers&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                     At last, a book that shows you how to build &#8211; design &#8211; a life you can thrive in, at any age or stage. A well-designed life means a life well-lived. Many of us are still looking for an answer to that perennial question, &#8216;What do I want to be when I grow up?&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     Stanford innovators Bill Burnett and Dave Evans show us how design thinking can help us create a life that is both meaningful and fulfilling, regardless of who and where we are, our careers and our age. Designing Your Life puts forward the idea that the same design thinking responsible for amazing technology, products and spaces can be used to build towards a better life and career by a design of your own making.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;[Designing Your Life] teaches you how to change what&#8217;s not working by turning ideas on their head&#8217; Viv Groskop, author of How To Own The Room    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;An empowering book based on their popular class of the same name at Stanford University&#8230;this book will easily earn a place among career-finding classics&#8217; Publishers Weekly</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/designing-your-life-for-fans-of-atomic-habits-bill-burnett-dave-evans-abridged/">Designing Your Life : For Fans of Atomic Habits &#8211; Bill Burnett, Dave Evans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ultralearning : Accelerate Your Career, Master Hard Skills and Outsmart the Competition &#8211; Scott H. Young (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ultralearning-accelerate-your-career-master-hard-skills-and-outsmart-the-competition-scott-h-young-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Secretarial, Clerical & Office Skills]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ultralearning-accelerate-your-career-master-hard-skills-and-outsmart-the-competition-scott-h-young-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Future-proof your career and maximize your competitive advantage by learning the skill necessary to stay relevant, reinvent yourself, and adapt to whatever the workplace throws your way in this essential guide. Faced with tumultuous economic times and rapid technological change, staying ahead in your career depends on continual learning-a lifelong mastery of new ideas, subjects, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultralearning-accelerate-your-career-master-hard-skills-and-outsmart-the-competition-scott-h-young-abridged/">Ultralearning : Accelerate Your Career, Master Hard Skills and Outsmart the Competition &#8211; Scott H. Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Future-proof your career and maximize your competitive advantage by learning the skill necessary to stay relevant, reinvent yourself, and adapt to whatever the workplace throws your way in this essential guide.    </p>
<p>                              Faced with tumultuous economic times and rapid technological change, staying ahead in your career depends on continual learning-a lifelong mastery of new ideas, subjects, and skills. If you want to accomplish more and stand apart from everyone else, you need to become an ultralearner.    </p>
<p>                              Scott Young incorporates the latest research about the most effective learning methods and the stories of other ultralearners like himself-among them Ben Franklin, Judit Polgar, and Richard Feynman, as well as a host of others, such as little-known modern polymaths like Nigel Richards who won the World Championship of French Scrabble-without knowing French.    </p>
<p>                              Young documents the methods he and others have used and shows that, far from being an obscure skill limited to aggressive autodidacts, ultralearning is a powerful tool anyone can use to improve their career, studies, and life. Ultralearning explores this fascinating subculture, shares the nine principles behind every successful ultralearning project, and offers insights into how you can organize and execute a plan to learn anything deeply and quickly, without teachers or budget-busting tuition costs.    </p>
<p>                              Whether the goal is to be fluent in a language (or ten languages), earn the equivalent of a college degree in a fraction of the time, or master multiple skills to build a product or business from the ground up, the principles in Ultralearning will guide you to success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultralearning-accelerate-your-career-master-hard-skills-and-outsmart-the-competition-scott-h-young-abridged/">Ultralearning : Accelerate Your Career, Master Hard Skills and Outsmart the Competition &#8211; Scott H. Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wired to Create : Unraveling the Mysteries of the Creative Mind &#8211; Scott Barry Kaufman, Carolyn Gregoire (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wired-to-create-unraveling-the-mysteries-of-the-creative-mind-scott-barry-kaufman-carolyn-gregoire-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wired-to-create-unraveling-the-mysteries-of-the-creative-mind-scott-barry-kaufman-carolyn-gregoire-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is it possible to make sense of something as elusive as creativity? Based on psychologist Scott Barry Kaufman&#8217;s groundbreaking research and Carolyn Gregoire&#8217;s popular article in the Huffington Post, Wired to Create offers a glimpse inside the &#8220;messy minds&#8221; of highly creative people. Revealing the latest findings in neuroscience and psychology, along with engaging examples [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wired-to-create-unraveling-the-mysteries-of-the-creative-mind-scott-barry-kaufman-carolyn-gregoire-abridged/">Wired to Create : Unraveling the Mysteries of the Creative Mind &#8211; Scott Barry Kaufman, Carolyn Gregoire (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is it possible to make sense of something as elusive as creativity?     </p>
<p>                     Based on psychologist Scott Barry Kaufman&#8217;s groundbreaking research and Carolyn Gregoire&#8217;s popular article in the Huffington Post, Wired to Create offers a glimpse inside the &#8220;messy minds&#8221; of highly creative people. Revealing the latest findings in neuroscience and psychology, along with engaging examples of artists and innovators throughout history, the book shines a light on the practices and habits of mind that promote creative thinking. Kaufman and Gregoire untangle a series of paradoxes&#8211; like mindfulness and daydreaming, seriousness and play, openness and sensitivity, and solitude and collaboration &#8211; to show that it is by embracing our own contradictions that we are able to tap into our deepest creativity. Each chapter explores one of the ten attributes and habits of highly creative people:     </p>
<p>                     Imaginative Play * Passion * Daydreaming * Solitude * Intuition * Openness to Experience * Mindfulness * Sensitivity * Turning Adversity into Advantage * Thinking Differently     </p>
<p>                     With insights from the work and lives of Pablo Picasso, Frida Kahlo, Marcel Proust, David Foster Wallace, Thomas Edison, Josephine Baker, John Lennon, Michael Jackson, musician Thom Yorke, chess champion Josh Waitzkin, video-game designer Shigeru Miyamoto, and many other creative luminaries, Wired to Create helps us better understand creativity &#8211; and shows us how to enrich this essential aspect of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wired-to-create-unraveling-the-mysteries-of-the-creative-mind-scott-barry-kaufman-carolyn-gregoire-abridged/">Wired to Create : Unraveling the Mysteries of the Creative Mind &#8211; Scott Barry Kaufman, Carolyn Gregoire (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orbiting the Giant Hairball : A Corporate Fool&#8217;s Guide to Surviving with Grace &#8211; Gordon MacKenzie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/orbiting-the-giant-hairball-a-corporate-fools-guide-to-surviving-with-grace-gordon-mackenzie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orbiting-the-giant-hairball-a-corporate-fools-guide-to-surviving-with-grace-gordon-mackenzie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Creativity is crucial to business success. But too often, even the most innovative organization quickly becomes a &#8220;giant hairball&#8221;&#8211;a tangled, impenetrable mass of rules, traditions, and systems, all based on what worked in the past&#8211;that exercises an inexorable pull into mediocrity. Gordon McKenzie worked at Hallmark Cards for thirty years, many of which he spent [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orbiting-the-giant-hairball-a-corporate-fools-guide-to-surviving-with-grace-gordon-mackenzie-abridged/">Orbiting the Giant Hairball : A Corporate Fool&#8217;s Guide to Surviving with Grace &#8211; Gordon MacKenzie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Creativity is crucial to business success. But too often, even the most innovative organization quickly becomes a &#8220;giant hairball&#8221;&#8211;a tangled, impenetrable mass of rules, traditions, and systems, all based on what worked in the past&#8211;that exercises an inexorable pull into mediocrity. Gordon McKenzie worked at Hallmark Cards for thirty years, many of which he spent inspiring his colleagues to slip the bonds of Corporate Normalcy and rise to orbit&#8211;to a mode of dreaming, daring and doing above and beyond the rubber-stamp confines of the administrative mind-set. In his deeply funny book, exuberantly illustrated in full color, he shares the story of his own professional evolution, together with lessons on awakening and fostering creative genius.Originally self-published and already a business &#8220;cult classic&#8221;, this personally empowering and entertaining look at the intersection between human creativity and the bottom line is now widely available to bookstores. It will be a must-read for any manager looking for new ways to invigorate employees, and any professional who wants to achieve his or her best, most self-expressive, most creative and fulfilling work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orbiting-the-giant-hairball-a-corporate-fools-guide-to-surviving-with-grace-gordon-mackenzie-abridged/">Orbiting the Giant Hairball : A Corporate Fool&#8217;s Guide to Surviving with Grace &#8211; Gordon MacKenzie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Accidental Creative &#8211; Preface by Todd Henry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/accidental-creative-preface-by-todd-henry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/accidental-creative-preface-by-todd-henry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Many of us assume that our creative process is beyond our ability to influence, and pay attention to it only when it isn&#8217;t working properly. For the most part, we go about our daily tasks and everything just works. Until it doesn&#8217;t. Adding to this lack of understanding is the rapidly accelerating pace of work. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accidental-creative-preface-by-todd-henry-abridged/">Accidental Creative &#8211; Preface by Todd Henry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Many of us assume that our creative process is beyond our ability to influence, and pay attention to it only when it isn&#8217;t working properly. For the most part, we go about our daily tasks and everything just works. Until it doesn&#8217;t. Adding to this lack of understanding is the rapidly accelerating pace of work. Each day we are face escalating expectations and a continual squeeze to do more with less. We are asked to produce an ever-increasing amount of brilliance in an ever-shrinking amount of time. There is an unspoken (or spoken!) expectation that we&#8217;ll be accessible 24/7, and as a result we frequently feel like we&#8217;re always on. Now business creativity expert Todd Henry explains how to unleash your creative potential. Whether you&#8217;re a creative by trade or an accidental creative, this book will help you quickly and effectively integrate new ideas into your daily life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accidental-creative-preface-by-todd-henry-abridged/">Accidental Creative &#8211; Preface by Todd Henry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peak : For Fans of Atomic Habits &#8211; Anders Ericsson, Robert Pool (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/peak-for-fans-of-atomic-habits-anders-ericsson-robert-pool-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/peak-for-fans-of-atomic-habits-anders-ericsson-robert-pool-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Anyone who wants to get better at anything should read Peak.&#8217; Fortune Do you want to stand out at work, improve your athletic or musical performance, or help your child achieve academic goals? Anders Ericsson has made a career studying chess champions, violin virtuosos, star athletes, and memory mavens. Peak distils three decades of myth-shattering [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/peak-for-fans-of-atomic-habits-anders-ericsson-robert-pool-abridged/">Peak : For Fans of Atomic Habits &#8211; Anders Ericsson, Robert Pool (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Anyone who wants to get better at anything should read Peak.&#8217; Fortune    </p>
<p>                     Do you want to stand out at work, improve your athletic or musical performance, or help your child achieve academic goals?     </p>
<p>                     Anders Ericsson has made a career studying chess champions, violin virtuosos, star athletes, and memory mavens. Peak distils three decades of myth-shattering research into a powerful learning strategy that is fundamentally different from the way people traditionally think about acquiring new abilities. Ericsson&#8217;s revolutionary methods will show you how to improve at almost any skill that matters to you, and that you don&#8217;t have to be a genius to achieve extraordinary things.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Remarkable&#8230;who among us doesn&#8217;t want to learn how to get better at life?&#8217; Stephen J. Dubner, co-author of Freakonomics    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;This book&#8230;could truly change the world&#8217; Joshua Foer, author of Moonwalking with Einstein</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/peak-for-fans-of-atomic-habits-anders-ericsson-robert-pool-abridged/">Peak : For Fans of Atomic Habits &#8211; Anders Ericsson, Robert Pool (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Keep Going : 10 Ways to Stay Creative in Good Times and Bad &#8211; Austin Kleon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/keep-going-10-ways-to-stay-creative-in-good-times-and-bad-austin-kleon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/keep-going-10-ways-to-stay-creative-in-good-times-and-bad-austin-kleon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The world is crazy. Creative work is hard. And nothing is getting any easier! In his previous books &#8211; Steal Like an Artistand Show Your Work!, New York Times bestsellers with over a million copies in print combined &#8211; Austin Kleon gave readers the key to unlock their creativity and then showed them how to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/keep-going-10-ways-to-stay-creative-in-good-times-and-bad-austin-kleon-abridged/">Keep Going : 10 Ways to Stay Creative in Good Times and Bad &#8211; Austin Kleon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world is crazy. Creative work is hard. And nothing is getting any easier!    </p>
<p>                    In his previous books &#8211; Steal Like an Artistand Show Your Work!, New York Times bestsellers with over a million copies in print combined &#8211; Austin Kleon gave readers the key to unlock their creativity and then showed them how to share it. Now he completes his trilogy with his most inspiring work yet.    </p>
<p>                    Keep Going gives the reader life-changing, illustrated advice and encouragement on how to stay creative, focused, and true to yourself in the face of personal burnout or external distractions. Here is how to Build a Bliss Station &#8211; a place or fixed period where you can disconnect from the world. How to see that Every Day Is Groundhog Day &#8211; yesterday&#8217;s over, tomorrow may never come, so just do what you can do today. How to Forget the Noun, Do the Verb &#8211; stop worrying about being a &#8220;painter&#8221; and just paint.    </p>
<p>                    Keep working. Keep playing. Keep searching. Keep giving. Keep living. Keep Going. It&#8217;s exactly the message all of us need, at exactly the right time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/keep-going-10-ways-to-stay-creative-in-good-times-and-bad-austin-kleon-abridged/">Keep Going : 10 Ways to Stay Creative in Good Times and Bad &#8211; Austin Kleon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thinking in New Boxes : A New Paradigm for Business Creativity &#8211; Luc De Brabandere, Alan Iny (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thinking-in-new-boxes-a-new-paradigm-for-business-creativity-luc-de-brabandere-alan-iny-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thinking-in-new-boxes-a-new-paradigm-for-business-creativity-luc-de-brabandere-alan-iny-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When BIC, manufacturer of disposable ballpoint pens, wanted to grow, it looked for an idea beyond introducing new sizes and ink colors. Someone suggested lighters. LIGHTERS? With an idea that seemed crazy at first, that bright executive, instead of seeing BIC as a pen company&#8211;a business in the PEN &#8220;box&#8221;&#8211;figured out that there was growth [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinking-in-new-boxes-a-new-paradigm-for-business-creativity-luc-de-brabandere-alan-iny-abridged/">Thinking in New Boxes : A New Paradigm for Business Creativity &#8211; Luc De Brabandere, Alan Iny (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When BIC, manufacturer of disposable ballpoint pens, wanted to grow, it looked for an idea beyond introducing new sizes and ink colors. Someone suggested lighters.     </p>
<p>                     LIGHTERS?     </p>
<p>                     With an idea that seemed crazy at first, that bright executive, instead of seeing BIC as a pen company&#8211;a business in the PEN &#8220;box&#8221;&#8211;figured out that there was growth to be found in the DISPOSABLE &#8220;box.&#8221; And he was right. Now there are disposable BIC lighters, razors, even phones. The company opened its door to a host of opportunities.     </p>
<p>                     IT INVENTED A NEW BOX.     </p>
<p>                     Your business can, too. And simply thinking &#8220;out of the box&#8221; is not the answer. True ingenuity needs structure, hard analysis, and bold brainstorming. It needs to start     </p>
<p>                     THINKING IN NEW BOXES    </p>
<p>                     &#8211;a revolutionary process for sustainable creativity from two strategic innovation experts from The Boston Consulting Group (BCG).     </p>
<p>                     To make sense of the world, we all rely on assumptions, on models&#8211;on what Luc de Brabandere and Alan Iny call &#8220;boxes.&#8221; If we are unaware of our boxes, they can blind us to risks and opportunities.     </p>
<p>                     This innovative book challenges everything you thought you knew about business creativity by breaking creativity down into five steps:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Doubt everything. Challenge your current perspectives.<br />
                     &#8211; Probe the possible. Explore options around you.<br />
                     &#8211; Diverge. Generate many new and exciting ideas, even if they seem absurd.<br />
                     &#8211; Converge. Evaluate and select the ideas that will drive breakthrough results.<br />
                     &#8211; Reevaluate. Relentlessly. No idea is a good idea forever. And did we mention Reevaluate? Relentlessly.     </p>
<p>                     Creativity is paramount if you are to thrive in a time of accelerating change. Replete with practical and potent creativity tools, and featuring fascinating case studies from BIC to Ford to Trader Joe&#8217;s, Thinking in New Boxes will help you and your company overcome missed opportunities and stay ahead of the curve.     </p>
<p>                     This book isn&#8217;t a simpleminded checklist. This is Thinking in New Boxes.     </p>
<p>                     And it will be fun. (We promise.)     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Thinking in New Boxes     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Excellent . . . While focusing on business creativity, the principles in this book apply anywhere change is needed and will be of interest to anyone seeking to reinvent herself.&#8221;&#8211;Blogcritics     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Thinking in New Boxes is a five-step guide that leverages the authors&#8217; deep understanding of human nature to enable readers to overcome their limitations and both imagine and create their own futures. This book is a must-read for people living and working in today&#8217;s competitive environment.&#8221;&#8211;Ray O. Johnson, Ph.D., chief technology officer, Lockheed Martin     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Thinking In New Boxes discusses what I believe to be one of the fundamental shifts all companies/brands need to be thinking about: how to think creatively, in order to innovate and differentiate our brands. We need to thrive and lead in a world of accelerating change and this book challenges us to even greater creativity in our thinking. One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in a long time.&#8221;&#8211;Jennifer Fox, CEO, Fairmont Hotels &#038; Resorts     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;As impressive as teaching new tricks to old dogs, Thinking in New Boxes is both inspirational and practical&#8211;a comprehensive, step-by-step guide to sharpening one&#8217;s wits in order to harness creativity in the workplace.&#8221;&#8211;Peter Gelb, general manager, Metropolitan Opera</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinking-in-new-boxes-a-new-paradigm-for-business-creativity-luc-de-brabandere-alan-iny-abridged/">Thinking in New Boxes : A New Paradigm for Business Creativity &#8211; Luc De Brabandere, Alan Iny (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Artist&#8217;s Way : 25th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Julia Cameron (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-artists-way-25th-anniversary-edition-julia-cameron-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-artists-way-25th-anniversary-edition-julia-cameron-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Julia Cameron invented the way people renovate the creative soul.&#8221; -The New York Times With its gentle affirmations, inspirational quotes, fill-in-the-blank lists and tasks &#8212; write yourself a thank-you letter, describe yourself at 80, for example &#8212; The Artist&#8217;s Way proposes an egalitarian view of creativity: Everyone&#8217;s got it.&#8211;The New York Times Morning Pages have [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-artists-way-25th-anniversary-edition-julia-cameron-abridged/">The Artist&#8217;s Way : 25th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Julia Cameron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Julia Cameron invented the way people renovate the creative soul.&#8221; -The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    With its gentle affirmations, inspirational quotes, fill-in-the-blank lists and tasks &#8212; write yourself a thank-you letter, describe yourself at 80, for example &#8212; The Artist&#8217;s Way proposes an egalitarian view of creativity: Everyone&#8217;s got it.&#8211;The New York Times      </p>
<p>                     Morning Pages have become a household name, a shorthand for unlocking your creative potential&#8211;Vogue     </p>
<p>                    Over four million copies sold!     </p>
<p>                    Since its first publication, The Artist&#8217;s Way phenomena has inspired the genius of Elizabeth Gilbert and millions of readers to embark on a creative journey and find a deeper connection to process and purpose. Julia Cameron&#8217;s novel approach guides readers in uncovering problems areas and pressure points that may be restricting their creative flow and offers techniques to free up any areas where they might be stuck, opening up opportunities for self-growth and self-discovery.     </p>
<p>                     The program begins with Cameron&#8217;s most vital tools for creative recovery &#8211; The Morning Pages, a daily writing ritual of three pages of stream-of-conscious, and The Artist Date, a dedicated block of time to nurture your inner artist. From there, she shares hundreds of exercises, activities, and prompts to help readers thoroughly explore each chapter. She also offers guidance on starting a &#8220;Creative Cluster&#8221; of fellow artists who will support you in your creative endeavors.     </p>
<p>                     A revolutionary program for personal renewal, The Artist&#8217;s Way will help get you back on track, rediscover your passions, and take the steps you need to change your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-artists-way-25th-anniversary-edition-julia-cameron-abridged/">The Artist&#8217;s Way : 25th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Julia Cameron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Six Thinking Hats : The multi-million bestselling guide to running better meetings and making faster decisions &#8211; Edward de Bono (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/six-thinking-hats-the-multi-million-bestselling-guide-to-running-better-meetings-and-making-faster-decisions-edward-de-bono-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decision Theory: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/six-thinking-hats-the-multi-million-bestselling-guide-to-running-better-meetings-and-making-faster-decisions-edward-de-bono-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE MULTI-MILLION COPY BESTSELLING PHENOMENON Do you regularly find yourself in long, unstructured meetings which end without a decision? Are you a team leader looking for tips on increasing productivity? Or are you looking for ways to enhance collaboration? Six Thinking Hats, Edward de Bono&#8217;s classic book on meetings, remains as relevant as ever. Used [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/six-thinking-hats-the-multi-million-bestselling-guide-to-running-better-meetings-and-making-faster-decisions-edward-de-bono-abridged/">Six Thinking Hats : The multi-million bestselling guide to running better meetings and making faster decisions &#8211; Edward de Bono (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE MULTI-MILLION COPY BESTSELLING PHENOMENON     </p>
<p>                    Do you regularly find yourself in long, unstructured meetings which end without a decision? Are you a team leader looking for tips on increasing productivity? Or are you looking for ways to enhance collaboration?    </p>
<p>                    Six Thinking Hats, Edward de Bono&#8217;s classic book on meetings, remains as relevant as ever. Used to huge success by big companies and organisations such as IBM, Siemens and NASA, the Six-Hats method is a proven way to:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Reduce meeting lengths to one quarter of what they were previously<br />
                    &#8211; Make decisions in just 15 minutes, rather than 3 hours<br />
                    &#8211; Increase productivity by nearly 500%    </p>
<p>                    This extremely simple tool not only increases efficiency in discussions and decision-making, but also encourages openness and trust among colleagues, resulting in happier team, a rise in productivity, and decisions which almost make themselves.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An inspiring man with brilliant ideas. De Bono never ceases to amaze&#8217; Sir Richard Branson</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/six-thinking-hats-the-multi-million-bestselling-guide-to-running-better-meetings-and-making-faster-decisions-edward-de-bono-abridged/">Six Thinking Hats : The multi-million bestselling guide to running better meetings and making faster decisions &#8211; Edward de Bono (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exploring the World of Lucid Dreaming &#8211; Stephen LaBerge, Howard Rheingold (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/exploring-the-world-of-lucid-dreaming-stephen-laberge-howard-rheingold-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dreams & Their Interpretation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychoanalytical Theory (Freudian Psychology)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/exploring-the-world-of-lucid-dreaming-stephen-laberge-howard-rheingold-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;[A] solid how-to book . . . For amateur dream researchers, this is a must.&#8221;&#8211;Whole Earth Review Lucid Dreaming&#8211;conscious awareness during the dream state&#8211;is an exhilarating experience. Because the world you are experiencing is one of your own creation, you can do the impossible and consciously influence the outcome of your dreams. Exploring the World [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/exploring-the-world-of-lucid-dreaming-stephen-laberge-howard-rheingold-abridged/">Exploring the World of Lucid Dreaming &#8211; Stephen LaBerge, Howard Rheingold (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;[A] solid how-to book . . . For amateur dream researchers, this is a must.&#8221;&#8211;Whole Earth Review    </p>
<p>                    Lucid Dreaming&#8211;conscious awareness during the dream state&#8211;is an exhilarating experience. Because the world you are experiencing is one of your own creation, you can do the impossible and consciously influence the outcome of your dreams.     </p>
<p>                    Exploring the World of Lucid Dreaming goes far beyond the confines of pop dream psychology, establishing a scientifically researched framework for using lucid dreaming. Based on Dr. Stephen LaBerge&#8217;s extensive laboratory work at Stanford University mapping mind/body relationships during the dream state, as well as the teachings of Tibetan dream yogis and the work of other scientists, including German psychologist Paul Tholey, this practical workbook will show you how to use your dreams to:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Solve problems<br />
                    &#8211; Gain greater confidence<br />
                    &#8211; Improve creativity<br />
                    &#8211; Face and overcome fears and inhibitions<br />
                    &#8211; Create a new sense of empowerment and liberation in your life     </p>
<p>                     The techniques you&#8217;ll learn in this exciting workbook will make your nightly dream journeys more enjoyable, increase your understanding of yourself, and make you realize that the possibilities of expanding consciousness are far greater than you might think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/exploring-the-world-of-lucid-dreaming-stephen-laberge-howard-rheingold-abridged/">Exploring the World of Lucid Dreaming &#8211; Stephen LaBerge, Howard Rheingold (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Learn Better : Mastering the Skills for Success in Life, Business, and School, or How to Become an Expert in Just About Anything &#8211; Ulrich Boser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For centuries, experts have argued that learning was about memorizing information: You&#8217;re supposed to study facts, dates, and details; burn them into your memory; and then apply that knowledge at opportune times. But this approach to learning isn&#8217;t nearly enough for the world that we live in today, and in Learn Better journalist and education [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/">Learn Better : Mastering the Skills for Success in Life, Business, and School, or How to Become an Expert in Just About Anything &#8211; Ulrich Boser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For centuries, experts have argued that learning was about memorizing information: You&#8217;re supposed to study facts, dates, and details; burn them into your memory; and then apply that knowledge at opportune times. But this approach to learning isn&#8217;t nearly enough for the world that we live in today, and in Learn Better journalist and education researcher Ulrich Boser demonstrates that how we learn can matter just as much as what we learn.     </p>
<p>                    In this brilliantly researched book, Boser maps out the new science of learning, showing how simple techniques like comprehension check-ins and making material personally relatable can help people gain expertise in dramatically better ways. He covers six key steps to help you &#8220;learn how to learn,&#8221; all illuminated with fascinating stories like how Jackson Pollock developed his unique painting style and why an ancient Japanese counting device allows kids to do math at superhuman speeds. Boser&#8217;s witty, engaging writing makes this book feel like a guilty pleasure, not homework.    </p>
<p>                    Learn Better will revolutionize the way students and society alike approach learning and makes the case that being smart is not an innate ability&#8211;learning is a skill everyone can master. With Boser as your guide, you will be able to fully capitalize on your brain&#8217;s remarkable ability to gain new skills and open up a whole new world of possibilities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/">Learn Better : Mastering the Skills for Success in Life, Business, and School, or How to Become an Expert in Just About Anything &#8211; Ulrich Boser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smarter : The New Science of Building Brain Power &#8211; Dan Hurley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/smarter-the-new-science-of-building-brain-power-dan-hurley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/smarter-the-new-science-of-building-brain-power-dan-hurley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A riveting look at the birth of a new science.&#8221; -Daniel H. Pink, author of Drive When he was eight years old, Dan Hurley was labeled a &#8220;slow learner&#8221; because he still couldn&#8217;t read. Three years later, he had become a straight A student. Until the publication of a major study in 2008, psychologists believed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smarter-the-new-science-of-building-brain-power-dan-hurley-abridged/">Smarter : The New Science of Building Brain Power &#8211; Dan Hurley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A riveting look at the birth of a new science.&#8221; -Daniel H. Pink, author of Drive    </p>
<p>                    When he was eight years old, Dan Hurley was labeled a &#8220;slow learner&#8221; because he still couldn&#8217;t read.  Three years later, he had become a straight A student.     </p>
<p>                    Until the publication of a major study in 2008, psychologists believed that intelligence is fixed at birth, that IQ is like a number tattooed on the soul. The new study showed that people can increase their &#8220;fluid&#8221; intelligence through training.    </p>
<p>                    Hurley, who grew up to become an award-winning science journalist, first explored the topic in The New York Times Magazine. In Smarter, he digs deeper by meeting with the field&#8217;s leading researchers-and becoming a human guinea pig. After just three months of playing computer brain-training games, joining a boot-camp exercise program, learning to play the Renaissance lute, practicing mindfulness meditation and and even getting his brain zapped in the name of science, Hurley improved his fluid intelligence by sixteen percent.    </p>
<p>                    With humor and heart, Smarter chronicles the roiling field of intelligence research and delivers practical findings to sharpen the minds of children, young adults, seniors, and those with cognitive challenges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smarter-the-new-science-of-building-brain-power-dan-hurley-abridged/">Smarter : The New Science of Building Brain Power &#8211; Dan Hurley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics & Communications Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phones: Consumer/user Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is your phone the first thing you reach for when you wake up? And the last thing you see before you sleep? Do you find the hours slip away as you idly scroll through your social media timeline? In short, are you addicted to your phone? If so, How to Break Up with Your Phone [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/">How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is your phone the first thing you reach for when you wake up? And the  last thing you see before you sleep? Do you find the hours slip away as  you idly scroll through your social media timeline?     </p>
<p>                     In short, are you addicted to your phone? If so, How to Break Up with Your Phone is here to help.     </p>
<p>                     How to Break Up With Your Phone  is a smart, practical and useful plan to help you conquer your mobile  phone addiction in just 30 days &#8211; and take back your life in the  process.     </p>
<p>                    Recent studies have shown that spending extended time  on our phones affects our ability to form new memories, think deeply,  focus and absorb information, and the hormones triggered every time we  hear our phones buzz both add to our stress levels and are the hallmark  signs of addiction. In How to Break Up with Your Phone,  award-winning science journalist Catherine Price explores the effects  that our constant connectivity is having on our brains, bodies,  relationships, and society at large and asks, how much time do you really want to spend on your phone?     </p>
<p>                    Over  the course of 30 days, Catherine will guide you through an  easy-to-follow plan that enables you to identify your goals, priorities  and bad habits, tidy your apps, prune your email, and take time away.  Lastly, you will create a new, healthier relationship with your phone  and establish habits and routines to ensure this new relationship  sticks.     </p>
<p>                    You don&#8217;t have to give up your phone forever; instead  you will be more mindful not only of how you use your phone, but also  about how you choose to spend the precious moments of your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/">How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Habits are more powerful than your will &#8211; if you know how to make them work for you Two strings are hanging from a ceiling, one at the centre of the room, one near the wall. You&#8217;re asked to tie the strings together, but you can&#8217;t reach both at the same time. You look around [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/">Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Habits are more powerful than your will &#8211; if you know how to make them work for you    </p>
<p>                    Two strings are hanging from a ceiling, one at the centre of the room, one near the wall. You&#8217;re asked to tie the strings together, but you can&#8217;t reach both at the same time. You look around the room and see a table and a pair of pliers. How would you solve the problem?    </p>
<p>                    When confronted with challenges, most people let habits rule them (in this case, ignoring the pliers, the creative tool at your disposal). That is not surprising when you realise that at least a third of our waking hours are lived on auto-pilot &#8211; ruminating over past events, clicking through websites trawling for updates and the like. Such unconscious thoughts and actions are powerful. But the habits of the mind do not have to control us &#8211; we can steer them.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on hundreds of fascinating studies, psychologist Jeremy Dean &#8211; the mind behind the hugely popular and insightful website PsyBlog &#8211; shares how the new brain science of habit can be harnessed to your benefit, whether you&#8217;re hoping to eat moreveg, take an evening run, clear out your email backlog, or be more creative when faced with challenges at work and at home.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/">Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unlimited Memory : How to Use Advanced Learning Strategies to Learn Faster, Remember More and be More Productive &#8211; Kevin Horsley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unlimited-memory-how-to-use-advanced-learning-strategies-to-learn-faster-remember-more-and-be-more-productive-kevin-horsley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unlimited-memory-how-to-use-advanced-learning-strategies-to-learn-faster-remember-more-and-be-more-productive-kevin-horsley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kevin Horsley Broke a World Memory Record in 2013&#8230; And You&#8217;re About to Learn How to Use His Memory Strategies to Learn Faster, Be More Productive and Achieve More Success Most people never tap into 10% of their potential for memory. In this book, you&#8217;re about to learn: How the World&#8217;s Top Memory Experts Concentrate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unlimited-memory-how-to-use-advanced-learning-strategies-to-learn-faster-remember-more-and-be-more-productive-kevin-horsley-abridged/">Unlimited Memory : How to Use Advanced Learning Strategies to Learn Faster, Remember More and be More Productive &#8211; Kevin Horsley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kevin Horsley Broke a World Memory Record in 2013&#8230;    </p>
<p>                     And You&#8217;re About to Learn How to Use His Memory Strategies to Learn Faster, Be More Productive and Achieve More Success    </p>
<p>                     Most people never tap into 10% of their potential for memory. In this book, you&#8217;re about to learn:     </p>
<p>                     How the World&#8217;s Top Memory Experts Concentrate and Remember Any Information at Will, and How You Can Too    </p>
<p>                     Do you ever feel like you&#8217;re too busy, too stressed or just too distracted to concentrate and get work done? In Unlimited Memory, you&#8217;ll learn how the world&#8217;s best memory masters get themselves to concentrate at will, anytime they want. When you can easily focus and concentrate on the task at hand, and store and recall useful information, you can easily double your productivity and eliminate wasted time, stress and mistakes at work.    </p>
<p>                     In this book, you&#8217;ll find all the tools, strategies and techniques you need to improve your memory.    </p>
<p>                     Here&#8217;s just a taste of the memory methods you&#8217;ll learn in this book:     </p>
<p>                       The 3 bad habits that keep you from easily remembering important information How a simple pattern of thinking can stop you from imprinting and remembering key facts, figures and ideas, and how to break this old pattern so you&#8217;ll never again be known as someone with a &#8220;bad memory&#8221; How to master your attention so you can focus and concentrate longer, even during challenging or stressful situations How to use your car to remember anything you want (like long lists or information you need to remember for your studies or personal life) without writing anything down Simple methods that allow you to nail down tough information or complex concepts quickly and easily How to combine your long-term memory (things you already know and will never forget) and short-term memory (information you want to remember right now) to create instant recall for tests, presentations and important projects The simple, invisible mental technique for remembering names without social awkwardness or anxiety How using your imagination to bring boring information to life can help you dramatically improve your attention span and recall An incredible strategy for remembering numbers (the same system Kevin used to remember Pi to 10,000 digits and beat the world memory record by 14 minutes) How to use a mental map to lock in and connect hundreds or even thousands of ideas in your long-term memory (this method will allow you to become a leading expert in your field faster than you ever dreamed possible)      </p>
<p>                     If you&#8217;re ready to harness the incredible power of your mind to remember more in less time, this book is for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unlimited-memory-how-to-use-advanced-learning-strategies-to-learn-faster-remember-more-and-be-more-productive-kevin-horsley-abridged/">Unlimited Memory : How to Use Advanced Learning Strategies to Learn Faster, Remember More and be More Productive &#8211; Kevin Horsley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Organized Mind : Thinking Straight in the Age of Information Overload &#8211; Daniel Levitin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-organized-mind-thinking-straight-in-the-age-of-information-overload-daniel-levitin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-organized-mind-thinking-straight-in-the-age-of-information-overload-daniel-levitin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Organized Mind, New York Times and Sunday Times bestselling author and neuroscientist Daniel Levitin offers solutions for the problems of information overload. ___________________________________________________ Overwhelmed by demands on your time? Baffled by the sheer volume of data? You&#8217;re not alone. Even the smartest mind can&#8217;t beat the organized mind &#8211; when we&#8217;re unable to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-organized-mind-thinking-straight-in-the-age-of-information-overload-daniel-levitin-abridged/">The Organized Mind : Thinking Straight in the Age of Information Overload &#8211; Daniel Levitin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Organized Mind, New York Times and Sunday Times bestselling author and neuroscientist Daniel Levitin offers solutions for the problems of information overload.<br />
                    ___________________________________________________<br />
                     Overwhelmed by demands on your time? Baffled by the sheer volume of data?<br />
                    You&#8217;re not alone. Even the smartest mind can&#8217;t beat the organized mind &#8211; when we&#8217;re unable to make sense of it all, our creativity plummets, our decision making suffers and we grow absent-minded. Nowadays, we drown under emails, forever juggle six tasks at once and try to make complex decisions ever more quickly. This is information overload.    </p>
<p>                     Using a combination of academic research and examples from daily life, Daniel Levitin explains how to take back control of your life, from healthcare to online dating to raising kids, showing that the secret to success is always organization. You&#8217;ll discover life-changing facts about:    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; How to make the most of your brain&#8217;s daily processing limit<br />
                     &#8211; Why pressing Send or clicking Like are addictive<br />
                     &#8211; Why daydreaming is your brain at its most productive<br />
                     &#8211; What the most successful people keep in their drawer<br />
                     &#8211; Why multitasking is a bad way to do nearly everything    </p>
<p>                     In a world where information is power, The Organized Mind holds the key to harnessing that information and making it work for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-organized-mind-thinking-straight-in-the-age-of-information-overload-daniel-levitin-abridged/">The Organized Mind : Thinking Straight in the Age of Information Overload &#8211; Daniel Levitin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-alcoholic Beverages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Gray&#8217;s tale of going sober is uplifting and inspiring&#8217; &#8211; The Evening Standard &#8216;An icon of the Quit Lit movement&#8217; &#8211; Conde Nast Traveller &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Bryony Gordon &#8216;Not remotely preachy&#8217; &#8211; The Times &#8216;Jaunty, shrewd and convincing&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Telegraph &#8216;Admirably honest, light, bubbly and remarkably rarely annoying&#8217; &#8211; Alice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/">The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gray&#8217;s tale of going sober is uplifting and inspiring&#8217; &#8211; The Evening Standard     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;An icon of the Quit Lit movement&#8217;  &#8211; Conde Nast Traveller      </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Bryony Gordon     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Not remotely preachy&#8217; &#8211; The Times     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Jaunty, shrewd and convincing&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Telegraph     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Admirably honest, light, bubbly and remarkably rarely annoying&#8217; &#8211; Alice O&#8217;Keeffe, Guardian     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Truthful, modern and real&#8217; &#8211; Stylist     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Brave, witty and brilliantly written&#8217; &#8211; Marie Claire     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober came to me at a time when I much needed it&#8230; The book became my best friend, and got me through, and took me on a journey.&#8217; &#8211; Sadie Frost     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Particularly lovely, because it&#8217;s not a deep and dark dive into someone&#8217;s terrible addiction. It&#8217;s a celebration of everything that she has gained from not drinking&#8217; &#8211; Laura Donnelly     </p>
<p>                    Ever sworn off alcohol for a month and found yourself drinking by the 7th? Think there&#8217;s &#8216;no point&#8217; in just one drink? Welcome! There are millions of us. 64% of Brits want to drink less.    </p>
<p>                    Catherine Gray was stuck in a hellish whirligig of Drink, Make horrible decisions, Hangover, Repeat. She had her fair share of &#8216;drunk tank&#8217; jail cells and topless-in-a-hot-tub misadventures.    </p>
<p>                    But this book goes beyond the binges and blackouts to deep-dive into uncharted territory: What happens after you quit drinking? This gripping, heart-breaking and witty book takes us down the rabbit-hole of an alternative reality. A life with zero hangovers, through sober weddings, sex, Christmases and breakups.     </p>
<p>                    In The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober, Catherine Gray shines a light on society&#8217;s drink-pushing and talks to top neuroscientists and psychologists about why we drink, delving into the science behind what it does to our brains and bodies.    </p>
<p>                    Much more than a tale from the netherworld of addicted drinking, this book is about the escape, and why a sober life can be more intoxicating than you ever imagined. Whether you&#8217;re a hopelessly devoted drinker, merely sober-curious, or you&#8217;ve already ditched the drink, you will love this book.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Haunting, admirable and enlightening&#8217; &#8211; The Pool     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;A riveting, raw, yet humorous memoir with actionable advice. A truly unique blend of storytelling and science that holds a universe of hope.&#8217; &#8211; Annie Grace, author of This Naked Mind     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Like listening to your best friend teach you to be sober. Lighthearted but serious, it&#8217;s packed with ideas, tools, tips and, most importantly, reasons for living a sober life. This book is excellent.&#8217;- Eric Zimmer, host of podcast The One You Feed     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gray&#8217;s fizzy writing succeeds in making this potentially boring-as-hell subject both engaging and highly seductive&#8217; &#8211; The Bookseller     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine Gray is an exceptional writer. Her exquisitely crafted thoughts on the joys of being sober are not only deeply honest and pragmatic, but she manages to infuse tons of humor. This is a delightful, informative, and compelling read for all those who are sober or seeking sobriety.&#8217; &#8211; Sasha Tozzi, Huffington Post columnist     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine&#8217;s writing style and voice captivate me. She has a way of translating her story into an experience I don&#8217;t want to end. I want to drink every drop she produces.&#8217; &#8211; Holly Whitaker, founder of Hip Sobriety School and co-presenter of Home podcast     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;This book is great. A balanced, informative and entertaining melange of memoir, sociology and psychology. I identified very strongly with huge sections of it.&#8217; &#8211; Jon Stewart, guitarist of Sleeper and Leaving AA, Staying Sober blogger >    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Sober is too often equated with &#8220;sombre&#8221; in our culture. Gray&#8217;s book turns that idea on its head. Her experience of sobriety is joyful and life-affirming. A must-read for anyone who has a nagging suspicion that alcohol may be taking away more than it&#8217;s giving.&#8217; &#8211; Hilda Burke, psychotherapist and couples counsellor     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Catherine Gray really captures the FUN we can have in sobriety. This book challenges the status quo; sobriet sounds as liberating as taking a trip to the jungle. Fun and inspirational. What an important book for our time! A joy to read.&#8217; &#8211; Samantha Moyo, founder of Morning Gloryville     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;No other author writes about sober living with as much warmth or emotional range as Catherine Gray. Her deep insight into the subtle psychologies of drinking, and of life, means that everything she writes is both utterly relatable and stretches our minds. Hers is a rare wisdom.&#8217; &#8211; Dr Richard Piper, CEO, Alcohol Change UK</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unexpected-joy-of-being-sober-the-sunday-times-bestseller-catherine-gray-abridged/">The Unexpected Joy of Being Sober : THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Catherine Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Problem Solving 101 : A simple book for smart people &#8211; Ken Watanabe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/problem-solving-101-a-simple-book-for-smart-people-ken-watanabe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/problem-solving-101-a-simple-book-for-smart-people-ken-watanabe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Problem Solving 101 started out as a simple guide to teach Japanese schoolchildren critical thinking skills. But it quickly became an international bestseller for readers of all ages, thanks to the powerful effectiveness of Ken Watanabe&#8217;s unique methods. Full of useful diagrams and quirky drawings, Problem Solving 101 is packed with practical tools and brain [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/problem-solving-101-a-simple-book-for-smart-people-ken-watanabe-abridged/">Problem Solving 101 : A simple book for smart people &#8211; Ken Watanabe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Problem Solving 101 started out as a simple guide to teach Japanese schoolchildren critical thinking skills. But it quickly became an international bestseller for readers of all ages, thanks to the powerful effectiveness of Ken Watanabe&#8217;s unique methods.     </p>
<p>                    Full of useful diagrams and quirky drawings, Problem Solving 101 is packed with practical tools and brain training techniques that will improve your problem-solving and decision-making ability, and enable you to find better solutions faster.    </p>
<p>                    Simple enough for a high school student to understand but sophisticated enough for CEOs to apply to their most challenging problems, Problem Solving 101 has helped millions of people around the world to find successful solutions to even the toughest of problems.    </p>
<p>                    Once you&#8217;ve mastered the problem-solving skills in this book, you&#8217;ll wonder how you ever got by without them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/problem-solving-101-a-simple-book-for-smart-people-ken-watanabe-abridged/">Problem Solving 101 : A simple book for smart people &#8211; Ken Watanabe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decision Theory: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking presents practical, lively, and inspiring ways for you to become more successful through better thinking. The idea is simple: You can learn how to think far better by adopting specific strategies. Brilliant people aren&#8217;t a special breed&#8211;they just use their minds differently. By using the straightforward and thought-provoking techniques [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/">The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking presents practical, lively, and inspiring ways for you to become more successful through better thinking. The idea is simple: You can learn how to think far better by adopting specific strategies. Brilliant people aren&#8217;t a special breed&#8211;they just use their minds differently. By using the straightforward and thought-provoking techniques in The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking, you will regularly find imaginative solutions to difficult challenges, and you will discover new ways of looking at your world and yourself&#8211;revealing previously hidden opportunities. The book offers real-life stories, explicit action items, and concrete methods that allow you to attain a deeper understanding of any issue, exploit the power of failure as a step toward success, develop a habit of creating probing questions, see the world of ideas as an ever-flowing stream of thought, and embrace the uplifting reality that we are all capable of change. No matter who you are, the practical mind-sets introduced in the book will empower you to realize any goal in a more creative, intelligent, and effective manner.<br />
                    Filled with engaging examples that unlock truths about thinking in every walk of life, The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking is written for all who want to reach their fullest potential&#8211;including students, parents, teachers, businesspeople, professionals, athletes, artists, leaders, and lifelong learners. Whenever you are stuck, need a new idea, or want to learn and grow, The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking will inspire and guide you on your way. To share thinking stories, go to: http://5elementsofthinking.wordpress.com/</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/">The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fluent Forever : How to Learn Any Language Fast and Never Forget It &#8211; Gabriel Wyner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Foreign Language Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language Teaching & Learning (other Than ELT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language Teaching & Learning Material & Coursework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; For anyone who wants to learn a foreign language, this is the method that will finally make the words stick. &#8220;A brilliant and thoroughly modern guide to learning new languages.&#8221;&#8211;Gary Marcus, cognitive psychologist and author of the New York Times bestseller Guitar Zero At thirty years old, Gabriel Wyner speaks six languages [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/">Fluent Forever : How to Learn Any Language Fast and Never Forget It &#8211; Gabriel Wyner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; For anyone who wants to learn a foreign language, this is the method that will finally make the words stick.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A brilliant and thoroughly modern guide to learning new languages.&#8221;&#8211;Gary Marcus, cognitive psychologist and author of the New York Times bestseller Guitar Zero     </p>
<p>                    At thirty years old, Gabriel Wyner speaks six languages fluently. He didn&#8217;t learn them in school&#8211;who does? Rather, he learned them in the past few years, working on his own and practicing on the subway, using simple techniques and free online resources&#8211;and here he wants to show others what he&#8217;s discovered.     </p>
<p>                    Starting with pronunciation, you&#8217;ll learn how to rewire your ears and turn foreign sounds into familiar sounds. You&#8217;ll retrain your tongue to produce those sounds accurately, using tricks from opera singers and actors. Next, you&#8217;ll begin to tackle words, and connect sounds and spellings to imagery rather than translations, which will enable you to think in a foreign language. And with the help of sophisticated spaced-repetition techniques, you&#8217;ll be able to memorize hundreds of words a month in minutes every day.     </p>
<p>                    This is brain hacking at its most exciting, taking what we know about neuroscience and linguistics and using it to create the most efficient and enjoyable way to learn a foreign language in the spare minutes of your day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/">Fluent Forever : How to Learn Any Language Fast and Never Forget It &#8211; Gabriel Wyner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Creative Habit : Learn it and Use I for Life &#8211; Twyla Tharp (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-creative-habit-learn-it-and-use-i-for-life-twyla-tharp-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sci Fi Books for Kids]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-creative-habit-learn-it-and-use-i-for-life-twyla-tharp-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What makes someone creative? How does someone face the empty page, the empty stage and making something where nothing existed before? Not just a dilemma for the artist, it is something everyone faces everyday. What will I cook that isn&#8217;t boring? How can I make that memo persuasive? What sales pitch will increase the order, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-creative-habit-learn-it-and-use-i-for-life-twyla-tharp-abridged/">The Creative Habit : Learn it and Use I for Life &#8211; Twyla Tharp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What makes someone creative? How does someone face the empty page, the empty stage and making something where nothing existed before? Not just a dilemma for the artist, it is something everyone faces everyday. What will I cook that isn&#8217;t boring? How can I make that memo persuasive? What sales pitch will increase the order, get me the job, lock in that bonus? These too, are creative acts, and they all share a common need: proper preparation. For Twyla Tharp, creativity is no mystery; it&#8217;s the product of hard work and preparation, of knowing one&#8217;s aims and one&#8217;s subject, of learning from approaches taken in the past. It&#8217;s a process undertaken every day. It&#8217;s a habit. The Creative Habit is not merely a look inside the mind of a remarkable woman with remarkable skills, but a programmatic, inspiring, encouraging guide to help each of us achieve our fullest creative potential.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-creative-habit-learn-it-and-use-i-for-life-twyla-tharp-abridged/">The Creative Habit : Learn it and Use I for Life &#8211; Twyla Tharp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Seven Sins of Memory Updated Edition : How the Mind Forgets and Remembers &#8211; Daniel L Schacter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-seven-sins-of-memory-updated-edition-how-the-mind-forgets-and-remembers-daniel-l-schacter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-seven-sins-of-memory-updated-edition-how-the-mind-forgets-and-remembers-daniel-l-schacter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>By one of the world&#8217;s foremost psychologists, a groundbreaking and award-winning study updated for the 20th anniversary with new research that delves into the complex behavior of memory Twenty years ago, The Seven Sins of Memory offered the first framework that explained common memory vices&#8211;and their surprising virtues. Now, in this updated edition, Daniel L. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seven-sins-of-memory-updated-edition-how-the-mind-forgets-and-remembers-daniel-l-schacter-abridged/">The Seven Sins of Memory Updated Edition : How the Mind Forgets and Remembers &#8211; Daniel L Schacter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By one of the world&#8217;s foremost psychologists, a groundbreaking and award-winning study updated for the 20th anniversary with new research that delves into the complex behavior of memory     </p>
<p>                    Twenty years ago, The Seven Sins of Memory offered the first framework that explained common memory vices&#8211;and their surprising virtues. Now, in this updated edition, Daniel L. Schacter revisits his groundbreaking research with the twenty-first century&#8217;s cultural trends and scientific discoveries. How does our ever-increasing reliance on Google, Instagram, and other websites harm our mind&#8217;s ability to store and retrieve memories? How has repeated exposure to &#8220;fake news&#8221; and other false statements increased our bias and made it easier for us to think these statements are true? Exploring the memory miscues that occur in everyday life&#8211;absentmindedness, transience, blocking, misattribution, suggestibility, bias, and persistence&#8211;Schacter delves into the striking scientific research, giving us a glimpse of the fascinating neurology of memory. Together, the stories and the scientific results provide a new look at our brains and at what we more generally think of as our minds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seven-sins-of-memory-updated-edition-how-the-mind-forgets-and-remembers-daniel-l-schacter-abridged/">The Seven Sins of Memory Updated Edition : How the Mind Forgets and Remembers &#8211; Daniel L Schacter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s Not How Good You Are, It&#8217;s How Good You Want to Be : The world&#8217;s best-selling book by Paul Arden &#8211; Paul Arden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/its-not-how-good-you-are-its-how-good-you-want-to-be-the-worlds-best-selling-book-by-paul-arden-paul-arden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[English Language: Reading & Writing Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/its-not-how-good-you-are-its-how-good-you-want-to-be-the-worlds-best-selling-book-by-paul-arden-paul-arden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s Not How Good You Are, It&#8217;s How Good You Want to Be is a handbook of how to succeed in the world: a pocket bible for the talented and timid alike to help make the unthinkable thinkable and the impossible possible. The world&#8217;s top advertising guru, Paul Arden, offers up his wisdom on issues [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-not-how-good-you-are-its-how-good-you-want-to-be-the-worlds-best-selling-book-by-paul-arden-paul-arden-abridged/">It&#8217;s Not How Good You Are, It&#8217;s How Good You Want to Be : The world&#8217;s best-selling book by Paul Arden &#8211; Paul Arden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s Not How Good You Are, It&#8217;s How Good You Want to Be is a handbook of how to succeed in the world: a pocket bible for the talented and timid alike to help make the unthinkable thinkable and the impossible possible.    </p>
<p>                    The world&#8217;s top advertising guru, Paul Arden, offers up his wisdom on issues as diverse as problem solving, responding to a brief, communicating, playing your cards right, making mistakes, and creativity &#8211; all endeavours that can be applied to aspects of modern life.    </p>
<p>                    This uplifting and humorous little book provides a unique insight into the world of advertising and is a quirky compilation of quotes, facts, pictures, wit and wisdom &#8211; all packed into easy-to-digest, bite-sized spreads. If you want to succeed in life or business, this book is a must.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-not-how-good-you-are-its-how-good-you-want-to-be-the-worlds-best-selling-book-by-paul-arden-paul-arden-abridged/">It&#8217;s Not How Good You Are, It&#8217;s How Good You Want to Be : The world&#8217;s best-selling book by Paul Arden &#8211; Paul Arden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Use Your Perfect Memory : Dramatic New Techniques for Improving Your Memory; Third Edition &#8211; Tony Buzan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/use-your-perfect-memory-dramatic-new-techniques-for-improving-your-memory-third-edition-tony-buzan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/use-your-perfect-memory-dramatic-new-techniques-for-improving-your-memory-third-edition-tony-buzan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the bestselling author of The Mind Map Book and Use Both Sides of Your Brain The potential of the human memory is phenomenal. But do you know how to make the most of yours? World-renowned expert on the brain, memory, speed reading, creativity, and innovation Tony Buzan, inventor of Mind Maps, shares the secrets [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/use-your-perfect-memory-dramatic-new-techniques-for-improving-your-memory-third-edition-tony-buzan-abridged/">Use Your Perfect Memory : Dramatic New Techniques for Improving Your Memory; Third Edition &#8211; Tony Buzan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the bestselling author of The Mind Map Book and Use Both Sides of Your Brain    </p>
<p>                     The potential of the human memory is phenomenal. But do you know how to make the most of yours?     </p>
<p>                     World-renowned expert on the brain, memory, speed reading, creativity, and innovation Tony Buzan, inventor of Mind Maps, shares the secrets of how to stretch your memory to its fullest. Buzan has devised an ingenious system for memory improvement, geared to handle each specific memory problem&#8211;from everyday names and phone numbers to special programs for card players to showing students how to prepare for and get optimum results on exams.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/use-your-perfect-memory-dramatic-new-techniques-for-improving-your-memory-third-edition-tony-buzan-abridged/">Use Your Perfect Memory : Dramatic New Techniques for Improving Your Memory; Third Edition &#8211; Tony Buzan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do the Work : Overcome Resistance and Get Out of Your Own Way &#8211; Steven Pressfield</title>
		<link>/do-the-work-overcome-resistance-and-get-out-of-your-own-way-steven-pressfield/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing Skills]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-the-work-overcome-resistance-and-get-out-of-your-own-way-steven-pressfield/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;There is an enemy. There is an intelligent, active, malign force working against us. Step one is to recognize this. This recognition alone is enormously powerful. It saved my life, and it will save yours.&#8221; &#8212; Steven Pressfield Could you be getting in your way of producing great work? Have you started a project but [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-the-work-overcome-resistance-and-get-out-of-your-own-way-steven-pressfield/">Do the Work : Overcome Resistance and Get Out of Your Own Way &#8211; Steven Pressfield</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;There is an enemy. There is an intelligent, active, malign force working against us. Step one is to recognize this. This recognition alone is enormously powerful. It saved my life, and it will save yours.&#8221; &#8212; Steven Pressfield Could you be getting in your way of producing great work? Have you started a project but never finished? Would you like to do work that matters, but don&#8217;t know where to start?The answer is Do the Work, a manifesto by bestselling author Steven Pressfield, that will show you that it&#8217;s not about better ideas, it&#8217;s about actually doing the work. Do the Work is a weapon against Resistance &#8211; a tool that will help you take action and successfully ship projects out the door. Picking up where The War of Art and Turning Pro left off, Do The Work takes the reader from the start to the finish of any long-form project-novel, screenplay, album, software piece, you name it. Do The Work identifies the predictable Resistance Points along the way and walks you through each of them. No, you are not crazy. No, you are not alone. No, you are not the first person to &#8220;hit the wall&#8221; in Act Two. Do The Work charts the territory. It&#8217;s the stage-by-stage road map for taking your project from Page One to THE END.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-the-work-overcome-resistance-and-get-out-of-your-own-way-steven-pressfield/">Do the Work : Overcome Resistance and Get Out of Your Own Way &#8211; Steven Pressfield</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
