<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Violence In Society Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/violence-in-society/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/violence-in-society/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Violence In Society Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/violence-in-society/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Macho Paradox : Why Some Men Hurt Women and and How All Men Can Help &#8211; Jackson Katz</title>
		<link>/the-macho-paradox-why-some-men-hurt-women-and-and-how-all-men-can-help-jackson-katz/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Men]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-macho-paradox-why-some-men-hurt-women-and-and-how-all-men-can-help-jackson-katz/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Praise for The Macho Paradox &#8220;An honest, intellectually rigorous and insightful work that challenges readers to truly engage in a political discourse that can change lives, communities and nations.&#8221; &#8211;Rosalind Wiseman, author of Queen Bees and Wannabes &#8220;Jackson Katz is an American hero! With integrity and courage, he has taken his message&#8211;that the epidemic of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-macho-paradox-why-some-men-hurt-women-and-and-how-all-men-can-help-jackson-katz/">The Macho Paradox : Why Some Men Hurt Women and and How All Men Can Help &#8211; Jackson Katz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Praise for The Macho Paradox</p>
<p>                    &#8220;An honest, intellectually rigorous and insightful work that challenges readers to truly engage in a political discourse that can change lives, communities and nations.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211;Rosalind Wiseman, author of Queen Bees and Wannabes</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Jackson Katz is an American hero! With integrity and courage, he has taken his message&#8211;that the epidemic of violence against women is a men&#8217;s issue&#8211;into athletic terms, the military and frat houses across the country. His book explains carefully and convincingly why&#8211;and how&#8211;men can become part of the solution, and work with women to build a world in which everyone is safer.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    &#8211;Michael Kimmel, author of Manhood in America, spokesperson, National Organization for Men Against Sexism (NOMAS)</p>
<p>                    &#8220;If only men would read Katz&#8217;s book, it could serve as a potent form of male consciousness-raising.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211;Publishers Weekly</p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book leaves no man behind when it comes to taking violence against women personally&#8230;.After reading this book you can see how important it is to be a stand-up guy and not a standy-by guy, no matter what race or culture you come from.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211;Alfred L. McMichael, 14th Sergeant Major of the Marine Corps and now serving as the Sergeant Major of NATO</p>
<p>                    &#8220;A candid look at the cultural factors that lend themselves to tolerance of abuse and violence against women.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211;Booklist</p>
<p>                    &#8220;These pages will empower both men and women to end the scourge of male violence and abuse. Katz knows how to cut to the core of the issues, demonstrating undeniably that stopping the degradation of women should be every man&#8217;s priority.&#8221;</p>
<p>                    &#8211;Lundy Bancroft, author of Why Does He Do That?: Inside the Minds of Angry and Controlling Men</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-macho-paradox-why-some-men-hurt-women-and-and-how-all-men-can-help-jackson-katz/">The Macho Paradox : Why Some Men Hurt Women and and How All Men Can Help &#8211; Jackson Katz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow</title>
		<link>/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a dramatic account of violence and espionage, Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter Ronan Farrow exposes serial abusers and a cabal of powerful interests hell-bent on covering up the truth, at any cost. In 2017, a routine network television investigation led Ronan Farrow to a story only whispered about: one of Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful producers was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow/">Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a dramatic account of violence and espionage, Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter Ronan Farrow exposes serial abusers and a cabal of powerful interests hell-bent on covering up the truth, at any cost.</p>
<p>                    In 2017, a routine network television investigation led Ronan Farrow to a story only whispered about: one of Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful producers was a predator, protected by fear, wealth, and a conspiracy of silence. As Farrow drew closer to the truth, shadowy operatives, from high-priced lawyers to elite war-hardened spies, mounted a secret campaign of intimidation, threatening his career, following his every move and weaponizing an account of abuse in his own family. </p>
<p>                    All the while, Farrow and his producer faced a degree of resistance that could not be explained &#8211; until now. And a trail of clues revealed corruption and cover-ups from Hollywood, to Washington, and beyond. </p>
<p>                    This is the untold story of the exotic tactics of surveillance and intimidation deployed by wealthy and connected men to threaten journalists, evade accountability and silence victims of abuse &#8211; and it&#8217;s the story of the women who risked everything to expose the truth and spark a global movement.</p>
<p>                    Both a spy thriller and a meticulous work of investigative journalism, Catch and Kill breaks devastating new stories about the rampant abuse of power &#8211; and sheds far-reaching light on investigations that shook the culture.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow/">Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</title>
		<link>/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ego]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If I could give each of you a graduation present, it would be this&#8211;the most inspiring book I&#8217;ve ever read. &#8211;Bill Gates A provocative history of violence&#8211;from the New York Times bestselling author of The Stuff of Thought, The Blank Slate, and Enlightenment Now. Believe it or not, today we may be living in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/">The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If I could give each of you a graduation present, it would be this&#8211;the most inspiring book I&#8217;ve ever read. &#8211;Bill Gates     </p>
<p>                    A provocative history of violence&#8211;from the New York Times bestselling author of The Stuff of Thought, The Blank Slate,  and Enlightenment Now.    </p>
<p>                    Believe it or not, today we may be living in the most peaceful moment in our species&#8217; existence. In his gripping and controversial new work, New York Times bestselling author Steven Pinker shows that despite the ceaseless news about war, crime, and terrorism, violence has actually been in decline over long stretches of history. Exploding myths about humankind&#8217;s inherent violence and the curse of modernity, this ambitious book continues Pinker&#8217;s exploration of the essence of human nature, mixing psychology and history to provide a remarkable picture of an increasingly enlightened world.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/">The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mobbing is a destructive social process in which individuals, groups, or organizations target a person for ridicule, humiliation, and removal from the workplace. It can lead to deteriorating physical and mental health, workplace violence, and even suicide. Studies indicate that as many as 37% of American workers have experienced workplace abuse at some time in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/">Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mobbing is a destructive social process in which individuals, groups, or organizations target a person for ridicule, humiliation, and removal from the workplace. It can lead to deteriorating physical and mental health, workplace violence, and even suicide. Studies indicate that as many as 37% of American workers have experienced workplace abuse at some time in their working lives.    </p>
<p>                    Overcoming Mobbing is an informative, comprehensive guidebook written for the victims of mobbing and their families who often can&#8217;t make sense of the experience or mobilize resources for recovery. In an engaging, reader-friendly style, the book distinguishes mobbing from bullying in that it takes place within organizational or institutional settings and involves organizational dynamics. Mobbing is not about the occasional negative experience at work; it is ongoing negative acts, both<br />
                    overt and covert, over time, that erode workers&#8217; confidence in themselves and in their workplaces and that no amount of sophistication or maturity can make sense of.  Duffy and Sperry, leading authorities on this special type of aggression, provide effective strategies for recovery from mobbing as well as for<br />
                    prevention, and they demystify the experience through the use of case vignettes. More than a simple self-help book, this volume brings the concept and terminology relating to mobbing into the public vocabulary by virtue of its strong foundation in psychological and organizational research. It offers a detailed presentation of the causes and consequences of mobbing, helps readers avoid falling into the trap of misplacing blame, and holds organizations at the center of responsibility for<br />
                    preventing the abuse. In addition to those who have experienced mobbing themselves, this book is an invaluable resource for workplace managers and human resources personnel who wish to prevent or reverse mobbing within their own professional settings.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/overcoming-mobbing-a-recovery-guide-for-workplace-aggression-and-bullying-maureen-duffy-len-sperry-abridged/">Overcoming Mobbing : A Recovery Guide for Workplace Aggression and Bullying &#8211; Maureen Duffy, Len Sperry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Asking for It : The Alarming Rise of Rape Culture&#8211;and What We Can Do about It &#8211; Kate Harding (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/asking-for-it-the-alarming-rise-of-rape-culture-and-what-we-can-do-about-it-kate-harding-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/asking-for-it-the-alarming-rise-of-rape-culture-and-what-we-can-do-about-it-kate-harding-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Every seven minutes, someone in America commits a rape. And whether that&#8217;s a football star, beloved celebrity, elected official, member of the clergy, or just an average Joe (or Joanna), there&#8217;s probably a community eager to make excuses for that person.In Asking for It , Kate Harding combines in-depth research with an in-your-face voice to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/asking-for-it-the-alarming-rise-of-rape-culture-and-what-we-can-do-about-it-kate-harding-abridged/">Asking for It : The Alarming Rise of Rape Culture&#8211;and What We Can Do about It &#8211; Kate Harding (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every seven minutes, someone in America commits a rape. And whether that&#8217;s a football star, beloved celebrity, elected official, member of the clergy, or just an average Joe (or Joanna), there&#8217;s probably a community eager to make excuses for that person.In  Asking for It , Kate Harding combines in-depth research with an in-your-face voice to make the case that twenty-first-century America supports rapists more effectively than it supports victims. Drawing on real-world examples of what feminists call &#8220;rape culture&#8221;,from politicos&#8217; revealing gaffes to institutional failures in higher education and the military,Harding offers ideas and suggestions for how we, as a society, can take sexual violence much more seriously without compromising the rights of the accused.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/asking-for-it-the-alarming-rise-of-rape-culture-and-what-we-can-do-about-it-kate-harding-abridged/">Asking for It : The Alarming Rise of Rape Culture&#8211;and What We Can Do about It &#8211; Kate Harding (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gift of Fear : Survival Signals That Protect Us from Violence &#8211; Gavin de Becker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-gift-of-fear-survival-signals-that-protect-us-from-violence-gavin-de-becker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gift-of-fear-survival-signals-that-protect-us-from-violence-gavin-de-becker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this empowering book, Gavin de Becker, the man Oprah Winfrey calls the US&#8217; leading expert on violent behaviour, shows you how to spot even subtle signs of danger &#8211; before it&#8217;s too late. Shattering the myth that most violent acts are unpredictable, de Becker, whose clients include top Hollywood stars and government agencies, offers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gift-of-fear-survival-signals-that-protect-us-from-violence-gavin-de-becker-abridged/">The Gift of Fear : Survival Signals That Protect Us from Violence &#8211; Gavin de Becker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this empowering book, Gavin de Becker, the man Oprah Winfrey calls the US&#8217; leading expert on violent behaviour, shows you how to spot even subtle signs of danger &#8211; before it&#8217;s too late. Shattering the myth that most violent acts are unpredictable, de Becker, whose clients include top Hollywood stars and government agencies, offers specific ways to protect yourself and those you love, including: how to act when approached by a stranger; when you should fear someone close to you; what to do if you are being stalked; how to uncover the source of anonymous threats or phone calls; the biggest mistake you can make with a threatening person; and more. You can learn to spot the danger signals others miss. It might just save your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gift-of-fear-survival-signals-that-protect-us-from-violence-gavin-de-becker-abridged/">The Gift of Fear : Survival Signals That Protect Us from Violence &#8211; Gavin de Becker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a dramatic account of violence and espionage, Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter Ronan Farrow exposes serial abusers and a cabal of powerful interests hell-bent on covering up the truth, at any cost. In 2017, a routine network television investigation led Ronan Farrow to a story only whispered about: one of Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful producers was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow-abridged/">Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a dramatic account of violence and espionage, Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter Ronan Farrow exposes serial abusers and a cabal of powerful interests hell-bent on covering up the truth, at any cost.    </p>
<p>                    In 2017, a routine network television investigation led Ronan Farrow to a story only whispered about: one of Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful producers was a predator, protected by fear, wealth, and a conspiracy of silence. As Farrow drew closer to the truth, shadowy operatives, from high-priced lawyers to elite war-hardened spies, mounted a secret campaign of intimidation, threatening his career, following his every move and weaponizing an account of abuse in his own family.     </p>
<p>                    All the while, Farrow and his producer faced a degree of resistance that could not be explained &#8211; until now. And a trail of clues revealed corruption and cover-ups from Hollywood, to Washington, and beyond.     </p>
<p>                    This is the untold story of the exotic tactics of surveillance and intimidation deployed by wealthy and connected men to threaten journalists, evade accountability and silence victims of abuse &#8211; and it&#8217;s the story of the women who risked everything to expose the truth and spark a global movement.    </p>
<p>                    Both a spy thriller and a meticulous work of investigative journalism, Catch and Kill breaks devastating new stories about the rampant abuse of power &#8211; and sheds far-reaching light on investigations that shook the culture.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow-abridged/">Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>From #blacklivesmatter To Black Liberation &#8211; Keeanga-Yamahtta Taylor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/from-blacklivesmatter-to-black-liberation-keeanga-yamahtta-taylor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/from-blacklivesmatter-to-black-liberation-keeanga-yamahtta-taylor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With the slogan of &#8216;Black Lives Matter&#8217;, a burgeoning movement has awakened a new generation of activists. In this stirring and insightful analysis, activist and scholar Keeanga-Yamahtta Taylor surveys the historical and contemporary ravages of racism and argues that the persistence of structural problems such as mass incarceration and Black unemployment have created a context [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/from-blacklivesmatter-to-black-liberation-keeanga-yamahtta-taylor-abridged/">From #blacklivesmatter To Black Liberation &#8211; Keeanga-Yamahtta Taylor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the slogan of &#8216;Black Lives Matter&#8217;, a burgeoning movement has awakened a new generation of activists. In this stirring and insightful analysis, activist and scholar Keeanga-Yamahtta Taylor surveys the historical and contemporary ravages of racism and argues that the persistence of structural problems such as mass incarceration and Black unemployment have created a context in which this new struggle against police violence holds the potential to reignite a broader push for Black liberation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/from-blacklivesmatter-to-black-liberation-keeanga-yamahtta-taylor-abridged/">From #blacklivesmatter To Black Liberation &#8211; Keeanga-Yamahtta Taylor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Professor in the Cage : Why Men Fight and Why We Like to Watch &#8211; Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-professor-in-the-cage-why-men-fight-and-why-we-like-to-watch-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Combat Sports & Self-defence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Sport & Leisure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-professor-in-the-cage-why-men-fight-and-why-we-like-to-watch-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An English professor starts training in mixed martial arts, exploring the science and history behind the violence of men When a mixed martial arts (MMA) gym opens across the street from his office, Jonathan Gottschall sees a challenge. Pushing forty, out of shape, and disenchanted with his job as an adjunct English professor, he works [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-professor-in-the-cage-why-men-fight-and-why-we-like-to-watch-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/">The Professor in the Cage : Why Men Fight and Why We Like to Watch &#8211; Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An English professor starts training in mixed martial arts, exploring the science and history behind the violence of men    </p>
<p>                     When a mixed martial arts (MMA) gym opens across the street from his office, Jonathan Gottschall sees a challenge. Pushing forty, out of shape, and disenchanted with his job as an adjunct English professor, he works up his nerve and finds himself training for an all-out cage fight. He sees it not just as a personal test, but also as an opportunity to answer questions that have intrigued him for years: Why do men fight? And why do so many seemingly decent people love to watch?    </p>
<p>                     In The Professor in the Cage, Gottschall&#8217;s unlikely journey from the college classroom to the fighting cage drives an important new investigation into the science and history of violence. The surging popularity of MMA-a full-contact sport in which fighters punch, choke, and kick each other into submission-is just one example of our species&#8217; insatiable interest both in violence and in the rituals that keep violence in check. From duels to football to the roughhousing of children, humans are masters of what Gottschall calls the monkey dance: a dizzying variety of rule-bound contests that establish hierarchies while minimizing risk and social disorder. Gottschall&#8217;s unsparing odyssey-through extremes of pain, occasional humiliation, his wife&#8217;s incredulity, and ultimately his own cage fight-opens his, and our, eyes to the uncomfortable truth that, as brutal as these contests can be, the world would be a much more chaotic and dangerous place without them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-professor-in-the-cage-why-men-fight-and-why-we-like-to-watch-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/">The Professor in the Cage : Why Men Fight and Why We Like to Watch &#8211; Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In the Name of Identity : Violence and the Need to Belong &#8211; Amin Maalouf, Translated by Professor Barbara Bray (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-the-name-of-identity-violence-and-the-need-to-belong-amin-maalouf-translated-by-professor-barbara-bray-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-the-name-of-identity-violence-and-the-need-to-belong-amin-maalouf-translated-by-professor-barbara-bray-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Makes for compelling reading in America today.&#8221;&#8211;New York Times Book Review. &#8220;I want to try and understand why so many people commit crimes in the name of identity,&#8221; writes Amin Maalouf. Identity is the crucible out of which we come: our background, our race, our gender, our tribal affiliations, our religion (or lack thereof), all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-the-name-of-identity-violence-and-the-need-to-belong-amin-maalouf-translated-by-professor-barbara-bray-abridged/">In the Name of Identity : Violence and the Need to Belong &#8211; Amin Maalouf, Translated by Professor Barbara Bray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Makes for compelling reading in America today.&#8221;&#8211;New York Times Book Review.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I want to try and understand why so many people commit crimes in the name of identity,&#8221; writes Amin Maalouf. Identity is the crucible out of which we come: our background, our race, our gender, our tribal affiliations, our religion (or lack thereof), all go into making up who we are. All too often, however, the notion of identity&#8211;personal, religious, ethnic, or national&#8211;has given rise to heated passions and even massive crimes.     </p>
<p>                    Moving across the world&#8217;s history, faiths, and politics, he argues against an oversimplified and hostile interpretation of the concept. He cogently and persuasively examines identity in the context of the modern world, where it can be viewed as both glory and poison. Evident here are the dangers of using identity as a protective&#8211;and therefore aggressive&#8211;mechanism, the root of racial, geographical, and colonialist subjugation throughout history.     </p>
<p>                    Maalouf contends that many of us would reject our inherited conceptions of identity, to which we cling through habit, if only we examined them more closely. The future of society depends on accepting all identities, while recognizing our individualism.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-the-name-of-identity-violence-and-the-need-to-belong-amin-maalouf-translated-by-professor-barbara-bray-abridged/">In the Name of Identity : Violence and the Need to Belong &#8211; Amin Maalouf, Translated by Professor Barbara Bray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Locust Effect : Why the End of Poverty Requires the End of Violence &#8211; Gary A. Haugen, Victor Boutros (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-locust-effect-why-the-end-of-poverty-requires-the-end-of-violence-gary-a-haugen-victor-boutros-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Armed Conflict]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Human Rights Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-locust-effect-why-the-end-of-poverty-requires-the-end-of-violence-gary-a-haugen-victor-boutros-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Washington Post bestseller While the world has made encouraging strides in the fight against global poverty, there is a hidden crisis silently undermining our best efforts to help the poor. It is a plague of everyday violence. Beneath the surface of the world&#8217;s poorest communities, common violence &#8211; like rape, forced labor, illegal detention, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-locust-effect-why-the-end-of-poverty-requires-the-end-of-violence-gary-a-haugen-victor-boutros-abridged/">The Locust Effect : Why the End of Poverty Requires the End of Violence &#8211; Gary A. Haugen, Victor Boutros (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Washington Post bestseller    </p>
<p>                    While the world has made encouraging strides in the fight against global poverty, there is a hidden crisis silently undermining our best efforts to help the poor.     </p>
<p>                    It is a plague of everyday violence.    </p>
<p>                    Beneath the surface of the world&#8217;s poorest communities, common violence &#8211; like rape, forced labor, illegal detention, land theft, police abuse and other brutality &#8211; has become routine and relentless.  And like a horde of locusts devouring everything in their path, the unchecked plague of violence ruins lives, blocks the road out of poverty, and undercuts development.     </p>
<p>                    How has this plague of violence grown so ferocious? The answer is terrifying, and startlingly simple: There&#8217;s nothing shielding the poor from violent people.  In one of the most remarkable &#8211; and unremarked upon &#8211; social disasters of the last half century, basic public justice systems in the developing world have descended into a state of utter collapse.     </p>
<p>                    Gary A. Haugen and Victor Boutros offer a searing account of how we got here &#8211; and what it will take to end the plague. Filled with vivid real-life stories and startling new data, The Locust Effect is a gripping journey into the streets and slums where fear is a daily reality for billions of the world&#8217;s poorest ,where safety is secured only for those with money, and where much of our well-intended aid is lost in the daily chaos of violence.    </p>
<p>                    While their call to action is urgent, Haugen and Boutros provide hope, a real solution and an ambitious way forward. The Locust Effect is a wake-up call: Its massive implications will forever change the way we understand global poverty &#8211; and will help secure a safe path to prosperity for the global poor in the 21st century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-locust-effect-why-the-end-of-poverty-requires-the-end-of-violence-gary-a-haugen-victor-boutros-abridged/">The Locust Effect : Why the End of Poverty Requires the End of Violence &#8211; Gary A. Haugen, Victor Boutros (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The True Believer : Thoughts on the Nature of Mass Movements &#8211; Eric Hoffer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-true-believer-thoughts-on-the-nature-of-mass-movements-eric-hoffer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-true-believer-thoughts-on-the-nature-of-mass-movements-eric-hoffer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Its theme is political fanaticism, with which it deals severely and brilliantly.&#8221; -New Yorker The famous bestseller with &#8220;concise insight into what drives the mind of the fanatic and the dynamics of a mass movement&#8221; (Wall St. Journal) by the legendary San Francisco longshoreman. A stevedore on the San Francisco docks in the 1940s, Eric [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-true-believer-thoughts-on-the-nature-of-mass-movements-eric-hoffer-abridged/">The True Believer : Thoughts on the Nature of Mass Movements &#8211; Eric Hoffer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Its theme is political fanaticism, with which it deals severely and brilliantly.&#8221;   -New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    The famous bestseller with &#8220;concise insight into what drives the mind of the fanatic and the dynamics of a mass movement&#8221; (Wall St. Journal) by the legendary San Francisco longshoreman.    </p>
<p>                    A stevedore on the San Francisco docks in the 1940s, Eric Hoffer wrote philosophical treatises in his spare time while living in the railroad yards. The True Believer-the first and most famous of his books-was made into a bestseller when President Eisenhower cited it during one of the earliest television press conferences.    </p>
<p>                    Called a &#8220;brilliant and original inquiry&#8221; and &#8220;a genuine contribution to our social thought&#8221; by Arthur Schlesinger, Jr., this landmark in the field of social psychology is completely relevant and essential for understanding the world today as it delivers a visionary, highly provocative look into the mind of the fanatic and a penetrating study of how an individual becomes one.    </p>
<p>                    In times of crisis, the great works of philosophy help us make sense of the world. This book is part of the Harper Perennial Resistance Library, a special five-book series highlighting short classic works of independent thought that illuminate the nature of truth, humanity&#8217;s dangerous attraction to authoritarianism, the influence of media and mass communication, and the philosophy of resistance-all critical in understanding today&#8217;s politically charged world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-true-believer-thoughts-on-the-nature-of-mass-movements-eric-hoffer-abridged/">The True Believer : Thoughts on the Nature of Mass Movements &#8211; Eric Hoffer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are mass violence and catastrophes the only forces that can seriously decrease economic inequality? To judge by thousands of years of history, the answer is yes. Tracing the global history of inequality from the Stone Age to today, Walter Scheidel shows that it never dies peacefully. The Great Leveler is the first book to chart [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/">The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are mass violence and catastrophes the only forces that can seriously decrease economic inequality? To judge by thousands of years of history, the answer is yes. Tracing the global history of inequality from the Stone Age to today, Walter Scheidel shows that it never dies peacefully. The Great Leveler is the first book to chart the crucial role of violent shocks in reducing inequality over the full sweep of human history around the world. The &#8220;Four Horsemen&#8221; of leveling-mass-mobilization warfare, transformative revolutions, state collapse, and catastrophic plagues-have repeatedly destroyed the fortunes of the rich. Today, the violence that reduced inequality in the past seems to have diminished, and that is a good thing. But it casts serious doubt on the prospects for a more equal future. An essential contribution to the debate about inequality, The Great Leveler provides important new insights about why inequality is so persistent-and why it is unlikely to decline anytime soon.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/">The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
