<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Travel &amp; Holiday Guides Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/travel-holiday-guides/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/travel-holiday-guides/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Travel &amp; Holiday Guides Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/travel-holiday-guides/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Take Me Back to Italy &#8211; Baby Professor</title>
		<link>/take-me-back-to-italy-baby-professor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Geography Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geography Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/take-me-back-to-italy-baby-professor/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Italy is a foreign country and their culture and traditions might be different than yours. But if you are aware of these differences, you will be better guided on what to expect when you actually go for a visit. Geography is a fun topic to study, if you take one region at a time. So [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/take-me-back-to-italy-baby-professor/">Take Me Back to Italy &#8211; Baby Professor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Italy is a foreign country and their culture and traditions might be different than yours. But if you are aware of these differences, you will be better guided on what to expect when you actually go for a visit. Geography is a fun topic to study, if you take one region at a time. So go ahead and grab a copy of this book today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/take-me-back-to-italy-baby-professor/">Take Me Back to Italy &#8211; Baby Professor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food    </p>
<p>                    There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; whole grains are healthy, whole grains are a disaster; eat everything in moderation; eat only certain foods&#8212;and on and on. In 100 Million Years of Food, biological anthropologist Stephen Le explains how cuisines of different cultures are a result of centuries of evolution, finely tuned to our biology and surroundings. Today many cultures have strayed from their ancestral diets, relying instead on mass-produced food often made with chemicals that may be contributing to a rise in so-called Western diseases, such as cancer, heart disease, and obesity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tips & Advice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Maps & Atlases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With a new foreword by Tim Ferriss &#8211; &#8220;Vagabonding easily remains in my top-10 list of life-changing books. Why? Because one incredible trip, especially a long-term trip, can change your life forever. And Vagabonding teaches you how to travel (and think), not just for one trip, but for the rest of your life.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Ferriss, from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With a new foreword by Tim Ferriss &#8211; &#8220;Vagabonding easily remains in my top-10 list of life-changing books. Why? Because one incredible trip, especially a long-term trip, can change your life forever. And Vagabonding teaches you how to travel (and think), not just for one trip, but for the rest of your life.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Ferriss, from the foreword     </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s nothing like vagabonding: taking time off from your normal life&#8211;from six weeks to four months to two years&#8211;to discover and experience the world on your own terms. In this one-of-a-kind handbook, veteran travel writer Rolf Potts explains how anyone armed with an independent spirit can achieve the dream of extended overseas travel. Now completely revised and updated, Vagabonding is an accessible and inspiring guide to     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; financing your travel time<br />
                     &#8211; determining your destination<br />
                     &#8211; adjusting to life on the road<br />
                     &#8211; working and volunteering overseas<br />
                     &#8211; handling travel adversity<br />
                     &#8211; re-assimilating back into ordinary life     </p>
<p>                     Praise for Vagabonding    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A crucial reference for any budget wanderer.&#8221;&#8211;Time    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The book is a meditation on the joys of hitting the road. . . . It&#8217;s also a primer for those with a case of pent-up wanderlust seeking to live the dream.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I couldn&#8217;t put this book down. It&#8217;s a whole different ethic of travel. . . . [Potts&#8217;s] practical advice might just convince you to enjoy that open-ended trip of a lifetime.&#8221;&#8211;Rick Steves     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Potts wants us to wander, to explore, to embrace the unknown, and, finally, to take our own damn time about it. I think this is the most sensible book of travel-related advice ever written.&#8221;&#8211;Tim Cahill, founding editor of Outside</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vagabonding-an-uncommon-guide-to-the-art-of-long-term-world-travel-rolf-potts-foreword-by-timothy-ferriss-abridged/">Vagabonding : An Uncommon Guide to the Art of Long-Term World Travel &#8211; Rolf Potts, Foreword by Timothy Ferriss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Travel as a Political Act (Third Edition) &#8211; Rick Steves (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/travel-as-a-political-act-third-edition-rick-steves-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/travel-as-a-political-act-third-edition-rick-steves-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the world through travel is a vital way to shape our political views and our social awareness. These days, it&#8217;s more important than ever to engage in travel as an activist. In this fully revised edition of his award-winning book Travel as a Political Act, acclaimed author and activist Rick Steves explains how to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/travel-as-a-political-act-third-edition-rick-steves-abridged/">Travel as a Political Act (Third Edition) &#8211; Rick Steves (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the world through travel is a vital way to shape our political views and our social awareness. These days, it&#8217;s more important than ever to engage in travel as an activist.    </p>
<p>                    In this fully revised edition of his award-winning book Travel as a Political Act, acclaimed author and activist Rick Steves explains how to travel thoughtfully and honestly, and to come home with a better understanding of how our nation fits into a universal puzzle. In Rick&#8217;s own words, travel connects us with nature, with culture, and most importantly, with people. When we experience the rest of the world, instead of fearing its diversity, we can learn to celebrate it.    </p>
<p>                    With entirely new chapters focused on the far-reaching impact of global events such as Brexit, Trump, and so much more, Rick shows readers how to travel with intention and an open mind. In times of political and cultural turmoil, his ardent philosophy rings truer than ever: beyond new experiences, great art, and tasty cuisine, travel emboldens us to become better citizens of this planet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/travel-as-a-political-act-third-edition-rick-steves-abridged/">Travel as a Political Act (Third Edition) &#8211; Rick Steves (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Travel &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy, From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER &#8216;Honest, funny and dripping with witty aphorisms. Extremely entertaining and enlightening [&#8230;] all the way to journey&#8217;s end&#8217; Herald One of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy, Religion for Atheists and The School of Life, presents a travel guide [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Art of Travel &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Honest, funny and dripping with witty aphorisms. Extremely entertaining and enlightening [&#8230;] all the way to journey&#8217;s end&#8217; Herald     </p>
<p>                    One of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy, Religion for Atheists and The School of Life, presents a travel guide with a difference &#8211; an exploration of why we travel, and what we learn along the way&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Few activities seem to promise as much happiness as going travelling: taking off for somewhere else, somewhere far from home, a place with more interesting weather, customs and landscapes. But although we are inundated with advice on where to travel to, we seldom ask why we go and how we might become more fulfilled by doing so.    </p>
<p>                    With the help of a selection of writers, artists and thinkers &#8211; including Flaubert, Edward Hopper, Wordsworth and Van Gogh &#8211; Alain de Botton provides invaluable insights into everything from holiday romance to hotel minibars, airports to sightseeing. The perfect antidote to those guides that tell us what to do when we get there, The Art of Travel tries to explain why we really went in the first place &#8211; and helpfully suggest how we might be happier on our journeys.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Delightful, profound, entertaining. I doubt if de Botton has written a dull sentence in his life&#8217; Jan Morris    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An elegant and subtle work, unlike any other. Beguiling&#8217; Colin Thubron, The Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Art of Travel &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
