<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Computer Security Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/computer-security/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/computer-security/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Computer Security Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/computer-security/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Social Engineering : The Science of Human Hacking &#8211; Christopher Hadnagy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/social-engineering-the-science-of-human-hacking-christopher-hadnagy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Network Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Privacy & Data Protection]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/social-engineering-the-science-of-human-hacking-christopher-hadnagy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Harden the human firewall against the most current threats Social Engineering: The Science of Human Hacking reveals the craftier side of the hacker&#8217;s repertoire-why hack into something when you could just ask for access? Undetectable by firewalls and antivirus software, social engineering relies on human fault to gain access to sensitive spaces; in this book, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-engineering-the-science-of-human-hacking-christopher-hadnagy-abridged/">Social Engineering : The Science of Human Hacking &#8211; Christopher Hadnagy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Harden the human firewall against the most current threats    </p>
<p>                     Social Engineering: The Science of Human Hacking reveals the craftier side of the hacker&#8217;s repertoire-why hack into something when you could just ask for access? Undetectable by firewalls and antivirus software, social engineering relies on human fault to gain access to sensitive spaces; in this book, renowned expert Christopher Hadnagy explains the most commonly-used techniques that fool even the most robust security personnel, and shows you how these techniques have been used in the past. The way that we make decisions as humans affects everything from our emotions to our security. Hackers, since the beginning of time, have figured out ways to exploit that decision making process and get you to take an action not in your best interest. This new Second Edition has been updated with the most current methods used by sharing stories, examples, and scientific study behind how those decisions are exploited.    </p>
<p>                     Networks and systems can be hacked, but they can also be protected; when the &#8220;system&#8221; in question is a human being, there is no software to fall back on, no hardware upgrade, no code that can lock information down indefinitely. Human nature and emotion is the secret weapon of the malicious social engineering, and this book shows you how to recognize, predict, and prevent this type of manipulation by taking you inside the social engineer&#8217;s bag of tricks.    </p>
<p>                    Examine the most common social engineering tricks used to gain access<br />
                    Discover which popular techniques generally don&#8217;t work in the real world<br />
                    Examine how our understanding of the science behind emotions and decisions can be used by social engineers<br />
                    Learn how social engineering factors into some of the biggest recent headlines<br />
                    Learn how to use these skills as a professional social engineer and secure your company    </p>
<p>                    Adopt effective counter-measures to keep hackers at bay    </p>
<p>                     By working from the social engineer&#8217;s playbook, you gain the advantage of foresight that can help you protect yourself and others from even their best efforts. Social Engineering gives you the inside information you need to mount an unshakeable defense.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-engineering-the-science-of-human-hacking-christopher-hadnagy-abridged/">Social Engineering : The Science of Human Hacking &#8211; Christopher Hadnagy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Viruses, Trojans & Worms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award! There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life. In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award!<br />
                    There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life.<br />
                    In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest spam and hacker operations targeting Americans and their bank accounts. Tracing the rise, fall, and alarming resurrection of the digital mafia behind the two largest spam pharmacies-and countless viruses, phishing, and spyware attacks-he delivers the first definitive narrative of the global spam problem and its threat to consumers everywhere.<br />
                    Blending cutting-edge research, investigative reporting, and firsthand interviews, this terrifying true story reveals how we unwittingly invite these digital thieves into our lives every day. From unassuming computer programmers right next door to digital mobsters like &#8220;Cosma&#8221;-who unleashed a massive malware attack that has stolen thousands of Americans&#8217; logins and passwords-Krebs uncovers the shocking lengths to which these people will go to profit from our data and our wallets.<br />
                    Not only are hundreds of thousands of Americans exposing themselves to fraud and dangerously toxic products from rogue online pharmacies, but even those who never open junk messages are at risk. As Krebs notes, spammers can-and do-hack into accounts through these emails, harvest personal information like usernames and passwords, and sell them on the digital black market. The fallout from this global epidemic doesn&#8217;t just cost consumers and companies billions, it costs lives too.<br />
                    Fast-paced and utterly gripping, Spam Nation ultimately proposes concrete solutions for protecting ourselves online and stemming this tidal wave of cybercrime-before it&#8217;s too late.<br />
                    &#8220;Krebs&#8217;s talent for exposing the weaknesses in online security has earned him respect in the IT business and loathing among cybercriminals&#8230; His track record of scoops&#8230;has helped him become the rare blogger who supports himself on the strength of his reputation for hard-nosed reporting.&#8221; -Bloomberg Businessweek</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tools and Weapons : The Promise and the Peril of the Digital Age &#8211; Brad Smith, Carol Ann Browne (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Certification: Microsoft (eg MCSE)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft Windows]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AND WORLD ECONOMIC FORUM BOOK CLUB PICK* &#8216;A clear, compelling guide to some of the most pressing debates in technology today.&#8217; Bill Gates &#8216;A colourful and insightful insiders&#8217; view of how technology is both empowering us and threatening us. From privacy to cyberattacks, this timely book is a useful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/">Tools and Weapons : The Promise and the Peril of the Digital Age &#8211; Brad Smith, Carol Ann Browne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AND WORLD ECONOMIC FORUM BOOK CLUB PICK*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A clear, compelling guide to some of the most pressing debates in technology today.&#8217; Bill Gates    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A colourful and insightful insiders&#8217; view of how technology is both empowering us and threatening us. From privacy to cyberattacks, this timely book is a useful guide for how to navigate the digital future.&#8217;  Walter Isaacson, bestselling author of Steve Jobs    </p>
<p>                    From Microsoft&#8217;s President and one of the tech industry&#8217;s wisest thinkers, a frank and thoughtful reckoning with how to balance enormous promise and existential risk as the digitization of everything accelerates. With new chapters on the pandemic and beyond.<br />
                    __________    </p>
<p>                    Microsoft President Brad Smith operates by a simple core belief: when your technology changes the world, you bear a responsibility to help address the world you have helped create.     </p>
<p>                    This might seem uncontroversial, but it flies in the face of a tech sector long obsessed with rapid growth and sometimes on disruption as an end in itself. While sweeping digital transformation holds great promise, we have reached an inflection point. The world has turned information technology into both a powerful tool and a formidable weapon, and new approaches are needed to manage an era defined by even more powerful inventions like artificial intelligence. Companies that create technology must accept greater responsibility for the future, and governments will need to regulate technology by moving faster and catching up with the pace of innovation.    </p>
<p>                    In Tools and Weapons, Brad Smith and Carol Ann Browne bring us a captivating narrative from the cockpit of one of the world&#8217;s largest and most powerful tech companies as it finds itself in the middle of some of the thorniest emerging issues of our time. These are challenges that come with no pre-existing playbook, including privacy, cybercrime and cyberwar, social media, the moral conundrums of artificial intelligence, big tech&#8217;s relationship to inequality, and the challenges for democracy, far and near. While in no way a self-glorifying &#8220;Microsoft memoir,&#8221; the book pulls back the curtain remarkably wide onto some of the company&#8217;s most crucial recent decision points as it strives to protect the hopes technology offers against the very real threats it also presents. There are huge ramifications for communities and countries, and Brad Smith provides a thoughtful and urgent contribution to that effort.    </p>
<p>                    __________    </p>
<p>                    In Tools and Weapons, Brad Smith takes us behind the scenes on some of the biggest stories to hit the tech industry in the past decade and some of the biggest threats we face. From Edward Snowden&#8217;s NSA leak to the NHS WannaCry ransomware attack, this book is essential reading to understand what&#8217;s happening in the world around us.    </p>
<p>                    Praise for Tools and Weapons:     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The de facto ambassador for the technology industry at large.&#8217; The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;In Tools and Weapons, Brad and Carol Ann Browne wrestle with some of the world&#8217;s toughest technology challenges with common sense and valuable insight reflecting their inside experience. The ideas in Tools and Weapons won&#8217;t solve all our problems, but they&#8217;re a very good place to start.&#8217; &#8211; Reed Hastings, CEO, Netflix    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Tools and Weapons is a glimpse behind the curtain as Microsoft reckoned with the Snowden revelations, defended against the vicious cyberattacks, and took both the Obama and Trump administrations to court.&#8217; &#8211; Rolling Stone</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/">Tools and Weapons : The Promise and the Peril of the Digital Age &#8211; Brad Smith, Carol Ann Browne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
