<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Ethics &amp; Moral Philosophy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/ethics-moral-philosophy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/ethics-moral-philosophy/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Ethics &amp; Moral Philosophy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/ethics-moral-philosophy/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Humankind : A Hopeful History &#8211; Rutger Bregman</title>
		<link>/humankind-a-hopeful-history-rutger-bregman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/humankind-a-hopeful-history-rutger-bregman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER A Guardian, Daily Telegraph, New Statesman and Daily Express Book of the Year &#8216;Hugely, highly and happily recommended&#8217; Stephen Fry &#8216;You should read Humankind. You&#8217;ll learn a lot (I did) and you&#8217;ll have good reason to feel better about the human race&#8217; Tim Harford &#8216;Made me see humanity from a fresh perspective&#8217; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humankind-a-hopeful-history-rutger-bregman/">Humankind : A Hopeful History &#8211; Rutger Bregman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER<br />
                    A Guardian, Daily Telegraph, New Statesman and Daily Express Book of the Year</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Hugely, highly and happily recommended&#8217; Stephen Fry<br />
                    &#8216;You should read Humankind. You&#8217;ll learn a lot (I did) and you&#8217;ll have good reason to feel better about the human race&#8217; Tim Harford<br />
                    &#8216;Made me see humanity from a fresh perspective&#8217; Yuval Noah Harari</p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s a belief that unites the left and right, psychologists and philosophers, writers and historians. It drives the headlines that surround us and the laws that touch our lives. From Machiavelli to Hobbes, Freud to Dawkins, the roots of this belief have sunk deep into Western thought. Human beings, we&#8217;re taught, are by nature selfish and governed by self-interest.</p>
<p>                    Humankind makes a new argument: that it is realistic, as well as revolutionary, to assume that people are good. By thinking the worst of others, we bring out the worst in our politics and economics too.</p>
<p>                    In this major book, internationally bestselling author Rutger Bregman takes some of the world&#8217;s most famous studies and events and reframes them, providing a new perspective on the last 200,000 years of human history. From the real-life Lord of the Flies to the Blitz, a Siberian fox farm to an infamous New York murder, Stanley Milgram&#8217;s Yale shock machine to the Stanford prison experiment, Bregman shows how believing in human kindness and altruism can be a new way to think &#8211; and act as the foundation for achieving true change in our society.</p>
<p>                    It is time for a new view of human nature.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humankind-a-hopeful-history-rutger-bregman/">Humankind : A Hopeful History &#8211; Rutger Bregman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enlightenment Now : The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress &#8211; Steven Pinker</title>
		<link>/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Enlightenment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP TEN SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Bristles with pure, crystalline intelligence, deep knowledge and human sympathy&#8217; Richard Dawkins Is modernity really failing? Or have we failed to appreciate progress and the ideals that make it possible? If you follow the headlines, the world in the 21st century appears to be sinking into chaos, hatred, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/">Enlightenment Now : The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP TEN SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Bristles with pure, crystalline intelligence, deep knowledge and human sympathy&#8217; Richard Dawkins  </p>
<p>                    Is modernity really failing? Or have we failed to appreciate progress and the ideals that make it possible?</p>
<p>                    If  you follow the headlines, the world in the 21st century appears to be  sinking into chaos, hatred, and irrationality. Yet Steven Pinker shows  that this is an illusion &#8211; a symptom of historical amnesia and  statistical fallacies. If you follow the trendlines rather than the  headlines, you discover that our lives have become longer, healthier,  safer, happier, more peaceful, more stimulating and more prosperous &#8211;  not just in the West, but worldwide. Such progress is no accident: it&#8217;s  the gift of a coherent and inspiring value system that many of us  embrace without even realizing it. These are the values of the  Enlightenment: of reason, science, humanism and progress.</p>
<p>                    The  challenges we face today are formidable, including inequality, climate  change, Artificial Intelligence and nuclear weapons. But the way to deal  with them is not to sink into despair or try to lurch back to a  mythical idyllic past; it&#8217;s to treat them as problems we can solve, as  we have solved other problems in the past. In making the case for an  Enlightenment newly recharged for the 21st century, Pinker shows how we  can use our faculties of reason and sympathy to solve the problems that  inevitably come with being products of evolution in an indifferent  universe. We will never have a perfect world, but &#8211; defying the chorus  of fatalism and reaction &#8211; we can continue to make it a better one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/">Enlightenment Now : The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Justice : What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? &#8211; Michael J. Sandel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/justice-whats-the-right-thing-to-do-michael-j-sandel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/justice-whats-the-right-thing-to-do-michael-j-sandel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Sandel&#8217;s Justice: What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? invites readers of all ages and political persuasions on a journey of moral reflection, and shows how reasoned debate can illuminate our lives. Is it always wrong to lie? Should there be limits to personal freedom? Can killing sometimes be justified? Is the free market fair? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/justice-whats-the-right-thing-to-do-michael-j-sandel-abridged/">Justice : What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? &#8211; Michael J. Sandel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Sandel&#8217;s Justice: What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? invites readers of all ages and political persuasions on a journey of moral reflection, and shows how reasoned debate can illuminate our lives.    </p>
<p>                    Is it always wrong to lie?<br />
                    Should there be limits to personal freedom?<br />
                    Can killing sometimes be justified?<br />
                    Is the free market fair?<br />
                    What is the right thing to do?    </p>
<p>                    Questions like these are at the heart of our lives. In this acclaimed book Michael Sandel &#8211; BBC Reith Lecturer and the Harvard professor whose &#8216;Justice&#8217; course has become world famous &#8211; gives us a lively and accessible introduction to the intersection of politics and philosophy. He helps us think our way through such hotly contested issues as equal rights, democracy, euthanasia, abortion and same-sex marriage, as well as the ethical dilemmas we face every day.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the most popular teachers in the world&#8217; &#8211; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Enormously refreshing &#8230; Michael Sandel transforms moral philosophy by putting it at the heart of civic debate&#8217; &#8211; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the world&#8217;s most interesting political philosophers&#8217; &#8211; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Spellbinding&#8217; &#8211; The Nation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/justice-whats-the-right-thing-to-do-michael-j-sandel-abridged/">Justice : What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? &#8211; Michael J. Sandel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Praise of Slowness : Challenging the Cult of Speed &#8211; Carl Honore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-praise-of-slowness-challenging-the-cult-of-speed-carl-honore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-praise-of-slowness-challenging-the-cult-of-speed-carl-honore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We live in the age of speed. We strain to be more efficient, to cram more into each minute, each hour, each day. Since the Industrial Revolution shifted the world into high gear, the cult of speed has pushed us to a breaking point. Consider these facts: Americans on average spend seventy-two minutes of every [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-praise-of-slowness-challenging-the-cult-of-speed-carl-honore-abridged/">In Praise of Slowness : Challenging the Cult of Speed &#8211; Carl Honore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We live in the age of speed. We strain to be more efficient, to cram more into each minute, each hour, each day. Since the Industrial Revolution shifted the world into high gear, the cult of speed has pushed us to a breaking point. Consider these facts: Americans on average spend seventy-two minutes of every day behind the wheel of a car, a typical business executive now loses sixty-eight hours a year to being put on hold, and American adults currently devote on average a mere half hour per week to making love.    </p>
<p>                    Living on the edge of exhaustion, we are constantly reminded by our bodies and minds that the pace of life is spinning out of control. In Praise of Slowness traces the history of our increasingly breathless relationship with time and tackles the consequences of living in this accelerated culture of our own creation. Why are we always in such a rush? What is the cure for time sickness? Is it possible, or even desirable, to slow down? Realizing the price we pay for unrelenting speed, people all over the world are reclaiming their time and slowing down the pace &#8212; and living happier, healthier, and more productive lives as a result. A Slow revolution is taking place.    </p>
<p>                    Here you will find no Luddite calls to overthrow technology and seek a preindustrial utopia. This is a modern revolution, championed by cell-phone using, e-mailing lovers of sanity. The Slow philosophy can be summed up in a single word &#8212; balance. People are discovering energy and efficiency where they may have been least expected &#8212; in slowing down.    </p>
<p>                    In this engaging and entertaining exploration, award-winning journalist and rehabilitated speedaholic Carl Honoré details our perennial love affair with efficiency and speed in a perfect blend of anecdotal reportage, history, and intellectual inquiry. In Praise of Slowness is the first comprehensive look at the worldwide Slow movements making their way into the mainstream &#8212; in offices, factories, neighborhoods, kitchens, hospitals, concert halls, bedrooms, gyms, and schools. Defining a movement that is here to stay, this spirited manifesto will make you completely rethink your relationship with time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-praise-of-slowness-challenging-the-cult-of-speed-carl-honore-abridged/">In Praise of Slowness : Challenging the Cult of Speed &#8211; Carl Honore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Ideals : The Real Story of Moral Choice &#8211; William Damon, Anne Colby (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-ideals-the-real-story-of-moral-choice-william-damon-anne-colby-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-ideals-the-real-story-of-moral-choice-william-damon-anne-colby-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cynicism often seems a smarter choice than idealism, and there are seemingly good reasons for this. Politicians have disappointed us time and again, trusted institutions have proven silf-serving and corrupt, and social inequities persist and increase, unabated by even the grandest of charitable efforts. Moreover, trends in contemporrary moral psychology support this bleak view of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-ideals-the-real-story-of-moral-choice-william-damon-anne-colby-abridged/">The Power of Ideals : The Real Story of Moral Choice &#8211; William Damon, Anne Colby (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cynicism often seems a smarter choice than idealism, and there are seemingly good reasons for this. Politicians have disappointed us time and again, trusted institutions have proven silf-serving and corrupt, and social inequities persist and increase, unabated by even the grandest of charitable efforts. Moreover, trends in contemporrary moral psychology support this bleak view of the human condition. Famous studies have shown that we have an almost unlimited<br />
                    potential for cruelty when placed in the wrong situations. Other studies imply that our moral responses are dictated by inborn biological intuitions, or that people do little more than act out conventional cultural scripts when confronted with moral chices.    </p>
<p>                    The Power of Ideals presents a different vision, supported by a different kind of evidence. It examines the lives and work of six 20th century moral leaders who pursued moral causes ranging from world peace to social justice and human rights. Using these six cases to illustrate how people can make choices guided by their moral convictions, rather than by base emotion or social pressures, authors William Damon and Anne Colby explore the workings of three virtues: inner truthfulness,<br />
                    humility, and faith. Through their portrayal of the noble lives of moral leaders, the authors argue that everyone -including those of us   with ordinary lives &#8211; can exercise control over important life decisions and pursue ideals that inspire us. The Power of Ideals offers a hopeful and much-needed vision for<br />
                    moral progress in the worl.    </p>
<p>                    This message flies in the face of contemporary thought in moral psychology, much of which has drawn  mainstream media coverage in recent years. But the more accurate, constructive, and inspiring view in The Power of Ideals provides a sound basis for helping all people achieve their moral potentials. The Power of Ideals offers a needed and hopeful vision for personal well-being, for rebuilding trust among disillusioned citizens, for the flourishing of democracy, and for moral<br />
                    progress in the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-ideals-the-real-story-of-moral-choice-william-damon-anne-colby-abridged/">The Power of Ideals : The Real Story of Moral Choice &#8211; William Damon, Anne Colby (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consumerism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How does our economic system impact the way we live? Does it really affect what we truly care about? Oxford economist E. F. Schumacher provides an enlightening study of our economic system and its purpose, challenging the current state of excessive consumption in our society. Offering a crucial message for the modern world struggling to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/">Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How does our economic system impact the way we live? Does it really affect what we truly care about?     </p>
<p>                    Oxford economist E. F. Schumacher provides an enlightening study of our economic system and its purpose, challenging the current state of excessive consumption in our society. Offering a crucial message for the modern world struggling to balance economic growth with the human costs of globalisation, Small Is Beautiful puts forward the revolutionary yet viable case for building our economies around the needs of communities, not corporations.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the 100 most influential books published since World War II&#8217; The Times Literary Supplement</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/">Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Autobiography &#8211; M. K. Gandhi, Translated by Mahadev Desai, Introduction by Sunil Khilnani (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/an-autobiography-m-k-gandhi-translated-by-mahadev-desai-introduction-by-sunil-khilnani-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National Liberation & Independence, Post-colonialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-autobiography-m-k-gandhi-translated-by-mahadev-desai-introduction-by-sunil-khilnani-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Gandhi&#8217;s non-violent struggles against racism, violence, and colonialism in South Africa and India had brought him to such a level of notoriety, adulation that when asked to write an autobiography midway through his career, he took it as an opportunity to explain himself. He feared the enthusiasm for his ideas tended to exceed a deeper [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-autobiography-m-k-gandhi-translated-by-mahadev-desai-introduction-by-sunil-khilnani-abridged/">An Autobiography &#8211; M. K. Gandhi, Translated by Mahadev Desai, Introduction by Sunil Khilnani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gandhi&#8217;s non-violent struggles against racism, violence, and colonialism in South Africa and India had brought him to such a level of notoriety, adulation that when asked to write an autobiography midway through his career, he took it as an opportunity to explain himself.  He feared the enthusiasm for his ideas tended to exceed a deeper understanding of his quest for truth rooted in devotion to God. His attempts to get closer to this divine power led him to seek purity through simple living, dietary practices, celibacy, and a life without violence. This is not a straightforward narrative biography, in The Story of My Experiments with Truth, Gandhi offers his life story as a reference for those who would follow in his footsteps.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-autobiography-m-k-gandhi-translated-by-mahadev-desai-introduction-by-sunil-khilnani-abridged/">An Autobiography &#8211; M. K. Gandhi, Translated by Mahadev Desai, Introduction by Sunil Khilnani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Walden: Or, Life in the Woods &#8211; Henry David Thoreau (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/walden-or-life-in-the-woods-henry-david-thoreau-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Ecology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/walden-or-life-in-the-woods-henry-david-thoreau-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nature was a form of religion for naturalist, essayist, and early environmentalist Henry David Thoreau (1817-62). In communing with the natural world, he wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and &#8230; learn what it had to teach. Toward that end Thoreau built a cabin in the spring of 1845 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walden-or-life-in-the-woods-henry-david-thoreau-abridged/">Walden: Or, Life in the Woods &#8211; Henry David Thoreau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nature was a form of religion for naturalist, essayist, and early environmentalist Henry David Thoreau (1817-62). In communing with the natural world, he wished to live deliberately, to front only the essential facts of life, and &#8230; learn what it had to teach. Toward that end Thoreau built a cabin in the spring of 1845 on the shores of Walden Pond &#8212; on land owned by Ralph Waldo Emerson &#8212; outside Concord, Massachusetts. There he observed nature, farmed, built fences, surveyed, and wrote in his journal.<br />
                    One product of his two-year sojourn was this book &#8212; a great classic of American letters. Interwoven with accounts of Thoreau&#8217;s daily life (he received visitors and almost daily walked into Concord) are mediations on human existence, society, government, and other topics, expressed with wisdom and beauty of style.<br />
                    Walden offers abundant evidence of Thoreau&#8217;s ability to begin with observations on a mundane incident or the minutiae of nature and then develop these observations into profound ruminations on the most fundamental human concerns. Credited with influencing Tolstoy, Gandhi, and other thinkers, the volume remains a masterpiece of philosophical reflection.<br />
                    A selection of the Common Core State Standards Initiative.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/walden-or-life-in-the-woods-henry-david-thoreau-abridged/">Walden: Or, Life in the Woods &#8211; Henry David Thoreau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conscious : A Brief Guide to the Fundamental Mystery of the Mind &#8211; Annaka Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/conscious-a-brief-guide-to-the-fundamental-mystery-of-the-mind-annaka-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conscious & Unconscious]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance, C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/conscious-a-brief-guide-to-the-fundamental-mystery-of-the-mind-annaka-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8220;If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how you have the capacity to wonder, some fascinating insights await you in these pages.&#8221; &#8211;Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of Originals As concise and enlightening as Seven Brief Lessons on Physics and Astrophysics for People in a Hurry, this mind-expanding dive into the mystery [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conscious-a-brief-guide-to-the-fundamental-mystery-of-the-mind-annaka-harris-abridged/">Conscious : A Brief Guide to the Fundamental Mystery of the Mind &#8211; Annaka Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how you have the capacity to wonder, some fascinating insights await you in these pages.&#8221; &#8211;Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    As concise and enlightening as Seven Brief Lessons on Physics and Astrophysics for People in a Hurry, this mind-expanding dive into the mystery of consciousness is an illuminating meditation on the self, free will, and felt experience.    </p>
<p>                    What is consciousness? How does it arise? And why does it exist? We take our experience of being in the world for granted. But the very existence of consciousness raises profound questions: Why would any collection of matter in the universe be conscious? How are we able to think about this? And why should we?    </p>
<p>                    In this wonderfully accessible book, Annaka Harris guides us through the evolving definitions, philosophies, and scientific findings that probe our limited understanding of consciousness. Where does it reside, and what gives rise to it? Could it be an illusion, or a universal property of all matter? As we try to understand consciousness, we must grapple with how to define it and, in the age of artificial intelligence, who or what might possess it.     </p>
<p>                    Conscious offers lively and challenging arguments that alter our ideas about consciousness-allowing us to think freely about it for ourselves, if indeed we can.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conscious-a-brief-guide-to-the-fundamental-mystery-of-the-mind-annaka-harris-abridged/">Conscious : A Brief Guide to the Fundamental Mystery of the Mind &#8211; Annaka Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Wisdom of Life &#8211; Arthur Schopenhauer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-wisdom-of-life-arthur-schopenhauer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wisdom-of-life-arthur-schopenhauer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A leading German metaphysician of the 19th century, Arthur Schopenhauer (1788-1860) exerted an influence far beyond the hermetic world of philosophy, with adherents ranging from Richard Wagner and Friedrich Nietzsche to Leo Tolstoy and Thomas Mann. Among Schopenhauer&#8217;s chief contributions to the field of philosophy are his rejection of the idealism of his contemporaries and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wisdom-of-life-arthur-schopenhauer-abridged/">The Wisdom of Life &#8211; Arthur Schopenhauer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A leading German metaphysician of the 19th century, Arthur Schopenhauer (1788-1860) exerted an influence far beyond the hermetic world of philosophy, with adherents ranging from Richard Wagner and Friedrich Nietzsche to Leo Tolstoy and Thomas Mann. Among Schopenhauer&#8217;s chief contributions to the field of philosophy are his rejection of the idealism of his contemporaries and his embrace of a practical variety of materialism. He jettisons the traditional philosophic jargon for a brisk, compelling style that employs direct terms to express the metaphysics of the will.<br />
                    In The Wisdom of Life, an essay from Schopenhauer&#8217;s final work, Parerga und Paralipomena (1851), the philosopher favors individual strength of will and independent, reasoned deliberation over the tendency to act on irrational impulses. He examines the ways in which life can be arranged to derive the highest degree of pleasure and success, presents guidelines to achieving this full and rich manner of living, and advises that even a life well lived must always aspire to grander heights. Abounding in subjects of enduring relevance, Schopenhauer&#8217;s highly readable work appears here in an excellent translation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wisdom-of-life-arthur-schopenhauer-abridged/">The Wisdom of Life &#8211; Arthur Schopenhauer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Guide to the Good Life : The Ancient Art of Stoic Joy &#8211; William B Irvine (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-guide-to-the-good-life-the-ancient-art-of-stoic-joy-william-b-irvine-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Ancient, To C 500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-guide-to-the-good-life-the-ancient-art-of-stoic-joy-william-b-irvine-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the great fears many of us face is that despite all our effort and striving, we will discover at the end that we have wasted our life. In A Guide to the Good Life, William B. Irvine plumbs the wisdom of Stoic philosophy, one of the most popular and successful schools of thought [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-guide-to-the-good-life-the-ancient-art-of-stoic-joy-william-b-irvine-abridged/">A Guide to the Good Life : The Ancient Art of Stoic Joy &#8211; William B Irvine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the great fears many of us face is that despite all our effort and striving, we will discover at the end that we have wasted our life. In A Guide to the Good Life, William B. Irvine plumbs the wisdom of Stoic philosophy, one of the most popular and successful schools of thought in ancient Rome, and shows how its insight and advice are still remarkably applicable to modern lives.<br />
                           In A Guide to the Good Life, Irvine offers a refreshing presentation of Stoicism, showing how this ancient philosophy can still direct us toward a better life. Using the psychological insights and the practical techniques of the Stoics, Irvine offers a roadmap for anyone seeking to avoid the feelings of chronic dissatisfaction that plague so many of us. Irvine looks at various Stoic techniques for attaining tranquility and shows how to put these techniques to work in our own<br />
                    life. As he does so, he describes his own experiences practicing Stoicism and offers valuable first-hand advice for anyone wishing to live better by following in the footsteps of these ancient philosophers. Readers learn how to minimize worry, how to let go of the past and focus our efforts on the things we can<br />
                    control, and how to deal with insults, grief, old age, and the distracting temptations of fame and fortune. We learn from Marcus Aurelius the importance of prizing only things of true value, and from Epictetus we learn how to be more content with what we have.<br />
                            Finally, A Guide to the Good Life shows readers how to become thoughtful observers of their own life.  If we watch ourselves as we go about our daily business and later reflect on what we saw, we can better identify the sources of distress and eventually avoid that pain in our life. By doing this, the Stoics thought, we can hope to attain a truly joyful life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-guide-to-the-good-life-the-ancient-art-of-stoic-joy-william-b-irvine-abridged/">A Guide to the Good Life : The Ancient Art of Stoic Joy &#8211; William B Irvine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Common Good &#8211; Robert B. Reich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-common-good-robert-b-reich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-common-good-robert-b-reich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Robert B. Reich makes a powerful case for the expansion of America&#8217;s moral imagination. Rooting his argument in common sense and everyday reality, he demonstrates that a common good constitutes the very essence of any society or nation. Societies, he says, undergo virtuous cycles that reinforce the common good as well as vicious cycles that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-common-good-robert-b-reich-abridged/">The Common Good &#8211; Robert B. Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Robert B. Reich makes a powerful case for the expansion of America&#8217;s moral imagination. Rooting his argument in common sense and everyday reality, he demonstrates that a common good constitutes the very essence of any society or nation. Societies, he says, undergo virtuous cycles that reinforce the common good as well as vicious cycles that undermine it, one of which America has been experiencing for the past five decades. This process can and must be reversed. But first we need to weigh the moral obligations of citizenship and carefully consider how we relate to honor, shame, patriotism, truth, and the meaning of leadership.     </p>
<p>                     Powerful, urgent, and utterly vital, this is a heartfelt missive from one of our foremost political thinkers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-common-good-robert-b-reich-abridged/">The Common Good &#8211; Robert B. Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lying &#8211; Sam Harris, Edited by Annaka Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lying-sam-harris-edited-by-annaka-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lying-sam-harris-edited-by-annaka-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As it was in Anna Karenina, Madame Bovary, and Othello, so it is in life. Most forms of private vice and public evil are kindled and sustained by lies. Acts of adultery and other personal betrayals, financial fraud, government corruption&#8211;even murder and genocide&#8211;generally require an additional moral defect: a willingness to lie. In Lying, best-selling [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lying-sam-harris-edited-by-annaka-harris-abridged/">Lying &#8211; Sam Harris, Edited by Annaka Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As it was in Anna Karenina, Madame Bovary, and Othello, so it is in life. Most forms of private vice and public evil are kindled and sustained by lies. Acts of adultery and other personal betrayals, financial fraud, government corruption&#8211;even murder and genocide&#8211;generally require an additional moral defect: a willingness to lie.  In Lying, best-selling author and neuroscientist Sam Harris argues that we can radically simplify our lives and improve society by merely telling the truth in situations where others often lie. He focuses on &#8220;white&#8221; lies&#8211;those lies we tell for the purpose of sparing people discomfort&#8211;for these are the lies that most often tempt us. And they tend to be the only lies that good people tell while imagining that they are being good in the process.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lying-sam-harris-edited-by-annaka-harris-abridged/">Lying &#8211; Sam Harris, Edited by Annaka Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Free Will &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The physiologist Benjamin Libet famously demonstrated that activity in the brain&#8217;s motor regions can be detected some 300 milliseconds before a person feels that he has decided to move. Another lab recently used fMRI data to show that some &#8220;conscious&#8221; decisions can be predicted up to 10 seconds before they enter awareness (long before the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/">Free Will &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The physiologist Benjamin Libet famously demonstrated that activity in the brain&#8217;s motor regions can be detected some 300 milliseconds before a person feels that he has decided to move. Another lab recently used fMRI data to show that some &#8220;conscious&#8221; decisions can be predicted up to 10 seconds before they enter awareness (long before the preparatory motor activity detected by Libet). Clearly, findings of this kind are difficult to reconcile with the sense that one is the conscious source of one&#8217;s actions.     </p>
<p>                    The question of free will is no mere curio of philosophy seminars. A belief in free will underwrites both the religious notion of &#8220;sin&#8221; and our enduring commitment to retributive justice. The Supreme Court has called free will a &#8220;universal and persistent&#8221; foundation for our system of law. Any scientific developments that threatened our notion of free will would seem to put the ethics of punishing people for their bad behaviour in question.In Free Will Harris debates these ideas and asks whether or not, given what brain science is telling us, we actually have free will?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/">Free Will &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Intelligent Disobedience: Doing Right When What You&#8217;re Told to Do Is Wrong &#8211; Ira Chaleff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/intelligent-disobedience-doing-right-when-what-youre-told-to-do-is-wrong-ira-chaleff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/intelligent-disobedience-doing-right-when-what-youre-told-to-do-is-wrong-ira-chaleff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When It&#8217;s Smart to Say No Nearly every week we read about a tragedy or scandal that could have been prevented if individuals had said no to ill-advised or illegitimate orders. In this timely book, Ira Chaleff explores when and how to disobey inappropriate orders, reduce unacceptable risk, and find better ways to achieve legitimate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/intelligent-disobedience-doing-right-when-what-youre-told-to-do-is-wrong-ira-chaleff-abridged/">Intelligent Disobedience: Doing Right When What You&#8217;re Told to Do Is Wrong &#8211; Ira Chaleff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When It&#8217;s Smart to Say No     </p>
<p>                     Nearly every week we read about a tragedy or scandal that could have been prevented if individuals had said no to ill-advised or illegitimate orders. In this timely book, Ira Chaleff explores when and how to disobey inappropriate orders, reduce unacceptable risk, and find better ways to achieve legitimate goals.     </p>
<p>                     The inspiration for the book, and its title, comes from the concept of intelligent disobedience used in guide dog training. Guide dogs must recognize and resist a command that would put their human and themselves at risk and identify safer options for achieving the goal. This is precisely what Chaleff helps humans do. Using both deeply disturbing and uplifting examples, as well as critical but largely forgotten research, he shows how to create a culture where, rather than &#8220;just following orders,&#8221; people hold themselves accountable to do the right thing, always.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/intelligent-disobedience-doing-right-when-what-youre-told-to-do-is-wrong-ira-chaleff-abridged/">Intelligent Disobedience: Doing Right When What You&#8217;re Told to Do Is Wrong &#8211; Ira Chaleff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a divided world, empathy is not the solution, it is the problem. We think of empathy &#8211; the ability to feel the suffering of others for ourselves &#8211; as the ultimate source of all good behaviour. But while it inspires care and protection in personal relationships, it has the opposite effect in the wider [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/">Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a divided world, empathy is not the solution, it is the problem.      </p>
<p>                    We think of empathy &#8211; the ability to feel the suffering of others for ourselves &#8211; as the ultimate source of all good behaviour. But while it inspires care and protection in personal relationships, it has the opposite effect in the wider world. As the latest research in psychology and neuroscience shows, we feel empathy most for those we find attractive and who seem similar to us and not at all for those who are different, distant or anonymous. Empathy therefore biases us in favour of individuals we know while numbing us to the plight of thousands. Guiding us expertly through the experiments, case studies and arguments on all sides, Paul Bloom ultimately shows that some of our worst decisions &#8211; in charity, child-raising, criminal justice, climate change and war &#8211; are motivated by this wolf in sheep&#8217;s clothing.     </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly argued, urgent and humane, Against Empathy overturns widely held assumptions to reveal one of the most profound yet overlooked sources of human conflict.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/">Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Adam Smith Can Change Your Life : An Unexpected Guide to Human Nature and Happiness &#8211; Russ Roberts (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-adam-smith-can-change-your-life-an-unexpected-guide-to-human-nature-and-happiness-russ-roberts-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-adam-smith-can-change-your-life-an-unexpected-guide-to-human-nature-and-happiness-russ-roberts-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fun, fascinating, and original book that will challenge you to become a better version of yourself&#8217; Daniel H. Pink, author of Drive What does it take to be truly happy? Should we pursue fame and fortune or the respect of our friends and family? How can we make the world a better place? Two [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-adam-smith-can-change-your-life-an-unexpected-guide-to-human-nature-and-happiness-russ-roberts-abridged/">How Adam Smith Can Change Your Life : An Unexpected Guide to Human Nature and Happiness &#8211; Russ Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fun, fascinating, and original book that will challenge you to become a better version of yourself&#8217;<br />
                    Daniel H. Pink, author of Drive    </p>
<p>                    What does it take to be truly happy? Should we pursue fame and fortune or the respect of our friends and family? How can we make the world a better place?     </p>
<p>                    Two hundred and fifty years ago, Adam Smith addressed these fundamental questions in his life-long project, The Theory of Modern Sentiments.    </p>
<p>                    Dwarfed by the success of Smith&#8217;s masterpiece The Wealth of Nations, The Theory of Modern Sentiments has been virtually forgotten. But when Russ Roberts finally picked up the epic tome, he realized he&#8217;d stumbled upon the greatest self-help book that almost no one has read.    </p>
<p>                    In How Adam Smith Can Change Your Life, Rob erts reinvigorates the neglected classic to unearth a treasure trove of timeless, practical wisdom that cuts to the core of what it means to be human. It will challenge you to think about the way you treat others, the decisions you make in pursuit of happiness, and your place in the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-adam-smith-can-change-your-life-an-unexpected-guide-to-human-nature-and-happiness-russ-roberts-abridged/">How Adam Smith Can Change Your Life : An Unexpected Guide to Human Nature and Happiness &#8211; Russ Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everyday Ubuntu : Living better together, the African way &#8211; Nompumelelo Mungi Ngomane (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everyday-ubuntu-living-better-together-the-african-way-nompumelelo-mungi-ngomane-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everyday-ubuntu-living-better-together-the-african-way-nompumelelo-mungi-ngomane-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book will open your eyes, mind and heart to a way of being in the world that will make our world a better and more caring one.&#8217; ARCHBISHOP DESMOND TUTU, author of The Book of Joy Ubuntu is an ancient Southern African philosophy about how to live life well, together. It is a belief [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everyday-ubuntu-living-better-together-the-african-way-nompumelelo-mungi-ngomane-abridged/">Everyday Ubuntu : Living better together, the African way &#8211; Nompumelelo Mungi Ngomane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book will open  your eyes, mind and heart to a way of being in the world that will make  our world a better and more caring one.&#8217; ARCHBISHOP DESMOND TUTU, author of The Book of Joy    </p>
<p>                    Ubuntu is an ancient Southern African philosophy about how to live life well, together. It is a belief in a universal human bond, which says: I am only because you are.     </p>
<p>                    It means that if you can see everyone as fully human, connected to  you by their humanity, you will never be able to treat others as  disposable or without worth. By embracing the philosophy of ubuntu  it&#8217;s possible to  overcome division and be stronger together in a world  where the wise build bridges and the foolish build walls.    </p>
<p>                    These  14 beautifully illustrated lessons from the Rainbow Nation are an  essential toolkit to helping us all to live better, together. In  stories, practical lessons and applications that recognise our common  humanity, our connectedness and interdependence, Everyday Ubuntu helps us to make sense of the world and our place in it.    </p>
<p>                    Exploring  ideas of kindness and forgiveness, tolerance and the power of  listening, this definitive guide offers practical tips on how we can all  benefit from embracing others and living a more fulfilling life as part  of the large family to which we all belong.<br />
                    __________    </p>
<p>                    What readers are saying about Everyday Ubuntu:    </p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;A concept we should all live by.&#8217;<br />
                    ***** &#8216;Lots of little gems to help with everyday life.&#8217;<br />
                    ***** &#8216;Must read&#8230; Very inspiring and thought-provoking.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everyday-ubuntu-living-better-together-the-african-way-nompumelelo-mungi-ngomane-abridged/">Everyday Ubuntu : Living better together, the African way &#8211; Nompumelelo Mungi Ngomane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Outgrowing God : A Beginner&#8217;s Guide &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/outgrowing-god-a-beginners-guide-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agnosticism & Atheism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eclectic & Esoteric Religions & Belief Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/outgrowing-god-a-beginners-guide-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>___________________ SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER Should we believe in God? In this new book, written for a new generation, the brilliant science writer and author of The God Delusion, explains why we shouldn&#8217;t. Should we believe in God? Do we need God in order to explain the existence of the universe? Do we need God in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outgrowing-god-a-beginners-guide-richard-dawkins-abridged/">Outgrowing God : A Beginner&#8217;s Guide &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>___________________    </p>
<p>                    SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    Should we believe in God? In this new book, written for a new generation, the brilliant science writer and author of The God Delusion, explains why we shouldn&#8217;t.    </p>
<p>                    Should we believe in God? Do we need God in order to explain the existence of the universe? Do we need God in order to be good? In twelve chapters that address some of the most profound questions human beings confront, Dawkins marshals science, philosophy and comparative religion to interrogate the hypocrisies of all the religious systems and explain to readers of all ages how life emerged without a Creator, how evolution works and how our world came into being.    </p>
<p>                    For anyone hoping to grapple with the meaning of life and what to believe, Outgrowing God is a challenging, thrilling and revelatory read.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outgrowing-god-a-beginners-guide-richard-dawkins-abridged/">Outgrowing God : A Beginner&#8217;s Guide &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Architecture of Happiness &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-architecture-of-happiness-alain-de-botton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Architecture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interior Design, Decor & Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Professional Interior Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Architecture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-architecture-of-happiness-alain-de-botton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER From one of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy and The School of Life, The Architecture of Happiness explores the fascinating hidden links between the buildings we live in and our long-term wellbeing. &#8216;Engaging and intelligent . . . Full [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-architecture-of-happiness-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Architecture of Happiness &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    From one of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy and The School of Life, The Architecture of Happiness explores the fascinating hidden links between the buildings we live in and our long-term wellbeing.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Engaging and intelligent . . . Full of splendid ideas, happily and beautifully expressed&#8217; Independent    </p>
<p>                    What makes a house truly beautiful? Why are many new houses so ugly? Why do we argue so bitterly about sofas and pictures &#8211; and can differences of taste ever be satisfactorily resolved?    </p>
<p>                    To answer these questions and many more, de Botton looks at buildings across the world, from medieval wooden huts to modern skyscrapers; he examines sofas and cathedrals, tea sets and office complexes, and teases out a host of often surprising philosophical insights. The Architecture of Happiness will take you on a beguiling tour through the history and psychology of architecture and interior design, and will change the way you look at your home.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Alain de Botton takes big, complex subjects and writes about them with thoughtful and deceptive innocence&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Clever, provocative and fresh as a daisy&#8217; Literary Review</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-architecture-of-happiness-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Architecture of Happiness &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Strangers Drowning : Voyages to the Brink of Moral Extremity &#8211; Larissa MacFarquhar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/strangers-drowning-voyages-to-the-brink-of-moral-extremity-larissa-macfarquhar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/strangers-drowning-voyages-to-the-brink-of-moral-extremity-larissa-macfarquhar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES and GUARDIAN BOOKS OF THE YEAR 2015 What does it mean to devote yourself wholly to helping others? In Strangers Drowning, Larissa MacFarquhar seeks out people living lives of extreme ethical commitment, and tells their intimate stories: their stubborn integrity and their compromises; their bravery and their recklessness; their wrenching dilemmas. A couple [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strangers-drowning-voyages-to-the-brink-of-moral-extremity-larissa-macfarquhar-abridged/">Strangers Drowning : Voyages to the Brink of Moral Extremity &#8211; Larissa MacFarquhar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES and GUARDIAN BOOKS OF THE YEAR 2015    </p>
<p>                    What does it mean to devote yourself wholly to helping others? In Strangers Drowning, Larissa MacFarquhar seeks out people living lives of extreme ethical commitment, and tells their intimate stories: their stubborn integrity and their compromises; their bravery and their recklessness; their wrenching dilemmas.    </p>
<p>                    A couple adopts two children in distress. But then they think: if they can change two lives, why not four? Or ten? They adopt twenty. But how do they weigh the needs of unknown children in distress against the needs of the children they already have?    </p>
<p>                    Another couple founds a leprosy colony in the wilderness in India, living in huts with no walls, knowing that their two small children may contract leprosy or be eaten by panthers. The children survive. But what if they hadn&#8217;t? How would their parents&#8217; risk have been judged?    </p>
<p>                    We honour such generosity and high ideals; but when we call people &#8216;do-gooders&#8217; there is scepticism in it, even hostility. Why do moral people make us uneasy? Between her stories, MacFarquhar threads a lively history of the novels, philosophy, social science, and self-help that have contributed to a deep suspicion of do-gooders in Western culture.    </p>
<p>                    Through its sympathetic and beautifully vivid storytelling, Strangers Drowning confronts us with fundamental questions about what it means to be human. In a world of strangers drowning in need, how much should we help, and how much can we help? Is it right to care for strangers even at the expense of those we are closest to? Moving and provocative, Strangers Drowning challenges us to think about what we value most, and why.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strangers-drowning-voyages-to-the-brink-of-moral-extremity-larissa-macfarquhar-abridged/">Strangers Drowning : Voyages to the Brink of Moral Extremity &#8211; Larissa MacFarquhar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rachel Carson: Silent Spring &#038; Other Environmental Writings &#8211; Rachel Carson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rachel-carson-silent-spring-other-environmental-writings-rachel-carson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rachel-carson-silent-spring-other-environmental-writings-rachel-carson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The book that sparked the modern environmental movement, with an unprecedented collection of letters, speeches, and other writings that reveal the extraordinary courage and vision of its author Library of America launches its Rachel Carson edition with this deluxe illustrated volume presenting one of the landmark books of the twentieth century together with rare letters, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rachel-carson-silent-spring-other-environmental-writings-rachel-carson-abridged/">Rachel Carson: Silent Spring &#038; Other Environmental Writings &#8211; Rachel Carson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The book that sparked the modern environmental movement, with an unprecedented collection of letters, speeches, and other writings that reveal the extraordinary courage and vision of its author     </p>
<p>                    Library of America launches its Rachel Carson edition with this deluxe illustrated volume presenting one of the landmark books of the twentieth century together with rare letters, speeches, and other writings that reveal the personal courage and passionate commitment of its author. A huge bestseller when published in September 1962, Silent Spring led not only to many of the laws and government agencies that protect our air, land, and water, but prompted a revolution in environmental consciousness. Now for the first time, in previously unpublished and newly collected letters to biochemists, ecologists, cancer specialists, ornithologists, and other experts, Carson&#8217;s groundbreaking expose of the unintended consequences of pesticide use comes together piece-by-piece, like a puzzle or detective story. She makes common cause with conservationists and other allies to build public awareness, hiding her private battle with cancer for fear it might distract from her message. And in the wake of her book&#8217;s astonishing impact, as she becomes the target of an organized campaign of disinformation by the chemical industry, Carson speaks out in defense of her findings while remaining a model of grace under pressure. Throughout the collection, Carson&#8217;s lifelong love of nature shines through. In writings both lyrical and intensely moving, she conveys her sense of wonder to her young nephew, dreams of conserving old-growth forest in Maine for posterity, and recounts her adventures and epiphanies as birdwatcher and beachcomber. A future companion volume will gather Carson&#8217;s sea trilogy: Under the Sea-Wind (1941), The Sea Around Us (1951), and The Edge of the Sea (1955).     </p>
<p>                    LIBRARY OF AMERICA is an independent nonprofit cultural organization founded in 1979 to preserve our nation&#8217;s literary heritage by publishing, and keeping permanently in print, America&#8217;s best and most significant writing. The Library of America series includes more than 300 volumes to date, authoritative editions that average 1,000 pages in length, feature cloth covers, sewn bindings, and ribbon markers, and are printed on premium acid-free paper that will last for centuries.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rachel-carson-silent-spring-other-environmental-writings-rachel-carson-abridged/">Rachel Carson: Silent Spring &#038; Other Environmental Writings &#8211; Rachel Carson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Letters from a Stoic : Epistulae Morales Ad Lucilium &#8211; Seneca, Introduction by Robin Campbell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/letters-from-a-stoic-epistulae-morales-ad-lucilium-seneca-introduction-by-robin-campbell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diaries, Letters & Journals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Ancient, To C 500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/letters-from-a-stoic-epistulae-morales-ad-lucilium-seneca-introduction-by-robin-campbell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It is philosophy that has the duty of protecting us &#8230; without it no one can lead a life free of fear or worry&#8217; For several years of his turbulent life, in which he was dogged by ill health, exile and danger, Seneca was the guiding hand of the Roman Empire. This selection of Seneca&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/letters-from-a-stoic-epistulae-morales-ad-lucilium-seneca-introduction-by-robin-campbell-abridged/">Letters from a Stoic : Epistulae Morales Ad Lucilium &#8211; Seneca, Introduction by Robin Campbell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It is philosophy that has the duty of protecting us &#8230; without it no one can lead a life free of fear or worry&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    For several years of his turbulent life, in which he was dogged by ill health, exile and danger, Seneca was the guiding hand of the Roman Empire. This selection of Seneca&#8217;s letters shows him upholding the ideals of Stoicism &#8211; the wisdom of the self-possessed person immune to life&#8217;s setbacks &#8211; while valuing friendship and courage, and criticizing the harsh treatment of slaves and the cruelties in the gladiatorial arena. The humanity and wit revealed in Seneca&#8217;s interpretation of Stoicism is a moving and inspiring declaration of the dignity of the individual mind.    </p>
<p>                    Selected and translated with an Introduction by Robin Campbell</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/letters-from-a-stoic-epistulae-morales-ad-lucilium-seneca-introduction-by-robin-campbell-abridged/">Letters from a Stoic : Epistulae Morales Ad Lucilium &#8211; Seneca, Introduction by Robin Campbell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sunflower : On the Possibilities and Limits of Forgiveness &#8211; Simon Wiesenthal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sunflower-on-the-possibilities-and-limits-of-forgiveness-simon-wiesenthal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holocaust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewish Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sunflower-on-the-possibilities-and-limits-of-forgiveness-simon-wiesenthal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Holocaust survivor&#8217;s surprising and thought-provoking study of forgiveness, justice, compassion, and human responsibility, featuring contributions from the Dalai Lama, Harry Wu, Cynthia Ozick, Primo Levi, and more. While imprisoned in a Nazi concentration camp, Simon Wiesenthal was taken one day from his work detail to the bedside of a dying member of the SS. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sunflower-on-the-possibilities-and-limits-of-forgiveness-simon-wiesenthal-abridged/">The Sunflower : On the Possibilities and Limits of Forgiveness &#8211; Simon Wiesenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Holocaust survivor&#8217;s surprising and thought-provoking study of forgiveness, justice, compassion, and human responsibility, featuring contributions from the Dalai Lama, Harry Wu, Cynthia Ozick, Primo Levi, and more.     </p>
<p>                    While imprisoned in a Nazi concentration camp, Simon Wiesenthal was taken one day from his work detail to the bedside of a dying member of the SS. Haunted by the crimes in which he had participated, the soldier wanted to confess to&#8211;and obtain absolution from&#8211;a Jew. Faced with the choice between compassion and justice, silence and truth, Wiesenthal said nothing. But even years after the way had ended, he wondered: Had he done the right thing? What would you have done in his place?     </p>
<p>                    In this important book, fifty-three distinguished men and women respond to Wiesenthal&#8217;s questions. They are theologians, political leaders, writers, jurists, psychiatrists, human rights activists, Holocaust survivors, and victims of attempted genocides in Bosnia, Cambodia, China and Tibet. Their responses, as varied as their experiences of the world, remind us that Wiesenthal&#8217;s questions are not limited to events of the past.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sunflower-on-the-possibilities-and-limits-of-forgiveness-simon-wiesenthal-abridged/">The Sunflower : On the Possibilities and Limits of Forgiveness &#8211; Simon Wiesenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beyond Good and Evil : Prelude to a Philosophy of the Future &#8211; Friedrich Nietzsche (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beyond-good-and-evil-prelude-to-a-philosophy-of-the-future-friedrich-nietzsche-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beyond-good-and-evil-prelude-to-a-philosophy-of-the-future-friedrich-nietzsche-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After kicking open the doors to twentieth-century philosophy in Thus Spake Zarathustra, Friedrich Nietzsche refined his ideal of the superman with the 1886 publication of Beyond Good and Evil. Conventional morality is a sign of slavery, Nietzsche maintains, and the superman goes beyond good and evil in action, thought, and creation. Nietzsche especially targets what [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-good-and-evil-prelude-to-a-philosophy-of-the-future-friedrich-nietzsche-abridged/">Beyond Good and Evil : Prelude to a Philosophy of the Future &#8211; Friedrich Nietzsche (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After kicking open the doors to twentieth-century philosophy in Thus Spake Zarathustra,  Friedrich Nietzsche refined his ideal of the superman with the 1886 publication of Beyond Good and Evil. Conventional morality is a sign of slavery, Nietzsche maintains, and the superman goes beyond good and evil in action, thought, and creation. Nietzsche especially targets what he calls a slave morality that fosters herdlike quiescence and stigmatizes the highest human types.<br />
                    In this pathbreaking work, Nietzsche&#8217;s philosophical and literary powers are at their height: with devastating irony and flashing wit he gleefully dynamites centuries of accumulated conventional wisdom in metaphysics, morals, and psychology, clearing a path for such twentieth-century innovators as Thomas Mann, André Gide, Sigmund Freud, George Bernard Shaw, André Malraux, and Jean-Paul Sartre, all of whom openly acknowledged their debt to him.<br />
                    Students of philosophy and literature as well as general readers will prize this rich sampling of Nietzsche&#8217;s thought in an unabridged and inexpensive edition of one of the philosopher&#8217;s most important works.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-good-and-evil-prelude-to-a-philosophy-of-the-future-friedrich-nietzsche-abridged/">Beyond Good and Evil : Prelude to a Philosophy of the Future &#8211; Friedrich Nietzsche (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
