<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Basketball Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/basketball/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/basketball/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Basketball Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/basketball/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Eleven Rings : The Soul of Success &#8211; Phil Jackson</title>
		<link>/eleven-rings-the-soul-of-success-phil-jackson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basketball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eleven-rings-the-soul-of-success-phil-jackson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Through candor and comprehensiveness, Jackson writes a convincing revisionist take, in which he emerges as an excellent coach . . . highly readable . . . reflects Jackson&#8217;s polymathy.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review &#8220;Part sports memoir, part New Age spirit quest, part pseudo-management tract . . . But the primary thing with Jackson-as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eleven-rings-the-soul-of-success-phil-jackson/">Eleven Rings : The Soul of Success &#8211; Phil Jackson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Through candor and comprehensiveness, Jackson writes a convincing revisionist take, in which he emerges as an excellent coach . . . highly readable . . . reflects Jackson&#8217;s polymathy.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Part sports memoir, part New Age spirit quest, part pseudo-management tract . . . But the primary thing with Jackson-as with all the old bards, who were also known for repeating themselves-is the voice.&#8221; -Sam Anderson, The New York Times Magazine</p>
<p>                    A New York Times Bestseller</p>
<p>                    The inside story of one of basketball&#8217;s most legendary and game-changing figures </p>
<p>                    During his storied career as head coach of the Chicago Bulls and Los Angeles Lakers, Phil Jackson won more championships than any coach in the history of professional sports. Even more important, he succeeded in never wavering from coaching his way, from a place of deep values. Jackson was tagged as the &#8220;Zen master&#8221; half in jest by sportswriters, but the nickname speaks to an important truth: this is a coach who inspired, not goaded; who led by awakening and challenging the better angels of his players&#8217; nature, not their egos, fear, or greed.</p>
<p>                     This is the story of a preacher&#8217;s kid from North Dakota who grew up to be one of the most innovative leaders of our time. In his quest to reinvent himself, Jackson explored everything from humanistic psychology and Native American philosophy to Zen meditation. In the process, he developed a new approach to leadership based on freedom, authenticity, and selfless teamwork that turned the hypercompetitive world of professional sports on its head.</p>
<p>                     In Eleven Rings, Jackson candidly describes how he: </p>
<p>                       *  Learned the secrets of mindfulness and team chemistry while playing for the champion New York Knicks in the 1970s<br />
                       *  Managed Michael Jordan, the greatest player in the world, and got him to embrace selflessness, even if it meant losing a scoring title<br />
                       *  Forged successful teams out of players of varying abilities by getting them to trust one another and perform in sync<br />
                       *  Inspired Dennis Rodman and other &#8220;uncoachable&#8221; personalities to devote themselves to something larger than themselves<br />
                       *  Transformed Kobe Bryant from a rebellious teenager into a mature leader of a championship team. </p>
<p>                     Eleven times, Jackson led his teams to the ultimate goal: the NBA championship-six times with the Chicago Bulls and five times with the Los Angeles Lakers. We all know the legendary stars on those teams, or think we do. What Eleven Rings shows us, however, is that when it comes to the most important lessons, we don&#8217;t know very much at all. This book is full of revelations: about fascinating personalities and their drive to win; about the wellsprings of motivation and competition at the highest levels; and about what it takes to bring out the best in ourselves and others.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eleven-rings-the-soul-of-success-phil-jackson/">Eleven Rings : The Soul of Success &#8211; Phil Jackson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mind Gym &#8211; Gary Mack, David Casstevens (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mind-gym-gary-mack-david-casstevens-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[American Football]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Baseball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basketball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Combat Sports & Self-defence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football (Soccer, Association Football)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Golf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gymnastics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ice-skating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Multidiscipline Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olympic Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Swimming & Diving]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tennis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Track & Field Sports, Athletics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Volleyball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wrestling]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mind-gym-gary-mack-david-casstevens-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Mind Gym &#8220;Believing in yourself is paramount to success for any athlete. Gary&#8217;s lessons and David&#8217;s writing provide examples of the importance of the mental game.&#8221; &#8211;Ben Crenshaw, two-time Masters champion and former Ryder Cup captain &#8220;Mind Gym hits a home run. If you want to build mental muscle for the major leagues, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mind-gym-gary-mack-david-casstevens-abridged/">Mind Gym &#8211; Gary Mack, David Casstevens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Mind Gym    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Believing in yourself is paramount to success for any athlete. Gary&#8217;s lessons and David&#8217;s writing provide examples of the importance of the mental game.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Ben Crenshaw, two-time Masters champion and former Ryder Cup captain    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Mind Gym hits a home run. If you want to build mental muscle for the major leagues, read this book.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Ken Griffey Jr., Major League Baseball MVP    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I read Mind Gym on my way to the Sydney Olympics and really got a lot out of it. Gary has important lessons to teach, and you&#8217;ll find the exercises fun and beneficial.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Jason Kidd, NBA All-Star and Olympic gold-medal winner    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I love the book Mind Gym.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Madison Kocian, 2016 U.S. Women&#8217;s Gymnastics Team, 2015 Uneven Bars World Champion, as told to Us Weekly    </p>
<p>                    In Mind Gym, noted sports psychology consultant Gary Mack explains how your mind influences your performance on the field or on the court as much as your physical skill does, if not more so. Through forty accessible lessons and inspirational anecdotes from prominent athletes&#8211;many of whom he has worked with&#8211;you will learn the same techniques and exercises Mack uses to help elite athletes build mental &#8220;muscle.&#8221; Mind Gym will give you the &#8220;head edge&#8221; over the competition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mind-gym-gary-mack-david-casstevens-abridged/">Mind Gym &#8211; Gary Mack, David Casstevens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Most Likely to Succeed : Preparing Our Kids for the Innovation Era &#8211; Tony Wagner, Ted Dintersmith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basketball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The basis for a major documentary, two leading experts sound an urgent call for the radical reimagining of American education so we can equip students for the realities of the twenty-first-century economy. We prize academic achievement, pressuring our children to get into the &#8220;right&#8221; colleges, have the highest GPAs, and pursue advanced degrees. But while [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/">Most Likely to Succeed : Preparing Our Kids for the Innovation Era &#8211; Tony Wagner, Ted Dintersmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The basis for a major documentary, two leading experts sound an urgent call for the radical reimagining of American education so we can equip students for the realities of the twenty-first-century economy.<br />
                         We prize academic achievement, pressuring our children to get into the &#8220;right&#8221; colleges, have the highest GPAs, and pursue advanced degrees. But while students may graduate with credentials, by and large they lack the competencies needed to be thoughtful, engaged citizens and to get good jobs in our rapidly evolving economy. Alarmingly, our methods of schooling crush the creativity and initiative young people really need to thrive in the twenty-first century.<br />
                         Now bestselling author and education expert Tony Wagner and venture capitalist Ted Dintersmith call for a complete overhaul of American schools, sharing insights and stories from the front lines. Their powerful, urgent message identifies the growing gap between credentials and competence-and offers a framework for change.<br />
                        Most Likely to Succeed presents a new vision of American education, one that puts wonder, creativity, and initiative at the very heart of the learning process and prepares students for today&#8217;s economy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/">Most Likely to Succeed : Preparing Our Kids for the Innovation Era &#8211; Tony Wagner, Ted Dintersmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
