<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Teaching Skills &amp; Techniques Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/teaching-skills-techniques/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/teaching-skills-techniques/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Teaching Skills &amp; Techniques Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/teaching-skills-techniques/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teacher Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Staff]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical framework to avoid burnout and keep great teachers teaching Onward tackles the problem of educator stress, and provides a practical framework for taking the burnout out of teaching. Stress is part of the job, but when 70 percent of teachers quit within their first five years because the stress is making them physically [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/">Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical framework to avoid burnout and keep great teachers teaching    </p>
<p>                     Onward tackles the problem of educator stress, and provides a practical framework for taking the burnout out of teaching. Stress is part of the job, but when 70 percent of teachers quit within their first five years because the stress is making them physically and mentally ill, things have gone too far. Unsurprisingly, these effects are highest in difficult-to-fill positions such as math, science, and foreign languages, and in urban areas and secondary classrooms-places where we need our teachers to be especially motivated and engaged. This book offers a path to resiliency to help teachers weather the storms and bounce back-and work toward banishing the rain for good.    </p>
<p>                     This actionable framework gives you concrete steps toward rediscovering yourself, your energy, and your passion for teaching. You&#8217;ll learn how a simple shift in mindset can affect your outlook, and how taking care of yourself physically, mentally, and emotionally is one of the most important things you can do. The companion workbook helps you put the framework into action, streamlining your way toward renewal and strength.    </p>
<p>                    Cultivate resilience with a four-part framework based on 12 key habits<br />
                    Uncover your true self, understand emotions, and use your energy where it counts<br />
                    Adopt a mindful, story-telling approach to communication and community building<br />
                    Keep learning, playing, and creating to create an environment of collective celebration    </p>
<p>                     By cultivating resilience in schools, we help ensure that we are working in, teaching in, and leading organizations where every child thrives, and where the potential of every child is recognized and nurtured. Onward provides a step-by-step plan for reigniting that spark.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/onward-cultivating-emotional-resilience-in-educators-elena-aguilar-abridged/">Onward : Cultivating Emotional Resilience in Educators &#8211; Elena Aguilar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Programming / Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Starting a new venture is like jumping off a cliff and sewing a parachute on the way down. This book is the parachute.&#8221; Joe Gebbia, cofounder and chief product officer, Airbnb How do you make your start-up a genuine success in the long term? While most books and press focus on the more sensational moments [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/">The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Starting a new venture is like jumping off a cliff and sewing a parachute on the way down. This book is the parachute.&#8221;<br />
                     Joe Gebbia, cofounder and chief product officer, Airbnb    </p>
<p>                    How do you make your start-up a genuine success in the long term?  While most books and press focus on the more sensational moments of creation and conclusion, The Messy Middle argues that the real key to success is how you navigate the ups-and-downs after initial investment is secured. It will give you all the insights you need to build and optimize your team, improve your product and develop your own capacity to lead covering:<br />
                    *         Coping with uncertainty and conflict<br />
                    *         Playing the long game<br />
                    *         Optimising your team<br />
                    *         Problem solving through the ups and downs<br />
                    *         Adapting your strategy<br />
                    *         When to quit<br />
                    Building on seven years&#8217; of meticulous research with entrepreneurs, small agencies, start-ups and billion-dollar companies, Scott Belsky offers indispensable lessons on how to endure and thrive in the long term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/">The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Innumeracy : Mathematical Illiteracy and Its Consequences &#8211; John Allen Paulos (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/innumeracy-mathematical-illiteracy-and-its-consequences-john-allen-paulos-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Citizenship & Social Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Of A Specific Subject]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/innumeracy-mathematical-illiteracy-and-its-consequences-john-allen-paulos-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Readers of Innumeracy will be rewarded with scores of astonishing facts, a fistful of powerful ideas, and, most important, a clearer, more quantitative way of looking at their world. Why do even well-educated people understand so little about mathematics? And what are the costs of our innumeracy? John Allen Paulos, in his celebrated bestseller first [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/innumeracy-mathematical-illiteracy-and-its-consequences-john-allen-paulos-abridged/">Innumeracy : Mathematical Illiteracy and Its Consequences &#8211; John Allen Paulos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Readers of Innumeracy will be rewarded with scores of astonishing facts, a fistful of powerful ideas, and, most important, a clearer, more quantitative way of looking at their world.     </p>
<p>                    Why do even well-educated people understand so little about mathematics? And what are the costs of our innumeracy? John Allen Paulos, in his celebrated bestseller first published in 1988, argues that our inability to deal rationally with very large numbers and the probabilities associated with them results in misinformed governmental policies, confused personal decisions, and an increased susceptibility to pseudoscience of all kinds. Innumeracy lets us know what we&#8217;re missing, and how we can do something about it.     </p>
<p>                    Sprinkling his discussion of numbers and probabilities with quirky stories and anecdotes, Paulos ranges freely over many aspects of modern life, from contested elections to sports stats, from stock scams and newspaper psychics to diet and medical claims, sex discrimination, insurance, lotteries, and drug testing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/innumeracy-mathematical-illiteracy-and-its-consequences-john-allen-paulos-abridged/">Innumeracy : Mathematical Illiteracy and Its Consequences &#8211; John Allen Paulos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ten Days to Faster Reading &#8211; Abby Marks-Beale (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ten-days-to-faster-reading-abby-marks-beale-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Of A Specific Subject]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ten-days-to-faster-reading-abby-marks-beale-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jump-Start Your Reading Skills! Speed reading used to require months of training. Now you can rev up your reading in just a few minutes a day. With quizzes to determine your present reading level and exercises to introduce new skills quickly, 10 Days to Faster Reading will improve your reading comprehension and speed as it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ten-days-to-faster-reading-abby-marks-beale-abridged/">Ten Days to Faster Reading &#8211; Abby Marks-Beale (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jump-Start Your Reading Skills! Speed reading used to require months of training. Now you can rev up your reading in just a few minutes a day. With quizzes to determine your present reading level and exercises to introduce new skills quickly, 10 Days to Faster Reading will improve your reading comprehension and speed as it shows you how to:     </p>
<p>                     Break the Bad Habits That Slow You Down<br />
                     Develop Your Powers of Concentration<br />
                     Cut Your Reading Time in Half<br />
                     Use Proven, Specially Designed Reading Techniques<br />
                     Boost the Power of Your Peripheral Vision     </p>
<p>                     Learn How to Scan and Skim a Written Report &#8230;And All in 10 Days!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ten-days-to-faster-reading-abby-marks-beale-abridged/">Ten Days to Faster Reading &#8211; Abby Marks-Beale (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School?: A Cognitive Scientist Answers Questions About How the Mind Works and What It Means for the Classroom &#8211; Daniel T. Willingham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-dont-students-like-school-a-cognitive-scientist-answers-questions-about-how-the-mind-works-and-what-it-means-for-the-classroom-daniel-t-willingham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-dont-students-like-school-a-cognitive-scientist-answers-questions-about-how-the-mind-works-and-what-it-means-for-the-classroom-daniel-t-willingham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Research-based insights and practical advice about effective learning strategies In this new edition of the highly regarded Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School? cognitive psychologist Daniel Willingham turns his research on the biological and cognitive basis of learning into workable teaching techniques. This book will help you improve your teaching practice by explaining how you and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-dont-students-like-school-a-cognitive-scientist-answers-questions-about-how-the-mind-works-and-what-it-means-for-the-classroom-daniel-t-willingham-abridged/">Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School?: A Cognitive Scientist Answers Questions About How the Mind Works and What It Means for the Classroom &#8211; Daniel T. Willingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Research-based insights and practical advice about effective learning strategies In this new edition of the highly regarded Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School? cognitive psychologist Daniel Willingham turns his research on the biological and cognitive basis of learning into workable teaching techniques. This book will help you improve your teaching practice by explaining how you and your students think and learn. It reveals the importance of story, emotion, memory, context, and routine in building knowledge and creating lasting learning experiences. With a treasure trove of updated material, this edition draws its themes from the most frequently asked questions in Willingham&#8217;s &#8216;Ask the Cognitive Scientist&#8217; column in the American Educator. How can you teach students the skills they need when standardized testing just requires facts? Why do students remember everything on TV, but forget everything you say? How can you adjust your teaching for different learning styles? Read this book for the answers to these questions and for practical advice on helping your learners learn better. Discover easy-to-understand, evidence-based principles with clear applications for the classroom Update yourself on the latest cognitive science research and new, teacher-tested pedagogical tools Learn about Willingham&#8217;s surprising findings, such as that you cannot develop &#8216;thinking skills&#8217; without facts Understand the brain&#8217;s workings to help you hone your teaching skills Why Students Don&#8217;t Like School is a valuable resource for both veteran and novice teachers, teachers-in-training, and for the principals, administrators, and staff development professionals who work with them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-dont-students-like-school-a-cognitive-scientist-answers-questions-about-how-the-mind-works-and-what-it-means-for-the-classroom-daniel-t-willingham-abridged/">Why Don&#8217;t Students Like School?: A Cognitive Scientist Answers Questions About How the Mind Works and What It Means for the Classroom &#8211; Daniel T. Willingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
