<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Impact Of Science &amp; Technology On Society Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/impact-of-science-technology-on-society/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/impact-of-science-technology-on-society/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Impact Of Science &amp; Technology On Society Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/impact-of-science-technology-on-society/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Augmented : Life in the Smart Lane &#8211; Brett King</title>
		<link>/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Internet and smartphone are just the latest in a 250 year long cycle of disruption that has continuously changed the way we live, the way we work and the way we interact. The coming Augmented Age, however, promises a level of disruption, behavioral shifts and changes that are unparalleled. While consumers today are camping [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/">Augmented : Life in the Smart Lane &#8211; Brett King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Internet and smartphone are just the latest in a 250 year long cycle of disruption that has continuously changed the way we live, the way we work and the way we interact. The coming Augmented Age, however, promises a level of disruption, behavioral shifts and changes that are unparalleled. While consumers today are camping outside of an Apple store waiting to be one of the first to score a new Apple Watch or iPhone, the next generation of wearables will be able to predict if we&#8217;re likely to have a heart attack and recommend a course of action. We watch news of Google&#8217;s self-driving cars, but don&#8217;t likely realize this means progressive cities will have to ban human drives in the next decade because us humans are too risky.  Following on from the Industrial or Machine Age, the Space Age and the Digital Age, the Augmented Age will be based on four key disruptive themes &#8211; Artificial Intelligence, Experience Design, Smart Infrastructure, and Health Tech. Historically the previous &#8216;ages&#8217; brought significant disruption and changes, but on a net basis jobs were created, wealth was enhanced, and the health and security of society improved. What will the Augmented Age bring?<br />
                    Will robots take our jobs, and AI&#8217;s subsume us as inferior intelligences, or will this usher in a new age of abundance?  Augmented is a book on future history, but more than that, it is a story about how you will live your life in a world that will change more in the next 20 years than it has in the last 250 years. Are you ready to adapt? Because if history proves anything, you don&#8217;t have much of a choice.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/">Augmented : Life in the Smart Lane &#8211; Brett King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</title>
		<link>/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ego]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If I could give each of you a graduation present, it would be this&#8211;the most inspiring book I&#8217;ve ever read. &#8211;Bill Gates A provocative history of violence&#8211;from the New York Times bestselling author of The Stuff of Thought, The Blank Slate, and Enlightenment Now. Believe it or not, today we may be living in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/">The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If I could give each of you a graduation present, it would be this&#8211;the most inspiring book I&#8217;ve ever read. &#8211;Bill Gates     </p>
<p>                    A provocative history of violence&#8211;from the New York Times bestselling author of The Stuff of Thought, The Blank Slate,  and Enlightenment Now.    </p>
<p>                    Believe it or not, today we may be living in the most peaceful moment in our species&#8217; existence. In his gripping and controversial new work, New York Times bestselling author Steven Pinker shows that despite the ceaseless news about war, crime, and terrorism, violence has actually been in decline over long stretches of history. Exploding myths about humankind&#8217;s inherent violence and the curse of modernity, this ambitious book continues Pinker&#8217;s exploration of the essence of human nature, mixing psychology and history to provide a remarkable picture of an increasingly enlightened world.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/">The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</title>
		<link>/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER** In twenty-one bite-sized lessons, Yuval Noah Harari explores what it means to be human in an age of bewilderment. &#8217;21 Lessons is, simply put, a crucial book&#8217; Adam Kay How can we protect ourselves from nuclear war, ecological cataclysms and technological disruptions? What can we do about the epidemic of fake [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/">21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER**</p>
<p>                    In twenty-one bite-sized lessons, Yuval Noah Harari explores what it means to be human in an age of bewilderment. </p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                              &#8217;21 Lessons is, simply put, a crucial book&#8217; Adam Kay</p>
<p>                    How can we protect ourselves from nuclear war, ecological cataclysms and technological disruptions? What can we do about the epidemic of fake news or the threat of terrorism? What should we teach our children? </p>
<p>                    Yuval Noah Harari takes us on a thrilling journey through today&#8217;s most urgent issues. The golden thread running through his exhilarating new book is the challenge of maintaining our collective and individual focus in the face of constant and disorienting change.</p>
<p>                    Are we still capable of understanding the world we have created?</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating&#8230; compelling&#8230; [Harari] has teed up a crucial global conversation about how to take on the problems of the 21st century&#8217; Bill Gates, New York Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Truly mind-expanding&#8230; Ultra-topical&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/">21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Superintelligence : Paths, Dangers, Strategies &#8211; Nick Bostrom</title>
		<link>/superintelligence-paths-dangers-strategies-nick-bostrom/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Risk Assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/superintelligence-paths-dangers-strategies-nick-bostrom/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The human brain has some capabilities that the brains of other animals lack. It is to these distinctive capabilities that our species owes its dominant position. Other animals have stronger muscles or sharper claws, but we have cleverer brains. If machine brains one day come to surpass human brains in general intelligence, then this new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superintelligence-paths-dangers-strategies-nick-bostrom/">Superintelligence : Paths, Dangers, Strategies &#8211; Nick Bostrom</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The human brain has some capabilities that the brains of other animals lack. It is to these distinctive capabilities that our species owes its dominant position. Other animals have stronger muscles or sharper claws, but we have cleverer brains.     </p>
<p>                    If machine brains one day come to surpass human brains in general intelligence, then this new superintelligence could become very powerful. As the fate of the gorillas now depends more on us humans than on the gorillas themselves, so the fate of our species then would come to depend on the actions of the machine superintelligence.     </p>
<p>                    But we have one advantage: we get to make the first move. Will it be possible to construct a seed AI or otherwise to engineer initial conditions so as to make an intelligence explosion survivable? How could one achieve a controlled detonation?     </p>
<p>                    To get closer to an answer to this question, we must make our way through a fascinating landscape of topics and considerations. Read the book and learn about oracles, genies, singletons; about boxing methods, tripwires, and mind crime; about humanity&#8217;s cosmic endowment and differential technological development; indirect normativity, instrumental convergence, whole brain emulation and technology couplings; Malthusian economics and dystopian evolution; artificial intelligence, and biological<br />
                    cognitive enhancement, and collective intelligence.     </p>
<p>                    This profoundly ambitious and original book picks its way carefully through a vast tract of forbiddingly difficult intellectual terrain. Yet the writing is so lucid that it somehow makes it all seem easy. After an utterly engrossing journey that takes us to the frontiers of thinking about the human condition and the future of intelligent life, we find in Nick Bostrom&#8217;s work nothing less than a reconceptualization of the essential task of our time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superintelligence-paths-dangers-strategies-nick-bostrom/">Superintelligence : Paths, Dangers, Strategies &#8211; Nick Bostrom</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Inevitable : Understanding the 12 Technological Forces That Will Shape Our Future &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-inevitable-understanding-the-12-technological-forces-that-will-shape-our-future-kevin-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-inevitable-understanding-the-12-technological-forces-that-will-shape-our-future-kevin-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A quintessential work of technological futurism.&#8221; &#8211; James Surowiecki, strategy + business, &#8220;Best Business Books 2017 &#8211; Innovation&#8221; From one of our leading technology thinkers and writers, a guide through the twelve technological imperatives that will shape the next thirty years and transform our lives Much of what will happen in the next thirty years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-inevitable-understanding-the-12-technological-forces-that-will-shape-our-future-kevin-kelly-abridged/">The Inevitable : Understanding the 12 Technological Forces That Will Shape Our Future &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A quintessential work of technological futurism.&#8221; &#8211; James Surowiecki, strategy + business, &#8220;Best Business Books 2017 &#8211; Innovation&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    From one of our leading technology thinkers and writers, a guide through the twelve technological imperatives that will shape the next thirty years and transform our lives     </p>
<p>                    Much of what will happen in the next thirty years is inevitable, driven by technological trends that are already in motion. In this fascinating, provocative new book, Kevin Kelly provides an optimistic road map for the future, showing how the coming changes in our lives&#8211;from virtual reality in the home to an on-demand economy to artificial intelligence embedded in everything we manufacture&#8211;can be understood as the result of a few long-term, accelerating forces. Kelly both describes these deep trends&#8211;interacting, cognifying, flowing, screening, accessing, sharing, filtering, remixing, tracking, and questioning&#8211;and demonstrates how they overlap and are codependent on one another. These larger forces will completely revolutionize the way we buy, work, learn, and communicate with each other. By understanding and embracing them, says Kelly, it will be easier for us to remain on top of the coming wave of changes and to arrange our day-to-day relationships with technology in ways that bring forth maximum benefits. Kelly&#8217;s bright, hopeful book will be indispensable to anyone who seeks guidance on where their business, industry, or life is heading&#8211;what to invent, where to work, in what to invest, how to better reach customers, and what to begin to put into place&#8211;as this new world emerges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-inevitable-understanding-the-12-technological-forces-that-will-shape-our-future-kevin-kelly-abridged/">The Inevitable : Understanding the 12 Technological Forces That Will Shape Our Future &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising. For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                     A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising.     </p>
<p>                     For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup founder, a small business owner, or part of a large corporation.     </p>
<p>                     No matter what your product or service, this book will help you reframe how it&#8217;s presented to the world, in order to meaningfully connect with people who want it. Seth employs his signature blend of insight, observation, and memorable examples to teach you:    </p>
<p>                     * How to build trust and permission with your target market.<br />
                     * The art of positioning&#8211;deciding not only who it&#8217;s for, but who it&#8217;s not for.<br />
                     * Why the best way to achieve your goals is to help others become who they want to be.<br />
                     * Why the old approaches to advertising and branding no longer work.<br />
                     * The surprising role of tension in any decision to buy (or not).<br />
                     * How marketing is at its core about the stories we tell ourselves about our social status.    </p>
<p>                     You can do work that matters for people who care. This book shows you the way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This Is Marketing is a very accessible way into Godin&#8217;s thinking&#8230;. Godin writes in pacy, jargon-free prose and this book is interesting and useful for anyone who wants an insight into how, and why, we buy things or change our habits in any way.&#8221; &#8211; The Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed reading this, check out Seth Godin&#8217;s Purple Cow, a true business classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Curious History of Dating : From Jane Austen to Tinder &#8211; Nichi Hodgson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-curious-history-of-dating-from-jane-austen-to-tinder-nichi-hodgson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-curious-history-of-dating-from-jane-austen-to-tinder-nichi-hodgson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN EMPHATICALLY FEMINIST HISTORY OF DATING &#8216;A new approach to romance&#8230; The heroines of Regency novels could teach today&#8217;s young women a trick or two&#8217; Sunday Times What if Mr Darcy had simply been able to swipe right? &#8216;This book was a real education for me. It&#8217;s like a Lonely Planet guidebook to dating.&#8217; Gilo [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-curious-history-of-dating-from-jane-austen-to-tinder-nichi-hodgson-abridged/">The Curious History of Dating : From Jane Austen to Tinder &#8211; Nichi Hodgson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN EMPHATICALLY FEMINIST HISTORY OF DATING    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A new approach to romance&#8230; The heroines of Regency novels could teach today&#8217;s young women a trick or two&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    What if Mr Darcy had simply been able to swipe right?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book was a real education for me. It&#8217;s like a Lonely Planet guidebook to dating.&#8217;<br />
                    Gilo    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Lessons to learn for committed singletons and happily married alike, and everyone in between.&#8217;<br />
                    Anon    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I loved it.&#8217;<br />
                    Adele Taylor    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I found it hard to put down.&#8217;<br />
                    richie666    </p>
<p>                    Dating has never been easy. The road to true love has always been rutted with heartbreak, but do we have it any easier today?     </p>
<p>                    How did Victorians &#8216;come out&#8217;? How did love blossom in war-torn Europe? And why did 80s video-dating never take off?    </p>
<p>                    Bursting with little-known facts and tantalizing tales of lovelorn men and besotted women, Nichi Hodgson&#8217;s intriguing history of amorous relationships, from enamoured Georgians to frenziedly swiping millennials (and everyone in between) may leave you grateful that you live &#8211; and love &#8211; today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-curious-history-of-dating-from-jane-austen-to-tinder-nichi-hodgson-abridged/">The Curious History of Dating : From Jane Austen to Tinder &#8211; Nichi Hodgson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bored and Brilliant : How Time Spent Doing Nothing Changes Everything &#8211; Manoush Zomorodi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bored-and-brilliant-how-time-spent-doing-nothing-changes-everything-manoush-zomorodi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bored-and-brilliant-how-time-spent-doing-nothing-changes-everything-manoush-zomorodi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Being bored is bad, right? We&#8217;ll certainly do anything to avoid it and with smartphones we need never be bored again, as we reply to our emails 24 hours a day, tweet as we watch TV, watch TV as we commute, check Facebook as we walk and Instagram while we eat. Stimulation is good. But [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bored-and-brilliant-how-time-spent-doing-nothing-changes-everything-manoush-zomorodi-abridged/">Bored and Brilliant : How Time Spent Doing Nothing Changes Everything &#8211; Manoush Zomorodi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Being bored is bad, right? We&#8217;ll certainly do anything to avoid it and with smartphones we need never be bored again, as we reply to our emails 24 hours a day, tweet as we watch TV, watch TV as we commute, check Facebook as we walk and Instagram while we eat.     </p>
<p>                     Stimulation is good.    </p>
<p>                     But what if it&#8217;s not? What if what happens when our mind &#8220;wanders&#8221; is an essential part of how our brains work and crucial to our concentration and ability to think creatively?<br />
                    What if your relationship with distraction is stopping you from living your fullest life?<br />
                    When award-winning journalist Manoush Zomorodi posed these question to her listeners on her hugely popular New York public radio Podcast, the answer, from neuroscientists, psychologists and experts was a resounding yes. So over the course of a week, she led her listeners through a week of exercises designed to help them reassess their technology habits, unplug for part of each week and jumpstart their creativity. The response was astonishing.     </p>
<p>                     Now, in Bored and Brilliant, she will show you why the key to changing everything may be making time to do nothing by taking you through a series of challenges that will help you rethink and recalibrate your relationship with technology in small but important ways.      </p>
<p>                     This book is both a fascinating account of our new relationship with boredom and a practical guide to inviting a little more of it into your life and reawakening your creativity and productivity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bored-and-brilliant-how-time-spent-doing-nothing-changes-everything-manoush-zomorodi-abridged/">Bored and Brilliant : How Time Spent Doing Nothing Changes Everything &#8211; Manoush Zomorodi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Power : Why outsiders are winning, institutions are failing, and how the rest of us can keep up in the age of mass participation &#8211; Jeremy Heimans, Henry Timms (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/new-power-why-outsiders-are-winning-institutions-are-failing-and-how-the-rest-of-us-can-keep-up-in-the-age-of-mass-participation-jeremy-heimans-henry-timms-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/new-power-why-outsiders-are-winning-institutions-are-failing-and-how-the-rest-of-us-can-keep-up-in-the-age-of-mass-participation-jeremy-heimans-henry-timms-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For most of human history the rules of power were clear: power was something to be seized, and then jealously guarded. Under this &#8216;Old Power&#8217; we lived in a world of rulers and subjects. Now, we all sense that something has changed. From #MeToo to Harvey Weinstein; Corbyn to Trump; from YouTube sensations to darker [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-power-why-outsiders-are-winning-institutions-are-failing-and-how-the-rest-of-us-can-keep-up-in-the-age-of-mass-participation-jeremy-heimans-henry-timms-abridged/">New Power : Why outsiders are winning, institutions are failing, and how the rest of us can keep up in the age of mass participation &#8211; Jeremy Heimans, Henry Timms (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For most of human history the rules of power were clear: power was something to be seized, and then jealously guarded. Under this &#8216;Old Power&#8217; we lived in a world of rulers and subjects.    </p>
<p>                    Now, we all sense that something has changed. From #MeToo to Harvey Weinstein; Corbyn to Trump; from YouTube sensations to darker phenomena such as the emergence of ISIS &#8211; in our new hyper-connected world, ideas and movements can spread and flourish with astonishing force and speed.    </p>
<p>                    In New Power, Jeremy Heimans and Henry Timms confront the biggest story of our age and trace how New Power is the key to understanding where we are and will prosper in the 21st Century.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on examples from business, politics, popular culture and social justice, as well as case studies of organisations like LEGO and TED, they explain the forces that are changing the course of our age.    </p>
<p>                    In a world increasingly shaped by New Power, this book will show you how to shape your future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-power-why-outsiders-are-winning-institutions-are-failing-and-how-the-rest-of-us-can-keep-up-in-the-age-of-mass-participation-jeremy-heimans-henry-timms-abridged/">New Power : Why outsiders are winning, institutions are failing, and how the rest of us can keep up in the age of mass participation &#8211; Jeremy Heimans, Henry Timms (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Humility Is the New Smart &#8211; Edward D. Hess, Katherine Ludwig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/humility-is-the-new-smart-edward-d-hess-katherine-ludwig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/humility-is-the-new-smart-edward-d-hess-katherine-ludwig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Humility Is the New Smart Your job is at risk&#8211;if not now, then soon. We are on the leading edge of a Smart Machine Age led by artificial intelligence that will be as transformative for us as the Industrial Revolution was for our ancestors. Smart machines will take over millions of jobs in manufacturing, office [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humility-is-the-new-smart-edward-d-hess-katherine-ludwig-abridged/">Humility Is the New Smart &#8211; Edward D. Hess, Katherine Ludwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Humility Is the New Smart     </p>
<p>                     Your job is at risk&#8211;if not now, then soon. We are on the leading edge of a Smart Machine Age led by artificial intelligence that will be as transformative for us as the Industrial Revolution was for our ancestors. Smart machines will take over millions of jobs in manufacturing, office work, the service sector, the professions, you name it. Not only can they know more data and analyze it faster than any mere human, say Edward Hess and Katherine Ludwig, but smart machines are free of the emotional, psychological, and cultural baggage that so often mars human thinking.     </p>
<p>                     So we can&#8217;t beat &#8217;em and we can&#8217;t join &#8217;em. To stay relevant, we have to play a different game. Hess and Ludwig offer us that game plan. We need to excel at critical, creative, and innovative thinking and at genuinely engaging with others&#8211;things machines can&#8217;t do well. The key is to change our definition of what it means to be smart. Hess and Ludwig call it being NewSmart. In this extraordinarily timely book, they offer detailed guidance for developing NewSmart attitudes and four critical behaviors that will help us adapt to the new reality.     </p>
<p>                     The crucial mindset underlying NewSmart is humility&#8211;not self-effacement but an accurate self-appraisal: acknowledging you can&#8217;t have all the answers, remaining open to new ideas, and committing yourself to lifelong learning. Drawing on extensive multidisciplinary research, Hess and Ludwig emphasize that the key to success in this new era is not to be more like the machines but to excel at the best of what makes us human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humility-is-the-new-smart-edward-d-hess-katherine-ludwig-abridged/">Humility Is the New Smart &#8211; Edward D. Hess, Katherine Ludwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enchanted Objects : Innovation, Design, and the Future of Technology &#8211; David Rose (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/enchanted-objects-innovation-design-and-the-future-of-technology-david-rose-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/enchanted-objects-innovation-design-and-the-future-of-technology-david-rose-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the tradition of Who Owns the Future, an MIT Media Lab scientist imagines how everyday objects can intuit our needs, improve our lives, and form &#8220;an ethereal interconnection of gadgets and human desires that&#8230;will pervade our lives in the very near future&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal). We are now standing at the precipice of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enchanted-objects-innovation-design-and-the-future-of-technology-david-rose-abridged/">Enchanted Objects : Innovation, Design, and the Future of Technology &#8211; David Rose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the tradition of Who Owns the Future, an MIT Media Lab scientist imagines how everyday objects can intuit our needs, improve our lives, and form &#8220;an ethereal interconnection of gadgets and human desires that&#8230;will pervade our lives in the very near future&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).     </p>
<p>                    We are now standing at the precipice of the next transformative development, a world in which technology becomes more human. Soon, connected technology will be embedded in hundreds of everyday objects we already use: our cars, wallets, watches, umbrellas, even our trash cans. These objects will respond to our needs, come to know us, and even learn to think ahead on our behalf. David Rose calls these devices&#8211;which are just beginning to creep into the marketplace&#8211;Enchanted Objects.     </p>
<p>                     In Rose&#8217;s vision of the future, technology atomizes, combining itself with the objects that make up the very fabric of daily living. Such innovations will be woven into the background of our environment, enhancing human relationships, channeling desires for omniscience, long life, and creative expression. The enchanted objects of fairy tales and science fiction will enter real life.     </p>
<p>                     Groundbreaking, timely, and provocative, Enchanted Objects is a &#8220;delightful&#8221; (The New York Times) blueprint for a better future, where efficient solutions come hand in hand with technology that delights our senses. It is essential reading for designers, technologists, entrepreneurs, business leaders, and anyone who wishes to take a glimpse into the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enchanted-objects-innovation-design-and-the-future-of-technology-david-rose-abridged/">Enchanted Objects : Innovation, Design, and the Future of Technology &#8211; David Rose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Seventh Sense : Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks &#8211; Joshua Cooper Ramo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WASHINGTON POST BESTSELLER Winner of the getAbstract 17th International Book Award &#8220;The Seventh Sense is a concept every businessman, diplomat, or student should aspire to master&#8211;a powerful idea, backed by stories and figures that will be impossible to forget.&#8221; &#8212; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs and Leonardo da Vinci Endless [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/">The Seventh Sense : Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks &#8211; Joshua Cooper Ramo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    WASHINGTON POST BESTSELLER Winner of the getAbstract 17th International Book Award &#8220;The Seventh Sense is a concept every businessman, diplomat, or student should aspire to master&#8211;a powerful idea, backed by stories and figures that will be impossible to forget.&#8221; &#8212; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs and Leonardo da Vinci Endless terror. Refugee waves. An unfixable global economy. Surprising election results. New billion-dollar fortunes. Miracle medical advances. What if they were all connected? What if you could understand why?  The Seventh Sense is the story of what all of today&#8217;s successful figures see and feel: the forces that are invisible to most of us but explain everything from explosive technological change to uneasy political ripples. The secret to power now is understanding our new age of networks. Not merely the Internet, but also webs of trade, finance, and even DNA. Based on his years of advising generals, CEOs, and politicians, Ramo takes us into the opaque heart of our world&#8217;s rapidly connected systems and teaches us what the losers are not yet seeing&#8211;and what the victors of this age already know.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/">The Seventh Sense : Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks &#8211; Joshua Cooper Ramo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Them : Why We Hate Each Other&#8211;and How to Heal &#8211; Ben Sasse (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Something is wrong. We all know it. American life expectancy is declining for a third straight year. Birth rates are dropping. Nearly half of us think the other political party isn&#8217;t just wrong; they&#8217;re evil. We&#8217;re the richest country in history, but we&#8217;ve never been more pessimistic. What&#8217;s causing the despair? In Them, bestselling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/">Them : Why We Hate Each Other&#8211;and How to Heal &#8211; Ben Sasse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Something is wrong. We all know it. American life expectancy is declining for a third straight year. Birth rates are dropping. Nearly half of us think the other political party isn&#8217;t just wrong; they&#8217;re evil. We&#8217;re the richest country in history, but we&#8217;ve never been more pessimistic. What&#8217;s causing the despair?    </p>
<p>                    In Them, bestselling author and U.S. senator Ben Sasse argues that our crisis isn&#8217;t really about politics. It&#8217;s that we&#8217;re so lonely we can&#8217;t see straight &#8211; and it bubbles out as anger. Local communities are collapsing. Across the nation, little leagues are disappearing, Rotary clubs are dwindling, and in all likelihood, we don&#8217;t know the neighbour two doors down. Work isn&#8217;t what we&#8217;d hoped: less certainty, few lifelong coworkers, shallow purpose. Stable families and enduring friendships &#8211; life&#8217;s fundamental pillars &#8211; are in statistical freefall.    </p>
<p>                    As traditional tribes of place evaporate, we rally against common enemies so we can feel part of a team. No institutions command widespread public trust, enabling foreign intelligence agencies to use technology to pick the scabs on our toxic divisions. We&#8217;re in danger of half of us believing different facts than the other half, and the digital revolution throws gas on the fire.    </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s a path forward &#8211; but reversing our decline requires something radical: a rediscovery of real places and human-to-human relationships. Even as technology nudges us to become rootless, Sasse shows how only a recovery of rootedness can heal our lonely souls. America wants you to be happy, but more urgently, America needs you to love your neighbour and connect with your community. Fixing what&#8217;s wrong with the country depends on it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/">Them : Why We Hate Each Other&#8211;and How to Heal &#8211; Ben Sasse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Nonfiction Pick; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly Best Book of the Year Clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair takes an in-depth look at how the Internet and the digital revolution are profoundly changing childhood and family dynamics, and offers solutions parents can use to successfully shepherd their children through the technological wilderness. As the focus of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/">The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Nonfiction Pick; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly Best Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair takes an in-depth look at how the Internet and the digital revolution are profoundly changing childhood and family dynamics, and offers solutions parents can use to successfully shepherd their children through the technological wilderness.    </p>
<p>                    As the focus of the family has turned to the glow of the screen&#8211;children constantly texting their friends or going online to do homework; parents working online around the clock&#8211;everyday life is undergoing a massive transformation. Easy access to the Internet and social media has erased the boundaries that protect children from damaging exposure to excessive marketing and the unsavory aspects of adult culture. Parents often feel they are losing a meaningful connection with their children. Children are feeling lonely and alienated. The digital world is here to stay, but what are families losing with technology&#8217;s gain?    </p>
<p>                    As renowned clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair explains, families are in crisis as they face this issue, and even more so than they realize. Not only do chronic tech distractions have deep and lasting effects but children also desperately need parents to provide what tech cannot: close, significant interactions with the adults in their lives. Drawing on real-life stories from her clinical work with children and parents and her consulting work with educators and experts across the country, Steiner-Adair offers insights and advice that can help parents achieve greater understanding, authority, and confidence as they engage with the tech revolution unfolding in their living rooms.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/">The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>So You&#8217;ve Been Publicly Shamed &#8211; Jon Ronson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/so-youve-been-publicly-shamed-jon-ronson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/so-youve-been-publicly-shamed-jon-ronson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Jon Ronson, the Sunday Times top ten bestselling author of The Psychopath Test, this is a captivating and brilliant exploration of one of our world&#8217;s most underappreciated forces: shame. &#8216;It&#8217;s about the terror, isn&#8217;t it?&#8217; &#8216;The terror of what?&#8217; I said. &#8216;The terror of being found out.&#8217; Jon Ronson has travelled the world meeting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/so-youve-been-publicly-shamed-jon-ronson-abridged/">So You&#8217;ve Been Publicly Shamed &#8211; Jon Ronson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Jon Ronson, the Sunday Times top ten bestselling author of The Psychopath Test, this is a captivating and brilliant exploration of one of our world&#8217;s most underappreciated forces: shame.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s about the terror, isn&#8217;t it?&#8217;<br />
                    &#8216;The terror of what?&#8217; I said.<br />
                    &#8216;The terror of being found out.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Jon Ronson has travelled the world meeting recipients of high-profile public shamings. The shamed are people like us &#8211; people who, say, made a joke on social media that came out badly, or made a mistake at work. Once their transgression is revealed, collective outrage circles with the force of a hurricane and the next thing they know they&#8217;re being torn apart by an angry mob, jeered at, demonized, sometimes even fired from their job.    </p>
<p>                    A great renaissance of public shaming is sweeping our land. Justice has been democratized. The silent majority are getting a voice. But what are we doing with our voice? We are mercilessly finding people&#8217;s faults. We are defining the boundaries of normality by ruining the lives of those outside it. We are using shame as a form of social control.    </p>
<p>                    Simultaneously powerful and hilarious in the way only Jon Ronson can be, So You&#8217;ve Been Publicly Shamed is a deeply honest book about modern life, full of eye-opening truths about the escalating war on human flaws &#8211; and the very scary part we all play in it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/so-youve-been-publicly-shamed-jon-ronson-abridged/">So You&#8217;ve Been Publicly Shamed &#8211; Jon Ronson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Surveillance Capitalism : The Fight for a Human Future at the New Frontier of Power: Barack Obama&#8217;s Books of 2019 &#8211; Professor Shoshana Zuboff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-the-fight-for-a-human-future-at-the-new-frontier-of-power-barack-obamas-books-of-2019-professor-shoshana-zuboff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-the-fight-for-a-human-future-at-the-new-frontier-of-power-barack-obamas-books-of-2019-professor-shoshana-zuboff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP 10 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER A NEW YORK TIMES NOTABLE BOOK OF THE YEAR ONE OF BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S TOP BOOKS OF THE YEAR Shortlisted for The Orwell Prize 2020 Shortlisted for the FT Business Book of the Year Award 2019 &#8216;Easily the most important book to be published this century. I find it hard [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-the-fight-for-a-human-future-at-the-new-frontier-of-power-barack-obamas-books-of-2019-professor-shoshana-zuboff-abridged/">The Age of Surveillance Capitalism : The Fight for a Human Future at the New Frontier of Power: Barack Obama&#8217;s Books of 2019 &#8211; Professor Shoshana Zuboff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP 10 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    A NEW YORK TIMES NOTABLE BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    ONE OF BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S TOP BOOKS OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for The Orwell Prize 2020    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the FT Business Book of the Year Award 2019    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Easily the most  important book to be published this  century. I find it hard to take any  young activist seriously who hasn&#8217;t  at least familarised themselves  with Zuboff&#8217;s central ideas.&#8217; &#8211; Zadie Smith, The Guardian    </p>
<p>                    The challenges to humanity posed by the digital future, the first detailed examination of the unprecedented form of power called &#8220;surveillance capitalism,&#8221; and the quest by powerful corporations to predict and control us.    </p>
<p>                    The heady optimism of the Internet&#8217;s early days is gone. Technologies that were meant to liberate us have deepened inequality and stoked divisions. Tech companies gather our information online and sell it to the highest bidder, whether government or retailer. Profits now depend not only on predicting our behaviour but modifying it too. How will this fusion of capitalism and the digital shape our values and define our future?    </p>
<p>                    Shoshana Zuboff shows that we are at a crossroads. We still have the power to decide what kind of world we want to live in, and what we decide now will shape the rest of the century. Our choices: allow technology to enrich the few and impoverish the many, or harness it and distribute its benefits.    </p>
<p>                     The Age of Surveillance Capitalism is a deeply-reasoned examination of the threat of unprecedented power free from democratic oversight. As it explores this new capitalism&#8217;s impact on society, politics, business, and technology, it exposes the struggles that will decide both the next chapter of capitalism and the meaning of information civilization. Most critically, it shows how we can protect ourselves and our communities and ensure we are the masters of the digital rather than its slaves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-the-fight-for-a-human-future-at-the-new-frontier-of-power-barack-obamas-books-of-2019-professor-shoshana-zuboff-abridged/">The Age of Surveillance Capitalism : The Fight for a Human Future at the New Frontier of Power: Barack Obama&#8217;s Books of 2019 &#8211; Professor Shoshana Zuboff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Soonish : Ten Emerging Technologies That Will Improve and/or Ruin Everything &#8211; Dr. Kelly Weinersmith, Zach Weinersmith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/soonish-ten-emerging-technologies-that-will-improve-and-or-ruin-everything-dr-kelly-weinersmith-zach-weinersmith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cartoons & Comic Strips]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Engineering: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inventions & Inventors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/soonish-ten-emerging-technologies-that-will-improve-and-or-ruin-everything-dr-kelly-weinersmith-zach-weinersmith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What will the world of tomorrow be like? How does progress happen? And why don&#8217;t we have a lunar colony already? In this witty and entertaining book, Kelly and Zach Weinersmith give us a snapshot of the transformative technologies that are coming next &#8211; from robot swarms to nuclear fusion powered-toasters &#8211; and explain how [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/soonish-ten-emerging-technologies-that-will-improve-and-or-ruin-everything-dr-kelly-weinersmith-zach-weinersmith-abridged/">Soonish : Ten Emerging Technologies That Will Improve and/or Ruin Everything &#8211; Dr. Kelly Weinersmith, Zach Weinersmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What will the world of tomorrow be like? How does progress happen? And why don&#8217;t we have a lunar colony already? In this witty and entertaining book, Kelly and Zach Weinersmith give us a snapshot of the transformative technologies that are coming next &#8211; from robot swarms to nuclear fusion powered-toasters &#8211; and explain how they will change our world in astonishing ways. By weaving together their own research, interviews with pioneering scientists and Zach&#8217;s trademark comics, the Weinersmiths investigate why these innovations are needed, how they would work, and what is standing in their way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/soonish-ten-emerging-technologies-that-will-improve-and-or-ruin-everything-dr-kelly-weinersmith-zach-weinersmith-abridged/">Soonish : Ten Emerging Technologies That Will Improve and/or Ruin Everything &#8211; Dr. Kelly Weinersmith, Zach Weinersmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Do Nothing : Resisting the Attention Economy &#8211; Jenny Odell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-do-nothing-resisting-the-attention-economy-jenny-odell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art & Photography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic & Video Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-do-nothing-resisting-the-attention-economy-jenny-odell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** A New York Times Bestseller ** NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY: Time &#8211; The New Yorker &#8211; NPR &#8211; GQ &#8211; Elle &#8211; Vulture &#8211; Fortune &#8211; Boing Boing &#8211; The Irish Times &#8211; The New York Public Library &#8211; The Brooklyn Public Library A complex, smart and ambitious [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-do-nothing-resisting-the-attention-economy-jenny-odell-abridged/">How To Do Nothing : Resisting the Attention Economy &#8211; Jenny Odell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** A New York Times Bestseller **     </p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY: Time &#8211; The New Yorker &#8211; NPR &#8211; GQ &#8211; Elle &#8211; Vulture &#8211; Fortune &#8211; Boing Boing &#8211; The Irish Times &#8211; The New York Public Library &#8211; The Brooklyn Public Library     </p>
<p>                    A complex, smart and ambitious book that at first reads like a self-help manual, then blossoms into a wide-ranging political manifesto.&#8211;Jonah Engel Bromwich, The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    One of President Barack Obama&#8217;s Favorite Books of 2019<br />
                    Porchlight&#8217;s Personal Development &#038; Human Behavior Book of the Year     </p>
<p>                    In a world where addictive technology is designed to buy and sell our attention, and our value is determined by our 24/7 data productivity, it can seem impossible to escape. But in this inspiring field guide to dropping out of the attention economy, artist and critic Jenny Odell shows us how we can still win back our lives.     </p>
<p>                     Odell sees our attention as the most precious&#8211;and overdrawn&#8211;resource we have. And we must actively and continuously choose how we use it. We might not spend it on things that capitalism has deemed important &#8230; but once we can start paying a new kind of attention, she writes, we can undertake bolder forms of political action, reimagine humankind&#8217;s role in the environment, and arrive at more meaningful understandings of happiness and progress.     </p>
<p>                     Far from the simple anti-technology screed, or the back-to-nature meditation we read so often, How to do Nothing is an action plan for thinking outside of capitalist narratives of efficiency and techno-determinism. Provocative, timely, and utterly persuasive, this book will change how you see your place in our world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-do-nothing-resisting-the-attention-economy-jenny-odell-abridged/">How To Do Nothing : Resisting the Attention Economy &#8211; Jenny Odell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agnosticism & Atheism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eclectic & Esoteric Religions & Belief Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An extraordinary book . . . It will shake up your most fundamental beliefs about everyday experience, and it just might change your life.&#8217; Paul Bloom ___ For the millions of people who want spirituality without religion, Sam Harris&#8217;s new book is a guide to meditation as a rational spiritual practice informed by neuroscience and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/">Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An extraordinary book . . . It will shake up your most fundamental beliefs about everyday experience, and it just might change your life.&#8217; Paul Bloom<br />
                    ___    </p>
<p>                    For the millions of people who want spirituality without religion, Sam Harris&#8217;s new book is a guide to meditation as a rational spiritual practice informed by neuroscience and psychology.    </p>
<p>                     Throughout the book, Harris argues that there are important truths to be found in the experience of contemplatives such as Jesus, Buddha and other saints and sages of history-and, therefore, that there is more to understanding reality than science and secular culture generally allow.    </p>
<p>                    Waking Up is part seeker&#8217;s memoir and part exploration of the scientific underpinnings of spirituality. No other book marries contemplative wisdom and modern science in this way, and no author other than Sam Harris-a scientist, philosopher, and famous sceptic-could write it.<br />
                     ___    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A demanding, illusion-shattering book.&#8217; Kirkus Reviews<br />
                    &#8216;A pleasure to read.&#8217; Huffington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/">Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult Education, Continuous Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employment & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Services & Welfare, Criminology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for ways to handle the transition to a digital economy.Robots, artificial intelligence, and driverless cars are no longer things of the distant future. They are with us today and will become increasingly common in coming years, along with virtual reality and digital personal assistants. As these tools advance deeper into everyday use, they raise [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/">The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Looking for ways to handle the transition to a digital economy.Robots, artificial intelligence, and driverless cars are no longer things of the distant future. They are with us today and will become increasingly common in coming years, along with virtual reality and digital personal assistants.    </p>
<p>                    As these tools advance deeper into everyday use, they raise the question-how will they transform society, the economy, and politics? If companies need fewer workers due to automation and robotics, what happens to those who once held those jobs and don&#8217;t have the skills for new jobs? And since many social benefits are delivered through jobs, how are people outside the workforce for a lengthy period of time going to earn a living and get health care and social benefits?    </p>
<p>                    Looking past today&#8217;s headlines, political scientist and cultural observer Darrell M. West argues that society needs to rethink the concept of jobs, reconfigure the social contract, move toward a system of lifetime learning, and develop a new kind of politics that can deal with economic dislocations. With the U.S. governance system in shambles because of political polarization and hyper-partisanship, dealing creatively with the transition to a fully digital economy will vex political leaders and complicate the adoption of remedies that could ease the transition pain. It is imperative that we make major adjustments in how we think about work and the social contract in order to prevent society from spiraling out of control.    </p>
<p>                    This book presents a number of proposals to help people deal with the transition from an industrial to a digital economy. We must broaden the  concept of employment to include volunteering and parenting and pay greater attention to the opportunities for leisure time. New forms of identity will be possible when the &#8220;job&#8221; no longer defines people&#8217;s sense of personal meaning, and they engage in a broader range of activities. Workers will need help throughout their lifetimes to acquire new skills and develop new job capabilities. Political reforms will be necessary to  reduce polarization and restore civility so there can be open and healthy debate about where responsibility lies for economic well-being.    </p>
<p>                    This book is an important contribution to a discussion about tomorrow-one that needs to take place today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/">The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Changing the Subject : Art and Attention in the Internet Age &#8211; Sven Birkerts (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/changing-the-subject-art-and-attention-in-the-internet-age-sven-birkerts-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/changing-the-subject-art-and-attention-in-the-internet-age-sven-birkerts-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Trenchant, expansive essays on the cultural consequences of ongoing, all-permeating technological innovation In 1994, Sven Birkerts published The Gutenberg Elegies, his celebrated rallying cry to resist the oncoming digital advances, especially those that might affect the way we read literature and experience art&#8211;the very cultural activities that make us human. After two decades of rampant [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/changing-the-subject-art-and-attention-in-the-internet-age-sven-birkerts-abridged/">Changing the Subject : Art and Attention in the Internet Age &#8211; Sven Birkerts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Trenchant, expansive essays on the cultural consequences of ongoing, all-permeating technological innovation    </p>
<p>                    In 1994, Sven Birkerts published The Gutenberg Elegies, his celebrated rallying cry to resist the oncoming digital advances, especially those that might affect the way we read literature and experience art&#8211;the very cultural activities that make us human.<br />
                     After two decades of rampant change, Birkerts has allowed a degree of everyday digital technology into his life. He refuses to use a smartphone, but communicates via e-mail and spends some time reading online. In Changing the Subject, he examines the changes that he observes in himself and others&#8211;the distraction when reading on the screen; the loss of personal agency through reliance on GPS and one-stop information resources; an increasing acceptance of &#8220;hive&#8221; behaviors. &#8220;An unprecedented shift is underway,&#8221; he argues, and &#8220;this transformation is dramatically accelerated and more psychologically formative than any previous technological innovation.&#8221; He finds solace in engagement with art, particularly literature, and he brilliantly describes the countering energy available to us through acts of sustained attention, even as he worries that our increasingly mediated existences are not conducive to creativity.<br />
                     It is impossible to read Changing the Subject without coming away with a renewed sense of what is lost by our wholesale acceptance of digital innovation and what is regained when we immerse ourselves in a good book.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/changing-the-subject-art-and-attention-in-the-internet-age-sven-birkerts-abridged/">Changing the Subject : Art and Attention in the Internet Age &#8211; Sven Birkerts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Autonomy : The Quest to Build the Driverless Car-And How It Will Reshape Our World &#8211; Lawrence D. Burns, Christopher Shulgan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automotive Technology & Trades]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Road Vehicle Manufacturing Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transport Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An automotive and tech world insider investigates the quest to develop and perfect the driverless car&#8211;an innovation that promises to be the most disruptive change to our way of life since the smartphone We stand on the brink of a technological revolution. Soon, few of us will own our own automobiles and instead will get [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/">Autonomy : The Quest to Build the Driverless Car-And How It Will Reshape Our World &#8211; Lawrence D. Burns, Christopher Shulgan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An automotive and tech world insider investigates the quest to develop and perfect the driverless car&#8211;an innovation that promises to be the most disruptive change to our way of life since the smartphone    </p>
<p>                    We stand on the brink of a technological revolution. Soon, few of us will own our own automobiles and instead will get around in driverless electric vehicles that we summon with the touch of an app. We will be liberated from driving, prevent over 90% of car crashes, provide freedom of mobility to the elderly and disabled, and decrease our dependence on fossil fuels.     </p>
<p>                    Autonomy is the story of the maverick engineers and computer nerds who are creating the revolution. Longtime advisor to the Google Self-Driving Car team and former GM research and development chief Lawrence D. Burns provides the perfectly-timed history of how we arrived at this point, in a character-driven and heavily reported account of the unlikely thinkers who accomplished what billion-dollar automakers never dared.    </p>
<p>                    Beginning with the way 9/11 spurred the U.S. government to set a million-dollar prize for a series of off-road robot races in the Mojave Desert up to the early 2016 stampede to develop driverless technology, Autonomy is a page-turner that represents a chronicle of the past, diagnosis of the present, and prediction of the future&#8211;the ultimate guide to understanding the driverless car and navigating the revolution it sparks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/">Autonomy : The Quest to Build the Driverless Car-And How It Will Reshape Our World &#8211; Lawrence D. Burns, Christopher Shulgan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Demon-Haunted World : Science as a Candle in the Dark &#8211; Carl Sagan, Ann Druyan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A prescient warning of a future we now inhabit, where fake news stories and Internet conspiracy theories play to a disaffected American populace &#8220;A glorious book . . . A spirited defense of science . . . From the first page to the last, this book is a manifesto for clear thought.&#8221;&#8211;Los Angeles Times How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/">The Demon-Haunted World : Science as a Candle in the Dark &#8211; Carl Sagan, Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A prescient warning of a future we now inhabit, where fake news stories and Internet conspiracy theories play to a disaffected American populace     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A glorious book . . . A spirited defense of science . . . From the first page to the last, this book is a manifesto for clear thought.&#8221;&#8211;Los Angeles Times     </p>
<p>                     How can we make intelligent decisions about our increasingly technology-driven lives if we don&#8217;t understand the difference between the myths of pseudoscience and the testable hypotheses of science? Pulitzer Prize-winning author and distinguished astronomer Carl Sagan argues that scientific thinking is critical not only to the pursuit of truth but to the very well-being of our democratic institutions.     </p>
<p>                     Casting a wide net through history and culture, Sagan examines and authoritatively debunks such celebrated fallacies of the past as witchcraft, faith healing, demons, and UFOs. And yet, disturbingly, in today&#8217;s so-called information age, pseudoscience is burgeoning with stories of alien abduction, channeling past lives, and communal hallucinations commanding growing attention and respect. As Sagan demonstrates with lucid eloquence, the siren song of unreason is not just a cultural wrong turn but a dangerous plunge into darkness that threatens our most basic freedoms.     </p>
<p>                     Praise for The Demon-Haunted World     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Powerful . . . A stirring defense of informed rationality. . . Rich in surprising information and beautiful writing.&#8221;&#8211;The Washington Post Book World     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Compelling.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A clear vision of what good science means and why it makes a difference. . . . A testimonial to the power of science and a warning of the dangers of unrestrained credulity.&#8221;&#8211;The Sciences     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Passionate.&#8221;&#8211;San Francisco Examiner-Chronicle</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/">The Demon-Haunted World : Science as a Candle in the Dark &#8211; Carl Sagan, Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As we approach a great turning point in history when technology is poised to redefine what it means to be human, The Fourth Age offers fascinating insight into AI, robotics, and their extraordinary implications for our species. &#8220;If you only read just one book about the AI revolution, make it this one&#8221; (John Mackey, cofounder [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/">The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As we approach a great turning point in history when technology is poised to redefine what it means to be human, The Fourth Age offers fascinating insight into AI, robotics, and their extraordinary implications for our species. &#8220;If you only read just one book about the AI revolution, make it this one&#8221; (John Mackey, cofounder and CEO, Whole Foods Market).     </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Age, Byron Reese makes the case that technology has reshaped humanity just three times in history: 100,000 years ago, we harnessed fire, which led to language; 10,000 years ago, we developed agriculture, which led to cities and warfare; 5,000 years ago, we invented the wheel and writing, which lead to the nation state.    </p>
<p>                    We are now on the doorstep of a fourth change brought about by two technologies: AI and robotics. &#8220;Timely, highly informative, and certainly optimistic&#8221; (Booklist), The Fourth Age provides an essential background on how we got to this point, and how-rather than what-we should think about the topics we&#8217;ll soon all be facing: machine consciousness, automation, changes in employment, creative computers, radical life extension, artificial life, AI ethics, the future of warfare, superintelligence, and the implications of extreme prosperity.    </p>
<p>                    By asking questions like &#8220;Are you a machine?&#8221; and &#8220;Could a computer feel anything?&#8221;, Reese leads you through a discussion along the cutting edge in robotics and AI, and provides a framework by which we can all understand, discuss, and act on the issues of the Fourth Age and how they&#8217;ll transform humanity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/">The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology: Mammals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans. Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests? By studying [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this thought-provoking book, the acclaimed author of Our Inner Ape examines how empathy comes naturally to a great variety of animals, including humans.      </p>
<p>                    Are we our brothers&#8217; keepers? Do we have an instinct for compassion? Or are we, as is often assumed, only on earth to serve our own survival and interests?     </p>
<p>                    By studying social behaviors in animals, such as bonding, the herd instinct, the forming of trusting alliances, expressions of consolation, and conflict resolution, Frans de Waal demonstrates that animals-and humans-are preprogrammed to reach out. He has found that chimpanzees care for mates that are wounded by leopards, elephants offer reassuring rumbles to youngsters in distress, and dolphins support sick companions near the water&#8217;s surface to prevent them from drowning. From day one humans have innate sensitivities to faces, bodies, and voices; we&#8217;ve been designed to feel for one another.     </p>
<p>                    De Waal&#8217;s theory runs counter to the assumption that humans are inherently selfish, which can be seen in the fields of politics, law, and finance. But he cites the public&#8217;s outrage at the U.S. government&#8217;s lack of empathy in the wake of Hurricane Katrina as a significant shift in perspective-one that helped Barack Obama become elected and ushered in what perhaps could become an Age of Empathy. Through a better understanding of empathy&#8217;s survival value in evolution, de Waal suggests, we can work together toward a more just society based on a more generous and accurate view of human nature.     </p>
<p>                    Written in layman&#8217;s prose with a wealth of anecdotes, wry humor, and incisive intelligence, The Age of Empathy is essential reading for our embattled times.     </p>
<p>                    An important and timely message about the biological roots of human kindness.&#8211;Desmond Morris, author of The Naked Ape</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-empathy-natures-lessons-for-a-kinder-society-frans-de-waal-abridged/">The Age of Empathy : Nature&#8217;s Lessons for a Kinder Society &#8211; Frans De Waal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wonderland : How Play Made the Modern World &#8211; Steven Johnson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wonderland-how-play-made-the-modern-world-steven-johnson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hobby and Gaming Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inventions & Inventors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wonderland-how-play-made-the-modern-world-steven-johnson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The book is a house of wonders&#8217; The New York Times &#8216;Steven Johnson is the Darwin of technology&#8217; Walter Issacson, author of Steve Jobs What connects Paleolithic bone flutes to the invention of computer software? Or the Murex sea snail to the death of the great American city? How does the bag of crisps you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wonderland-how-play-made-the-modern-world-steven-johnson-abridged/">Wonderland : How Play Made the Modern World &#8211; Steven Johnson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The book is a house of wonders&#8217; The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Steven Johnson is the Darwin of technology&#8217; Walter Issacson, author of Steve Jobs    </p>
<p>                    What connects Paleolithic bone flutes to the invention of computer software? Or the Murex sea snail to the death of the great American city? How does the bag of crisps you hold in your hand help tell the story of humanity itself?     </p>
<p>                    In his brilliant new work on the history of innovation, international bestseller Steven Johnson argues that the pursuit of novelty and wonder has always been a powerful driver of world-shaping technological change. He finds that  that throughout history, the cutting edge of innovation lies wherever people are working the hardest to keep themselves and others amused.     </p>
<p>                    Johnson&#8217;s storytelling is just as delightful as the inventions he describes, full of surprising stops along the journey from simple concepts to complex modern systems. He introduces us to the colourful innovators of leisure: the explorers, proprietors, showmen, and artists who changed the trajectory of history with their luxurious wares, exotic meals, taverns, gambling tables, and magic shows.    </p>
<p>                    Johnson compellingly argues that observers of technological and social trends should be looking for clues in novel amusements. You&#8217;ll find the future wherever people are having the most fun.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wonderland-how-play-made-the-modern-world-steven-johnson-abridged/">Wonderland : How Play Made the Modern World &#8211; Steven Johnson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Speak Machine : Computational Thinking for the Rest of Us &#8211; John Maeda (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-speak-machine-computational-thinking-for-the-rest-of-us-john-maeda-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Programming / Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-speak-machine-computational-thinking-for-the-rest-of-us-john-maeda-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Visionary designer and technologist John Maeda defines the fundamental laws of how computers think, and why you should care even if you aren&#8217;t a programmer. &#8220;Maeda is to design what Warren Buffett is to finance.&#8221; &#8211;Wired John Maeda is one of the world&#8217;s preeminent interdisciplinary thinkers on technology and design. In How to Speak Machine, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-speak-machine-computational-thinking-for-the-rest-of-us-john-maeda-abridged/">How to Speak Machine : Computational Thinking for the Rest of Us &#8211; John Maeda (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Visionary designer and technologist John Maeda defines the fundamental laws of how computers think, and why you should care even if you aren&#8217;t a programmer.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Maeda is to design what Warren Buffett is to finance.&#8221; &#8211;Wired    </p>
<p>                    John Maeda is one of the world&#8217;s preeminent interdisciplinary thinkers on technology and design. In How to Speak Machine, he offers a set of simple laws that govern not only the computers of today, but the unimaginable machines of the future.     </p>
<p>                    Technology is already more powerful than we can comprehend, and getting more powerful at an exponential pace. Once set in motion, algorithms never tire. And when a program&#8217;s size, speed, and tirelessness combine with its ability to learn and transform itself, the outcome can be unpredictable and dangerous. Take the seemingly instant transformation of Microsoft&#8217;s chatbot Tay into a hate-spewing racist, or how crime-predicting algorithms reinforce racial bias.    </p>
<p>                    How to Speak Machine provides a coherent framework for today&#8217;s product designers, business leaders, and policymakers to grasp this brave new world. Drawing on his wide-ranging experience from engineering to computer science to design, Maeda shows how businesses and individuals can identify opportunities afforded by technology to make world-changing and inclusive products&#8211;while avoiding the pitfalls inherent to the medium.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-speak-machine-computational-thinking-for-the-rest-of-us-john-maeda-abridged/">How to Speak Machine : Computational Thinking for the Rest of Us &#8211; John Maeda (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What To Do When Machines Do Everything : How to Get Ahead in a World of AI, Algorithms, Bots, and Big Data &#8211; Malcolm Frank, Paul Roehrig, Ben Pring (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Systems & Equipment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The essential playbook for the future of your business What To Do When Machines Do Everything is a guidebook to succeeding in the next generation of the digital economy. When systems running on Artificial Intelligence can drive our cars, diagnose medical patients, and manage our finances more effectively than humans it raises profound questions on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/">What To Do When Machines Do Everything : How to Get Ahead in a World of AI, Algorithms, Bots, and Big Data &#8211; Malcolm Frank, Paul Roehrig, Ben Pring (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The essential playbook for the future of your business What To Do When Machines Do Everything is a guidebook to succeeding in the next generation of the digital economy. When systems running on Artificial Intelligence can drive our cars, diagnose medical patients, and manage our finances more effectively than humans it raises profound questions on the future of work and how companies compete. Illustrated with real-world cases, data, and insight, the authors provide clear strategic guidance and actionable steps to help you and your organization move ahead in a world where exponentially developing new technologies are changing how value is created. Written by a team of business and technology expert practitioners who also authored Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business this book provides a clear path to the future of your work. The first part of the book examines the once in a generation upheaval most every organization will soon face as systems of intelligence go mainstream.<br />
                    The authors argue that contrary to the doom and gloom that surrounds much of IT and business at the moment, we are in fact on the cusp of the biggest wave of opportunity creation since the Industrial Revolution. Next, the authors detail a clear-cut business model to help leaders take part in this coming boom; the AHEAD model outlines five strategic initiatives Automate, Halos, Enhance, Abundance, and Discovery that are central to competing in the next phase of global business by driving new levels of efficiency, customer intimacy and innovation. Business leaders today have two options: be swallowed up by the ongoing technological evolution, or ride the crest of the wave to new profits and better business. This book shows you how to avoid your own extinction event, and will help you; * Understand the untold full extent of technology&#8217;s impact on the way we work and live.<br />
                    * Find out where we&#8217;re headed, and how soon the future will arrive * Leverage the new emerging paradigm into a sustainable business advantage * Adopt a strategic model for winning in the new economy The digital world is already transforming how we work, live, and shop, how we are governed and entertained, and how we manage our money, health, security, and relationships. Don&#8217;t let your business or your career get left behind. What To Do When Machines Do Everything is your strategic roadmap to a future full of possibility and success. Or peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/">What To Do When Machines Do Everything : How to Get Ahead in a World of AI, Algorithms, Bots, and Big Data &#8211; Malcolm Frank, Paul Roehrig, Ben Pring (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award A New York Times technology and business reporter charts the dramatic rise of Bitcoin and the fascinating personalities who are striving to create a new global money for the Internet age. Digital Gold is New York Times reporter Nathaniel Popper&#8217;s brilliant and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/">Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award    </p>
<p>                    A New York Times technology and business reporter charts the dramatic rise of Bitcoin and the fascinating personalities who are striving to create a new global money for the Internet age.    </p>
<p>                    Digital Gold is New York Times reporter Nathaniel Popper&#8217;s brilliant and engrossing history of Bitcoin, the landmark digital money and financial technology that has spawned a global social movement.    </p>
<p>                    The notion of a new currency, maintained by the computers of users around the world, has been the butt of many jokes, but that has not stopped it from growing into a technology worth billions of dollars, supported by the hordes of followers who have come to view it as the most important new idea since the creation of the Internet. Believers from Beijing to Buenos Aires see the potential for a financial system free from banks and governments. More than just a tech industry fad, Bitcoin has threatened to decentralize some of society&#8217;s most basic institutions.    </p>
<p>                    An unusual tale of group invention, Digital Gold charts the rise of the Bitcoin technology through the eyes of the movement&#8217;s colorful central characters, including an Argentinian millionaire, a Chinese entrepreneur, Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss, and Bitcoin&#8217;s elusive creator, Satoshi Nakamoto. Already, Bitcoin has led to untold riches for some, and prison terms for others.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/">Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Fly A Horse : The Secret History of Creation, Invention, and Discovery &#8211; Kevin Ashton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-fly-a-horse-the-secret-history-of-creation-invention-and-discovery-kevin-ashton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inventions & Inventors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-fly-a-horse-the-secret-history-of-creation-invention-and-discovery-kevin-ashton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE 800-CEO-READ BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR 2015 In the vein of Susan Cain&#8217;s QUIET and Malcolm Gladwell&#8217;s DAVID AND GOLIATH, HOW TO FLY A HORSE is a smart, empowering book that dispels the myths around genius and creativity. There is a myth about how something new comes to be; that geniuses have [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fly-a-horse-the-secret-history-of-creation-invention-and-discovery-kevin-ashton-abridged/">How To Fly A Horse : The Secret History of Creation, Invention, and Discovery &#8211; Kevin Ashton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE 800-CEO-READ BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR 2015    </p>
<p>                    In the vein of Susan Cain&#8217;s QUIET and Malcolm Gladwell&#8217;s DAVID AND GOLIATH, HOW TO FLY A HORSE is a smart, empowering book that dispels the myths around genius and creativity.    </p>
<p>                    There is a myth about how something new comes to be; that geniuses have dramatic moments of insight where great things and thoughts are born whole. Symphonies are composed complete. Science is accomplished with eureka shrieks. Businesses are built by magic touch.    </p>
<p>                    The myth is wrong. Anyone can create.     </p>
<p>                    Acclaimed technology pioneer Kevin Ashton takes us behind the scenes of creation to reveal the true process of discovery and how &#8216;new&#8217; comes to be. From Archimedes to Apple, from Kandinsky to the Coke can, from the Wright brothers &#8211; who set out to &#8216;fly a horse&#8217; &#8211; to Woody Allen, he exposes the seemingly unremarkable individuals, gradual steps, multiple failures and countless ordinary and often uncredited acts that led to our most astounding breakthroughs.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fly-a-horse-the-secret-history-of-creation-invention-and-discovery-kevin-ashton-abridged/">How To Fly A Horse : The Secret History of Creation, Invention, and Discovery &#8211; Kevin Ashton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper : How Innovation Keeps Proving the Catastrophists Wrong &#8211; Robert Bryce (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/smaller-faster-lighter-denser-cheaper-how-innovation-keeps-proving-the-catastrophists-wrong-robert-bryce-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nanotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/smaller-faster-lighter-denser-cheaper-how-innovation-keeps-proving-the-catastrophists-wrong-robert-bryce-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the face of today&#8217;s environmental and economic challenges, doomsayers preach that the only way to stave off disaster is for humans to reverse course: to de-industrialize, re-localize, ban the use of modern energy sources, and forswear prosperity. But in this provocative and optimistic rebuke to the catastrophists, Robert Bryce shows how innovation and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smaller-faster-lighter-denser-cheaper-how-innovation-keeps-proving-the-catastrophists-wrong-robert-bryce-abridged/">Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper : How Innovation Keeps Proving the Catastrophists Wrong &#8211; Robert Bryce (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the face of today&#8217;s environmental and economic challenges, doomsayers preach that the only way to stave off disaster is for humans to reverse course: to de-industrialize, re-localize, ban the use of modern energy sources, and forswear prosperity. But in this provocative and optimistic rebuke to the catastrophists, Robert Bryce shows how innovation and the inexorable human desire to make things Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper is providing consumers with Cheaper and more abundant energy, Faster computing, Lighter vehicles, and myriad other goods. That same desire is fostering unprecedented prosperity, greater liberty, and yes, better environmental protection.Utilizing on-the-ground reporting from Ottawa to Panama City and Pittsburgh to Bakersfield, Bryce shows how we have, for centuries, been pushing for Smaller Faster solutions to our problems. From the vacuum tube, mass-produced fertilizer, and the printing press to mobile phones, nanotech, and advanced drill rigs, Bryce demonstrates how cutting-edge companies and breakthrough technologies have created a world in which people are living longer, freer, healthier, lives than at any time in human history.The push toward Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper is happening across multiple sectors. Bryce profiles innovative individuals and companies, from long-established ones like Ford and Intel to upstarts like Aquion Energy and Khan Academy. And he zeroes in on the energy industry, proving that the future belongs to the high power density sources that can provide the enormous quantities of energy the world demands.The tools we need to save the planet aren&#8217;t to be found in the technologies or lifestyles of the past. Nor must we sacrifice prosperity and human progress to ensure our survival. The catastrophists have been wrong since the days of Thomas Malthus. This is the time to embrace the innovators and businesses all over the world who are making things Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smaller-faster-lighter-denser-cheaper-how-innovation-keeps-proving-the-catastrophists-wrong-robert-bryce-abridged/">Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper : How Innovation Keeps Proving the Catastrophists Wrong &#8211; Robert Bryce (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Human/Machine : The Future of our Partnership with Machines &#8211; Daniel Newman, Olivier Blanchard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Will the workplace of the future be overrun by machines and robots? Are the new frontiers of artificial intelligence (AI) on the cusp of dethroning us in efficiency, intelligence and innovative potential? Automation and AI will augment our human world and potential. The winners of the future of work are those that harness the power [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/">Human/Machine : The Future of our Partnership with Machines &#8211; Daniel Newman, Olivier Blanchard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Will the workplace of the future be overrun by machines and robots? Are the new frontiers of artificial intelligence (AI) on the cusp of dethroning us in efficiency, intelligence and innovative potential? Automation and AI will augment our human world and potential.     </p>
<p>                    The winners of the future of work are those that harness the power of machines to their advantage. Human/Machine is the only guide you need to understand the fourth industrial revolution. It sets out a road map to the challenges ahead, but also unlocks the wondrous opportunities that it offers.     </p>
<p>                    Human/Machine explores how we will work symbiotically with machines, detailing how institutions, companies, individuals and education providers will evolve to integrate seamlessly with new technologies. With exclusive case studies, this book offers a glimpse into the future and details how top companies are already thriving on this very special relationship. From gamification in job training to project management teams integrated with bots and predictive technologies that fix problems in the supply chain before they happen, the authors deliver a powerful manifesto for the adoption and celebration of automation and AI. In a much more fluid, skills-based economy, we will all need to prove our worth and future-proof our skills base. This book offers a blueprint to avoid being left behind and unearth the opportunities unique to human-machine partnership ecosystems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/">Human/Machine : The Future of our Partnership with Machines &#8211; Daniel Newman, Olivier Blanchard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Merchants of Doubt : How a Handful of Scientists Obscured the Truth on Issues from Tobacco Smoke to Global Warming &#8211; Erik M. Conway, Naomi Oreskes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/merchants-of-doubt-how-a-handful-of-scientists-obscured-the-truth-on-issues-from-tobacco-smoke-to-global-warming-erik-m-conway-naomi-oreskes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/merchants-of-doubt-how-a-handful-of-scientists-obscured-the-truth-on-issues-from-tobacco-smoke-to-global-warming-erik-m-conway-naomi-oreskes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. scientific community has long led the world in research on such areas as public health, environmental science, and issues affecting quality of life. Our scientists have produced landmark studies on the dangers of DDT, tobacco smoke, acid rain, and global warming. But at the same time, a small yet potent subset of this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/merchants-of-doubt-how-a-handful-of-scientists-obscured-the-truth-on-issues-from-tobacco-smoke-to-global-warming-erik-m-conway-naomi-oreskes-abridged/">Merchants of Doubt : How a Handful of Scientists Obscured the Truth on Issues from Tobacco Smoke to Global Warming &#8211; Erik M. Conway, Naomi Oreskes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. scientific community has long led the world in research on such areas as public health, environmental science, and issues affecting quality of life. Our scientists have produced landmark studies on the dangers of DDT, tobacco smoke, acid rain, and global warming. But at the same time, a small yet potent subset of this community leads the world in vehement denial of these dangers.    </p>
<p>                    Merchants of Doubt tells the story of how a loose-knit group of high-level scientists and scientific advisers, with deep connections in politics and industry, ran effective campaigns to mislead the public and deny well-established scientific knowledge over four decades. Remarkably, the same individuals surface repeatedly &#8211; some of the same figures who have claimed that the science of global warming is &#8220;not settled&#8221; denied the truth of studies linking smoking to lung cancer, coal smoke to acid rain, and CFCs to the ozone hole. &#8220;Doubt is our product,&#8221; wrote one tobacco executive. These &#8216;experts&#8217; supplied it.     </p>
<p>                    Naomi Oreskes and Erik M. Conway, historians of science, roll back the rug on this dark corner of the American scientific community, showing how ideology and corporate interests, aided by a too-compliant media, have skewed public understanding of some of the most pressing issues of our era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/merchants-of-doubt-how-a-handful-of-scientists-obscured-the-truth-on-issues-from-tobacco-smoke-to-global-warming-erik-m-conway-naomi-oreskes-abridged/">Merchants of Doubt : How a Handful of Scientists Obscured the Truth on Issues from Tobacco Smoke to Global Warming &#8211; Erik M. Conway, Naomi Oreskes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Information: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT    </p>
<p>                    We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need to be late.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A master class &#8230; As a guide for perplexed Westerners, this book is very hard to beat &#8230; an honest, cohesive explanation for why the world is the way it is, without miracle cures or scapegoats&#8217; John Micklethwait, The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; admirably honest &#8230; injects a badly needed dose of optimism into the modern debate&#8217; Gillian Tett, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;His main piece of advice for individuals, corporations, and countries is clear: Take a deep breath and adapt. This world isn&#8217;t going to wait for you&#8217; Fortune    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A humane and empathetic book&#8217; David Henkin, The Washington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the inventor of the most innovative and compelling technology of our era, an international authority on artificial intelligence, and one of our greatest living visionaries. Now he offers a framework for envisioning the twenty-first century&#8211;an age in which the marriage of human sensitivity and artificial intelligence fundamentally alters and improves the way [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the inventor of the most innovative and compelling technology of our era, an international authority on artificial intelligence, and one of our greatest living visionaries. Now he offers a framework for envisioning the twenty-first century&#8211;an age in which the marriage of human sensitivity and artificial intelligence fundamentally alters and improves the way we live. Kurzweil&#8217;s prophetic blueprint for the future takes us through the advances that inexorably result in computers exceeding the memory capacity and computational ability of the human brain by the year 2020 (with human-level capabilities not far behind); in relationships with automated personalities who will be our teachers, companions, and lovers; and in information fed straight into our brains along direct neural pathways. Optimistic and challenging, thought-provoking and engaging, The Age of Spiritual Machines is the ultimate guide on our road into the next century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Move Fast and Break Things : How Facebook, Google and Amazon Have Cornered Culture and Undermined Democracy &#8211; Jonathan Taplin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Network Security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Financial Times &#8216;Best Thing I Read This Year&#8217; LONGLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD Google. Amazon. Facebook. The modern world is defined by vast digital monopolies turning ever-larger profits. Those of us who consume the content that feeds them are farmed for the purposes of being sold ever [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/">Move Fast and Break Things : How Facebook, Google and Amazon Have Cornered Culture and Undermined Democracy &#8211; Jonathan Taplin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Financial Times &#8216;Best Thing I Read This Year&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    LONGLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD    </p>
<p>                    Google. Amazon. Facebook. The modern world is defined by vast digital monopolies turning ever-larger profits. Those of us who consume the content that feeds them are farmed for the purposes of being sold ever more products and advertising. Those that create the content &#8211; the artists, writers and musicians &#8211; are finding they can no longer survive in this unforgiving economic landscape.     </p>
<p>                     But it didn&#8217;t have to be this way.     </p>
<p>                     In Move Fast and Break Things, Jonathan Taplin offers a succinct and powerful history of how online life began to be shaped around the values of the entrepreneurs like Peter Thiel and Larry Page who founded these all-powerful companies. Their unprecedented growth came at the heavy cost of tolerating piracy of books, music and film, while at the same time promoting opaque business practices and subordinating the privacy of individual users to create the surveillance marketing monoculture in which we now live.    </p>
<p>                    It is the story of a massive reallocation of revenue in which $50 billion a year has moved from the creators and owners of content to the monopoly platforms. With this reallocation of money comes a shift in power. Google, Facebook and Amazon now enjoy political power on par with Big Oil and Big Pharma, which in part explains how such a tremendous shift in revenues from creators to platforms could have been achieved and why it has gone unchallenged for so long.    </p>
<p>                    And if you think that&#8217;s got nothing to do with you, their next move is to come after your jobs.     </p>
<p>                    Move Fast and Break Things is a call to arms, to say that is enough is enough and to demand that we do everything in our power to create a different future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/">Move Fast and Break Things : How Facebook, Google and Amazon Have Cornered Culture and Undermined Democracy &#8211; Jonathan Taplin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Economic Singularity : Artificial intelligence and the death of capitalism &#8211; Calum Chace (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-economic-singularity-artificial-intelligence-and-the-death-of-capitalism-calum-chace-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-economic-singularity-artificial-intelligence-and-the-death-of-capitalism-calum-chace-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Read The Economic Singularity if you want to think intelligently about the future.&#8221;Aubrey de GreyArtificial intelligence (AI) is overtaking our human ability to absorb and process information. Robots are becoming increasingly dextrous, flexible, and safe to be around (except the military ones). It is our most powerful technology, and you need to understand it. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-economic-singularity-artificial-intelligence-and-the-death-of-capitalism-calum-chace-abridged/">The Economic Singularity : Artificial intelligence and the death of capitalism &#8211; Calum Chace (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Read The Economic Singularity if you want to think intelligently about the future.&#8221;Aubrey de GreyArtificial intelligence (AI) is overtaking our human ability to absorb and process information. Robots are becoming increasingly dextrous, flexible, and safe to be around (except the military ones). It is our most powerful technology, and you need to understand it. This new book from best-selling AI writer Calum Chace argues that within a few decades, most humans will not be able to work for money. Self-driving cars will probably be the canary in the coal mine, providing a wake-up call for everyone who isn&#8217;t yet paying attention. All jobs will be affected, from fast food McJobs to lawyers and journalists. This is the single most important development facing humanity in the first half of the 21st century.The fashionable belief that Universal Basic Income is the solution is only partly correct. We are probably going to need an entirely new economic system, and we better start planning soon &#8211; for the Economic Singularity! The outcome can be very good &#8211; a world in which machines do all the boring jobs and humans do pretty much what they please. But there are major risks, which we can only avoid by being alert to the possible futures and planning how to avoid the negative ones.ENDORSEMENTS&#8221;The advance of automation, described with great care and accuracy in this book, will almost certainly constitute the substrate within which all other technological developments &#8211; be they biomedical, environmental or something else entirely &#8211; will occur, and thus within which they should be discussed as regards their value to humanity. Read &#8220;The Economic Singularity&#8221; if you want to think intelligently about the future.&#8221;Aubrey de Grey &#8211; CSO of SENS Research Foundation; former AI researcher&#8221;Following his insightful foray into the burgeoning AI revolution and associated existential risks in Surviving AI, Calum focuses his attention on a nearer term challenge &#8211; the likelihood that intelligent machines will render much of humanity unemployable in the foreseeable future. Once again he proves a reliable guide through this complex yet fascinating topic.&#8221;Ben Medlock, co-founder of Swiftkey, the best-selling app on Android&#8221;Calum Chace is an acknowledged expert on the likely impact of artificial intelligence on society. In his new book, he investigates the possibility that machine intelligence will, over the coming few decades, make it impossible for most people to find paid work. He arrives at some surprising and radical conclusions, which merit careful consideration.&#8221;Hugh Pym, former chief economics correspondent, BBC News&#8221;The Economic Singularity is fascinating. I couldn&#8217;t put this book down.&#8221;Ben Goldsmith &#8211; Menhaden Capital&#8221;Chace does a good job answering the question whether robots will take our jobs.&#8221;Prof. Dr. Hugo de Garis &#8211; former director of the Artificial Brain Lab, Xiamen University, China&#8221;This fast-paced new book explains the challenge facing humanity: to navigate through a dramatic transition which he christens the economic singularity. Unexpectedly, it threatens the end of capitalism itself, and potentially the fracturing of the human species.&#8221;David Wood &#8211; chairman, London Futurists&#8221;Unprecedented productivity gains and unlimited leisure-what could possibly go wrong? Everything, says Calum Chace, if we don&#8217;t evolve a social system suited to the inevitable world of connected intelligent systems.&#8221;Christopher Meyer, author of &#8220;Blur&#8221;, &#8220;Future Wealth&#8221;, and &#8220;Standing on the Sun&#8221;It&#8217;s important that this book and others like it are written. Not because the future will necessarily happen exactly in the way described, but because it&#8217;s important to be prepared if it does.&#8221;Dr Stuart Armstrong, James Martin Research Fellow at the Future of Humanity Institute, Oxford University</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-economic-singularity-artificial-intelligence-and-the-death-of-capitalism-calum-chace-abridged/">The Economic Singularity : Artificial intelligence and the death of capitalism &#8211; Calum Chace (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The War on Normal People : The Truth About America&#8217;s Disappearing Jobs and Why Universal Basic Income Is Our Future &#8211; Andrew Yang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The shift toward automation is about to create a tsunami of unemployment. Not in the distant future&#8211;now. One recent estimate predicts 13 million American workers will lose their jobs within the next seven years-jobs that won&#8217;t be replaced. In a future marked by restlessness and chronic unemployment, what will happen to American society? In The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/">The War on Normal People : The Truth About America&#8217;s Disappearing Jobs and Why Universal Basic Income Is Our Future &#8211; Andrew Yang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The shift toward automation is about to create a tsunami of unemployment. Not in the distant future&#8211;now. One recent estimate predicts 13 million American workers will lose their jobs within the next seven years-jobs that won&#8217;t be replaced. In a future marked by restlessness and chronic unemployment, what will happen to American society?    </p>
<p>                    In The War on Normal People, Andrew Yang paints a dire portrait of the American economy. Rapidly advancing technologies like artificial intelligence, robotics and automation software are making millions of Americans&#8217; livelihoods irrelevant. The consequences are these trends are already being felt across our communities in the form of political unrest, drug use, and other social ills. The future looks dire-but is it unavoidable?    </p>
<p>                    In The War on Normal People, Yang imagines a different future &#8212; one in which having a job is distinct from the capacity to prosper and seek fulfillment. At this vision&#8217;s core is Universal Basic Income, the concept of providing all citizens with a guaranteed income-and one that is rapidly gaining popularity among forward-thinking politicians and economists. Yang proposes that UBI is an essential step toward a new, more durable kind of economy, one he calls &#8220;human capitalism.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-normal-people-the-truth-about-americas-disappearing-jobs-and-why-universal-basic-income-is-our-future-andrew-yang-abridged/">The War on Normal People : The Truth About America&#8217;s Disappearing Jobs and Why Universal Basic Income Is Our Future &#8211; Andrew Yang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics & Communications Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phones: Consumer/user Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is your phone the first thing you reach for when you wake up? And the last thing you see before you sleep? Do you find the hours slip away as you idly scroll through your social media timeline? In short, are you addicted to your phone? If so, How to Break Up with Your Phone [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/">How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is your phone the first thing you reach for when you wake up? And the  last thing you see before you sleep? Do you find the hours slip away as  you idly scroll through your social media timeline?     </p>
<p>                     In short, are you addicted to your phone? If so, How to Break Up with Your Phone is here to help.     </p>
<p>                     How to Break Up With Your Phone  is a smart, practical and useful plan to help you conquer your mobile  phone addiction in just 30 days &#8211; and take back your life in the  process.     </p>
<p>                    Recent studies have shown that spending extended time  on our phones affects our ability to form new memories, think deeply,  focus and absorb information, and the hormones triggered every time we  hear our phones buzz both add to our stress levels and are the hallmark  signs of addiction. In How to Break Up with Your Phone,  award-winning science journalist Catherine Price explores the effects  that our constant connectivity is having on our brains, bodies,  relationships, and society at large and asks, how much time do you really want to spend on your phone?     </p>
<p>                    Over  the course of 30 days, Catherine will guide you through an  easy-to-follow plan that enables you to identify your goals, priorities  and bad habits, tidy your apps, prune your email, and take time away.  Lastly, you will create a new, healthier relationship with your phone  and establish habits and routines to ensure this new relationship  sticks.     </p>
<p>                    You don&#8217;t have to give up your phone forever; instead  you will be more mindful not only of how you use your phone, but also  about how you choose to spend the precious moments of your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/">How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Industries of the Future &#8211; Alec Ross (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-industries-of-the-future-alec-ross-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-industries-of-the-future-alec-ross-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book answers the question: &#8216;What&#8217;s next?&#8217; The Internet had a world-changing impact on businesses and the global community over the twenty years from 1994 to 2014. In the next ten years, change will happen even faster. As Hillary Clinton&#8217;s Senior Advisor for Innovation, Alec Ross travelled nearly a million miles to forty-one countries, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-industries-of-the-future-alec-ross-abridged/">The Industries of the Future &#8211; Alec Ross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book answers the question: &#8216;What&#8217;s next?&#8217; The Internet had a world-changing impact on businesses and the global community over the twenty years from 1994 to 2014. In the next ten years, change will happen even faster.     </p>
<p>                    As Hillary Clinton&#8217;s Senior Advisor for Innovation, Alec Ross travelled nearly a million miles to forty-one countries, the equivalent of two round-trips to the moon. From refugee camps in the Congo and Syrian war zones, to visiting the world&#8217;s most powerful people in business and government, Ross&#8217;s travels amounted to a four-year masterclass in the changing nature of innovation.     </p>
<p>                    In The Industries of the Future, Ross distils his observations on the forces that are changing the world. He highlights the best opportunities for progress and explains how countries thrive or sputter. Ross examines the specific fields that will most shape our economic future over the next ten years, including robotics, artificial intelligence, the commercialization of genomics, cybercrime and the impact of digital technology.     </p>
<p>                    Blending storytelling and economic analysis, he answers questions on how we will need to adapt. Ross gives readers a vivid and informed perspective on how sweeping global trends are affecting the ways we live, now and tomorrow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-industries-of-the-future-alec-ross-abridged/">The Industries of the Future &#8211; Alec Ross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Listening Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BRILLIANT&#8217; Chris Evans, Virgin Radio Breakfast Show When was the last time you listened to someone, or someone really listened to you? This life-changing book will transform your conversations forever. At work, we&#8217;re taught to lead the conversation. On social media, we shape our personal narratives. At parties, we talk over one another. So do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/">You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BRILLIANT&#8217; Chris Evans, Virgin Radio Breakfast Show    </p>
<p>                    When was the last time you listened to someone, or someone really listened to you?     </p>
<p>                    This life-changing book will transform your conversations forever.    </p>
<p>                     At work, we&#8217;re taught to lead the conversation.    </p>
<p>                     On social media, we shape our personal narratives.    </p>
<p>                     At parties, we talk over one another. So do our politicians.    </p>
<p>                     We&#8217;re not listening.    </p>
<p>                     And no one is listening to us.    </p>
<p>                    Now more than ever, we need to listen to those around us. New York Times contributor Kate Murphy draws on countless conversations she has had with everyone from priests to CIA interrogators, focus group moderators to bartenders, her great-great aunt to her friend&#8217;s toddler, to show how only by listening well can we truly connect with others.    </p>
<p>                     Listening has the potential to transform our relationships and our working lives, improve our self-knowledge, and increase our creativity and happiness. While it may take some effort, it&#8217;s a skill that can be learnt and perfected.    </p>
<p>                     When all we crave is to understand and be understood, You&#8217;re Not Listening shows us how.    </p>
<p>                    * With a new afterword by the author *    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book couldn&#8217;t be more timely. Inspiringly profound&#8230;smart and playful&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;ll be adopting Murphy&#8217;s advice&#8217; Sunday Times, Style</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/">You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weapons of Math Destruction : How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy &#8211; Cathy O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A manual for the 21st-century citizen&#8230; accessible, refreshingly critical, relevant and urgent&#8217; &#8211; Financial Times &#8216;Fascinating and deeply disturbing&#8217; &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari, Guardian Books of the Year In this New York Times bestseller, Cathy O&#8217;Neil, one of the first champions of algorithmic accountability, sounds an alarm on the mathematical models that pervade modern life [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/">Weapons of Math Destruction : How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy &#8211; Cathy O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A manual for the 21st-century citizen&#8230; accessible, refreshingly critical, relevant and urgent&#8217; &#8211;  Financial Times     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating and deeply disturbing&#8217; &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari, Guardian Books of the Year     </p>
<p>                    In this New York Times bestseller, Cathy O&#8217;Neil, one of the first champions of algorithmic accountability, sounds an alarm on the mathematical models that pervade modern life &#8212; and threaten to rip apart our social fabric.    </p>
<p>                    We live in the age of the algorithm. Increasingly, the decisions that affect our lives &#8211; where we go to school, whether we get a loan, how much we pay for insurance &#8211; are being made not by humans, but by mathematical models. In theory, this should lead to greater fairness: everyone is judged according to the same rules, and bias is eliminated.     </p>
<p>                    And yet, as Cathy O&#8217;Neil reveals in this urgent and necessary book, the opposite is true. The models being used today are opaque, unregulated, and incontestable, even when they&#8217;re wrong. Most troubling, they reinforce discrimination. Tracing the arc of a person&#8217;s life, O&#8217;Neil exposes the black box models that shape our future, both as individuals and as a society. These &#8220;weapons of math destruction&#8221; score teachers and students, sort CVs, grant or deny loans, evaluate workers, target voters, and monitor our health.     </p>
<p>                    O&#8217;Neil calls on modellers to take more responsibility for their algorithms and on policy makers to regulate their use. But in the end, it&#8217;s up to us to become more savvy about the models that govern our lives. This important book empowers us to ask the tough questions, uncover the truth, and demand change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/">Weapons of Math Destruction : How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy &#8211; Cathy O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene<br />
                    Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the future of our species for fans of Homo Deus and The Gene.<br />
                    After 3.8 billion years humankind is about to start evolving by new rules&#8230;<br />
                    From leading geopolitical expert and technology futurist Jamie Metzl comes a groundbreaking exploration of the many ways genetic-engineering is shaking the core foundations of our lives-sex, war, love, and death.<br />
                    At the dawn of the genetics revolution, our DNA is becoming as readable, writable, and hackable as our information technology. But as humanity starts retooling our own genetic code, the choices we make today will be the difference between realizing breathtaking advances in human well-being and descending into a dangerous and potentially deadly genetic arms race.<br />
                    Enter the laboratories where scientists are turning science fiction into reality. Look towards a future where our deepest beliefs, morals, religions, and politics are challenged like never before and the very essence of what it means to be human is at play. When we can engineer our future children, massively extend our lifespans, build life from scratch, and recreate the plant and animal world, should we?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Death of Expertise : The Campaign Against Established Knowledge and Why it Matters &#8211; Tom Nichols (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Epistemology & Theory Of Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>People are now exposed to more information than ever before, provided both by technology and by increasing access to every level of education. These societal gains, however, have also helped fuel a surge in narcissistic and misguided intellectual egalitarianism that has crippled informed debates on any number of issues. Today, everyone knows everything: with only [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/">The Death of Expertise : The Campaign Against Established Knowledge and Why it Matters &#8211; Tom Nichols (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>People are now exposed to more information than ever before, provided both by technology and by increasing access to every level of education. These societal gains, however, have also helped fuel a surge in narcissistic and misguided intellectual egalitarianism that has crippled informed debates on any number of issues. Today, everyone knows everything: with only a quick trip through WebMD or Wikipedia, average citizens believe themselves to be on an equal<br />
                    intellectual footing with doctors and diplomats. All voices, even the most ridiculous, demand to be taken with equal seriousness, and any claim to the contrary is dismissed as undemocratic elitism.    </p>
<p>                    As Tom Nichols shows in The Death of Expertise, this rejection of experts has occurred for many reasons, including the openness of the internet, the emergence of a customer satisfaction model in higher education, and the transformation of the news industry into a 24-hour entertainment machine. Paradoxically, the increasingly democratic dissemination of information, rather than producing an educated public, has instead created an army of ill-informed and angry citizens who denounce<br />
                    intellectual achievement.    </p>
<p>                    Nichols has deeper concerns than the current rejection of expertise and learning, noting that when ordinary citizens believe that no one knows more than anyone else, democratic institutions themselves are in danger of falling either to populism or to technocracy-or in the worst case, a combination of both. The Death of Expertise is not only an exploration of a dangerous phenomenon but also a warning about the stability and survival of modern democracy in the Information<br />
                    Age.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/">The Death of Expertise : The Campaign Against Established Knowledge and Why it Matters &#8211; Tom Nichols (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Master Algorithm : How the Quest for the Ultimate Learning Machine Will Remake Our World &#8211; Pedro Domingos (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-master-algorithm-how-the-quest-for-the-ultimate-learning-machine-will-remake-our-world-pedro-domingos-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-master-algorithm-how-the-quest-for-the-ultimate-learning-machine-will-remake-our-world-pedro-domingos-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pedro Domingos demystifies machine learning and shows how wondrous and exciting the future will be&#8217; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs Society is changing, one learning algorithm at a time, from search engines to online dating, personalized medicine to predicting the stock market. But learning algorithms are not just about Big Data &#8211; these algorithms [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-master-algorithm-how-the-quest-for-the-ultimate-learning-machine-will-remake-our-world-pedro-domingos-abridged/">The Master Algorithm : How the Quest for the Ultimate Learning Machine Will Remake Our World &#8211; Pedro Domingos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pedro Domingos demystifies machine learning and shows how wondrous and exciting the future will be&#8217; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs    </p>
<p>                    Society is changing, one learning algorithm at a time, from search engines to online dating, personalized medicine to predicting the stock market. But learning algorithms are not just about Big Data &#8211; these algorithms take raw data and make it useful by creating more algorithms. This is something new under the sun: a technology that builds itself. In The Master Algorithm, Pedro Domingos reveals how machine learning is remaking business, politics, science and war. And he takes us on an awe-inspiring quest to find &#8216;The Master Algorithm&#8217; &#8211; a universal learner capable of deriving all knowledge from data.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-master-algorithm-how-the-quest-for-the-ultimate-learning-machine-will-remake-our-world-pedro-domingos-abridged/">The Master Algorithm : How the Quest for the Ultimate Learning Machine Will Remake Our World &#8211; Pedro Domingos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world where all the news you see is defined by your salary, where you live, and who your friends are. Imagine a world where you never discover new ideas. And where you can&#8217;t have secrets. Welcome to 2011. Google and Facebook are already feeding you what they think you want to see. Advertisers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/">The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world where all the news you see is defined by your salary, where you live, and who your friends are. Imagine a world where you never discover new ideas. And where you can&#8217;t have secrets.    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to 2011.    </p>
<p>                    Google and Facebook are already feeding you what they think you want to see. Advertisers are following your every click. Your computer monitor is becoming a one-way mirror, reflecting your interests and reinforcing your prejudices.    </p>
<p>                    The internet is no longer a free, independent space. It is commercially controlled and ever more personalised. The Filter Bubble reveals how this hidden web is starting to control our lives &#8211; and shows what we can do about it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/">The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WTF?: What&#8217;s the Future and Why It&#8217;s Up to Us &#8211; Tim O&#8217;Reilly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An indispensable guide.&#8217; Reid Hoffman, co-founder of LinkedIn &#8216;Tech&#8217;s most valuable teacher.&#8217; Forbes Silicon Valley&#8217;s leading intellectual and the founder of O&#8217;Reilly Media explores the upside and the potential downsides of our future &#8211; what he calls the &#8216;next economy&#8217;. Tim O&#8217;Reilly&#8217;s genius is to identify and explain emerging technologies with world shaking potential &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/">WTF?: What&#8217;s the Future and Why It&#8217;s Up to Us &#8211; Tim O&#8217;Reilly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An indispensable guide.&#8217; Reid Hoffman, co-founder of LinkedIn    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Tech&#8217;s most valuable teacher.&#8217; Forbes    </p>
<p>                    Silicon Valley&#8217;s leading intellectual and the founder of O&#8217;Reilly Media explores the upside and the potential downsides of our future &#8211; what he calls the &#8216;next economy&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    Tim O&#8217;Reilly&#8217;s genius is to identify and explain emerging technologies with world shaking potential &#8211; the World Wide Web, Open Source Software, Web 2.0, Open Government data, the Maker Movement, Big Data. &#8216;The man who can really can make a whole industry happen,&#8217; according to Executive Chairman of Google Eric Schmidt, O&#8217;Reilly has most recently focused on the future of work &#8211; AI, algorithms, and new approaches to business organisation that will shape our lives. He has brought together an unlikely coalition of technologists, business leaders, labour advocates, and policy makers to wrestle with these issues. In WTF? he shares the evolution of his intellectual development, applying his approach to a number of challenging issues we will face as citizens, employees, business leaders, and a nation.    </p>
<p>                    What is the future when an increasing number of jobs can be performed by intelligent machines instead of people, or only done by people in partnership with those machines? What happens to our consumer based societies &#8211; to workers and to the companies that depend on their purchasing power? Is income inequality and unemployment an inevitable consequence of technological advancement, or are there paths to a better future? What will happen to business when technology-enabled networks and marketplaces are better at deploying talent than traditional companies? What&#8217;s the future of education when on-demand learning outperforms traditional institutions? Will the fundamental social safety nets of the developed world survive the transition, and if not, what will replace them?    </p>
<p>                    The digital revolution has transformed the world of media, upending centuries-old companies and business models. Now, it is restructuring every business, every job, and every sector of society. Yet the biggest changes are still ahead. To survive, every industry and organisation will have to transform itself in multiple ways. O&#8217;Reilly explores what the next economy will mean for the world and every aspect of our lives &#8211; and what we can do to shape it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/">WTF?: What&#8217;s the Future and Why It&#8217;s Up to Us &#8211; Tim O&#8217;Reilly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Laws of Thermodynamics: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Peter Atkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-laws-of-thermodynamics-a-very-short-introduction-peter-atkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thermodynamics & Heat]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-laws-of-thermodynamics-a-very-short-introduction-peter-atkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the sudden expansion of a cloud of gas or the cooling of a hot metal, to the unfolding of a thought in our minds and even the course of life itself, everything is governed by the four Laws of Thermodynamics. These laws specify the nature of &#8216;energy&#8217; and &#8216;temperature&#8217;, and are soon revealed to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-laws-of-thermodynamics-a-very-short-introduction-peter-atkins-abridged/">The Laws of Thermodynamics: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Peter Atkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the sudden expansion of a cloud of gas or the cooling of a hot metal, to the unfolding of a thought in our minds and even the course of life itself, everything is governed by the four Laws of Thermodynamics. These laws specify the nature of &#8216;energy&#8217; and &#8216;temperature&#8217;, and are soon revealed to reach out and define the arrow of time itself: why things change and why death must come.     </p>
<p>                    In this Very Short Introduction Peter Atkins explains the basis and deeper implications of each law, highlighting their relevance in everyday examples. Using the minimum of mathematics, he introduces concepts such as entropy, free energy, and to the brink and beyond of the absolute zero temperature. These are not merely abstract ideas: they govern our lives.     </p>
<p>                    In this concise and compelling introduction Atkins paints a lucid picture of the four elegant laws that, between them, drive the Universe.    </p>
<p>                    ABOUT THE SERIES: The Very Short Introductions series from Oxford University Press contains hundreds of titles in almost every subject area. These pocket-sized books are the perfect way to get ahead in a new subject quickly. Our expert authors combine facts, analysis, perspective, new ideas, and enthusiasm to make interesting and challenging topics highly readable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-laws-of-thermodynamics-a-very-short-introduction-peter-atkins-abridged/">The Laws of Thermodynamics: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Peter Atkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Present Shock : When Everything Happens Now &#8211; Douglas Rushkoff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/present-shock-when-everything-happens-now-douglas-rushkoff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/present-shock-when-everything-happens-now-douglas-rushkoff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>People spent the twentieth century obsessed with the future. We created technologies that would help connect us faster, gather news, map the planet, and compile knowledge. We strove for an instantaneous network where time and space could be compressed. Well, the future&#8217;s arrived. We live in a continuous now enabled by Twitter, email, and a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/present-shock-when-everything-happens-now-douglas-rushkoff-abridged/">Present Shock : When Everything Happens Now &#8211; Douglas Rushkoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>People spent the twentieth century obsessed with the future. We created technologies that would help connect us faster, gather news, map the planet, and compile knowledge. We strove for an instantaneous network where time and space could be compressed. Well, the future&#8217;s arrived. We live in a continuous now enabled by Twitter, email, and a so-called real-time technological shift. Yet this now is an elusive goal that we can never quite reach. And the dissonance between our digital selves and our analog bodies has thrown us into a new state of anxiety: present shock.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/present-shock-when-everything-happens-now-douglas-rushkoff-abridged/">Present Shock : When Everything Happens Now &#8211; Douglas Rushkoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tyranny of E-mail : The Four-Thousand-Year Journey to Your Inbox &#8211; John Freeman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tyranny-of-e-mail-the-four-thousand-year-journey-to-your-inbox-john-freeman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tyranny-of-e-mail-the-four-thousand-year-journey-to-your-inbox-john-freeman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s no question that e-mail is an incredible phenomenon that represents a kind of cultural and technological advancement. The first e-mail was sent less than forty years ago; by 2011, there will be 3.2 billion e-mail users. The average corporate worker now receives upwards of two hundred e-mails per day. The flood of messages is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tyranny-of-e-mail-the-four-thousand-year-journey-to-your-inbox-john-freeman-abridged/">Tyranny of E-mail : The Four-Thousand-Year Journey to Your Inbox &#8211; John Freeman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s no question that e-mail is an incredible phenomenon that represents a kind of cultural and technological advancement. The first e-mail was sent less than forty years ago; by 2011, there will be 3.2 billion e-mail users. The average corporate worker now receives upwards of two hundred e-mails per day. The flood of messages is ceaseless and follows us everywhere.     </p>
<p>                    In The Tyranny of E-mail, John Freeman takes an entertaining look at the unrelenting nature of correspondence through the ages. Put down your smart phone and consider the consequences. As the toll of e-mail mounts, reducing our time for leisure and contemplation and separating us in an unending and lonely battle with the overfull inbox, John Freeman&#8211;one of America&#8217;s preeminent literary critics&#8211;enters a plea for communication that is more selective and nuanced and, above all, more sociable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tyranny-of-e-mail-the-four-thousand-year-journey-to-your-inbox-john-freeman-abridged/">Tyranny of E-mail : The Four-Thousand-Year Journey to Your Inbox &#8211; John Freeman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>To Be a Machine : Adventures Among Cyborgs, Utopians, Hackers, and the Futurists Solving the Modest Problem of Death &#8211; Mark O&#8217;Connell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/to-be-a-machine-adventures-among-cyborgs-utopians-hackers-and-the-futurists-solving-the-modest-problem-of-death-mark-oconnell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/to-be-a-machine-adventures-among-cyborgs-utopians-hackers-and-the-futurists-solving-the-modest-problem-of-death-mark-oconnell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE WELLCOME BOOK PRIZE 2018 Shortlisted for the Baillie Gifford Prize 2017 A stunning new non-fiction voice tackles an urgent question&#8230; what next for mankind? &#8216;Troubling and humorous, this is one of my current give-it-to-everyone books &#8211; I buy six copies at a time&#8217; Jeanette Winterson</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/to-be-a-machine-adventures-among-cyborgs-utopians-hackers-and-the-futurists-solving-the-modest-problem-of-death-mark-oconnell-abridged/">To Be a Machine : Adventures Among Cyborgs, Utopians, Hackers, and the Futurists Solving the Modest Problem of Death &#8211; Mark O&#8217;Connell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE WELLCOME BOOK PRIZE 2018<br />
                    Shortlisted for the Baillie Gifford Prize 2017    </p>
<p>                    A stunning new non-fiction voice tackles an urgent question&#8230; what next for mankind?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Troubling and humorous, this is one of my current give-it-to-everyone books &#8211; I buy six copies at a time&#8217;<br />
                    Jeanette Winterson</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/to-be-a-machine-adventures-among-cyborgs-utopians-hackers-and-the-futurists-solving-the-modest-problem-of-death-mark-oconnell-abridged/">To Be a Machine : Adventures Among Cyborgs, Utopians, Hackers, and the Futurists Solving the Modest Problem of Death &#8211; Mark O&#8217;Connell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control  chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Create a Mind : The Secret of Human Thought Revealed &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-create-a-mind-the-secret-of-human-thought-revealed-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-create-a-mind-the-secret-of-human-thought-revealed-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the best person I know at predicting the future of artificial intelligence.&#8217; Bill Gates In How to Create a Mind, Ray Kurzweil offers a provocative exploration of the most important project in human-machine civilisation: reverse engineering the brain to understand precisely how it works and using that knowledge to create even more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-create-a-mind-the-secret-of-human-thought-revealed-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">How to Create a Mind : The Secret of Human Thought Revealed &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the best person I know at predicting the future of artificial intelligence.&#8217; Bill Gates    </p>
<p>                    In How to Create a Mind, Ray Kurzweil offers a provocative exploration of the most important project in human-machine civilisation: reverse engineering the brain to understand precisely how it works and using that knowledge to create even more intelligent machines. Kurzweil explores how the brain functions, how the mind emerges from the brain, and the implications of vastly increasing the powers of our intelligence in addressing the world&#8217;s problems. He thoughtfully examines emotional and moral intelligence and the origins of consciousness and envisions the radical &#8211; arguably inevitable &#8211; future of our merging with the intelligent technology we are creating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-create-a-mind-the-secret-of-human-thought-revealed-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">How to Create a Mind : The Secret of Human Thought Revealed &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Distracted Mind : Ancient Brains in a High-Tech World &#8211; Adam Gazzaley, Larry D. Rosen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world-adam-gazzaley-larry-d-rosen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world-adam-gazzaley-larry-d-rosen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why our brains aren&#8217;t built for media multitasking, and how we can learn to live with technology in a more balanced way. Brilliant and practical, just what we need in these techno-human times.&#8211;Jack Kornfield, author of The Wise Heart Most of us will freely admit that we are obsessed with our devices. We pride ourselves [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world-adam-gazzaley-larry-d-rosen-abridged/">The Distracted Mind : Ancient Brains in a High-Tech World &#8211; Adam Gazzaley, Larry D. Rosen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why our brains aren&#8217;t built for media multitasking, and how we can learn to live with technology in a more balanced way.    </p>
<p>                    Brilliant and practical, just what we need in these techno-human times.&#8211;Jack Kornfield, author of The Wise Heart    </p>
<p>                    Most of us will freely admit that we are obsessed with our devices. We pride ourselves on our ability to multitask&#8211;read work email, reply to a text, check Facebook, watch a video clip. Talk on the phone, send a text, drive a car. Enjoy family dinner with a glowing smartphone next to our plates. We can do it all, 24/7! Never mind the errors in the email, the near-miss on the road, and the unheard conversation at the table. In The Distracted Mind, Adam Gazzaley and Larry Rosen&#8211;a neuroscientist and a psychologist&#8211;explain why our brains aren&#8217;t built for multitasking, and suggest better ways to live in a high-tech world without giving up our modern technology.    </p>
<p>                    The authors explain that our brains are limited in their ability to pay attention. We don&#8217;t really multitask but rather switch rapidly between tasks. Distractions and interruptions, often technology-related&#8211;referred to by the authors as &#8220;interference&#8221;&#8211;collide with our goal-setting abilities. We want to finish this paper/spreadsheet/sentence, but our phone signals an incoming message and we drop everything. Even without an alert, we decide that we &#8220;must&#8221; check in on social media immediately.    </p>
<p>                    Gazzaley and Rosen offer practical strategies, backed by science, to fight distraction. We can change our brains with meditation, video games, and physical exercise; we can change our behavior by planning our accessibility and recognizing our anxiety about being out of touch even briefly. They don&#8217;t suggest that we give up our devices, but that we use them in a more balanced way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world-adam-gazzaley-larry-d-rosen-abridged/">The Distracted Mind : Ancient Brains in a High-Tech World &#8211; Adam Gazzaley, Larry D. Rosen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Humans Are Underrated : What High Achievers Know that Brilliant Machines Never Will &#8211; Geoff Colvin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/humans-are-underrated-what-high-achievers-know-that-brilliant-machines-never-will-geoff-colvin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/humans-are-underrated-what-high-achievers-know-that-brilliant-machines-never-will-geoff-colvin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the dawning age of brilliant machines, what will people do better than computers? It&#8217;s easy to imagine a frightening future in which technology takes over the jobs that we now get paid to do, working more accurately and for barely any cost. Computers can already perform surgery, drive vehicles, write articles and do intricate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humans-are-underrated-what-high-achievers-know-that-brilliant-machines-never-will-geoff-colvin-abridged/">Humans Are Underrated : What High Achievers Know that Brilliant Machines Never Will &#8211; Geoff Colvin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the dawning age of brilliant machines, what will people do better than computers?    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s easy to imagine a frightening future in which technology takes over the jobs that we now get paid to do, working more accurately and for barely any cost. Computers can already perform surgery, drive vehicles, write articles and do intricate legal work, so what hope will there be for tomorrow&#8217;s workforce?    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on a wealth of research, Geoff Colvin uncovers the skills that will be in great demand as technology advances &#8211; and how they can be developed. In this new machine age, we shouldn&#8217;t try to beat computers at what they can do. We&#8217;ll lose that contest. Instead we must look to unlikely places, learn from the best, and cultivate the human abilities that make us unique.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humans-are-underrated-what-high-achievers-know-that-brilliant-machines-never-will-geoff-colvin-abridged/">Humans Are Underrated : What High Achievers Know that Brilliant Machines Never Will &#8211; Geoff Colvin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Whiplash : How to Survive Our Faster Future &#8211; Joi Ito, Jeff Howe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This &#8220;brilliant and provocative&#8221; (Walter Isaacson) guide shares nine principles to adapt and survive the technological changes shaping our future from the director of the MIT Media Lab and a veteran Wired journalist. The world is more complex and volatile today than at any other time in our history. The tools of our modern existence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/">Whiplash : How to Survive Our Faster Future &#8211; Joi Ito, Jeff Howe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This &#8220;brilliant and provocative&#8221; (Walter Isaacson) guide shares nine principles to adapt and survive the technological changes shaping our future from the director of the MIT Media Lab and a veteran Wired journalist.  The world is more complex and volatile today than at any other time in our history. The tools of our modern existence are getting faster, cheaper, and smaller at an exponential rate, transforming every aspect of society, from business to culture and from the public sphere to our most private moments. The people who succeed will be the ones who learn to think differently.  In Whiplash, Joi Ito and Jeff Howe distill that logic into nine organizing principles for navigating and surviving this tumultuous period: Emergence over Authority Pull over Push Compasses over Maps Risk over Safety Disobedience over Compliance Practice over Theory Diversity over Ability Resilience over Strength Systems over Objects   Filled with incredible case studies and cutting-edge research and philosophies from the MIT Media Lab and beyond, Whiplash will help you adapt and succeed in this unpredictable world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whiplash-how-to-survive-our-faster-future-joi-ito-jeff-howe-abridged/">Whiplash : How to Survive Our Faster Future &#8211; Joi Ito, Jeff Howe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Minimalism : Choosing a Focused Life in a Noisy World &#8211; Cal Newport (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/digital-minimalism-choosing-a-focused-life-in-a-noisy-world-cal-newport-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/digital-minimalism-choosing-a-focused-life-in-a-noisy-world-cal-newport-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to switch off and find calm &#8211; from the New York Times bestselling author of A World Without Email &#8216;Digital Minimalism is the Marie Kondo of technology&#8217; Evening Standard &#8216;An eloquent, powerful and enjoyably practical guide to cutting back on screen time&#8217; The Times &#8216;An urgent call to action for anyone serious about [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/digital-minimalism-choosing-a-focused-life-in-a-noisy-world-cal-newport-abridged/">Digital Minimalism : Choosing a Focused Life in a Noisy World &#8211; Cal Newport (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to switch off and find calm &#8211; from the New York Times bestselling author of A World Without Email    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Digital Minimalism is the Marie Kondo of technology&#8217; Evening Standard    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;An eloquent, powerful and enjoyably practical guide to cutting back on screen time&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;An urgent call to action for anyone serious about being in command of their own life&#8217; Ryan Holiday    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;What a timely and useful book&#8217; Naomi Alderman, author of The Power    </p>
<p>                     Do you find yourself endlessly scrolling through social media or the news while your anxiety rises? Are you feeling frazzled after a long day of endless video calls?     </p>
<p>                     In this timely book, professor Cal Newport shows us how to pair back digital distractions and live a more meaningful life with less technology.    </p>
<p>                     By following a &#8216;digital declutter&#8217; process, you&#8217;ll learn to:    </p>
<p>                     *      Rethink your relationship with social media<br />
                     *      Prioritize &#8216;high bandwidth&#8217; conversations over low quality text chains<br />
                     *      Rediscover the pleasures of the offline world    </p>
<p>                     Take back control from your devices and find calm amongst the chaos with Digital Minimalism.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/digital-minimalism-choosing-a-focused-life-in-a-noisy-world-cal-newport-abridged/">Digital Minimalism : Choosing a Focused Life in a Noisy World &#8211; Cal Newport (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutionary Groups & Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. To manage the risks and spread the benefits, we have to act now, and in the interest of stakeholders everywhere&#8217; Andrew McAfee, Co-Founder, MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy, MIT, USA    </p>
<p>                    We are on the brink of the Fourth Industrial Revolution. And this one will be unlike any other in human history.    </p>
<p>                    Characterized by new technologies fusing the physical, digital and biological worlds, the Fourth Industrial Revolution will impact all disciplines, economies and industries &#8211; and it will do so at an unprecedented rate. World Economic Forum data predicts that by 2025 we will see: commercial use of nanomaterials 200 times stronger than steel and a million times thinner than human hair; the first transplant of a 3D-printed liver; 10% of all cars on US roads being driverless; and much more besides.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Industrial Revolution, Schwab outlines the key technologies driving this revolution, discusses the major impacts on governments, businesses, civil society and individuals, and offers bold ideas for what can be done to shape a better future for all.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The technologies of the Fourth Industrial Revolution are extraordinary. Leadership has to be equally extraordinary to manage the complexities of systemic change&#8217; Eric Schmidt, Technical Advisor, Alphabet, USA</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The People Vs Tech : How the internet is killing democracy (and how we save it) &#8211; Jamie Bartlett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-people-vs-tech-how-the-internet-is-killing-democracy-and-how-we-save-it-jamie-bartlett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-people-vs-tech-how-the-internet-is-killing-democracy-and-how-we-save-it-jamie-bartlett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**Winner of the 2019 Transmission Prize** **Longlisted for the 2019 Orwell Prize for Political Writing** &#8216;A superb book by one of the world&#8217;s leading experts on the digital revolution&#8217; David Patrikarakos, Literary Review &#8216;This book could not have come at a better moment&#8230; The People Vs Tech makes clear that there is still time &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-people-vs-tech-how-the-internet-is-killing-democracy-and-how-we-save-it-jamie-bartlett-abridged/">The People Vs Tech : How the internet is killing democracy (and how we save it) &#8211; Jamie Bartlett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**Winner of the 2019 Transmission Prize**<br />
                    **Longlisted for the 2019 Orwell Prize for Political Writing**    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A superb book by one of the world&#8217;s leading experts on the digital revolution&#8217; David Patrikarakos, Literary Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book could not have come at a better moment&#8230; The People Vs Tech makes clear that there is still time &#8211; just &#8211; for us to take back control&#8217; &#8211; Camilla Cavendish, Sunday Times     </p>
<p>                    The internet was meant to set us free.    </p>
<p>                    Tech has radically changed the way we live our lives. But have we unwittingly handed too much away to shadowy powers behind a wall of code, all manipulated by a handful of Silicon Valley utopians, ad men, and venture capitalists? And, in light of recent data breach scandals around companies like Facebook and Cambridge Analytica, what does that mean for democracy, our delicately balanced system of government that was created long before big data, total information and artificial intelligence? In this urgent polemic, Jamie Bartlett argues that through our unquestioning embrace of big tech, the building blocks of democracy are slowly being removed. The middle class is being eroded, sovereign authority and civil society is weakened, and we citizens are losing our critical faculties, maybe even our free will.    </p>
<p>                    The People Vs Tech is an enthralling account of how our fragile political system is being threatened by the digital revolution. Bartlett explains that by upholding six key pillars of democracy, we can save it before it is too late. We need to become active citizens; uphold a shared democratic culture; protect free elections; promote equality; safeguard competitive and civic freedoms; and trust in a sovereign authority. This essential book shows that the stakes couldn&#8217;t be higher and that, unless we radically alter our course, democracy will join feudalism, supreme monarchies and communism as just another political experiment that quietly disappeared.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-people-vs-tech-how-the-internet-is-killing-democracy-and-how-we-save-it-jamie-bartlett-abridged/">The People Vs Tech : How the internet is killing democracy (and how we save it) &#8211; Jamie Bartlett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employment & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a rational explanation of the ways in which the AI revolution will affect us all. Tackling the implications of Artificial Intelligence on growth, productivity, inflation and the distribution of wealth and power, THE AI ECONOMY also examines coming changes to the the way we educate, work and spend our leisure time.    </p>
<p>                    A fundamentally optimistic view which will help you plan for changing times, this book explains AI and leads you towards a more certain future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER* &#8216;HELL YES. This is one of those books that has the potential to change things &#8211; a monumental piece of research&#8217; Caitlin Moran Imagine a world where&#8230; * Your phone is too big for your hand * Your doctor prescribes a drug that is wrong for your body * [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/">Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;HELL YES. This is one of those books that has the potential to change things &#8211; a monumental piece of research&#8217; Caitlin Moran    </p>
<p>                    Imagine a world where&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    *        Your phone is too big for your hand<br />
                    *        Your doctor prescribes a drug that is wrong for your body<br />
                    *        In a car accident you are 47% more likely to be injured.    </p>
<p>                    If any of that sounds familiar, chances are you&#8217;re a woman.    </p>
<p>                    From government policy and medical research, to technology, workplaces, and the media. Invisible Women reveals how in a world built for and by men we are systematically ignoring half of the population, often with disastrous consequences. Caroline Criado Perez brings together for the first time an impressive range of case studies, stories and new research from across the world that illustrate the hidden ways in which women are forgotten, and the profound impact this has on us all.    </p>
<p>                    Discover the shocking gender bias that affects our everyday lives.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book that changes the way you see the world&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Revelatory, frightening, hopeful&#8217; Jeanette Winterson</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/">Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER The creator of the Gaia hypothesis and the greatest environmental thinker of our time has produced an astounding new theory about the future of life on Earth. James Lovelock argues that the anthropocene &#8211; the age in which humans acquired planetary-scale technologies &#8211; is, after three centuries, coming to an end. A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/">Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The creator of the Gaia hypothesis and the greatest environmental thinker of our time has produced an astounding new theory about the future of life on Earth. James Lovelock argues that the anthropocene &#8211; the age in which humans acquired planetary-scale technologies &#8211; is, after three centuries, coming to an end. A new age &#8211; the novacene &#8211; has already begun.    </p>
<p>                    New beings will emerge from existing artificial intelligence systems. They will think 10,000 times faster than we do and will regard us as we now regard plants. The cruel, violent machine takeover imagined by sci-fi writers will not happen: these hyper-intelligent beings will be as dependent on the health of the planet as we are. They will need the planetary cooling system of Gaia to defend from the increasing heat of the sun. Gaia depends on organic life. We will be partners in this project. It is crucial, Lovelock argues, that the intelligence of Earth survives and prospers. We are at present the only beings capable of understanding the cosmos, but he speculates that the novacene could be the beginning of a process that will see intelligence suffusing the entire cosmos. At the age 100, Lovelock has produced the most compelling work of his life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/">Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger : Heretics, Activists, and One Scholar&#8217;s Search for Justice &#8211; Alice Dreger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/galileos-middle-finger-heretics-activists-and-one-scholars-search-for-justice-alice-dreger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues & Debates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/galileos-middle-finger-heretics-activists-and-one-scholars-search-for-justice-alice-dreger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Smart, delightful . . . a splendidly entertaining education in ethics, activism, and science.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review (Editor&#8217;s Choice) An impassioned defense of intellectual freedom and a clarion call to intellectual responsibility, Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger is one American&#8217;s eye-opening story of life in the trenches of scientific controversy. For two decades, historian [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/galileos-middle-finger-heretics-activists-and-one-scholars-search-for-justice-alice-dreger-abridged/">Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger : Heretics, Activists, and One Scholar&#8217;s Search for Justice &#8211; Alice Dreger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Smart, delightful . . . a splendidly entertaining education in ethics, activism, and science.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review (Editor&#8217;s Choice)    </p>
<p>                     An impassioned defense of intellectual freedom and a clarion call to intellectual responsibility, Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger is one American&#8217;s eye-opening story of life in the trenches of scientific controversy. For two decades, historian Alice Dreger has led a life of extraordinary engagement, combining activist service to victims of unethical medical research with defense of scientists whose work has outraged identity politics activists. With spirit and wit, Dreger offers in Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger an unforgettable vision of the importance of rigorous truth seeking in today&#8217;s America, where both the free press and free scholarly inquiry struggle under dire economic and political threats.    </p>
<p>                     This illuminating chronicle begins with Dreger&#8217;s own research into the treatment of people born intersex (once called hermaphrodites). Realization of the shocking surgical and ethical abuses conducted in the name of &#8220;normalizing&#8221; intersex children&#8217;s gender identities moved Dreger to become an internationally recognized patient rights activist. But even as the intersex rights movement succeeded, Dreger began to realize how some fellow progressive activists were employing lies and personal attacks to silence scientists whose data revealed uncomfortable truths about humans. In researching one such case, Dreger suddenly became the target of just these kinds of attacks.    </p>
<p>                     Troubled, she decided to try to understand more-to travel the country to ferret out the truth behind various controversies, to obtain a global view of the nature and costs of these battles. Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger describes Dreger&#8217;s long and harrowing journeys between the two camps for which she felt equal empathy: social justice activists determined to win and researchers determined to put hard truths before comfort. Ultimately what emerges is a lesson about the intertwining of justice and of truth-and a lesson of the importance of responsible scholars and journalists to our fragile democracy.    </p>
<p>                     Praise for Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger:<br />
                     &#8220;An engrossing volume that is sure to undo any lingering notions that academic debate is the province of empiricists who pledge allegiance to the truth, the whole truth, and nothing but the truth . . . Dreger&#8217;s clear and well-paced prose makes for compelling . . . reading.&#8221; -The Chicago Tribune</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/galileos-middle-finger-heretics-activists-and-one-scholars-search-for-justice-alice-dreger-abridged/">Galileo&#8217;s Middle Finger : Heretics, Activists, and One Scholar&#8217;s Search for Justice &#8211; Alice Dreger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who Can You Trust? : How Technology Brought Us Together &#8211; and Why It Could Drive Us Apart &#8211; Rachel Botsman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/who-can-you-trust-how-technology-brought-us-together-and-why-it-could-drive-us-apart-rachel-botsman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/who-can-you-trust-how-technology-brought-us-together-and-why-it-could-drive-us-apart-rachel-botsman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TRUST IS FUNDAMENTAL TO EVERY ACTION, EVERY RELATIONSHIP, EVERY TRANSACTION AND IT MATTERS NOW MORE THAN EVER BEFORE&#8230; In this ground-breaking book world-renowned trust expert Rachel Botsman reveals that we are at the tipping point of one of the biggest social transformations in human history. We might have lost faith in institutions and leaders, but [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-can-you-trust-how-technology-brought-us-together-and-why-it-could-drive-us-apart-rachel-botsman-abridged/">Who Can You Trust? : How Technology Brought Us Together &#8211; and Why It Could Drive Us Apart &#8211; Rachel Botsman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TRUST IS FUNDAMENTAL TO EVERY ACTION, EVERY RELATIONSHIP, EVERY TRANSACTION    </p>
<p>                    AND IT MATTERS NOW MORE THAN EVER BEFORE&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    In this ground-breaking book world-renowned trust expert Rachel Botsman reveals that we are at the tipping point of one of the biggest social transformations in human history. We might have lost faith in institutions and leaders, but millions of people travel in cars with total strangers, exchange digital currencies, or find themselves trusting a bot.     </p>
<p>                    We still trust: but not the way we used to.    </p>
<p>                    If we are to benefit from this radical shift, we must understand how trust is built, managed, lost and repaired in the digital age. In the first book to explain this new world, Botsman provides a definitive guide of this uncharted landscape &#8211; and explores what&#8217;s next for humanity.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brilliantly describes how the established trust framework is undergoing a radical transformation as digital technologies take root in every facet of our lives&#8217; Marc Benioff, Chairman &#038; CEO, Salesforce    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating and well researched&#8230;every reader will gain new insights&#8217; Geoff Mulgan, Chief Executive, Nesta    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A rare book that will cause you to think deeply about your business, your relationships and your life&#8217; Don Tapscott, bestselling author of Wikinomics and Blockchain Revolution</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-can-you-trust-how-technology-brought-us-together-and-why-it-could-drive-us-apart-rachel-botsman-abridged/">Who Can You Trust? : How Technology Brought Us Together &#8211; and Why It Could Drive Us Apart &#8211; Rachel Botsman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Creativity Code : How Ai is Learning to Write, Paint and Think &#8211; Marcus du Sautoy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-creativity-code-how-ai-is-learning-to-write-paint-and-think-marcus-du-sautoy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural Language & Machine Translation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-creativity-code-how-ai-is-learning-to-write-paint-and-think-marcus-du-sautoy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Du Sautoy&#8217;s discussion of computer creativity is fascinating&#8217; Observer CAN MACHINES BE CREATIVE? In The Creativity Code, Marcus du Sautoy examines the nature of creativity, asking how much of our emotional response to art is a product of our brains reacting to pattern and structure, and exactly what it is to be creative in mathematics, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-creativity-code-how-ai-is-learning-to-write-paint-and-think-marcus-du-sautoy-abridged/">The Creativity Code : How Ai is Learning to Write, Paint and Think &#8211; Marcus du Sautoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Du Sautoy&#8217;s discussion of computer creativity is fascinating&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                                CAN MACHINES BE CREATIVE?    </p>
<p>                              In The Creativity Code, Marcus du Sautoy examines the nature of creativity, asking how much of our emotional response to art is a product of our brains reacting to pattern and structure, and exactly what it is to be creative in mathematics, art, language and music.    </p>
<p>                              Exploring how long it might be before machines compose a symphony or paint a masterpiece, and whether they might jolt us into being more imaginative in turn, The Creativity Code is a fascinating and very different exploration into the essence of what it means to be human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-creativity-code-how-ai-is-learning-to-write-paint-and-think-marcus-du-sautoy-abridged/">The Creativity Code : How Ai is Learning to Write, Paint and Think &#8211; Marcus du Sautoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Throwing Rocks at the Google Bus : How Growth Became the Enemy of Prosperity &#8211; Douglas Rushkoff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/throwing-rocks-at-the-google-bus-how-growth-became-the-enemy-of-prosperity-douglas-rushkoff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/throwing-rocks-at-the-google-bus-how-growth-became-the-enemy-of-prosperity-douglas-rushkoff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why doesn&#8217;t the explosive growth of companies like Facebook and Uber deliver more prosperity for everyone? What is the systemic problem that sets the rich against the poor and the technologists against everybody else? When protesters shattered the windows of a bus carrying Google employees to work, their anger may have been justifiable, but it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/throwing-rocks-at-the-google-bus-how-growth-became-the-enemy-of-prosperity-douglas-rushkoff-abridged/">Throwing Rocks at the Google Bus : How Growth Became the Enemy of Prosperity &#8211; Douglas Rushkoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why doesn&#8217;t the explosive growth of companies like Facebook and Uber deliver more prosperity for everyone?     </p>
<p>                    What is the systemic problem that sets the rich against the poor and the technologists against everybody else?     </p>
<p>                    When protesters shattered the windows of a bus carrying Google employees to work, their anger may have been justifiable, but it was misdirected. The true conflict of our age isn&#8217;t between the unemployed and the digital elite, or even the 99 percent and the 1 percent. Rather, a tornado of technological improvements has spun our economic program out of control, and humanity as a whole&#8211;the protesters and the Google employees as well as the shareholders and the executives&#8211;are all trapped by the consequences. It&#8217;s time to optimize our economy for the human beings it&#8217;s supposed to be serving.     </p>
<p>                    In this groundbreaking book, acclaimed media scholar and author Douglas Rushkoff tells us how to combine the best of human nature with the best of modern technology. Tying together disparate threads&#8211;big data, the rise of robots and AI, the increasing participation of algorithms in stock market trading, the gig economy, the collapse of the eurozone&#8211;Rushkoff provides a critical vocabulary for our economic moment and a nuanced portrait of humans and commerce at a critical crossroads.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/throwing-rocks-at-the-google-bus-how-growth-became-the-enemy-of-prosperity-douglas-rushkoff-abridged/">Throwing Rocks at the Google Bus : How Growth Became the Enemy of Prosperity &#8211; Douglas Rushkoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
