<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Mathematics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/mathematics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/mathematics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Mathematics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/mathematics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Innumeracy : Mathematical Illiteracy and Its Consequences &#8211; John Allen Paulos (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/innumeracy-mathematical-illiteracy-and-its-consequences-john-allen-paulos-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Citizenship & Social Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Of A Specific Subject]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/innumeracy-mathematical-illiteracy-and-its-consequences-john-allen-paulos-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Readers of Innumeracy will be rewarded with scores of astonishing facts, a fistful of powerful ideas, and, most important, a clearer, more quantitative way of looking at their world. Why do even well-educated people understand so little about mathematics? And what are the costs of our innumeracy? John Allen Paulos, in his celebrated bestseller first [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/innumeracy-mathematical-illiteracy-and-its-consequences-john-allen-paulos-abridged/">Innumeracy : Mathematical Illiteracy and Its Consequences &#8211; John Allen Paulos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Readers of Innumeracy will be rewarded with scores of astonishing facts, a fistful of powerful ideas, and, most important, a clearer, more quantitative way of looking at their world.     </p>
<p>                    Why do even well-educated people understand so little about mathematics? And what are the costs of our innumeracy? John Allen Paulos, in his celebrated bestseller first published in 1988, argues that our inability to deal rationally with very large numbers and the probabilities associated with them results in misinformed governmental policies, confused personal decisions, and an increased susceptibility to pseudoscience of all kinds. Innumeracy lets us know what we&#8217;re missing, and how we can do something about it.     </p>
<p>                    Sprinkling his discussion of numbers and probabilities with quirky stories and anecdotes, Paulos ranges freely over many aspects of modern life, from contested elections to sports stats, from stock scams and newspaper psychics to diet and medical claims, sex discrimination, insurance, lotteries, and drug testing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/innumeracy-mathematical-illiteracy-and-its-consequences-john-allen-paulos-abridged/">Innumeracy : Mathematical Illiteracy and Its Consequences &#8211; John Allen Paulos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Algorithms to Live By : The Computer Science of Human Decisions &#8211; Brian Christian, Tom Griffiths (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/algorithms-to-live-by-the-computer-science-of-human-decisions-brian-christian-tom-griffiths-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/algorithms-to-live-by-the-computer-science-of-human-decisions-brian-christian-tom-griffiths-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fascinating exploration of how computer algorithms can be applied to our everyday lives. In this dazzlingly interdisciplinary work, acclaimed author Brian Christian and cognitive scientist Tom Griffiths show us how the simple, precise algorithms used by computers can also untangle very human questions. Modern life is constrained by limited space and time, limits that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/algorithms-to-live-by-the-computer-science-of-human-decisions-brian-christian-tom-griffiths-abridged/">Algorithms to Live By : The Computer Science of Human Decisions &#8211; Brian Christian, Tom Griffiths (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fascinating exploration of how computer algorithms can be applied to our everyday lives.    </p>
<p>                              In this dazzlingly interdisciplinary work, acclaimed author Brian Christian and cognitive scientist Tom Griffiths show us how the simple, precise algorithms used by computers can also untangle very human questions. Modern life is constrained by limited space and time, limits that give rise to a particular set of problems. What should we do, or leave undone, in a day or a lifetime? How much messiness should we accept? The authors explain how to have better hunches and when to leave things to chance, how to deal with overwhelming choices and how best to connect with others.    </p>
<p>                              From finding a spouse to finding a parking spot, from organizing one&#8217;s inbox to understanding the workings of human memory, Algorithms To Live By is full of practical takeaways to help you solve common decision-making problems and illuminate the workings of the human mind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/algorithms-to-live-by-the-computer-science-of-human-decisions-brian-christian-tom-griffiths-abridged/">Algorithms to Live By : The Computer Science of Human Decisions &#8211; Brian Christian, Tom Griffiths (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Soccermatics : Mathematical Adventures in the Beautiful Game Pro-Edition &#8211; David Sumpter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/soccermatics-mathematical-adventures-in-the-beautiful-game-pro-edition-david-sumpter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football (Soccer, Association Football)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/soccermatics-mathematical-adventures-in-the-beautiful-game-pro-edition-david-sumpter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Football looked at in a very different way&#8217; Pat Nevin, former Chelsea and Everton star and football media analyst Football &#8211; the most mathematical of sports. From shot statistics and league tables to the geometry of passing and managerial strategy, the modern game is filled with numbers, patterns and shapes. How do we make sense [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/soccermatics-mathematical-adventures-in-the-beautiful-game-pro-edition-david-sumpter-abridged/">Soccermatics : Mathematical Adventures in the Beautiful Game Pro-Edition &#8211; David Sumpter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Football looked at in a very different way&#8217; Pat Nevin, former Chelsea and Everton star and football media analyst    </p>
<p>                    Football &#8211; the most mathematical of sports. From shot statistics and league tables to the geometry of passing and managerial strategy, the modern game is filled with numbers, patterns and shapes. How do we make sense of them? The answer lies in the mathematical models applied in biology, physics and economics.     </p>
<p>                    Soccermatics brings football and mathematics together in a mind-bending synthesis, using numbers to help reveal the inner workings of the beautiful game.    </p>
<p>                    This new and expanded edition analyses the current big-name players and teams using mathematics, and meets the professionals working inside football who use numbers and statistics to boost performance.    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to the world of mathematical modelling, expressed brilliantly by David Sumpter through the prism of football. No matter who you follow &#8211; from your local non-league side to the big boys of the Premiership, La Liga, the Bundesliga, Serie A or the MLS &#8211; you&#8217;ll be amazed at what mathematics has to teach us about the world&#8217;s favourite sport.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/soccermatics-mathematical-adventures-in-the-beautiful-game-pro-edition-david-sumpter-abridged/">Soccermatics : Mathematical Adventures in the Beautiful Game Pro-Edition &#8211; David Sumpter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Code Book : The Secret History of Codes and Code-Breaking &#8211; Simon Singh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Science of Secrecy from Ancient Egypt to Quantum Cryptography From the best-selling author of Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, The Code Book is a history of man&#8217;s urge to uncover the secrets of codes, from Egyptian puzzles to modern day computer encryptions. As in Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, Simon Singh brings life to an anstonishing story of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/">The Code Book : The Secret History of Codes and Code-Breaking &#8211; Simon Singh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Science of Secrecy from Ancient Egypt to Quantum Cryptography    </p>
<p>                              From the best-selling author of Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, The Code Book is a history of man&#8217;s urge to uncover the secrets of codes, from Egyptian puzzles to modern day computer encryptions.    </p>
<p>                              As in Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, Simon Singh brings life to an anstonishing story of puzzles, codes, languages and riddles that reveals man&#8217;s continual pursuit to disguise and uncover, and to work out the secret languages of others.    </p>
<p>                              Codes have influenced events throughout history, both in the stories of those who make them and those who break them. The betrayal of Mary Queen of Scots and the cracking of the enigma code that helped the Allies in World War II are major episodes in a continuing history of cryptography. In addition to stories of intrigue and warfare, Simon Singh also investigates other codes, the unravelling of genes and the rediscovery of ancient languages and most tantalisingly, the Beale ciphers, an unbroken code that could hold the key to a $20 million treasure.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/">The Code Book : The Secret History of Codes and Code-Breaking &#8211; Simon Singh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Pursuit of the Unknown &#8211; Ian Stewart (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-pursuit-of-the-unknown-ian-stewart-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Calculus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relativity Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wave Mechanics (vibration & Acoustics)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-pursuit-of-the-unknown-ian-stewart-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most people are familiar with history&#8217;s great equations: Newton&#8217;s Law of Gravity, for instance, or Einstein&#8217;s theory of relativity. But the way these mathematical breakthroughs have contributed to human progress is seldom appreciated. In In Pursuit of the Unknown, celebrated mathematician Ian Stewart untangles the roots of our most important mathematical statements to show that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-pursuit-of-the-unknown-ian-stewart-abridged/">In Pursuit of the Unknown &#8211; Ian Stewart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most people are familiar with history&#8217;s great equations: Newton&#8217;s Law of Gravity, for instance, or Einstein&#8217;s theory of relativity. But the way these mathematical breakthroughs have contributed to human progress is seldom appreciated. In In Pursuit of the Unknown, celebrated mathematician Ian Stewart untangles the roots of our most important mathematical statements to show that equations have long been a driving force behind nearly every aspect of our lives. Using seventeen of our most crucial equations&#8211;including the Wave Equation that allowed engineers to measure a building&#8217;s response to earthquakes, saving countless lives, and the Black-Scholes model, used by bankers to track the price of financial derivatives over time&#8211;Stewart illustrates that many of the advances we now take for granted were made possible by mathematical discoveries. An approachable, lively, and informative guide to the mathematical building blocks of modern life, In Pursuit of the Unknown is a penetrating exploration of how we have also used equations to make sense of, and in turn influence, our world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-pursuit-of-the-unknown-ian-stewart-abridged/">In Pursuit of the Unknown &#8211; Ian Stewart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
