<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Neurosciences Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/neurosciences/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/neurosciences/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Neurosciences Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/neurosciences/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Behave : The Biology of Humans at Our Best and Worst &#8211; Robert M. Sapolsky</title>
		<link>/behave-the-biology-of-humans-at-our-best-and-worst-robert-m-sapolsky/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/behave-the-biology-of-humans-at-our-best-and-worst-robert-m-sapolsky/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller &#8220;It&#8217;s no exaggeration to say that Behave is one of the best nonfiction books I&#8217;ve ever read.&#8221; -David P. Barash, The Wall Street Journal &#8220;It has my vote for science book of the year.&#8221; -Parul Sehgal, The New York Times &#8220;Hands-down one of the best books I&#8217;ve read in years. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-biology-of-humans-at-our-best-and-worst-robert-m-sapolsky/">Behave : The Biology of Humans at Our Best and Worst &#8211; Robert M. Sapolsky</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller</p>
<p>                    &#8220;It&#8217;s no exaggeration to say that Behave is one of the best nonfiction books I&#8217;ve ever read.&#8221; -David P. Barash, The Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>                    &#8220;It has my vote for science book of the year.&#8221; -Parul Sehgal, The New York Times</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Hands-down one of the best books I&#8217;ve read in years. I loved it.&#8221; -Dina Temple-Raston, The Washington Post</p>
<p>                    Named a Best Book of the Year by The Washington Post and The Wall Street Journal </p>
<p>                    From the celebrated neurobiologist and primatologist, a landmark, genre-defining examination of human behavior, both good and bad, and an answer to the question: Why do we do the things we do?</p>
<p>                    Sapolsky&#8217;s storytelling concept is delightful but it also has a powerful intrinsic logic: he starts by looking at the factors that bear on a person&#8217;s reaction in the precise moment a behavior occurs, and then hops back in time from there, in stages, ultimately ending up at the deep history of our species and its evolutionary legacy.</p>
<p>                    And so the first category of explanation is the neurobiological one. A behavior occurs&#8211;whether an example of humans at our best, worst, or somewhere in between. What went on in a person&#8217;s brain a second before the behavior happened? Then Sapolsky pulls out to a slightly larger field of vision, a little earlier in time: What sight, sound, or smell caused the nervous system to produce that behavior? And then, what hormones acted hours to days earlier to change how responsive that individual is to the stimuli that triggered the nervous system? By now he has increased our field of vision so that we are thinking about neurobiology and the sensory world of our environment and endocrinology in trying to explain what happened.</p>
<p>                    Sapolsky keeps going: How was that behavior influenced by structural changes in the nervous system over the preceding months, by that person&#8217;s adolescence, childhood, fetal life, and then back to his or her genetic makeup? Finally, he expands the view to encompass factors larger than one individual. How did culture shape that individual&#8217;s group, what ecological factors millennia old formed that culture? And on and on, back to evolutionary factors millions of years old. </p>
<p>                    The result is one of the most dazzling tours d&#8217;horizon of the science of human behavior ever attempted, a majestic synthesis that harvests cutting-edge research across a range of disciplines to provide a subtle and nuanced perspective on why we ultimately do the things we do&#8230;for good and for ill. Sapolsky builds on this understanding to wrestle with some of our deepest and thorniest questions relating to tribalism and xenophobia, hierarchy and competition, morality and free will, and war and peace. Wise, humane, often very funny, Behave is a towering achievement, powerfully humanizing, and downright heroic in its own right.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-biology-of-humans-at-our-best-and-worst-robert-m-sapolsky/">Behave : The Biology of Humans at Our Best and Worst &#8211; Robert M. Sapolsky</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</title>
		<link>/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ego]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Identity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If I could give each of you a graduation present, it would be this&#8211;the most inspiring book I&#8217;ve ever read. &#8211;Bill Gates A provocative history of violence&#8211;from the New York Times bestselling author of The Stuff of Thought, The Blank Slate, and Enlightenment Now. Believe it or not, today we may be living in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/">The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If I could give each of you a graduation present, it would be this&#8211;the most inspiring book I&#8217;ve ever read. &#8211;Bill Gates     </p>
<p>                    A provocative history of violence&#8211;from the New York Times bestselling author of The Stuff of Thought, The Blank Slate,  and Enlightenment Now.    </p>
<p>                    Believe it or not, today we may be living in the most peaceful moment in our species&#8217; existence. In his gripping and controversial new work, New York Times bestselling author Steven Pinker shows that despite the ceaseless news about war, crime, and terrorism, violence has actually been in decline over long stretches of history. Exploding myths about humankind&#8217;s inherent violence and the curse of modernity, this ambitious book continues Pinker&#8217;s exploration of the essence of human nature, mixing psychology and history to provide a remarkable picture of an increasingly enlightened world.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-better-angels-of-our-nature-why-violence-has-declined-steven-pinker/">The Better Angels of Our Nature : Why Violence Has Declined &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Brain That Changes Itself : Stories of Personal Triumph from the Frontiers of Brain Science &#8211; Norman Doidge</title>
		<link>/the-brain-that-changes-itself-stories-of-personal-triumph-from-the-frontiers-of-brain-science-norman-doidge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-brain-that-changes-itself-stories-of-personal-triumph-from-the-frontiers-of-brain-science-norman-doidge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD &#8216;A remarkable and hopeful portrait of the endless adaptability of the human brain&#8217; Oliver Sacks &#8216;Utterly wonderful . . . without question one of the most important books about the brain you will ever read; yet it is beautifully written, immensely approachable, and full of humanity&#8217; Iain McGilchrist MA, author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brain-that-changes-itself-stories-of-personal-triumph-from-the-frontiers-of-brain-science-norman-doidge/">The Brain That Changes Itself : Stories of Personal Triumph from the Frontiers of Brain Science &#8211; Norman Doidge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A remarkable and hopeful portrait of the endless adaptability of the human brain&#8217; Oliver Sacks</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Utterly wonderful . . . without question one of the most important books about the brain you will ever read; yet it is beautifully written, immensely approachable, and full of humanity&#8217; Iain McGilchrist MA, author of The Master and His Emissary</p>
<p>                    Meet the ninety-year-old doctor who is still practicing medicine, the stroke victim who learned to move and talk again and the woman with half a brain that rewired itself to work as a whole. All these people had their lives transformed by the remarkable discovery that our brains can repair themselves through the power of positive thinking. </p>
<p>                    Here bestselling author, psychiatrist and psychoanalyst Norman Doidge reveals the secrets of the cutting-edge science of &#8216;neuroplasticity&#8217;. He introduces incredible case histories &#8211; blind people helped to see, IQs raised and memories sharpened &#8211; and tells the stories of the maverick scientists who are overturning centuries of assumptions about the brain.   </p>
<p>                    This inspiring book will leave you with a sense of wonder at the capabilities of the mind, and the self-healing power that lies within all of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brain-that-changes-itself-stories-of-personal-triumph-from-the-frontiers-of-brain-science-norman-doidge/">The Brain That Changes Itself : Stories of Personal Triumph from the Frontiers of Brain Science &#8211; Norman Doidge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future of the Mind : The Scientific Quest to Understand, Enhance, and Empower the Mind &#8211; Michio Kaku</title>
		<link>/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michio Kaku, the New York Times bestselling author of Physics of the Impossible and Physics of the Future tackles the most fascinating and complex object in the known universe: the human brain. The Future of the Mind brings a topic that once belonged solely to the province of science fiction into a startling new reality. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/">The Future of the Mind : The Scientific Quest to Understand, Enhance, and Empower the Mind &#8211; Michio Kaku</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michio Kaku, the New York Times bestselling author of Physics of the Impossible and Physics of the Future tackles the most fascinating and complex object in the known universe: the human brain.     </p>
<p>                    The Future of the Mind brings a topic that once belonged solely to the province of science fiction into a startling new reality. This scientific tour de force unveils the astonishing research being done in top laboratories around the world&#8211;all based on the latest advancements in neuroscience and physics&#8211;including recent experiments in telepathy, mind control, avatars, telekinesis, and recording memories and dreams. The Future of the Mind is an extraordinary, mind-boggling exploration of the frontiers of neuroscience. Dr. Kaku looks toward the day when we may achieve the ability to upload the human brain to a computer, neuron for neuron; project thoughts and emotions around the world on a brain-net; take a &#8220;smart pill&#8221; to enhance cognition; send our consciousness across the universe; and push the very limits of immortality.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/">The Future of the Mind : The Scientific Quest to Understand, Enhance, and Empower the Mind &#8211; Michio Kaku</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Your Mind On Plants : Opium-Caffeine-Mescaline &#8211; Michael Pollan</title>
		<link>/this-is-your-mind-on-plants-opium-caffeine-mescaline-michael-pollan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Botany & Plant Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drug-induced States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trees]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildflowers & Plants]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-your-mind-on-plants-opium-caffeine-mescaline-michael-pollan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s a trip &#8211; engrossing, eye-opening, mind altering&#8217; New Statesman &#8216;Fascinating. Pollan is the perfect guide &#8230; curious, careful, open minded&#8217; The Guardian From the international bestselling author of How to Change Your Mind comes a ground-breaking exploration of our relationship with natural drugs Of all the many things humans rely on plants for, surely [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-mind-on-plants-opium-caffeine-mescaline-michael-pollan/">This Is Your Mind On Plants : Opium-Caffeine-Mescaline &#8211; Michael Pollan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s a trip &#8211; engrossing, eye-opening, mind altering&#8217; New Statesman</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating. Pollan is the perfect guide &#8230; curious, careful, open minded&#8217; The Guardian</p>
<p>                    From the international bestselling author of How to Change Your Mind comes a ground-breaking exploration of our relationship with natural drugs</p>
<p>                    Of all the many things humans rely on plants for, surely the most curious is our use of them to change consciousness: to stimulate, calm, or completely alter the qualities of our mental experience. In This Is Your Mind On Plants, Michael Pollan explores three very different drugs &#8211; opium, caffeine and mescaline &#8211; and throws the fundamental strangeness of our thinking about them into sharp relief. Exploring and participating in the cultures that have grown up around these drugs, while consuming (or in the case of caffeine, trying not to consume) them, Pollan reckons with the powerful human attraction to psychoactive plants, and the equally powerful taboos. </p>
<p>                    In a unique blend of history, science, memoir and reportage, Pollan shines a fresh light on a subject that is all too often treated reductively. In doing so, he proves that there is much more to say about these plants than simply debating their regulation, for when we take them into our bodies and let them change our minds, we are engaging with nature in one of the most profound ways we can. This ground-breaking and singular book holds up a mirror to our fundamental human needs and aspirations, the operations of our minds and our entanglement with the natural world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-mind-on-plants-opium-caffeine-mescaline-michael-pollan/">This Is Your Mind On Plants : Opium-Caffeine-Mescaline &#8211; Michael Pollan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Biological Mind : How Brain, Body, and Environment Collaborate to Make Us Who We Are &#8211; Alan Jasanoff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-biological-mind-how-brain-body-and-environment-collaborate-to-make-us-who-we-are-alan-jasanoff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-biological-mind-how-brain-body-and-environment-collaborate-to-make-us-who-we-are-alan-jasanoff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A pioneering neuroscientist argues that we are more than our brains To many, the brain is the seat of personal identity and autonomy. But the way we talk about the brain is often rooted more in mystical conceptions of the soul than in scientific fact. This blinds us to the physical realities of mental function. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-biological-mind-how-brain-body-and-environment-collaborate-to-make-us-who-we-are-alan-jasanoff-abridged/">The Biological Mind : How Brain, Body, and Environment Collaborate to Make Us Who We Are &#8211; Alan Jasanoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A pioneering neuroscientist argues that we are more than our brains    </p>
<p>                    To many, the brain is the seat of personal identity and autonomy. But the way we talk about the brain is often rooted more in mystical conceptions of the soul than in scientific fact. This blinds us to the physical realities of mental function. We ignore bodily influences on our psychology, from chemicals in the blood to bacteria in the gut, and overlook the ways that the environment affects our behavior, via factors varying from subconscious sights and sounds to the weather. As a result, we alternately overestimate our capacity for free will or equate brains to inorganic machines like computers. But a brain is neither a soul nor an electrical network: it is a bodily organ, and it cannot be separated from its surroundings. Our selves aren&#8217;t just inside our heads&#8211;they&#8217;re spread throughout our bodies and beyond. Only once we come to terms with this can we grasp the true nature of our humanity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-biological-mind-how-brain-body-and-environment-collaborate-to-make-us-who-we-are-alan-jasanoff-abridged/">The Biological Mind : How Brain, Body, and Environment Collaborate to Make Us Who We Are &#8211; Alan Jasanoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marine Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oceanography (seas)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Aquatic Creatures]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BBC R4 Book of the Week &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Fascinating and often delightful&#8217; The Times What if intelligent life on Earth evolved not once, but twice? The octopus is the closest we will come to meeting an intelligent alien. What can we learn from the encounter? In Other Minds, Peter Godfrey-Smith, a distinguished philosopher of science [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/">Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BBC R4 Book of the Week<br />
                              &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian<br />
                              &#8216;Fascinating and often delightful&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                                What if intelligent life on Earth evolved not once, but twice? The octopus is the closest we will come to meeting an intelligent alien. What can we learn from the encounter?    </p>
<p>                              In Other Minds, Peter Godfrey-Smith, a distinguished philosopher of science and a skilled scuba diver, tells a bold new story of how nature became aware of itself &#8211; a story that largely occurs in the ocean, where animals first appeared.    </p>
<p>                              Tracking the mind&#8217;s fitful development from unruly clumps of seaborne cells to the first evolved nervous systems in ancient relatives of jellyfish, he explores the incredible evolutionary journey of the cephalopods, which began as inconspicuous molluscs who would later abandon their shells to rise above the ocean floor, searching for prey and acquiring the greater intelligence needed to do so &#8211; a journey completely independent from the route that mammals and birds would later take.    </p>
<p>                              But what kind of intelligence do cephalopods possess? How did the octopus, a solitary creature with little social life, become so smart? What is it like to have eight tentacles that are so packed with neurons that they virtually &#8216;think for themselves&#8217;? By tracing the question of inner life back to its roots and comparing human beings with our most remarkable animal relatives, Godfrey-Smith casts crucial new light on the octopus mind &#8211; and on our own.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/">Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spark &#8211; Dr John J. Ratey, Eric Hagerman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/spark-dr-john-j-ratey-eric-hagerman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/spark-dr-john-j-ratey-eric-hagerman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exercise is not only good for the body: it can transform your mind too. This new scientific revolution will teach you how to boost brain cells, protect yourself against mental illness and dementia, and ensure success in exams and the workplace. We all know that exercise is good for the body. But did you know [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spark-dr-john-j-ratey-eric-hagerman-abridged/">Spark &#8211; Dr John J. Ratey, Eric Hagerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exercise is not only good for the body: it can transform your mind  too. This new scientific revolution will teach you how to boost brain  cells, protect yourself against mental illness and dementia, and ensure  success in exams and the workplace.    </p>
<p>                    We all know that exercise is good for the body. But did you know that it can transform your mind? This new scientific revolution will teach you how to boost brain cells, protect yourself against mental illness and dementia, and ensure success in exams and the workplace.     </p>
<p>                    Follow the SPARK! training regimen and build your brain to its peak performance. This book will change the way you think about exercise &#8211; and, for that matter, the way you think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spark-dr-john-j-ratey-eric-hagerman-abridged/">Spark &#8211; Dr John J. Ratey, Eric Hagerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fooling Houdini : Magicians, Mentalists, Math Geeks &#038; the Hidden Powers of the Mind &#8211; Alex Stone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fooling-houdini-magicians-mentalists-math-geeks-the-hidden-powers-of-the-mind-alex-stone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conjuring & Magic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fooling-houdini-magicians-mentalists-math-geeks-the-hidden-powers-of-the-mind-alex-stone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the back rooms of New York City&#8217;s age-old magic societies to cutting-edge psychology labs, three-card monte games on Canal Street to glossy Las Vegas casinos, Fooling Houdini recounts Alex Stone&#8217;s quest to join the ranks of master magicians. As he navigates this quirky and occasionally hilarious subculture populated by brilliant eccentrics, Stone pulls back [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fooling-houdini-magicians-mentalists-math-geeks-the-hidden-powers-of-the-mind-alex-stone-abridged/">Fooling Houdini : Magicians, Mentalists, Math Geeks &#038; the Hidden Powers of the Mind &#8211; Alex Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the back rooms of New York City&#8217;s age-old magic societies to cutting-edge psychology labs, three-card monte games on Canal Street to glossy Las Vegas casinos, Fooling Houdini recounts Alex Stone&#8217;s quest to join the ranks of master magicians.    </p>
<p>                    As he navigates this quirky and occasionally hilarious subculture populated by brilliant eccentrics, Stone pulls back the curtain on a community shrouded in secrecy, fueled by obsession and brilliance, and organized around one overriding need: to prove one&#8217;s worth by deceiving others.    </p>
<p>                    But his journey is more than a tale of tricks, gigs, and geeks. By investing some of the lesser-known corners of psychology, neuroscience, physics, history, and even crime, all through the lens of trickery and illusion, Fooling Houdini arrives at a host of startling revelations about how the mind works&#8211;and why, sometimes, it doesn&#8217;t.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fooling-houdini-magicians-mentalists-math-geeks-the-hidden-powers-of-the-mind-alex-stone-abridged/">Fooling Houdini : Magicians, Mentalists, Math Geeks &#038; the Hidden Powers of the Mind &#8211; Alex Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Emotions Are Made : The Secret Life of the Brain &#8211; Lisa Feldman Barrett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-emotions-are-made-the-secret-life-of-the-brain-lisa-feldman-barrett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Perception]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-emotions-are-made-the-secret-life-of-the-brain-lisa-feldman-barrett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How Emotions Are Made did what all great books do. It took a subject I thought I understood and turned my understanding upside down&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell, author of The Tipping Point. When you feel anxious, angry, happy, or surprised, what&#8217;s really going on inside of you? Many scientists believe that emotions come from a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-emotions-are-made-the-secret-life-of-the-brain-lisa-feldman-barrett-abridged/">How Emotions Are Made : The Secret Life of the Brain &#8211; Lisa Feldman Barrett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How Emotions Are Made did what all great books do. It took a subject I thought I understood and turned my understanding upside down&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell, author of The Tipping Point.    </p>
<p>                    When you feel anxious, angry, happy, or surprised, what&#8217;s really going on inside of you?     </p>
<p>                    Many scientists believe that emotions come from a specific part of the brain, triggered by the world around us. The thrill of seeing an old friend, the fear of losing someone we love &#8211; each of these sensations seems to arise automatically and uncontrollably from within us, finding expression on our faces and in our behaviour, carrying us away with the experience.    </p>
<p>                    This understanding of emotion has been around since Plato. But what if it is wrong? In How Emotions Are Made, pioneering psychologist and neuroscientist Lisa Feldman Barrett draws on the latest scientific evidence to reveal that our common-sense ideas about emotions are dramatically, even dangerously, out of date &#8211; and that we have been paying the price. Emotions aren&#8217;t universally pre-programmed in our brains and bodies; rather they are psychological experiences that each of us constructs based on our unique personal history, physiology and environment.    </p>
<p>                    This new view of emotions has serious implications: when judges issue lesser sentences for crimes of passion, when police officers fire at threatening suspects, or when doctors choose between one diagnosis and another, they&#8217;re all, in some way, relying on the ancient assumption that emotions are hardwired into our brains and bodies. Revising that conception of emotion isn&#8217;t just good science, Barrett shows; it&#8217;s vital to our well-being and the health of society itself.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-emotions-are-made-the-secret-life-of-the-brain-lisa-feldman-barrett-abridged/">How Emotions Are Made : The Secret Life of the Brain &#8211; Lisa Feldman Barrett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Storytelling Animal : How Stories Make Us Human &#8211; Instructor Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-storytelling-animal-how-stories-make-us-human-instructor-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-storytelling-animal-how-stories-make-us-human-instructor-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this delightful and original book, Jonathan Gottschall offers the first unified theory of storytelling. Drawing on neuroscience and evolutionary biology, The Storytelling Animal explores what stories reveal about human nature, how we process information, and think about the world. Humans live in landscapes of make-believe. We spin fantasies. We devour novels, films, and plays. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-storytelling-animal-how-stories-make-us-human-instructor-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/">The Storytelling Animal : How Stories Make Us Human &#8211; Instructor Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this delightful and original book, Jonathan Gottschall offers the first unified theory of storytelling. Drawing on neuroscience and evolutionary biology, The Storytelling Animal explores what stories reveal about human nature, how we process information, and think about the world.<br />
                    Humans live in landscapes of make-believe. We spin fantasies. We devour novels, films, and plays. Even sporting events and criminal trials unfold as narratives. Gottschall argues that stories help us navigate life&#8217;s complex social problems &#8212; just as flight simulators prepare pilots for difficult situations. Storytelling has evolved, like other behaviors, to ensure our survival. Gottschall tells us what it means to be a storytelling animal and explains how stories can change the world for the better.<br />
                    We know we are master shapers of story. The Storytelling Animal finally reveals how stories shape us.<br />
                    A NYTimes.com Editor&#8217;s Choice<br />
                    A Los Angeles Times Book Prizes Finalist<br />
                    &#8220;A jaunty, insightful new book . . . [that] draws from disparate corners of history and science to celebrate our compulsion to storify everything around us.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-storytelling-animal-how-stories-make-us-human-instructor-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/">The Storytelling Animal : How Stories Make Us Human &#8211; Instructor Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moral Tribes : Emotion, Reason and the Gap Between Us and Them &#8211; Joshua Greene (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/moral-tribes-emotion-reason-and-the-gap-between-us-and-them-joshua-greene-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/moral-tribes-emotion-reason-and-the-gap-between-us-and-them-joshua-greene-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Our brains were designed for tribal life, for getting along with a select group of others (Us), and for fighting off everyone else (Them). But modern life has thrust the world&#8217;s tribes into a shared space, creating conflicts of interest and clashes of values, along with unprecedented opportunities. As the world shrinks, the moral lines [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moral-tribes-emotion-reason-and-the-gap-between-us-and-them-joshua-greene-abridged/">Moral Tribes : Emotion, Reason and the Gap Between Us and Them &#8211; Joshua Greene (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our brains were designed for tribal life, for getting along with a select group of others (Us), and for fighting off everyone else (Them). But modern life has thrust the world&#8217;s tribes into a shared space, creating conflicts of interest and clashes of values, along with unprecedented opportunities. As the world shrinks, the moral lines that divide us become more salient and more puzzling. We fight over everything from tax codes to gay marriage to global warming, and we wonder where, if at all, we can find our common ground.    </p>
<p>                    A grand synthesis of neuroscience, psychology, and philosophy, Moral Tribes reveals the underlying causes of modern conflict and lights a way forward. Our emotions make us social animals, turning Me into Us. But they also make us tribal animals, turning Us against Them. Our tribal emotions make us fight, sometimes with bombs, sometimes with words, and often with life-and-death stakes. Drawing inspiration from moral philosophy and cutting-edge science, Moral Tribes shows when we should trust our instincts, when we should reason, and how the right kind of reasoning can move us forward.    </p>
<p>                    Joshua Greene is the director of Harvard University&#8217;s Moral Cognition Lab, a pioneering scientist, a philosopher, and an acclaimed teacher. The great challenge of Moral Tribes is this: How can we get along with Them when what they want feels so wrong? Finally, Greene offers a surprisingly simple set of maxims for navigating the modern moral terrain, a practical road map for solving problems and living better lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moral-tribes-emotion-reason-and-the-gap-between-us-and-them-joshua-greene-abridged/">Moral Tribes : Emotion, Reason and the Gap Between Us and Them &#8211; Joshua Greene (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Science of Storytelling : Why Stories Make Us Human, and How to Tell Them Better &#8211; Will Storr (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-science-of-storytelling-why-stories-make-us-human-and-how-to-tell-them-better-will-storr-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-science-of-storytelling-why-stories-make-us-human-and-how-to-tell-them-better-will-storr-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;If you want to write a novel or a script, read this book&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;The best book on the craft of storytelling I&#8217;ve ever read&#8217; Matt Haig &#8216;Rarely has a book engrossed me more, and forced me to question everything I&#8217;ve ever read, seen or written. A masterpiece&#8217; Adam Rutherford Why [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-of-storytelling-why-stories-make-us-human-and-how-to-tell-them-better-will-storr-abridged/">The Science of Storytelling : Why Stories Make Us Human, and How to Tell Them Better &#8211; Will Storr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;If you want to write a novel or a script, read this book&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                              &#8216;The best book on the craft of storytelling I&#8217;ve ever read&#8217; Matt Haig    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Rarely has a book engrossed me more, and forced me to question everything I&#8217;ve ever read, seen or written. A masterpiece&#8217; Adam Rutherford    </p>
<p>                                Why stories make us human and how to tell them better.    </p>
<p>                              There have been many attempts to understand what makes a good story &#8211; but few have used a scientific approach.    </p>
<p>                              In this incisive, thought-provoking book, award-winning writer Will Storr demonstrates how master storytellers manipulate and compel us.    </p>
<p>                              Applying dazzling psychological research and cutting-edge neuroscience to the foundations of our myths and archetypes, he shows how we can use these tools to tell better stories &#8211; and make sense of our chaotic modern world.    </p>
<p>                                INCLUDES NEW MATERIAL.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-of-storytelling-why-stories-make-us-human-and-how-to-tell-them-better-will-storr-abridged/">The Science of Storytelling : Why Stories Make Us Human, and How to Tell Them Better &#8211; Will Storr (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Tale of the Dueling Neurosurgeons : The History of the Human Brain as Revealed by True Stories of Trauma, Madness, and Recovery &#8211; Sam Kean (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-tale-of-the-dueling-neurosurgeons-the-history-of-the-human-brain-as-revealed-by-true-stories-of-trauma-madness-and-recovery-sam-kean-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tale-of-the-dueling-neurosurgeons-the-history-of-the-human-brain-as-revealed-by-true-stories-of-trauma-madness-and-recovery-sam-kean-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The author of the bestseller The Disappearing Spoon reveals the secret inner workings of the brain through strange but true stories. Early studies of the human brain used a simple method: wait for misfortune to strike &#8212; strokes, seizures, infectious diseases, horrendous accidents &#8212; and see how victims coped. In many cases their survival was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tale-of-the-dueling-neurosurgeons-the-history-of-the-human-brain-as-revealed-by-true-stories-of-trauma-madness-and-recovery-sam-kean-abridged/">The Tale of the Dueling Neurosurgeons : The History of the Human Brain as Revealed by True Stories of Trauma, Madness, and Recovery &#8211; Sam Kean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author of the bestseller The Disappearing Spoon reveals the secret inner workings of the brain through strange but true stories.      </p>
<p>                     Early studies of the human brain used a simple method: wait for misfortune to strike &#8212; strokes, seizures, infectious diseases, horrendous accidents &#8212; and see how victims coped. In many cases their survival was miraculous, if puzzling. Observers were amazed by the transformations that took place when different parts of the brain were destroyed, altering victims&#8217; personalities. Parents suddenly couldn&#8217;t recognize their own children. Pillars of the community became pathological liars. Some people couldn&#8217;t speak but could still sing.     </p>
<p>                     In The Tale of the Dueling Neurosurgeons, Sam Kean travels through time with stories of neurological curiosities: phantom limbs, Siamese twin brains, viruses that eat patients&#8217; memories, blind people who see through their tongues. He weaves these narratives together with prose that makes the pages fly by, to create a story of discovery that reaches back to the 1500s and the high-profile jousting accident that inspired this book&#8217;s title.     </p>
<p>                     With the lucid, masterful explanations and razor-sharp wit his fans have come to expect, Kean explores the brain&#8217;s secret passageways and recounts the forgotten tales of the ordinary people whose struggles, resilience, and deep humanity made neuroscience possible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tale-of-the-dueling-neurosurgeons-the-history-of-the-human-brain-as-revealed-by-true-stories-of-trauma-madness-and-recovery-sam-kean-abridged/">The Tale of the Dueling Neurosurgeons : The History of the Human Brain as Revealed by True Stories of Trauma, Madness, and Recovery &#8211; Sam Kean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Aesthetic Brain : How We Evolved to Desire Beauty and Enjoy Art &#8211; Anjan Chatterjee, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-aesthetic-brain-how-we-evolved-to-desire-beauty-and-enjoy-art-anjan-chatterjee-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-aesthetic-brain-how-we-evolved-to-desire-beauty-and-enjoy-art-anjan-chatterjee-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Aesthetic Brain takes readers on an exciting journey through the world of beauty, pleasure, and art. Using the latest advances in neuroscience and evolutionary psychology, Anjan Chatterjee investigates how an aesthetic sense is etched into our minds, and explains why artistic concerns feature centrally in our lives. Along the way, Chatterjee addresses such fundamental [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-aesthetic-brain-how-we-evolved-to-desire-beauty-and-enjoy-art-anjan-chatterjee-md-abridged/">The Aesthetic Brain : How We Evolved to Desire Beauty and Enjoy Art &#8211; Anjan Chatterjee, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Aesthetic Brain takes readers on an exciting journey through the world of beauty, pleasure, and art. Using the latest advances in neuroscience and evolutionary psychology, Anjan Chatterjee investigates how an aesthetic sense is etched into our minds, and explains why artistic concerns feature centrally in our lives. Along the way, Chatterjee addresses such fundamental questions as: What is beauty? Is it universal? How is beauty related to pleasure? What<br />
                    is art? Should art be beautiful? Do we have an instinct for art?    </p>
<p>                    Early on, Chatterjee probes the reasons why we find people, places, and even numbers beautiful, highlighting the important relationship between beauty and pleasure. Examining our pleasures allows him to reveal why we enjoy things like food, sex, and money, and how these rewards relate to our aesthetic encounters. Chatterjee&#8217;s detailed discussion of beauty and pleasure equips readers to confront essential questions about the nature of art, the problems of defining it, and the challenges of<br />
                    interpreting its modern, non-traditional forms. Replete with facts, anecdotes, and analogies, this lively empirical guide to aesthetics offers scientific answers to fundamental questions without deflating the intrinsic wonders of beauty and art in an affordable paperback edition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-aesthetic-brain-how-we-evolved-to-desire-beauty-and-enjoy-art-anjan-chatterjee-md-abridged/">The Aesthetic Brain : How We Evolved to Desire Beauty and Enjoy Art &#8211; Anjan Chatterjee, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Brain : The Story of You &#8211; David Eagleman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-brain-the-story-of-you-david-eagleman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-brain-the-story-of-you-david-eagleman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is the story of how your life shapes your brain, and how your brain shapes your life.&#8217; Join renowned neuroscientist David Eagleman on a whistle-stop tour of the inner cosmos. It&#8217;s a journey that will take you into the world of extreme sports, criminal justice, genocide, brain surgery, robotics and the search for immortality. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brain-the-story-of-you-david-eagleman-abridged/">The Brain : The Story of You &#8211; David Eagleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is the story of how your life shapes your brain, and how your brain shapes your life.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     Join renowned neuroscientist David Eagleman on a whistle-stop tour of the inner cosmos. It&#8217;s a journey that will take you into the world of extreme sports, criminal justice, genocide, brain surgery, robotics and the search for immortality. On the way, amidst the infinitely dense tangle of brain cells and their trillions of connections, something emerges that you might not have expected to see: you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brain-the-story-of-you-david-eagleman-abridged/">The Brain : The Story of You &#8211; David Eagleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wired for Story : The Writer&#8217;s Guide to Using Brain Science to Hook Readers from the Very First Sentence &#8211; Lisa Cron (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wired-for-story-the-writers-guide-to-using-brain-science-to-hook-readers-from-the-very-first-sentence-lisa-cron-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing Skills]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wired-for-story-the-writers-guide-to-using-brain-science-to-hook-readers-from-the-very-first-sentence-lisa-cron-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This guide reveals how writers can utilize cognitive storytelling strategies to craft stories that ignite readers&#8217; brains and captivate them through each plot element. Imagine knowing what the brain craves from every tale it encounters, what fuels the success of any great story, and what keeps readers transfixed. Wired for Story reveals these cognitive secrets&#8211;and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wired-for-story-the-writers-guide-to-using-brain-science-to-hook-readers-from-the-very-first-sentence-lisa-cron-abridged/">Wired for Story : The Writer&#8217;s Guide to Using Brain Science to Hook Readers from the Very First Sentence &#8211; Lisa Cron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This guide reveals how writers can utilize cognitive storytelling strategies to craft stories that ignite readers&#8217; brains and captivate them through each plot element.     </p>
<p>                    Imagine knowing what the brain craves from every tale it encounters, what fuels the success of any great story, and what keeps readers transfixed. Wired for Story reveals these cognitive secrets&#8211;and it&#8217;s a game-changer for anyone who has ever set pen to paper.     </p>
<p>                    The vast majority of writing advice focuses on &#8220;writing well&#8221; as if it were the same as telling a great story. This is exactly where many aspiring writers fail&#8211;they strive for beautiful metaphors, authentic dialogue, and interesting characters, losing sight of the one thing that every engaging story must do: ignite the brain&#8217;s hardwired desire to learn what happens next. When writers tap into the evolutionary purpose of story and electrify our curiosity, it triggers a delicious dopamine rush that tells us to pay attention. Without it, even the most perfect prose won&#8217;t hold anyone&#8217;s interest.     </p>
<p>                    Backed by recent breakthroughs in neuroscience as well as examples from novels, screenplays, and short stories, Wired for Story offers a revolutionary look at story as the brain experiences it. Each chapter zeroes in on an aspect of the brain, its corresponding revelation about story, and the way to apply it to your storytelling right now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wired-for-story-the-writers-guide-to-using-brain-science-to-hook-readers-from-the-very-first-sentence-lisa-cron-abridged/">Wired for Story : The Writer&#8217;s Guide to Using Brain Science to Hook Readers from the Very First Sentence &#8211; Lisa Cron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A General Theory of Love &#8211; Thomas Lewis, Fari Amini, Richard Lannon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-general-theory-of-love-thomas-lewis-fari-amini-richard-lannon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-general-theory-of-love-thomas-lewis-fari-amini-richard-lannon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This original and lucid account of the complexities of love and its essential role in human well-being draws on the latest scientific research. Three eminent psychiatrists tackle the difficult task of reconciling what artists and thinkers have known for thousands of years about the human heart with what has only recently been learned about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-general-theory-of-love-thomas-lewis-fari-amini-richard-lannon-abridged/">A General Theory of Love &#8211; Thomas Lewis, Fari Amini, Richard Lannon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This original and lucid account of the complexities of love and its essential role in human well-being draws on the latest scientific research. Three eminent psychiatrists tackle the difficult task of reconciling what artists and thinkers have known for thousands of years about the human heart with what has only recently been learned about the primitive functions of the human brain.    </p>
<p>                    A General Theory of Love demonstrates that our nervous systems are not self-contained: from earliest childhood, our brains actually link with those of the people close to us, in a silent rhythm that alters the very structure of our brains, establishes life-long emotional patterns, and makes us, in large part, who we are. Explaining how relationships function, how parents shape their child&#8217;s developing self, how psychotherapy really works, and how our society dangerously flouts essential emotional laws, this is a work of rare passion and eloquence that will forever change the way you think about human intimacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-general-theory-of-love-thomas-lewis-fari-amini-richard-lannon-abridged/">A General Theory of Love &#8211; Thomas Lewis, Fari Amini, Richard Lannon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanistic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Why do human beings behave as they do? &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**    </p>
<p>                    Why do human beings behave as they do?     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm    </p>
<p>                     We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of our nature destined to win out over the other?    </p>
<p>                     Every act of human behaviour has multiple layers of causation, spiralling back seconds, minutes, hours, days, months, years, even centuries, right back to the dawn of time and the origins of our species.     </p>
<p>                     In the epic sweep of history, how does our biology affect the arc of war and peace, justice and persecution? How have our brains evolved alongside our cultures?    </p>
<p>                     This is the exhilarating story of human morality and the science underpinning the biggest question of all: what makes us human?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the best scientist-writers of our time&#8217; Oliver Sacks</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ignorance : How It Drives Science &#8211; Stuart Firestein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ignorance-how-it-drives-science-stuart-firestein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Epistemology & Theory Of Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ignorance-how-it-drives-science-stuart-firestein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Knowledge is a big subject, says Stuart Firestein, but ignorance is a bigger one. And it is ignorance-not knowledge-that is the true engine of science. Most of us have a false impression of science as a surefire, deliberate, step-by-step method for finding things out and getting things done. In fact, says Firestein, more often than [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ignorance-how-it-drives-science-stuart-firestein-abridged/">Ignorance : How It Drives Science &#8211; Stuart Firestein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Knowledge is a big subject, says Stuart Firestein, but ignorance is a bigger one. And it is ignorance-not knowledge-that is the true engine of science.     </p>
<p>                        Most of us have a false impression of science as a surefire, deliberate, step-by-step method for finding things out and getting things done. In fact, says Firestein, more often than not, science is like looking for a black cat in a dark room, and there may not be a cat in the room. The process is more hit-or-miss than you might imagine, with much stumbling and groping after phantoms. But it is exactly this &#8220;not knowing,&#8221; this puzzling over thorny questions or inexplicable data, that gets<br />
                    researchers into the lab early and keeps them there late, the thing that propels them, the very driving force of science. Firestein shows how scientists use ignorance to program their work, to identify what should be done, what the next steps are, and where they should concentrate their energies. And<br />
                    he includes a catalog of how scientists use ignorance, consciously or unconsciously-a remarkable range of approaches that includes looking for connections to other research, revisiting apparently settled questions, using small questions to get at big ones, and tackling a problem simply out of curiosity. The book concludes with four case histories-in cognitive psychology, theoretical physics, astronomy, and neuroscience-that provide a feel for the nuts and bolts of ignorance, the day-to-day<br />
                    battle that goes on in scientific laboratories and in scientific minds with questions that range from the quotidian to the profound.     </p>
<p>                       Turning the conventional idea about science on its head, Ignorance opens a new window on the true nature of research. It is a must-read for anyone curious about science.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ignorance-how-it-drives-science-stuart-firestein-abridged/">Ignorance : How It Drives Science &#8211; Stuart Firestein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reader, Come Home : The Reading Brain in a Digital World &#8211; Maryanne Wolf (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reader-come-home-the-reading-brain-in-a-digital-world-maryanne-wolf-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociolinguistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reader-come-home-the-reading-brain-in-a-digital-world-maryanne-wolf-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed Proust and the Squid follows up with a lively, ambitious, and deeply informative book that considers the future of the reading brain and our capacity for critical thinking, empathy, and reflection as we become increasingly dependent on digital technologies. A decade ago, Maryanne Wolf&#8217;s Proust and the Squid revealed what [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reader-come-home-the-reading-brain-in-a-digital-world-maryanne-wolf-abridged/">Reader, Come Home : The Reading Brain in a Digital World &#8211; Maryanne Wolf (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed Proust and the Squid follows up with a lively, ambitious, and deeply informative book that considers the future of the reading brain and our capacity for critical thinking, empathy, and reflection as we become increasingly dependent on digital technologies.    </p>
<p>                    A decade ago, Maryanne Wolf&#8217;s Proust and the Squid revealed what we know about how the brain learns to read and how reading changes the way we think and feel. Since then, the ways we process written language have changed dramatically with many concerned about both their own changes and that of children. New research on the reading brain chronicles these changes in the brains of children and adults as they learn to read while immersed in a digitally dominated medium.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing deeply on this research, this book comprises a series of letters Wolf writes to us&#8211;her beloved readers&#8211;to describe her concerns and her hopes about what is happening to the reading brain as it unavoidably changes to adapt to digital mediums. Wolf raises difficult questions, including: Will children learn to incorporate the full range of deep reading processes that are at the core of the expert reading brain?Will the mix of a seemingly infinite set of distractions for children&#8217;s attention and their quick access to immediate, voluminous information alter their ability to think for themselves?With information at their fingertips, will the next generation learn to build their own storehouse of knowledge, which could impede the ability to make analogies and draw inferences from what they know?Will all these influences change the formation in children and the use in adults of slower cognitive processes like critical thinking, personal reflection, imagination, and empathy that comprise deep reading and that influence both how we think and how we live our lives?How can we preserve deep reading processes in future iterations of the reading brain?    </p>
<p>                    Concerns about attention span, critical reasoning, and over-reliance on technology are never just about children&#8211;Wolf herself has found that, though she is a reading expert, her ability to read deeply has been impacted as she has become increasingly dependent on screens.    </p>
<p>                    Wolf draws on neuroscience, literature, education, and philosophy and blends historical, literary, and scientific facts with down-to-earth examples and warm anecdotes to illuminate complex ideas that culminate in a proposal for a biliterate reading brain. Provocative and intriguing, Reader, Come Home is a roadmap that provides a cautionary but hopeful perspective on the impact of technology on our brains and our most essential intellectual capacities&#8211;and what this could mean for our future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reader-come-home-the-reading-brain-in-a-digital-world-maryanne-wolf-abridged/">Reader, Come Home : The Reading Brain in a Digital World &#8211; Maryanne Wolf (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smarter Faster Better : The Secrets of Being Productive &#8211; Charles Duhigg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/smarter-faster-better-the-secrets-of-being-productive-charles-duhigg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/smarter-faster-better-the-secrets-of-being-productive-charles-duhigg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his international bestseller The Power of Habit, Pulitzer Prize-winner Charles Duhigg explained why we do what we do. Now he applies the same relentless curiosity and masterful analysis to the question: how can each of us achieve more? Drawing on the very latest findings in neuroscience, psychology and behavioural economics, he demonstrates the eight [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smarter-faster-better-the-secrets-of-being-productive-charles-duhigg-abridged/">Smarter Faster Better : The Secrets of Being Productive &#8211; Charles Duhigg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his international bestseller The Power of Habit, Pulitzer Prize-winner Charles Duhigg explained why we do what we do. Now he applies the same relentless curiosity and masterful analysis to the question: how can each of us achieve more?    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the very latest findings in neuroscience, psychology and behavioural economics, he demonstrates the eight simple principles that govern productivity. He demonstrates how the most dynamic and effective people &#8211; from CEOs to film-makers to software entrepreneurs  &#8211; deploy them. And he shows how you can, too.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Charles has some wonderful advice for increasing productivity . . . the tips he highlights have most definitely played a huge part in helping me to build the Virgin brand.&#8217; Richard Branson    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;In Smarter Faster Better Duhigg finds provocative answers to a riddle of our age: how to become more productive (by two times, or even ten times) and less busy.&#8217; Jim Collins    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;There are valuable lessons in Smarter Faster Better . . . I never felt like putting it down.&#8217; Financial Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smarter-faster-better-the-secrets-of-being-productive-charles-duhigg-abridged/">Smarter Faster Better : The Secrets of Being Productive &#8211; Charles Duhigg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Evolution of Everything : How Small Changes Transform Our World &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If there is one dominant myth about the world, one huge mistake we all make &#8230; it is that we all go around assuming the world is much more of a planned place than it is.&#8217; From the industrial revolution and the rise of China, to urbanisation and the birth of bitcoin, Matt Ridley demolishes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/">The Evolution of Everything : How Small Changes Transform Our World &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If there is one dominant myth about the world, one huge mistake we all make &#8230; it is that we all go around assuming the world is much more of a planned place than it is.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                              From the industrial revolution and the rise of China, to urbanisation and the birth of bitcoin, Matt Ridley demolishes conventional assumptions that the great events and trends of our day are dictated by those on high. On the contrary, our most important achievements develop from the ground up. In this wide-ranging and erudite book, Matt Ridley brilliantly makes the case for evolution as the force that has shaped much of our culture, our minds, and that even now is shaping our future.    </p>
<p>                              As compelling as it is controversial, as authoritative as it is ambitious, Ridley&#8217;s deeply thought-provoking book will change the way we think about the world and how it works.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/">The Evolution of Everything : How Small Changes Transform Our World &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Knowledge Illusion : The myth of individual thought and the power of collective wisdom &#8211; Steven Sloman, Philip Fernbach (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-knowledge-illusion-the-myth-of-individual-thought-and-the-power-of-collective-wisdom-steven-sloman-philip-fernbach-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-knowledge-illusion-the-myth-of-individual-thought-and-the-power-of-collective-wisdom-steven-sloman-philip-fernbach-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The human mind is both brilliant and pathetic. We have mastered fire and have stood on the moon, and yet every one of us is fundamentally ignorant, irrational and prone to making simple mistakes every day. &#8216;In The Knowledge Illusion, the cognitive scientists Steven Sloman and Philip Fernbach hammer another nail into the coffin of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-knowledge-illusion-the-myth-of-individual-thought-and-the-power-of-collective-wisdom-steven-sloman-philip-fernbach-abridged/">The Knowledge Illusion : The myth of individual thought and the power of collective wisdom &#8211; Steven Sloman, Philip Fernbach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The human mind is both brilliant and pathetic. We have mastered fire and have stood on the moon, and yet every one of us is fundamentally ignorant, irrational and prone to making simple mistakes every day.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;In The Knowledge Illusion, the cognitive scientists Steven Sloman and Philip Fernbach hammer another nail into the coffin of the rational individual . . . positing that not just rationality but the very idea of individual thinking is a myth.&#8217;<br />
                    Yuval Harari, bestselling author of Sapiens and Homo Deus    </p>
<p>                    In this groundbreaking book, cognitive scientists Steven Sloman and Philip Fernbach show how our success as a species is down to us living in a rich community of knowledge where we are drawing on information and expertise outside our heads. And we have no idea that we are even doing it.    </p>
<p>                    Utilizing cutting-edge research, The Knowledge Illusion explains why we think we know more than we do, why beliefs are so hard to change and why we are so prone to making mistakes. Providing a blueprint for successful ways to work in collaboration to do amazing things, it reveals why the key to human intelligence lies in the way we think and work together.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-knowledge-illusion-the-myth-of-individual-thought-and-the-power-of-collective-wisdom-steven-sloman-philip-fernbach-abridged/">The Knowledge Illusion : The myth of individual thought and the power of collective wisdom &#8211; Steven Sloman, Philip Fernbach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Never Enough : the neuroscience and experience of addiction &#8211; Judith Grisel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/never-enough-the-neuroscience-and-experience-of-addiction-judith-grisel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Addiction & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drug & Substance Abuse: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/never-enough-the-neuroscience-and-experience-of-addiction-judith-grisel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A former drug addict turned behavioural neuroscientist reveals how drugs work in the brain &#8211; and what we can do to fight addiction. Judith Grisel was a daily drug user when she began to consider that her addiction might have a cure, one that she herself could perhaps discover by studying the brain. Now, after [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-enough-the-neuroscience-and-experience-of-addiction-judith-grisel-abridged/">Never Enough : the neuroscience and experience of addiction &#8211; Judith Grisel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A former drug addict turned behavioural neuroscientist reveals how drugs work in the brain &#8211; and what we can do to fight addiction.    </p>
<p>                    Judith Grisel was a daily drug user when she began to consider that her addiction might have a cure, one that she herself could perhaps discover by studying the brain. Now, after twenty-five years as a neuroscientist, she shares what she and other scientists have learned about addiction, enriched by captivating glimpses of her personal journey.    </p>
<p>                    In Never Enough, Grisel reveals the unfortunate bottom line of all regular drug use: there is no such thing as a free lunch. All drugs act on the brain in a way that diminishes their enjoyable effects and creates unpleasant ones with repeated use. Delving into the science of one of the world&#8217;s most pressing health problems, she reveals what is different about the brains of addicts even before they first pick up a drink or drug, and highlights the changes that take place in the brain and behaviour as a result of chronic using.    </p>
<p>                    With compassion and clarity, Grisel describes what drove her to addiction, what helped her recover, and her belief that a &#8216;cure&#8217; for addiction will not be found in our individual brains but in the way we interact with our communities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-enough-the-neuroscience-and-experience-of-addiction-judith-grisel-abridged/">Never Enough : the neuroscience and experience of addiction &#8211; Judith Grisel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Wandering Mind : What the Brain Does When You&#8217;re Not Looking &#8211; Michael C. Corballis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-wandering-mind-what-the-brain-does-when-youre-not-looking-michael-c-corballis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wandering-mind-what-the-brain-does-when-youre-not-looking-michael-c-corballis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If I&#8217;ve done my job well &#8211; and, let&#8217;s be honest, if I&#8217;m lucky &#8211; you&#8217;ll read to the end of this piece of copy. Most likely, however, you won&#8217;t. Somewhere in the middle of the next paragraph, your mind will wander off. Minds wander. That&#8217;s just how it is. That may be bad news [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wandering-mind-what-the-brain-does-when-youre-not-looking-michael-c-corballis-abridged/">The Wandering Mind : What the Brain Does When You&#8217;re Not Looking &#8211; Michael C. Corballis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If I&#8217;ve done my job well &#8211; and, let&#8217;s be honest, if I&#8217;m lucky &#8211; you&#8217;ll read to the end of this piece of copy. Most likely, however, you won&#8217;t. Somewhere in the middle of the next paragraph, your mind will wander off. Minds wander. That&#8217;s just how it is.  That may be bad news for me, but is it bad news for people in general? Does the fact that as much as fifty percent of our waking hours find us failing to focus on the task at hand represent a problem? Michael Corballis doesn&#8217;t think so, and with The Wandering Mind, he shows us why, rehabilitating woolgathering and revealing its incredibly useful effects. Drawing on the latest research from cognitive science and evolutionary biology, Corballis shows us how mind-wandering not only frees us from moment-to-moment drudgery, but also from the limitations of our immediate selves. Mind-wandering strengthens our imagination, fueling the flights of invention, storytelling, and empathy that underlie our shared humanity; furthermore, he explains, our tendency to wander back and forth through the timeline of our lives is fundamental to our very sense of ourselves as coherent, continuing personalities.<br />
                    Full of unusual examples and surprising discoveries, The Wandering Mind mounts a vigorous defense of inattention- &#8211; even as it never fails to hold the reader&#8217;s.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wandering-mind-what-the-brain-does-when-youre-not-looking-michael-c-corballis-abridged/">The Wandering Mind : What the Brain Does When You&#8217;re Not Looking &#8211; Michael C. Corballis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Optimism Bias : Why we&#8217;re wired to look on the bright side &#8211; Tali Sharot (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-optimism-bias-why-were-wired-to-look-on-the-bright-side-tali-sharot-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Methodology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-optimism-bias-why-were-wired-to-look-on-the-bright-side-tali-sharot-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the British Psychological Society Book Award for Popular Psychology Psychologists have long been aware that most people tend to maintain an irrationally positive outlook on life. In fact, optimism may be crucial to our existence. Tali Sharot&#8217;s original cognitive research demonstrates in surprising ways the biological basis for optimism. In this fascinating exploration, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-optimism-bias-why-were-wired-to-look-on-the-bright-side-tali-sharot-abridged/">The Optimism Bias : Why we&#8217;re wired to look on the bright side &#8211; Tali Sharot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the British Psychological Society Book Award for Popular Psychology    </p>
<p>                    Psychologists have long been aware that most people tend to maintain an irrationally positive outlook on life. In fact, optimism may be crucial to our existence. Tali Sharot&#8217;s original cognitive research demonstrates in surprising ways the biological basis for optimism. In this fascinating exploration, she takes an in-depth, clarifying look at how the brain generates hope and what happens when it fails; how the brains of optimists and pessimists differ; why we are terrible at predicting what will make us happy; how anticipation and dread affect us; and how our optimistic illusions affect our financial, professional, and emotional decisions.    </p>
<p>                    With its cutting-edge science and its wide-ranging and accessible narrative, The Optimism Bias provides us with startling new insight into how the workings of the brain create our hopes and dreams.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-optimism-bias-why-were-wired-to-look-on-the-bright-side-tali-sharot-abridged/">The Optimism Bias : Why we&#8217;re wired to look on the bright side &#8211; Tali Sharot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cure : A Journey Into the Science of Mind over Body &#8211; Jo Marchant (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cure-a-journey-into-the-science-of-mind-over-body-jo-marchant-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cure-a-journey-into-the-science-of-mind-over-body-jo-marchant-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER SHORTLISTED FOR THE ROYAL SOCIETY SCIENCE BOOK PRIZE LONGLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME PRIZE ALL IN THE MIND? &#8211; Can meditation fend off dementia? &#8211; Can the smell of lavender affect the immune system? &#8211; Can your thoughts ease physical pain? In Cure, award-winning science writer Jo Marchant travels the world [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cure-a-journey-into-the-science-of-mind-over-body-jo-marchant-abridged/">Cure : A Journey Into the Science of Mind over Body &#8211; Jo Marchant (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    SHORTLISTED FOR THE ROYAL SOCIETY SCIENCE BOOK PRIZE<br />
                    LONGLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME PRIZE    </p>
<p>                    ALL IN THE MIND?    </p>
<p>                      &#8211;       Can meditation fend off dementia?<br />
                      &#8211;       Can the smell of lavender affect the immune system?<br />
                      &#8211;       Can your thoughts ease physical pain?    </p>
<p>                     In Cure, award-winning science writer Jo Marchant travels the world to meet the physicians, patients and researchers on the cutting edge of mind-body medicine, asking how the brain can heal the body and how we can all make changes to keep ourselves healthier.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cure-a-journey-into-the-science-of-mind-over-body-jo-marchant-abridged/">Cure : A Journey Into the Science of Mind over Body &#8211; Jo Marchant (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peak : For Fans of Atomic Habits &#8211; Anders Ericsson, Robert Pool (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/peak-for-fans-of-atomic-habits-anders-ericsson-robert-pool-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/peak-for-fans-of-atomic-habits-anders-ericsson-robert-pool-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Anyone who wants to get better at anything should read Peak.&#8217; Fortune Do you want to stand out at work, improve your athletic or musical performance, or help your child achieve academic goals? Anders Ericsson has made a career studying chess champions, violin virtuosos, star athletes, and memory mavens. Peak distils three decades of myth-shattering [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/peak-for-fans-of-atomic-habits-anders-ericsson-robert-pool-abridged/">Peak : For Fans of Atomic Habits &#8211; Anders Ericsson, Robert Pool (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Anyone who wants to get better at anything should read Peak.&#8217; Fortune    </p>
<p>                     Do you want to stand out at work, improve your athletic or musical performance, or help your child achieve academic goals?     </p>
<p>                     Anders Ericsson has made a career studying chess champions, violin virtuosos, star athletes, and memory mavens. Peak distils three decades of myth-shattering research into a powerful learning strategy that is fundamentally different from the way people traditionally think about acquiring new abilities. Ericsson&#8217;s revolutionary methods will show you how to improve at almost any skill that matters to you, and that you don&#8217;t have to be a genius to achieve extraordinary things.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Remarkable&#8230;who among us doesn&#8217;t want to learn how to get better at life?&#8217; Stephen J. Dubner, co-author of Freakonomics    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;This book&#8230;could truly change the world&#8217; Joshua Foer, author of Moonwalking with Einstein</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/peak-for-fans-of-atomic-habits-anders-ericsson-robert-pool-abridged/">Peak : For Fans of Atomic Habits &#8211; Anders Ericsson, Robert Pool (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thirty Million Words : Building a Child&#8217;s Brain &#8211; Dana Suskind (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The founder and director of the Thirty Million Words Initiative, Professor Dana Suskind, explains why the most important&#8211;and astoundingly simple&#8211;thing you can do for your child&#8217;s future success in life is to to talk to them. What nurtures the brain to optimum intelligence and stability? It is a secret hiding in plain sight: the most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/">Thirty Million Words : Building a Child&#8217;s Brain &#8211; Dana Suskind (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The founder and director of the Thirty Million Words Initiative, Professor Dana Suskind, explains why the most important&#8211;and astoundingly simple&#8211;thing you can do for your child&#8217;s future success in life is to to talk to them.     </p>
<p>                    What nurtures the brain to optimum intelligence and stability?     </p>
<p>                    It is a secret hiding in plain sight: the most important thing we can do for our children is to have conversations with them. The way you talk with your growing child literally builds his or her brain. Parent talk can drastically improve school readiness and lifelong learning in everything from math to art. Indeed, parent-child talk is a fundamental, critical factor in building grit, self-control, leadership skills, and generosity. It is crucial to making the most in life of the luck you have with your genes.     </p>
<p>                    This landmark account of a new scientific perspective describes what works and what doesn&#8217;t (baby talk is fine; relentless correction isn&#8217;t). Discover how to create the best language environments for children by following the simple structure of the Three Ts: Tune In; Talk More; Take Turns. Dr. Suskind and her colleagues around the country have worked with thousands of families; now their insights and successful, measured approaches are available to all.     </p>
<p>                    This is the first book to reveal how and why the first step in nurturing successful lives is talking to children in ways that build their brains. Your family&#8211;and our nation&#8211;need to know.     </p>
<p>                    *Nominated for the Books for a Better Life Award*</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/">Thirty Million Words : Building a Child&#8217;s Brain &#8211; Dana Suskind (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Bite : How We Learn to Eat &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cooking For/with Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cooking With Meat & Game]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fortnum &#038; Mason Food Book of the Year 2016 We are not born knowing what to eat; we each have to figure it out for ourselves. From childhood onwards, we learn how big a portion is and how sweet is too sweet. The way we learn to eat holds the key to why food has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/">First Bite : How We Learn to Eat &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fortnum &#038; Mason Food Book of the Year 2016    </p>
<p>                              We are not born knowing what to eat; we each have to figure it out for ourselves. From childhood onwards, we learn how big a portion is and how sweet is too sweet. The way we learn to eat holds the key to why food has gone so disastrously wrong for so many people. But how does this happen? And can we ever change our food habits for the better?    </p>
<p>                              An exploration of the extraordinary and surprising origins of our taste and eating habits, in First Bite award-winning food writer Bee Wilson explains how we can change our palates to lead healthier, happier lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/">First Bite : How We Learn to Eat &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Altered Traits : Science Reveals How Meditation Changes Your Mind, Brain, and Body &#8211; Daniel Goleman, Richard J. Davidson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/altered-traits-science-reveals-how-meditation-changes-your-mind-brain-and-body-daniel-goleman-richard-j-davidson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/altered-traits-science-reveals-how-meditation-changes-your-mind-brain-and-body-daniel-goleman-richard-j-davidson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two New York Times-bestselling authors unveil new research showing what meditation can really do for the brain. In the last twenty years, meditation and mindfulness have gone from being kind of cool to becoming an omnipresent Band-Aid for fixing everything from your weight to your relationship to your achievement level. Unveiling here the kind of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/altered-traits-science-reveals-how-meditation-changes-your-mind-brain-and-body-daniel-goleman-richard-j-davidson-abridged/">Altered Traits : Science Reveals How Meditation Changes Your Mind, Brain, and Body &#8211; Daniel Goleman, Richard J. Davidson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two New York Times-bestselling authors unveil new research showing what meditation can really do for the brain.     </p>
<p>                     In the last twenty years, meditation and mindfulness have gone from being kind of cool to becoming an omnipresent Band-Aid for fixing everything from your weight to your relationship to your achievement level. Unveiling here the kind of cutting-edge research that has made them giants in their fields, Daniel Goleman and Richard Davidson show us the truth about what meditation can really do for us, as well as exactly how to get the most out of it.     </p>
<p>                    Sweeping away common misconceptions and neuromythology to open readers&#8217; eyes to the ways data has been distorted to sell mind-training methods, the authors demonstrate that beyond the pleasant states mental exercises can produce, the real payoffs are the lasting personality traits that can result. But short daily doses will not get us to the highest level of lasting positive change&#8211;even if we continue for years&#8211;without specific additions. More than sheer hours, we need smart practice, including crucial ingredients such as targeted feedback from a master teacher and a more spacious, less attached view of the self, all of which are missing in widespread versions of mind training. The authors also reveal the latest data from Davidson&#8217;s own lab that point to a new methodology for developing a broader array of mind-training methods with larger implications for how we can derive the greatest benefits from the practice.     </p>
<p>                    Exciting, compelling, and grounded in new research, this is one of those rare books that has the power to change us at the deepest level.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/altered-traits-science-reveals-how-meditation-changes-your-mind-brain-and-body-daniel-goleman-richard-j-davidson-abridged/">Altered Traits : Science Reveals How Meditation Changes Your Mind, Brain, and Body &#8211; Daniel Goleman, Richard J. Davidson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Hidden Chimp : From the best-selling author of The Chimp Paradox &#8211; Prof Steve Peters (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/my-hidden-chimp-from-the-best-selling-author-of-the-chimp-paradox-prof-steve-peters-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intergenerational Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self-Esteem]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-hidden-chimp-from-the-best-selling-author-of-the-chimp-paradox-prof-steve-peters-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how TEN habits can help children to understand and manage their emotions and behaviour &#8211; the NEW book from the creator of the chimp management mind model and author of the million copy selling The Chimp Paradox . My Hidden Chimp is an effective and powerful new educational book that offers parents, teachers and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-hidden-chimp-from-the-best-selling-author-of-the-chimp-paradox-prof-steve-peters-abridged/">My Hidden Chimp : From the best-selling author of The Chimp Paradox &#8211; Prof Steve Peters (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how TEN habits can help children to understand and manage their emotions and behaviour &#8211; the NEW book from the creator of the chimp management mind model and author of the million copy selling The Chimp Paradox .    </p>
<p>                    My Hidden Chimp is an effective and powerful new educational book that offers parents, teachers and carers some ideas and thoughts on how to help children to develop healthy habits for life. The science behind the habits is discussed in a practical way with exercises and activities to help children think the habits through and start putting them into practice. The neuroscience of the mind is simplified for children to understand and then use to their advantage.    </p>
<p>                    Professor Steve Peters explains neuroscience in a straightforward and intuitive way &#8211; offering up 10 simple habits that we as adults and children should have in our arsenal to deal with everyday life.    </p>
<p>                    They include:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Smiling<br />
                    &#8211; The importance of talking through your feelings<br />
                    &#8211; Learning how to say sorry<br />
                    &#8211; Knowing how to ask for help    </p>
<p>                    By also explaining the developing &#8216;chimp&#8217; brain in children, he shows us how 10 habits can help children to understand and manage their emotions and behaviour. These 10 habits should and can be retained for life.    </p>
<p>                    This is an important and another groundbreaking new book from the bestselling author of The Chimp Paradox and the creator of the chimp management mind model.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-hidden-chimp-from-the-best-selling-author-of-the-chimp-paradox-prof-steve-peters-abridged/">My Hidden Chimp : From the best-selling author of The Chimp Paradox &#8211; Prof Steve Peters (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are men literally born to cheat? Does monogamy actually serve women&#8217;s interests? These are among the questions that have made The Moral Animal one of the most provocative science books in recent years. Wright unveils the genetic strategies behind everything from our sexual preferences to our office politics&#8211;as well as their implications for our moral [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/">The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are men literally born to cheat? Does monogamy actually serve women&#8217;s interests? These are among the questions that have made The Moral Animal one of the most provocative science books in recent years. Wright unveils the genetic strategies behind everything from our sexual preferences to our office politics&#8211;as well as their implications for our moral codes and public policies. Illustrations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moral-animal-why-we-are-the-way-we-are-the-new-science-of-evolutionary-psychology-robert-wright-abridged/">The Moral Animal : Why We Are, the Way We Are: The New Science of Evolutionary Psychology &#8211; Robert Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Book of Why : The New Science of Cause and Effect &#8211; Judea Pearl, Dana Mackenzie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-book-of-why-the-new-science-of-cause-and-effect-judea-pearl-dana-mackenzie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Methodology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-book-of-why-the-new-science-of-cause-and-effect-judea-pearl-dana-mackenzie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The hugely influential book on how the understanding of causality revolutionized science and the world, by the pioneer of artificial intelligence &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; illuminating and fun to read&#8217; Daniel Kahneman, Nobel Prize-winner and author of Thinking, Fast and Slow &#8216;Correlation does not imply causation.&#8217; For decades, this mantra was invoked by scientists in order to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-why-the-new-science-of-cause-and-effect-judea-pearl-dana-mackenzie-abridged/">The Book of Why : The New Science of Cause and Effect &#8211; Judea Pearl, Dana Mackenzie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The hugely influential book on how the understanding of causality revolutionized science and the world, by the pioneer of artificial intelligence    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; illuminating and fun to read&#8217; Daniel Kahneman, Nobel Prize-winner and author of Thinking, Fast and Slow    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Correlation  does not imply causation.&#8217; For decades, this mantra was invoked by scientists in order to avoid taking positions as to whether one thing  caused another, such as smoking and cancer, or carbon dioxide and global  warming. But today, that taboo is dead. The causal revolution, sparked  by world-renowned computer scientist Judea Pearl and his colleagues, has  cut through a century of confusion and placed cause and effect on a  firm scientific basis. Now, Pearl and science journalist Dana Mackenzie explain causal thinking to general readers for the first time, showing  how it allows us to explore the world that is and the worlds that could  have been. It is the essence of human and artificial intelligence. And  just as Pearl&#8217;s discoveries have enabled machines to think better, The  Book of Why explains how we too can think better.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Pearl&#8217;s accomplishments over the last 30 years have provided the theoretical basis for progress in artificial intelligence and have redefined the term &#8220;thinking machine&#8221;&#8216; Vint Cerf</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-why-the-new-science-of-cause-and-effect-judea-pearl-dana-mackenzie-abridged/">The Book of Why : The New Science of Cause and Effect &#8211; Judea Pearl, Dana Mackenzie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conscious : A Brief Guide to the Fundamental Mystery of the Mind &#8211; Annaka Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/conscious-a-brief-guide-to-the-fundamental-mystery-of-the-mind-annaka-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conscious & Unconscious]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance, C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/conscious-a-brief-guide-to-the-fundamental-mystery-of-the-mind-annaka-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8220;If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how you have the capacity to wonder, some fascinating insights await you in these pages.&#8221; &#8211;Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of Originals As concise and enlightening as Seven Brief Lessons on Physics and Astrophysics for People in a Hurry, this mind-expanding dive into the mystery [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conscious-a-brief-guide-to-the-fundamental-mystery-of-the-mind-annaka-harris-abridged/">Conscious : A Brief Guide to the Fundamental Mystery of the Mind &#8211; Annaka Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how you have the capacity to wonder, some fascinating insights await you in these pages.&#8221; &#8211;Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    As concise and enlightening as Seven Brief Lessons on Physics and Astrophysics for People in a Hurry, this mind-expanding dive into the mystery of consciousness is an illuminating meditation on the self, free will, and felt experience.    </p>
<p>                    What is consciousness? How does it arise? And why does it exist? We take our experience of being in the world for granted. But the very existence of consciousness raises profound questions: Why would any collection of matter in the universe be conscious? How are we able to think about this? And why should we?    </p>
<p>                    In this wonderfully accessible book, Annaka Harris guides us through the evolving definitions, philosophies, and scientific findings that probe our limited understanding of consciousness. Where does it reside, and what gives rise to it? Could it be an illusion, or a universal property of all matter? As we try to understand consciousness, we must grapple with how to define it and, in the age of artificial intelligence, who or what might possess it.     </p>
<p>                    Conscious offers lively and challenging arguments that alter our ideas about consciousness-allowing us to think freely about it for ourselves, if indeed we can.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conscious-a-brief-guide-to-the-fundamental-mystery-of-the-mind-annaka-harris-abridged/">Conscious : A Brief Guide to the Fundamental Mystery of the Mind &#8211; Annaka Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Your Brain On Parasites : How Tiny Creatures Manipulate Our Behavior and Shape Society &#8211; Kathleen McAuliffe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-your-brain-on-parasites-how-tiny-creatures-manipulate-our-behavior-and-shape-society-kathleen-mcauliffe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Microbiology & Virology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Parasitology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-your-brain-on-parasites-how-tiny-creatures-manipulate-our-behavior-and-shape-society-kathleen-mcauliffe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Engrossing &#8230; [An] expedition through the hidden and sometimes horrifying microbial domain.&#8221; -Wall Street Journal &#8220;Fascinating-and full of the kind of factoids you can&#8217;t wait to share.&#8221; -Scientific American Parasites can live only inside another animal and, as Kathleen McAuliffe reveals, these tiny organisms have many evolutionary motives for manipulating the behavior of their hosts. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-brain-on-parasites-how-tiny-creatures-manipulate-our-behavior-and-shape-society-kathleen-mcauliffe-abridged/">This Is Your Brain On Parasites : How Tiny Creatures Manipulate Our Behavior and Shape Society &#8211; Kathleen McAuliffe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Engrossing &#8230; [An] expedition through the hidden and sometimes horrifying microbial domain.&#8221; -Wall Street Journal    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Fascinating-and full of the kind of factoids you can&#8217;t wait to share.&#8221; -Scientific American    </p>
<p>                     Parasites can live only inside another animal and, as Kathleen McAuliffe reveals, these tiny organisms have many evolutionary motives for manipulating the behavior of their hosts. With astonishing precision, parasites can coax rats to approach cats, spiders to transform the patterns of their webs, and fish to draw the attention of birds that then swoop down to feast on them. We humans are hardly immune to their influence. Organisms we pick up from our own pets are strongly suspected of changing our personality traits and contributing to recklessness and impulsivity-even suicide. Germs that cause colds and the flu may alter our behavior even before symptoms become apparent.    </p>
<p>                     Parasites influence our species on the cultural level, too. Drawing on a huge body of research, McAuliffe argues that our dread of contamination is an evolved defense against parasites. The horror and revulsion we are programmed to feel when we come in contact with people who appear diseased or dirty helped pave the way for civilization, but may also be the basis for major divisions in societies that persist to this day. This Is Your Brain on Parasites is both a journey into cutting-edge science and a revelatory examination of what it means to be human.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If you&#8217;ve ever doubted the power of microbes to shape society and offer us a grander view of life, read on and find yourself duly impressed.&#8221; -Heather Havrilesky, Bookforum</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-brain-on-parasites-how-tiny-creatures-manipulate-our-behavior-and-shape-society-kathleen-mcauliffe-abridged/">This Is Your Brain On Parasites : How Tiny Creatures Manipulate Our Behavior and Shape Society &#8211; Kathleen McAuliffe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genius Foods : Become Smarter, Happier, and More Productive, While Protecting Your Brain Health for Life &#8211; Max Lugavere (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/genius-foods-become-smarter-happier-and-more-productive-while-protecting-your-brain-health-for-life-max-lugavere-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/genius-foods-become-smarter-happier-and-more-productive-while-protecting-your-brain-health-for-life-max-lugavere-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller Discover the critical link between your brain and the food you eat and change the way your brain ages, in this cutting-edge, practical guide to eliminating brain fog, optimizing brain health, and achieving peak mental performance from media personality and leading voice in health Max Lugavere. After his mother was diagnosed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genius-foods-become-smarter-happier-and-more-productive-while-protecting-your-brain-health-for-life-max-lugavere-abridged/">Genius Foods : Become Smarter, Happier, and More Productive, While Protecting Your Brain Health for Life &#8211; Max Lugavere (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    Discover the critical link between your brain and the food you eat and change the way your brain ages, in this cutting-edge, practical guide to eliminating brain fog, optimizing brain health, and achieving peak mental performance from media personality and leading voice in health Max Lugavere.     </p>
<p>                    After his mother was diagnosed with a mysterious form of dementia, Max Lugavere put his successful media career on hold to learn everything he could about brain health and performance. For the better half of a decade, he consumed the most up-to-date scientific research, talked to dozens of leading scientists and clinicians around the world, and visited the country&#8217;s best neurology departments-all in the hopes of understanding his mother&#8217;s condition.     </p>
<p>                    Now, in Genius Foods, Lugavere presents a comprehensive guide to brain optimization. He uncovers the stunning link between our dietary and lifestyle choices and our brain functions, revealing how the foods you eat directly affect your ability to focus, learn, remember, create, analyze new ideas, and maintain a balanced mood.     </p>
<p>                    Weaving together pioneering research on dementia prevention, cognitive optimization, and nutritional psychiatry, Lugavere distills groundbreaking science into actionable lifestyle changes. He shares invaluable insights into how to improve your brain power, including     </p>
<p>                    the nutrients that can boost your memory and improve mental clarity (and where to find them);<br />
                    the foods and tactics that can energize and rejuvenate your brain, no matter your age;<br />
                    a brain-boosting fat-loss method so powerful it has been called &#8220;biochemical liposuction&#8221;; and<br />
                    the foods that can improve your happiness, both now and for the long term.    </p>
<p>                    With Genius Foods, Lugavere offers a cutting-edge yet practical road map to eliminating brain fog and optimizing the brain&#8217;s health and performance today-and decades into the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genius-foods-become-smarter-happier-and-more-productive-while-protecting-your-brain-health-for-life-max-lugavere-abridged/">Genius Foods : Become Smarter, Happier, and More Productive, While Protecting Your Brain Health for Life &#8211; Max Lugavere (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out of Character : Surprising Truths About the Liar, Cheat, Sinner (and Saint) Lurking in All of Us &#8211; David Desteno, Piercarlo Valdesolo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/out-of-character-surprising-truths-about-the-liar-cheat-sinner-and-saint-lurking-in-all-of-us-david-desteno-piercarlo-valdesolo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/out-of-character-surprising-truths-about-the-liar-cheat-sinner-and-saint-lurking-in-all-of-us-david-desteno-piercarlo-valdesolo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever wondered why a trumpeter of family values would suddenly turn around and cheat on his wife? Why jealousy would send an otherwise level-headed person into a violent rage? What could drive a person to blow a family fortune at the blackjack tables? Or have you ever pondered what might make Mr. Right [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-character-surprising-truths-about-the-liar-cheat-sinner-and-saint-lurking-in-all-of-us-david-desteno-piercarlo-valdesolo-abridged/">Out of Character : Surprising Truths About the Liar, Cheat, Sinner (and Saint) Lurking in All of Us &#8211; David Desteno, Piercarlo Valdesolo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Have you ever wondered why a trumpeter of family values would suddenly turn around and cheat on his wife? Why jealousy would send an otherwise level-headed person into a violent rage? What could drive a person to blow a family fortune at the blackjack tables?     </p>
<p>                    Or have you ever pondered what might make Mr. Right leave his beloved at the altar, why hypocrisy seems to be rampant, or even why, every once in awhile, even you are secretly tempted, to lie, cheat, or steal (or, conversely, help someone you never even met)?     </p>
<p>                    This book answers these questions and more, and in doing so, turns the prevailing wisdom about who we are upside down. Our character, argue psychologists DeSteno and Valdesolo, isn&#8217;t a stable set of traits, but rather a shifting state that is subject to the constant push and pull of hidden mechanisms in our mind. And it&#8217;s the battle between these dueling psychological forces that determine how we act at any given point in time.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the surprising results of the clever experiments concocted in their own laboratory, DeSteno and Valdesolo shed new scientific light on so many of the puzzling behaviors that regularly grace the headlines. For example, you&#8217;ll learn:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Why Tiger Woods just couldn&#8217;t resist the allure of his mistresses even though he had a picture-perfect family at home. And why no one, including those who knew him best, ever saw it coming.     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Why even the shrewdest of investors can be tempted to gamble their fortunes away (and why risky financial behavior is driven by the same mechanisms that compel us to root for the underdog in sports).     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Why Eliot Spitzer, who made a career of crusading against prostitution, turned out to be one of the most famous johns of all time.     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Why Mel Gibson, a noted philanthropist and devout Catholic, has been repeatedly caught spewing racist rants, even though close friends say he doesn&#8217;t have a racist bone in his body.     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; And why any of us is capable of doing the same, whether we believe it or not!    </p>
<p>                    A surprising look at the hidden forces driving the saint and sinner lurking in us all, Out of Character reveals why human behavior is so much more unpredictable than we ever realized.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-character-surprising-truths-about-the-liar-cheat-sinner-and-saint-lurking-in-all-of-us-david-desteno-piercarlo-valdesolo-abridged/">Out of Character : Surprising Truths About the Liar, Cheat, Sinner (and Saint) Lurking in All of Us &#8211; David Desteno, Piercarlo Valdesolo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Descartes&#8217; Error : Emotion, Reason and the Human Brain &#8211; Antonio Damasio (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/descartes-error-emotion-reason-and-the-human-brain-antonio-damasio-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/descartes-error-emotion-reason-and-the-human-brain-antonio-damasio-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the centuries since Descartes famously proclaimed, &#8216;I think, therefore I am,&#8217; science has often overlooked emotions as the source of a person&#8217;s true being. Even modern neuroscience has tended until recently to concentrate on the cognitive aspects of brain function, disregarding emotions. This attitude began to change with the publication of Descartes&#8217; Error. Antonio [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/descartes-error-emotion-reason-and-the-human-brain-antonio-damasio-abridged/">Descartes&#8217; Error : Emotion, Reason and the Human Brain &#8211; Antonio Damasio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the centuries since Descartes famously proclaimed, &#8216;I think, therefore I am,&#8217; science has often overlooked emotions as the source of a person&#8217;s true being. Even modern neuroscience has tended until recently to concentrate on the cognitive aspects of brain function, disregarding emotions. This attitude began to change with the publication of Descartes&#8217; Error. Antonio Damasio challenged traditional ideas about the connection between emotions and rationality. In this wonderfully engaging book, Damasio takes the reader on a journey of scientific discovery through a series of case studies, demonstrating what many of us have long suspected: emotions are not a luxury, they are essential to rational thinking and to normal social behaviour.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/descartes-error-emotion-reason-and-the-human-brain-antonio-damasio-abridged/">Descartes&#8217; Error : Emotion, Reason and the Human Brain &#8211; Antonio Damasio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Life Lessons from a Brain Surgeon : The New Science and Stories of the Brain &#8211; Dr Rahul Jandial (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-lessons-from-a-brain-surgeon-the-new-science-and-stories-of-the-brain-dr-rahul-jandial-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosurgery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rehabilitation: Brain & Spinal Injuries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-lessons-from-a-brain-surgeon-the-new-science-and-stories-of-the-brain-dr-rahul-jandial-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER *As heard on Chris Evans&#8217; Virgin Radio* &#8216;You&#8217;re amazing I could talk to you (Rahul) all day&#8217; Chris Evans &#8216;This is a gripping new book&#8217; The Times World-leading neuroscientist and neurosurgeon Dr Rahul Jandial draws on his years of work with patients suffering from the most extreme cases of brain damage, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-lessons-from-a-brain-surgeon-the-new-science-and-stories-of-the-brain-dr-rahul-jandial-abridged/">Life Lessons from a Brain Surgeon : The New Science and Stories of the Brain &#8211; Dr Rahul Jandial (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    *As heard on Chris Evans&#8217; Virgin Radio*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;You&#8217;re amazing I could talk to you (Rahul) all day&#8217; Chris Evans    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is a gripping new book&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    World-leading neuroscientist and neurosurgeon Dr Rahul Jandial draws on his years of work with patients suffering from the most extreme cases of brain damage, disorders and illnesses to reveal what they can tell us about the science of the mind.    </p>
<p>                    From a languages teacher who has to choose whether to lose her ability to speak Spanish or English after brain surgery, to a former TV exec, now homeless, who discovers that his life-altering despondency is the result of a tumour, to a fainting teen who learns that deep breathing can mean the difference between life or death, these stories uncover the secret workings of the brain.    </p>
<p>                    Blending cutting-edge research and beautiful storytelling, Life Lessons from a Brain Surgeon is a vital resource on the best ways to boost your memory, control stress and emotions, minimize pain, unleash your creativity, raise smart kids and reduce the risk of Alzheimer&#8217;s. This is a deeply practical and readable book, which will take you on an expedition through the anatomy of the most fascinating &#8211; and mysterious &#8211; of organs.    </p>
<p>                    Rahul&#8217;s new book Life on a Knife&#8217;s Edge is out now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-lessons-from-a-brain-surgeon-the-new-science-and-stories-of-the-brain-dr-rahul-jandial-abridged/">Life Lessons from a Brain Surgeon : The New Science and Stories of the Brain &#8211; Dr Rahul Jandial (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rest : Why You Get More Done When You Work Less &#8211; Alex Soojung-Kim Pang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Take a break and read Rest: you&#8217;ll make smarter decisions, have better relationships, and be happier and more creative&#8221; James Wallman, author of Stuffocation Do you regularly find yourself too tired after a long day at your desk to do anything other than binge TV, or scroll mindlessly through social media? Do you go on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/">Rest : Why You Get More Done When You Work Less &#8211; Alex Soojung-Kim Pang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Take a break and read Rest: you&#8217;ll make smarter decisions, have better relationships, and be happier and more creative&#8221; James Wallman, author of Stuffocation    </p>
<p>                     Do you regularly find yourself too tired after a long day at your desk to do anything other than binge TV, or scroll mindlessly through social media? Do you go on holiday and still compulsively check your email? Do you work through your lunch-break, often not even leaving your desk to get some fresh air?    </p>
<p>                     For most of us, overwork is the new norm, and we never truly take the time to rest and recharge. But as Silicon Valley consultant Alex Soojung-Kim Pang explains in this groundbreaking book, rest needs to be taken seriously and to be done properly, because when you rest better you work better.    </p>
<p>                     Drawing on emerging neuroscience, Rest is packed with easy practical tips for incorporating rest into our everyday:    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Go for a long walk to stimulate and sustain creativity<br />
                     &#8211; Schedule deliberate active rest periods into your diary to try out new activities like painting or learning a language<br />
                     &#8211; Stop working on a task when you know what the next step will be, this will make it easier to get started the next day<br />
                    &#8211; Establish clear boundaries between work and rest time<br />
                     &#8211; Take a nap during the day to increase alertness, boost your concentration and decrease fatigue<br />
                     &#8211; Get good quality sleep at night to stay healthy, solidify memories and generate new ideas    </p>
<p>                     When you rest better you&#8217;ll find that it won&#8217;t just be your work which improves &#8211; you&#8217;ll have more time for hobbies, stronger relationships and you&#8217;ll sleep better, too.    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;An incredibly timely read for my own increasingly rest-starved life. This might be the book to finally persuade us that downtime isn&#8217;t in conflict with good work; rather, it&#8217;s an essential ingredient of it&#8221; Oliver Burkeman, Guardian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less-alex-soojung-kim-pang-abridged/">Rest : Why You Get More Done When You Work Less &#8211; Alex Soojung-Kim Pang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smarter : The New Science of Building Brain Power &#8211; Dan Hurley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/smarter-the-new-science-of-building-brain-power-dan-hurley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/smarter-the-new-science-of-building-brain-power-dan-hurley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A riveting look at the birth of a new science.&#8221; -Daniel H. Pink, author of Drive When he was eight years old, Dan Hurley was labeled a &#8220;slow learner&#8221; because he still couldn&#8217;t read. Three years later, he had become a straight A student. Until the publication of a major study in 2008, psychologists believed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smarter-the-new-science-of-building-brain-power-dan-hurley-abridged/">Smarter : The New Science of Building Brain Power &#8211; Dan Hurley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A riveting look at the birth of a new science.&#8221; -Daniel H. Pink, author of Drive    </p>
<p>                    When he was eight years old, Dan Hurley was labeled a &#8220;slow learner&#8221; because he still couldn&#8217;t read.  Three years later, he had become a straight A student.     </p>
<p>                    Until the publication of a major study in 2008, psychologists believed that intelligence is fixed at birth, that IQ is like a number tattooed on the soul. The new study showed that people can increase their &#8220;fluid&#8221; intelligence through training.    </p>
<p>                    Hurley, who grew up to become an award-winning science journalist, first explored the topic in The New York Times Magazine. In Smarter, he digs deeper by meeting with the field&#8217;s leading researchers-and becoming a human guinea pig. After just three months of playing computer brain-training games, joining a boot-camp exercise program, learning to play the Renaissance lute, practicing mindfulness meditation and and even getting his brain zapped in the name of science, Hurley improved his fluid intelligence by sixteen percent.    </p>
<p>                    With humor and heart, Smarter chronicles the roiling field of intelligence research and delivers practical findings to sharpen the minds of children, young adults, seniors, and those with cognitive challenges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smarter-the-new-science-of-building-brain-power-dan-hurley-abridged/">Smarter : The New Science of Building Brain Power &#8211; Dan Hurley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breakpoint : Why the Web Will Implode, Search Will be Obsolete, and Everything Else You Need to Know About Technology is in Your Brain &#8211; Robert David Grant, Jeff Stibel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/breakpoint-why-the-web-will-implode-search-will-be-obsolete-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-technology-is-in-your-brain-robert-david-grant-jeff-stibel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/breakpoint-why-the-web-will-implode-search-will-be-obsolete-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-technology-is-in-your-brain-robert-david-grant-jeff-stibel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller USA Today Bestseller We are living in a world in which cows send texts to farmers when they&#8217;re in heat, where the most valuable real estate in New York City houses computers, not people, and some of humanity&#8217;s greatest works are created by crowds, not individuals. We are in the midst [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/breakpoint-why-the-web-will-implode-search-will-be-obsolete-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-technology-is-in-your-brain-robert-david-grant-jeff-stibel-abridged/">Breakpoint : Why the Web Will Implode, Search Will be Obsolete, and Everything Else You Need to Know About Technology is in Your Brain &#8211; Robert David Grant, Jeff Stibel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller     </p>
<p>                    USA Today Bestseller     </p>
<p>                    We are living in a world in which cows send texts to farmers when they&#8217;re in heat, where the most valuable real estate in New York City houses computers, not people, and some of humanity&#8217;s greatest works are created by crowds, not individuals.     </p>
<p>                    We are in the midst of a networking revolution&#8211;set to transform the way we access the world&#8217;s information and the way we connect with one another. Studying biological systems is perhaps the best way to understand such networks, and nature has a lesson for us if we care to listen: bigger is rarely better in the long run. The deadliest creature is the mosquito, not the lion. It is the quality of a network that is important for survival, not the size, and all networks&#8211;the human brain, Facebook, Google, even the internet itself&#8211;eventually reach a breakpoint and collapse. That&#8217;s the bad news. The good news is that reaching a breakpoint can be a step forward, allowing a network to substitute quality for quantity.     </p>
<p>                    In Breakpoint, brain scientist and entrepreneur Jeff Stibel takes readers to the intersection of the brain, biology, and technology. He shows how exceptional companies are using their understanding of the internet&#8217;s brain-like powers to create a competitive advantage by building more effective websites, utilizing cloud computing, engaging social media, monetizing effectively, and leveraging a collective consciousness. Indeed, the result of these technologies is a more tightly connected world with capabilities far beyond the sum of our individual minds. Breakpoint offers a fresh and exciting perspective about the future of technology and its effects on all of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/breakpoint-why-the-web-will-implode-search-will-be-obsolete-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-technology-is-in-your-brain-robert-david-grant-jeff-stibel-abridged/">Breakpoint : Why the Web Will Implode, Search Will be Obsolete, and Everything Else You Need to Know About Technology is in Your Brain &#8211; Robert David Grant, Jeff Stibel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The as If Principle : The Radically New Approach to Changing Your Life &#8211; Dr Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-as-if-principle-the-radically-new-approach-to-changing-your-life-dr-richard-wiseman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-as-if-principle-the-radically-new-approach-to-changing-your-life-dr-richard-wiseman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a bestselling author and the most-followed psychologist on Twitter, this &#8220;intriguing new slant to personal transformation&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews) shows you how to take control of your life in an instant. Victorian philosopher William James had a theory about emotion and behavior: It isn&#8217;t that our feelings guide our actions (feel happy and you will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-as-if-principle-the-radically-new-approach-to-changing-your-life-dr-richard-wiseman-abridged/">The as If Principle : The Radically New Approach to Changing Your Life &#8211; Dr Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a bestselling author and the most-followed psychologist on Twitter, this &#8220;intriguing new slant to personal transformation&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews) shows you how to take control of your life in an instant.  Victorian philosopher William James had a theory about emotion and behavior: It isn&#8217;t that our feelings guide our actions (feel happy and you will laugh). On the contrary, it is our actions that guide our emotions (laugh and you will feel happy). This led James to a remarkable conclusion: &#8220;If you want a quality, act as if you already have it.&#8221; Roused by James&#8217;s astonishing discovery, renowned psychologist and bestselling author Richard Wiseman confirms James&#8217;s principle and shows how the self-help genre has for too long put the cart before the horse in trying to help us take control of our lives. Bringing to the table a dazzling array of firsthand experiments, surprising histories, and psychological case studies, Wiseman illustrates in brilliant detail how we can apply this principle in our daily lives:  Smile to become measurably happier Wash your hands to drive away guilt Clench your fist to increase your willpower Eat with your nondominant hand to lose weight Nod while speaking to become more persuasive Act like a newlywed to rekindle your marriage  Lively, engaging, and truly mind-changing, The As If Principle is that rare gem that offers real, workable solutions for your day-to-day goals while helping you to instantly take control of your emotions. Whether it&#8217;s quitting a bad habit, persevering through a difficult task, or achieving your dream self, The As If Principle can help. Don&#8217;t just think about changing your life. Do it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-as-if-principle-the-radically-new-approach-to-changing-your-life-dr-richard-wiseman-abridged/">The as If Principle : The Radically New Approach to Changing Your Life &#8211; Dr Richard Wiseman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Habits are more powerful than your will &#8211; if you know how to make them work for you Two strings are hanging from a ceiling, one at the centre of the room, one near the wall. You&#8217;re asked to tie the strings together, but you can&#8217;t reach both at the same time. You look around [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/">Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Habits are more powerful than your will &#8211; if you know how to make them work for you    </p>
<p>                    Two strings are hanging from a ceiling, one at the centre of the room, one near the wall. You&#8217;re asked to tie the strings together, but you can&#8217;t reach both at the same time. You look around the room and see a table and a pair of pliers. How would you solve the problem?    </p>
<p>                    When confronted with challenges, most people let habits rule them (in this case, ignoring the pliers, the creative tool at your disposal). That is not surprising when you realise that at least a third of our waking hours are lived on auto-pilot &#8211; ruminating over past events, clicking through websites trawling for updates and the like. Such unconscious thoughts and actions are powerful. But the habits of the mind do not have to control us &#8211; we can steer them.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on hundreds of fascinating studies, psychologist Jeremy Dean &#8211; the mind behind the hugely popular and insightful website PsyBlog &#8211; shares how the new brain science of habit can be harnessed to your benefit, whether you&#8217;re hoping to eat moreveg, take an evening run, clear out your email backlog, or be more creative when faced with challenges at work and at home.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/">Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a divided world, empathy is not the solution, it is the problem. We think of empathy &#8211; the ability to feel the suffering of others for ourselves &#8211; as the ultimate source of all good behaviour. But while it inspires care and protection in personal relationships, it has the opposite effect in the wider [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/">Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a divided world, empathy is not the solution, it is the problem.      </p>
<p>                    We think of empathy &#8211; the ability to feel the suffering of others for ourselves &#8211; as the ultimate source of all good behaviour. But while it inspires care and protection in personal relationships, it has the opposite effect in the wider world. As the latest research in psychology and neuroscience shows, we feel empathy most for those we find attractive and who seem similar to us and not at all for those who are different, distant or anonymous. Empathy therefore biases us in favour of individuals we know while numbing us to the plight of thousands. Guiding us expertly through the experiments, case studies and arguments on all sides, Paul Bloom ultimately shows that some of our worst decisions &#8211; in charity, child-raising, criminal justice, climate change and war &#8211; are motivated by this wolf in sheep&#8217;s clothing.     </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly argued, urgent and humane, Against Empathy overturns widely held assumptions to reveal one of the most profound yet overlooked sources of human conflict.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/">Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What&#8217;s Going on in There? : How the Brain and Mind Develop in the First Five Years of Life &#8211; Lise Eliot (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/whats-going-on-in-there-how-the-brain-and-mind-develop-in-the-first-five-years-of-life-lise-eliot-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pregnancy, Birth & Baby Care]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/whats-going-on-in-there-how-the-brain-and-mind-develop-in-the-first-five-years-of-life-lise-eliot-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As a research neuroscientist, Lise Eliot has made the study of the human brain her life&#8217;s work. But it wasn&#8217;t until she was pregnant with her first child that she became intrigued with the study of brain development. She wanted to know precisely how the baby&#8217;s brain is formed, and when and how each sense, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whats-going-on-in-there-how-the-brain-and-mind-develop-in-the-first-five-years-of-life-lise-eliot-abridged/">What&#8217;s Going on in There? : How the Brain and Mind Develop in the First Five Years of Life &#8211; Lise Eliot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As a research neuroscientist, Lise Eliot has made the study of the human brain her life&#8217;s work. But it wasn&#8217;t until she was pregnant with her first child that she became intrigued with the study of brain development. She wanted to know precisely how the baby&#8217;s brain is formed, and when and how each sense, skill, and cognitive ability is developed. And just as important, she was interested in finding out how her role as a nurturer can affect this complex process. How much of her baby&#8217;s development is genetically ordained&#8211;and how much is determined by environment? Is there anything parents can do to make their babies&#8217; brains work better&#8211;to help them become smarter, happier people? Drawing upon the exploding research in this field as well as the stories of real children, What&#8217;s Going On in There? is a lively and thought-provoking book that charts the brain&#8217;s development from conception through the critical first five years. In examining the many factors that play crucial roles in that process, What&#8217;s Going On in There? explores the evolution of the senses, motor skills, social and emotional behaviors, and mental functions such as attention, language, memory, reasoning, and intelligence. This remarkable book also discusses:     </p>
<p>                     how a baby&#8217;s brain is &#8220;assembled&#8221; from scratch<br />
                    the critical prenatal factors that shapebrain development<br />
                    how the birthing process itself affects the brain<br />
                    which forms of stimulation are most effective at promoting cognitive development<br />
                    how boys&#8217; and girls&#8217; brains develop differently<br />
                    how nutrition, stress, and other physical and social factors can permanently affect a child&#8217;s brain     </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly blending cutting-edge science with a mother&#8217;s wisdom and insight, What&#8217;s Going On in There? is an invaluable contribution to the nature versus nurture debate. Children&#8217;s development is determined both by the genes they are born with and the richness of their early environment. This timely and important book shows parents the innumerable ways in which they can actually help their children grow better brains.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/whats-going-on-in-there-how-the-brain-and-mind-develop-in-the-first-five-years-of-life-lise-eliot-abridged/">What&#8217;s Going on in There? : How the Brain and Mind Develop in the First Five Years of Life &#8211; Lise Eliot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep & Dreams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sleep Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the man dubbed the &#8216;Sleep Whisperer&#8217; comes a brand-new approach to fixing your sleep, once and for all. Challenging the reader to take control and to stop hiding behind excuses for a bad night&#8217;s sleep, neurologist W. Chris Winter explains the basic, often-counterintuitive rules of sleep science. Dr Winter explores revolutionary findings, including surprising [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/">The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the man dubbed the &#8216;Sleep Whisperer&#8217; comes a brand-new approach to fixing your sleep, once and for all.    </p>
<p>                    Challenging the reader to take control and to stop hiding behind excuses for a bad night&#8217;s sleep, neurologist W. Chris Winter explains the basic, often-counterintuitive rules of sleep science. Dr Winter explores revolutionary findings, including surprising solutions for insomnia and other sleep disturbances, empowering readers to stop taking sleeping pills and enjoy the best sleep of their lives.    </p>
<p>                    Written in a clear and entertaining way, The Sleep Solution contains tips, tricks, exercises, and illustrations throughout. Dr Winter is an international expert on sleep and has helped thousands of patients &#8211; including professional athletes &#8211; rest better at night. Now, he&#8217;s ready to help you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sleep-solution-why-your-sleep-is-broken-and-how-to-fix-it-w-chris-winter-abridged/">The Sleep Solution : why your sleep is broken and how to fix it &#8211; W. Chris Winter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fear Factor : How One Emotion Connects Altruists, Psychopaths and Everyone In-Between &#8211; Abigail Marsh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fear-factor-how-one-emotion-connects-altruists-psychopaths-and-everyone-in-between-abigail-marsh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fear-factor-how-one-emotion-connects-altruists-psychopaths-and-everyone-in-between-abigail-marsh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A riveting ride through your own brain&#8217; &#8211; Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of Originals WINNER of the Society for Personality and Social Psychology&#8217;s book prize for &#8216;The Promotion of Social and Personality Science&#8217; If humans are fundamentally good, why do we engage in acts of great cruelty? If we are evil, why [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fear-factor-how-one-emotion-connects-altruists-psychopaths-and-everyone-in-between-abigail-marsh-abridged/">The Fear Factor : How One Emotion Connects Altruists, Psychopaths and Everyone In-Between &#8211; Abigail Marsh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A riveting ride through your own brain&#8217; &#8211; Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    WINNER of the Society for Personality and Social Psychology&#8217;s book prize for &#8216;The Promotion of Social and Personality Science&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    If humans are fundamentally good, why do we engage in acts of great cruelty? If we are evil, why do we sometimes help others at a cost to ourselves?     </p>
<p>                    Whether humans are good or evil is a question that has plagued philosophers and scientists for as long as there have been philosophers and scientists.    </p>
<p>                    Many argue that we are fundamentally selfish, and only the rules and laws of our societies and our own relentless efforts of will can save us from ourselves. But is this really true?     </p>
<p>                    Abigail Marsh is a social neuroscientist who has closely studied the brains of both the worst and the best among us-from children with psychopathic traits whose families live in fear of them, to adult altruists who have given their own kidneys to strangers. Her groundbreaking findings suggest a possibility that is more optimistic than the dominant view. Humans are not good or evil, but are equally (and fundamentally) capable of good and evil.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fear Factor Marsh explores the human capacity for caring, drawing on cutting edge research findings from clinical, translational and brain imaging investigations on the nature of empathy, altruism, and aggression and brings us closer to understanding the basis of humans&#8217; social nature.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;You won&#8217;t be able to put it down&#8217; &#8211; Daniel Gilbert, New York Times bestselling author of Stumbling on Happiness    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;[It] reads like a thriller&#8230; One of the most mind-opening books I have read in years&#8217; &#8211; Matthieu Ricard, author of Altruism</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fear-factor-how-one-emotion-connects-altruists-psychopaths-and-everyone-in-between-abigail-marsh-abridged/">The Fear Factor : How One Emotion Connects Altruists, Psychopaths and Everyone In-Between &#8211; Abigail Marsh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unconscious Branding : How Neuroscience Can Empower (and Inspire) Marketing &#8211; Douglas van Praet (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unconscious-branding-how-neuroscience-can-empower-and-inspire-marketing-douglas-van-praet-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unconscious-branding-how-neuroscience-can-empower-and-inspire-marketing-douglas-van-praet-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For too long marketers have been asking the wrong question. If consumers make decisions unconsciously, why do we persist in asking them directly through traditional marketing research why they do what they do? They simply can&#8217;t tell us because they don&#8217;t really know. Before marketers develop strategies, they need to recognize that consumers have strategies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unconscious-branding-how-neuroscience-can-empower-and-inspire-marketing-douglas-van-praet-abridged/">Unconscious Branding : How Neuroscience Can Empower (and Inspire) Marketing &#8211; Douglas van Praet (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For too long marketers have been asking the wrong question. If consumers make decisions unconsciously, why do we persist in asking them directly through traditional marketing research why they do what they do? They simply can&#8217;t tell us because they don&#8217;t really know. Before marketers develop strategies, they need to recognize that consumers have strategies too &#8230;human strategies, not consumer strategies. We need to go beyond asking why, and begin to ask how, behavior change occurs. Here, author Douglas Van Praet takes the most brilliant and revolutionary concepts from cognitive science and applies them to how we market, advertise, and consume in the modern digital age. Van Praet simplifies the most complex object in the known universe &#8211; the human brain &#8211; into seven codified actionable steps to behavior change. These steps are illustrated using real world examples from advertising, marketing, media, and business to consciously unravel what brilliant marketers and ad practitioners have long done intuitively, deconstructing the real story behind some of the greatest marketing and business successes in recent history, such as Nike&#8217;s &#8220;Just Do It&#8221; campaign; &#8220;Got Milk?&#8221;<br />
                    ; Wendy&#8217;s &#8220;Where&#8217;s the Beef?&#8221;; and the infamous Volkswagen &#8220;Punch Buggy&#8221; launch as well as their beloved &#8220;The Force&#8221; (Mini Darth Vader) Super Bowl commercial.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unconscious-branding-how-neuroscience-can-empower-and-inspire-marketing-douglas-van-praet-abridged/">Unconscious Branding : How Neuroscience Can Empower (and Inspire) Marketing &#8211; Douglas van Praet (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Brain Sell : When Science Meets Shopping &#8211; David Lewis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-brain-sell-when-science-meets-shopping-david-lewis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-brain-sell-when-science-meets-shopping-david-lewis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Science has made the leap from the lab to come to a store near you and the effects on us are phenomenal. Corporations in hyper-competition are now using the new mind sciences to analyze how and when we shop, and the hidden triggers that persuade us to consume. From bargains in the Big Apple to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brain-sell-when-science-meets-shopping-david-lewis-abridged/">The Brain Sell : When Science Meets Shopping &#8211; David Lewis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Science has made the leap from the lab to come to a store near you and the effects on us are phenomenal.    </p>
<p>                    Corporations in hyper-competition are now using the new mind sciences to analyze how and when we shop, and the hidden triggers that persuade us to consume. From bargains in the Big Apple to the bustling bazaars of Istanbul, from in-store to interactive and online to mobile, neuromarketing pioneer Dr. David Lewis goes behind the scenes of the persuasion industry to reveal the powerful tools and techniques, technologies and psychologies seeking to stimulate us all to buy more often without us consciously realizing it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brain-sell-when-science-meets-shopping-david-lewis-abridged/">The Brain Sell : When Science Meets Shopping &#8211; David Lewis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Compass of Pleasure : How Our Brains Make Fatty Foods, Orgasm, Exercise, Marijuana, Generosity, Vodka, Learning, and Gambling Feel So Good &#8211; David J. Linden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-compass-of-pleasure-how-our-brains-make-fatty-foods-orgasm-exercise-marijuana-generosity-vodka-learning-and-gambling-feel-so-good-david-j-linden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-compass-of-pleasure-how-our-brains-make-fatty-foods-orgasm-exercise-marijuana-generosity-vodka-learning-and-gambling-feel-so-good-david-j-linden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author comes a &#8220;hugely entertaining&#8221; (NPR.org) look at vice and virtue through cutting-edge scienceAs he did in his award-winning book The Accidental Mind, David J. Linden-highly regarded neuroscientist, professor, and writer-weaves empirical science with entertaining anecdotes to explain how the gamut of behaviors that give us a buzz actually [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-compass-of-pleasure-how-our-brains-make-fatty-foods-orgasm-exercise-marijuana-generosity-vodka-learning-and-gambling-feel-so-good-david-j-linden-abridged/">The Compass of Pleasure : How Our Brains Make Fatty Foods, Orgasm, Exercise, Marijuana, Generosity, Vodka, Learning, and Gambling Feel So Good &#8211; David J. Linden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author comes a &#8220;hugely entertaining&#8221; (NPR.org) look at vice and virtue through cutting-edge scienceAs he did in his award-winning book The Accidental Mind, David J. Linden-highly regarded neuroscientist, professor, and writer-weaves empirical science with entertaining anecdotes to explain how the gamut of behaviors that give us a buzz actually operates. The Compass of Pleasure makes clear why drugs like nicotine and heroin are addictive while LSD is not, how fast food restaurants ensure that diners will eat more, why some people cannot resist the appeal of a new sexual encounter, and much more. Provocative and illuminating, this is a radically new and thorough look at the desires that define us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-compass-of-pleasure-how-our-brains-make-fatty-foods-orgasm-exercise-marijuana-generosity-vodka-learning-and-gambling-feel-so-good-david-j-linden-abridged/">The Compass of Pleasure : How Our Brains Make Fatty Foods, Orgasm, Exercise, Marijuana, Generosity, Vodka, Learning, and Gambling Feel So Good &#8211; David J. Linden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Successful Aging : A Neuroscientist Explores the Power and Potential of Our Lives &#8211; Daniel J. Levitin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/successful-aging-a-neuroscientist-explores-the-power-and-potential-of-our-lives-daniel-j-levitin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/successful-aging-a-neuroscientist-explores-the-power-and-potential-of-our-lives-daniel-j-levitin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT TOP 10 BESTSELLER *New York Times *USAToday *Washington Post *LA Times Debunks the idea that aging inevitably brings infirmity and unhappiness and instead offers a trove of practical, evidence-based guidance for living longer and better. &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, author of When and Drive SUCCESSFUL AGING delivers powerful insights: &#8211; Debunking the myth that memory [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/successful-aging-a-neuroscientist-explores-the-power-and-potential-of-our-lives-daniel-j-levitin-abridged/">Successful Aging : A Neuroscientist Explores the Power and Potential of Our Lives &#8211; Daniel J. Levitin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT TOP 10 BESTSELLER *New York Times *USAToday *Washington Post *LA Times     </p>
<p>                    Debunks the idea that aging inevitably brings infirmity and unhappiness and instead offers a trove of practical, evidence-based guidance for living longer and better.<br />
                    &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, author of When and Drive     </p>
<p>                    SUCCESSFUL AGING delivers powerful insights:<br />
                     &#8211; Debunking the myth that memory always declines with age<br />
                     &#8211; Confirming that health span&#8211;not life span&#8211;is what matters<br />
                     &#8211; Proving that sixty-plus years is a unique and newly recognized developmental stage<br />
                     &#8211; Recommending that people look forward to joy, as reminiscing doesn&#8217;t promote health     </p>
<p>                     Levitin looks at the science behind what we all can learn from those who age joyously, as well as how to adapt our culture to take full advantage of older people&#8217;s wisdom and experience. Throughout his exploration of what aging really means, using research from developmental neuroscience and the psychology of individual differences, Levitin reveals resilience strategies and practical, cognitive- enhancing tricks everyone should do as they age.     </p>
<p>                     Successful Aging inspires a powerful new approach to how readers think about our final decades, and it will revolutionize the way we plan for old age as individuals, family members, and citizens within a society where the average life expectancy continues to rise.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/successful-aging-a-neuroscientist-explores-the-power-and-potential-of-our-lives-daniel-j-levitin-abridged/">Successful Aging : A Neuroscientist Explores the Power and Potential of Our Lives &#8211; Daniel J. Levitin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Activate Your Brain : How Understanding Your Brain Can Improve Your Work &#8211; and Your Life &#8211; Scott G Halford (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/activate-your-brain-how-understanding-your-brain-can-improve-your-work-and-your-life-scott-g-halford-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/activate-your-brain-how-understanding-your-brain-can-improve-your-work-and-your-life-scott-g-halford-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Wall Street Journal bestselling ebook! Axiom Business Book Bronze Award Winner Push your brain to full power, for success at the office and at home Would you like more control over your life and your work? Would you like greater stamina as you carry out</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/activate-your-brain-how-understanding-your-brain-can-improve-your-work-and-your-life-scott-g-halford-abridged/">Activate Your Brain : How Understanding Your Brain Can Improve Your Work &#8211; and Your Life &#8211; Scott G Halford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Wall Street Journal bestselling ebook! Axiom Business Book Bronze Award Winner Push your brain to full power, for success at the office and at home Would you like more control over your life and your work? Would you like greater stamina as you carry out</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/activate-your-brain-how-understanding-your-brain-can-improve-your-work-and-your-life-scott-g-halford-abridged/">Activate Your Brain : How Understanding Your Brain Can Improve Your Work &#8211; and Your Life &#8211; Scott G Halford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Can Hear You Whisper : An Intimate Journey Through the Science of Sound and Language &#8211; Lydia Denworth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Audiology & Otology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Speech & Language Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A skilled science translator, Denworth makes decibels, teslas and brain plasticity understandable to all.&#8221;-Washington Post Lydia Denworth&#8217;s third son, Alex, was nearly two when he was identified with significant hearing loss that was likely to get worse. Denworth knew the importance of enrichment to the developing brain but had never contemplated the opposite: deprivation. How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/">I Can Hear You Whisper : An Intimate Journey Through the Science of Sound and Language &#8211; Lydia Denworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A skilled science translator, Denworth makes decibels, teslas and brain plasticity understandable to all.&#8221;-Washington Post    </p>
<p>                    Lydia Denworth&#8217;s third son, Alex, was nearly two when he was identified with significant hearing loss that was likely to get worse. Denworth knew the importance of enrichment to the developing brain but had never contemplated the opposite: deprivation. How would a child&#8217;s brain grow outside the world of sound? How would he communicate? Would he learn to read and write?    </p>
<p>                    An acclaimed science journalist as well as a mother, Denworth made it her mission to find out, interviewing experts on language development, inventors of groundbreaking technology, Deaf leaders, and neuroscientists at the frontiers of brain plasticity research. I Can Hear You Whisper chronicles Denworth&#8217;s search for answers-and her new understanding of Deaf culture and the exquisite relationship between sound, language, and learning.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/">I Can Hear You Whisper : An Intimate Journey Through the Science of Sound and Language &#8211; Lydia Denworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Addiction & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to make real, lasting changes in your life We all have bad habits &#8211; whether it&#8217;s a weakness for junk food, a smartphone addiction or a lack of exercise. But change is hard. Forty percent of dieters quit within a week. Eighty percent of New Year&#8217;s resolutions don&#8217;t last beyond January. How can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/">Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to make real, lasting changes in your life    </p>
<p>                    We all have bad habits &#8211; whether it&#8217;s a weakness for junk food, a smartphone addiction or a lack of exercise. But change is hard. Forty percent of dieters quit within a week. Eighty percent of New Year&#8217;s resolutions don&#8217;t last beyond January. How can we kick bad habits &#8211; and stick with it?    </p>
<p>                    According to psychologist and behaviour researcher Dr Sean Young, the answer is to stop trying to change the person, and instead change the process. In Stick With It, Dr Young draws on his own research and that of other leading experts to explain how the mind often interferes with breaking bad habits, and how we can outsmart it, increasing the likelihood of lasting change by 200%.     </p>
<p>                    Packed with practical exercises and real-life case studies, Stick With It shows that it is possible to control spending, stick to a diet, exercise regularly and overcome problem behaviours &#8211; forever.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Scientifically grounded and personally implementable. It&#8217;s a winner&#8217; &#8211; Robert Cialdini, author of Influence and Pre-Suasion    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A must-read for anyone who&#8217;s been unable to keep a New Year&#8217;s resolution or failed at making a lasting change in any other area of their life or work. &#8211; Jonah Berger, author of Contagious    </p>
<p>                    Dr Sean Young is one of the world&#8217;s leading experts in the field of habit-forming. He is an acclaiedpsychologist and the founder and Executive Director of the UCLA Center for Digital Behavior. His research involves the study of cutting-edge ways of using social media and mobile technologies to change and predict human behaviour.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stick-with-it-the-science-of-lasting-behaviour-dr-sean-young-abridged/">Stick with It : The Science of Lasting Behaviour &#8211; Dr Sean Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Diets Make Us Fat : the unintended consequences of our obsession with weight loss &#8211; Contributions bySandra Aamodt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-diets-make-us-fat-the-unintended-consequences-of-our-obsession-with-weight-loss-contributions-by-sandra-aamodt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-diets-make-us-fat-the-unintended-consequences-of-our-obsession-with-weight-loss-contributions-by-sandra-aamodt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everything we know about dieting and weight loss is wrong. In the UK, almost two-thirds of adults are overweight. We think we know the answer: cut calories; eat less. We conclude that being fat is a failure of willpower, perhaps supplemented by a quirk of genetics. Yet research shows that losing weight by willpower alone [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-diets-make-us-fat-the-unintended-consequences-of-our-obsession-with-weight-loss-contributions-by-sandra-aamodt-abridged/">Why Diets Make Us Fat : the unintended consequences of our obsession with weight loss &#8211; Contributions bySandra Aamodt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everything we know about dieting and weight loss is wrong.    </p>
<p>                    In the UK, almost two-thirds of adults are overweight. We think we know the answer: cut calories; eat less. We conclude that being fat is a failure of willpower, perhaps supplemented by a quirk of genetics. Yet research shows that losing weight by willpower alone is almost guaranteed to fail in the long run. In fact, there is no evidence that dieting improves long-term health, and some that suggests yo-yo dieting is more dangerous than being overweight.    </p>
<p>                    Combining deep research and brutal candour about her own experience as a yo-yo dieter, neuroscientist Sandra Aamodt explains the science of the obesity epidemic, including new findings about gut bacteria, why bariatric surgery works (it has more to do with your brain than your stomach), and what a real alternative to dieting and weight cycling might look like.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-diets-make-us-fat-the-unintended-consequences-of-our-obsession-with-weight-loss-contributions-by-sandra-aamodt-abridged/">Why Diets Make Us Fat : the unintended consequences of our obsession with weight loss &#8211; Contributions bySandra Aamodt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Social : Why Our Brains Are Wired to Connect &#8211; Matthew D. Lieberman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/social-why-our-brains-are-wired-to-connect-matthew-d-lieberman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/social-why-our-brains-are-wired-to-connect-matthew-d-lieberman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are profoundly social creatures&#8211;more than we know. In Social, renowned psychologist Matthew Lieberman explores groundbreaking research in social neuroscience revealing that our need to connect with other people is even more fundamental, more basic, than our need for food or shelter. Because of this, our brain uses its spare time to learn about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-why-our-brains-are-wired-to-connect-matthew-d-lieberman-abridged/">Social : Why Our Brains Are Wired to Connect &#8211; Matthew D. Lieberman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We are profoundly social creatures&#8211;more than we know.      </p>
<p>                    In Social, renowned psychologist Matthew Lieberman explores groundbreaking research in social neuroscience revealing that our need to connect with other people is even more fundamental, more basic, than our need for food or shelter. Because of this, our brain uses its spare time to learn about the social world&#8211;other people and our relation to them. It is believed that we must commit 10,000 hours to master a skill. According to Lieberman, each of us has spent 10,000 hours learning to make sense of people and groups by the time we are ten.     </p>
<p>                     Social argues that our need to reach out to and connect with others is a primary driver behind our behavior. We believe that pain and pleasure alone guide our actions. Yet, new research using fMRI&#8211;including a great deal of original research conducted by Lieberman and his UCLA lab&#8211;shows that our brains react to social pain and pleasure in much the same way as they do to physical pain and pleasure. Fortunately, the brain has evolved sophisticated mechanisms for securing our place in the social world. We have a unique ability to read other people&#8217;s minds, to figure out their hopes, fears, and motivations, allowing us to effectively coordinate our lives with one another. And our most private sense of who we are is intimately linked to the important people and groups in our lives. This wiring often leads us to restrain our selfish impulses for the greater good. These mechanisms lead to behavior that might seem irrational, but is really just the result of our deep social wiring and necessary for our success as a species.     </p>
<p>                     Based on the latest cutting edge research, the findings in Social have important real-world implications. Our schools and businesses, for example, attempt to minimalize social distractions. But this is exactly the wrong thing to do to encourage engagement and learning, and literally shuts down the social brain, leaving powerful neuro-cognitive resources untapped. The insights revealed in this pioneering book suggest ways to improve learning in schools, make the workplace more productive, and improve our overall well-being.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-why-our-brains-are-wired-to-connect-matthew-d-lieberman-abridged/">Social : Why Our Brains Are Wired to Connect &#8211; Matthew D. Lieberman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life : A Psychologist Investigates How Evolution, Cognition, and Complexity are Revolutionizing Our View of Human Nature &#8211; Douglas Kenrick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sex-murder-and-the-meaning-of-life-a-psychologist-investigates-how-evolution-cognition-and-complexity-are-revolutionizing-our-view-of-human-nature-douglas-kenrick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sex-murder-and-the-meaning-of-life-a-psychologist-investigates-how-evolution-cognition-and-complexity-are-revolutionizing-our-view-of-human-nature-douglas-kenrick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#038;ldquoKenrick writes like a dream.&#8221;- Robert Sapolsky, Professor of Biology and Neurology, Stanford University author of A Primate&#8217;s Memoir and Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers What do sex and murder have to do with the meaning of life? Everything. In Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life , social psychologist Douglas Kenrick exposes the selfish [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-murder-and-the-meaning-of-life-a-psychologist-investigates-how-evolution-cognition-and-complexity-are-revolutionizing-our-view-of-human-nature-douglas-kenrick-abridged/">Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life : A Psychologist Investigates How Evolution, Cognition, and Complexity are Revolutionizing Our View of Human Nature &#8211; Douglas Kenrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#038;ldquoKenrick writes like a dream.&#8221;- Robert Sapolsky, Professor of Biology and Neurology, Stanford University author of  A Primate&#8217;s Memoir  and  Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers  What do sex and murder have to do with the meaning of life? Everything. In  Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life , social psychologist Douglas Kenrick exposes the selfish animalistic underside of human nature, and shows how it is intimately connected to our greatest and most selfless achievements. Masterfully integrating cognitive science, evolutionary psychology, and complexity theory, this intriguing book paints a comprehensive picture of the principles that govern our lives. As Kenrick divulges, beneath our civilized veneer, human beings are a lot like howling hyenas and barking baboons, with heads full of homicidal tendencies and sexual fantasies. But, in his view, many ingrained, apparently irrational behaviours- such as inclinations to one-night stands, racial prejudices, and conspicuous consumption- ultimately manifest what he calls&#8221;Deep Rationality.&#8221;  Although our heads are full of simple selfish biases that evolved to help our ancestors survive, modern human beings are anything but simple and selfish cavemen. Kenrick argues that simple and selfish mental mechanisms we inherited from our ancestors ultimately give rise to the multifaceted social lives that we humans lead today, and to the most positive features of humanity, including generosity, artistic creativity, love, and familial bonds. And out of those simple mechanisms emerge all the complexities of society, including international conflicts and global economic markets. By exploring the nuance of social psychology and the surprising results of his own research, Kenrick offers a detailed picture of what makes us caring, creative, and complex- that is, fully human.   Illuminated with stories from Kenrick&#8217;s own colourful experiences &#8211;  from his criminally inclined shantytown Irish relatives, his own multiple high school expulsions, broken marriages, and homicidal fantasies, to his eventual success as an evolutionary psychologist and loving father of two boys separated by 26 years &#8211;  this book is an exploration of our mental biases and failures, and our mind&#8217;s great successes. Idiosyncratic, controversial, and fascinating,  Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life  uncovers the pitfalls and promise of our biological inheritance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-murder-and-the-meaning-of-life-a-psychologist-investigates-how-evolution-cognition-and-complexity-are-revolutionizing-our-view-of-human-nature-douglas-kenrick-abridged/">Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life : A Psychologist Investigates How Evolution, Cognition, and Complexity are Revolutionizing Our View of Human Nature &#8211; Douglas Kenrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
