<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Biography: Business &amp; Industry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/biography-business-industry/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/biography-business-industry/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Biography: Business &amp; Industry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/biography-business-industry/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</title>
		<link>/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR </p>
<p>                     When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch a cable news network in 1996, American politics and media changed forever. With a remarkable level of detail and insight, Vanity Fair magazine reporter Gabriel Sherman puts Ailes&#8217;s unique genius on display, along with the outsize personalities&#8211;Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Sean Hannity, Megyn Kelly, Sarah Palin, Karl Rove, Glenn Beck, Mike Huckabee, Gretchen Carlson, Bill Shine, and others&#8211;who have helped Fox News play a defining role in the great social and political controversies of the past two decades. From the Clinton-Lewinsky scandal to the Bush-Gore recount, from the war in Iraq to the Tea Party attack on the Obama presidency, Roger Ailes developed an unrivaled power to sway the national agenda. Even more, he became the indispensable figure in conservative America and the man any Republican politician with presidential aspirations had to court. </p>
<p>                     How did this man become the master strategist of our political landscape? In revelatory detail, Sherman chronicles the rise of Ailes, a frail kid from an Ohio factory town who, through sheer willpower, the flair of a showman, fierce corporate politicking, and a profound understanding of the priorities of middle America, built the most influential television news empire of our time. </p>
<p>                     Drawing on hundreds of interviews with Fox News insiders past and present, Sherman documents Ailes&#8217;s tactical acuity as he battled the press, business rivals, and countless real and perceived enemies inside and outside Fox. Sherman takes us inside the morning meetings in which Ailes and other high-level executives strategized Fox&#8217;s presentation of the news to advance Ailes&#8217;s political agenda; provides behind-the-scenes details of Ailes&#8217;s crucial role as finder and shaper of talent, including his sometimes rocky relationships with Fox News stars such as O&#8217;Reilly, Hannity, and Carlson; and probes Ailes&#8217;s fraught partnership with his equally brash and mercurial boss, Rupert Murdoch. </p>
<p>                     Roger Ailes&#8217;s life is a story worthy of Citizen Kane. Featuring an afterword about Ailes&#8217;s epic downfall during the extraordinary 2016 election, The Loudest Voice in the Room is an extraordinary feat of reportage with a compelling human drama at its heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trump: The Art of the Deal &#8211; Donald J. Trump</title>
		<link>/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Golf]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>President Donald J. Trump lays out his professional and personal worldview in this classic work&#8211;a firsthand account of the rise of America&#8217;s foremost deal-maker. &#8220;I like thinking big. I always have. To me it&#8217;s very simple: If you&#8217;re going to be thinking anyway, you might as well think big.&#8221;&#8211;Donald J. Trump Here is Trump in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/">Trump: The Art of the Deal &#8211; Donald J. Trump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>President Donald J. Trump lays out his professional and personal worldview in this classic work&#8211;a firsthand account of the rise of America&#8217;s foremost deal-maker. </p>
<p>                     &#8220;I like thinking big. I always have. To me it&#8217;s very simple: If you&#8217;re going to be thinking anyway, you might as well think big.&#8221;&#8211;Donald J. Trump </p>
<p>                    Here is Trump in action&#8211;how he runs his organization and how he runs his life&#8211;as he meets the people he needs to meet, chats with family and friends, clashes with enemies, and challenges conventional thinking. But even a maverick plays by rules, and Trump has formulated time-tested guidelines for success. He isolates the common elements in his greatest accomplishments; he shatters myths; he names names, spells out the zeros, and fully reveals the deal-maker&#8217;s art. And throughout, Trump talks&#8211;really talks&#8211;about how he does it. Trump: The Art of the Deal is an unguarded look at the mind of a brilliant entrepreneur&#8211;the ultimate read for anyone interested in the man behind the spotlight. </p>
<p>                     Praise for Trump: The Art of the Deal </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Trump makes one believe for a moment in the American dream again.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times  </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Donald Trump is a deal maker. He is a deal maker the way lions are carnivores and water is wet.&#8221;&#8211;Chicago Tribune</p>
<p>                     &#8220;Fascinating . . . wholly absorbing . . . conveys Trump&#8217;s larger-than-life demeanor so vibrantly that the reader&#8217;s attention is instantly and fully claimed.&#8221;&#8211;Boston Herald</p>
<p>                     &#8220;A chatty, generous, chutzpa-filled autobiography.&#8221;&#8211;New York Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trump-the-art-of-the-deal-donald-j-trump/">Trump: The Art of the Deal &#8211; Donald J. Trump</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger</title>
		<link>/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019 _____________________________ The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES<br />
                    THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019<br />
                    _____________________________</p>
<p>                    The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in the world and inspire the people who bring the magic to life. </p>
<p>                    Robert Iger became CEO of The Walt Disney Company in 2005, during a difficult time. Morale had deteriorated, competition was intense, and technology was changing faster than at any time in the company&#8217;s history. His vision came down to three clear ideas: Recommit to the concept that quality matters, embrace technology instead of fighting it, and think bigger-think global-and turn Disney into a stronger brand in international markets. </p>
<p>                    Fourteen years later, Disney is the largest, most respected media company in the world, counting Pixar, Marvel, Lucasfilm and 21st Century Fox among its properties. Its value is nearly five times what it was when Iger took over, and he is recognized as one of the most innovative and successful CEOs of our era.</p>
<p>                    In The Ride of a Lifetime, Robert Iger shares the lessons he&#8217;s learned while running Disney and leading its 200,000 employees, and he explores the principles that are necessary for true leadership, including:</p>
<p>                     Optimism. Even in the face of difficulty, an optimistic leader will find the path toward the best possible outcome and focus on that, rather than give in to pessimism and blaming.<br />
                     Courage. Leaders have to be willing to take risks and place big bets. Fear of failure destroys creativity.<br />
                     Decisiveness. All decisions, no matter how difficult, can be made on a timely basis. Indecisiveness is both wasteful and destructive to morale.<br />
                     Fairness. Treat people decently, with empathy, and be accessible to them. </p>
<p>                    This book is about the relentless curiosity that has driven Iger for forty-five years, since the day he started as the lowliest studio grunt at ABC. It&#8217;s also about thoughtfulness and respect, and a decency-over-dollars approach that has become the bedrock of every project and partnership Iger pursues, from a deep friendship with Steve Jobs in his final years to an abiding love of the Star Wars mythology.</p>
<p>                    &#8220;The ideas in this book strike me as universal&#8221; Iger writes. &#8220;Not just to the aspiring CEOs of the world, but to anyone wanting to feel less fearful, more confidently themselves, as they navigate their professional and even personal lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review</p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.</p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.</p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.</p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New New Thing : A Silicon Valley Story &#8211; Michael Lewis</title>
		<link>/the-new-new-thing-a-silicon-valley-story-michael-lewis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-new-thing-a-silicon-valley-story-michael-lewis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the weird glow of the dying millennium, Michael Lewis set out on a safari through Silicon Valley to find the world&#8217;s most important technology entrepreneur. He found this in Jim Clark, a man whose achievements include the founding of three separate billion-dollar companies. Lewis also found much more, and the result-the best-selling book The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-new-thing-a-silicon-valley-story-michael-lewis/">The New New Thing : A Silicon Valley Story &#8211; Michael Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the weird glow of the dying millennium, Michael Lewis set out on a safari through Silicon Valley to find the world&#8217;s most important technology entrepreneur. He found this in Jim Clark, a man whose achievements include the founding of three separate billion-dollar companies. Lewis also found much more, and the result-the best-selling book The New New Thing-is an ingeniously conceived history of the Internet revolution.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-new-thing-a-silicon-valley-story-michael-lewis/">The New New Thing : A Silicon Valley Story &#8211; Michael Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creative Confidence : Unleashing the Creative Potential within Us All &#8211; David Kelley, Tom Kelley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/creative-confidence-unleashing-the-creative-potential-within-us-all-david-kelley-tom-kelley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/creative-confidence-unleashing-the-creative-potential-within-us-all-david-kelley-tom-kelley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A powerful and inspiring book from the founders of IDEO, the award-winning design firm, on unleashing the creativity that lies within each and every one of us. Too often, companies and individuals assume that creativity and innovation are the domain of the &#8216;creative types&#8217;. But two of the foremost experts in innovation, design and creativity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/creative-confidence-unleashing-the-creative-potential-within-us-all-david-kelley-tom-kelley-abridged/">Creative Confidence : Unleashing the Creative Potential within Us All &#8211; David Kelley, Tom Kelley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A powerful and inspiring book from the founders of IDEO, the award-winning design firm, on unleashing the creativity that lies within each and every one of us.    </p>
<p>                              Too often, companies and individuals assume that creativity and innovation are the domain of the &#8216;creative types&#8217;. But two of the foremost experts in innovation, design and creativity on the planet show us that each and every one of us is creative.    </p>
<p>                              In an entertaining and inspiring narrative that draws on countless stories from their work at IDEO, and with many of the world&#8217;s top companies and design firms, David and Tom Kelley identify the principles and strategies that will allow us to tap into our creative potential in our work lives, and in our personal lives, allow us to think outside the box in terms of how we approach and solve problems.    </p>
<p>                              &#8216;Creative Confidence&#8217; is a book that will help each of us be more productive and successful in our lives and in our careers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/creative-confidence-unleashing-the-creative-potential-within-us-all-david-kelley-tom-kelley-abridged/">Creative Confidence : Unleashing the Creative Potential within Us All &#8211; David Kelley, Tom Kelley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do the KIND Thing : Think Boundlessly, Work Purposefully, Live Passionately &#8211; Daniel Lubetzky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For the socially conscious, the intellectually curious, or the creative soul comes an inspiring, New York Times bestselling handbook for success in business, life, and the all-important task of building a more compassionate world&#8211;by the visionary founder and CEO of KIND Healthy Snacks. When Daniel Lubetzky started KIND Healthy Snacks in 2004, he aimed to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/">Do the KIND Thing : Think Boundlessly, Work Purposefully, Live Passionately &#8211; Daniel Lubetzky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For the socially conscious, the intellectually curious, or the creative soul comes an inspiring, New York Times bestselling handbook for success in business, life, and the all-important task of building a more compassionate world&#8211;by the visionary founder and CEO of KIND Healthy Snacks.    </p>
<p>                     When Daniel Lubetzky started KIND Healthy Snacks in 2004, he aimed to defy the conventional wisdom that snack bars could never be both tasty and healthy, convenient and wholesome. A decade later, the transformative power of the company&#8217;s &#8220;AND&#8221; philosophy has resulted in an astonishing record of achievement. KIND has become the fastest-growing purveyor of healthy snacks in the country. Meanwhile, the KIND Movement&#8211;the company&#8217;s social mission to make the world a little kinder&#8211;has sparked more than a million good deeds worldwide.  In Do the KIND Thing,  Lubetzky shares the revolutionary principles that have shaped KIND&#8217;s business model and led to its success, while offering an unfiltered and intensely personal look into the mind of a pioneering social entrepreneur. Inspired by his father, who survived the Holocaust thanks to the courageous kindness of strangers, Lubetzky began his career handselling a sun-dried tomato spread made collaboratively by Arabs and Jews in the war-torn Middle East. Despite early setbacks, he never lost his faith in his vision of a &#8220;not-only-for-profit&#8221; business&#8211;one that sold great products and helped to make the world a better place.  While other companies let circumstances force them into choosing between two seemingly incompatible options, people at KIND say &#8220;AND.&#8221; At its core, this idea is about challenging assumptions and false compromises. It is about not settling for less and being willing to take greater risks, often financial. It is about learning to think boundlessly and critically, and choosing what at first may be the tougher path for later, greater rewards. By using illuminating anecdotes from his own career, and celebrating some past failures through the lessons learned from them, Lubetzky outlines his core tenets for building a successful business and a thriving social enterprise. He explores the value of staying true to your brand, highlights the importance of transparency and communication in the workplace, and explains why good intentions alone won&#8217;t sell products.  Engaging and inspirational, Do the KIND Thing shows how the power of AND worked wonders for one company&#8211;and could empower the next generation of social entrepreneurs to improve their bottom line and change the world. Advance praise for Do the KIND Thing  &#8220;An enjoyable read . . . wise advice about matters from product development to people management.&#8221;&#8211;Financial Times &#8220;By sharing the ten tenets that helped KIND grow, Daniel Lubetzky has given entrepreneurs a road map to success that includes both passion and purpose.&#8221;&#8211;Arianna Huffington, president and editor in chief, Huffington Post Media Group  &#8220;Lubetzky uses the power of kindness to build purpose into his business and his community. He&#8217;s a role model for future leaders.&#8221;&#8211;Mehmet Oz, M.D., professor of surgery, Columbia University  &#8220;I&#8217;ve always been a fan of the KIND brand. This engaging and inspirational book shows how coupling a social mission with creativity can spark change and empower a generation.&#8221;&#8211;Bobbi Brown, founder and CCO, Bobbi Brown Cosmetics</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-the-kind-thing-think-boundlessly-work-purposefully-live-passionately-daniel-lubetzky-abridged/">Do the KIND Thing : Think Boundlessly, Work Purposefully, Live Passionately &#8211; Daniel Lubetzky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sam Walton : Made In America &#8211; Sam Walton, Contributions by John Huey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sam-walton-made-in-america-sam-walton-contributions-by-john-huey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sam-walton-made-in-america-sam-walton-contributions-by-john-huey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Meet a genuine American folk hero cut from the homespun cloth of America&#8217;s heartland: Sam Walton, who parlayed a single dime store in a hardscrabble cotton town into Wal-Mart, the largest retailer in the world. The undisputed merchant king of the late twentieth century, Sam never lost the common touch. Here, finally, inimitable words. Genuinely [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sam-walton-made-in-america-sam-walton-contributions-by-john-huey-abridged/">Sam Walton : Made In America &#8211; Sam Walton, Contributions by John Huey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meet a genuine American folk hero cut from the homespun cloth of America&#8217;s heartland: Sam Walton, who parlayed a single dime store in a hardscrabble cotton town into Wal-Mart, the largest retailer in the world. The undisputed merchant king of the late twentieth century, Sam never lost the common touch. Here, finally, inimitable words. Genuinely modest, but always sure if his ambitions and achievements. Sam shares his thinking in a candid, straight-from-the-shoulder style.     </p>
<p>                    In a story rich with anecdotes and the &#8220;rules of the road&#8221; of both Main Street and Wall Street, Sam Walton chronicles the inspiration, heart, and optimism that propelled him to lasso the American Dream.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sam-walton-made-in-america-sam-walton-contributions-by-john-huey-abridged/">Sam Walton : Made In America &#8211; Sam Walton, Contributions by John Huey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Intel Trinity : How Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove Built the World&#8217;s Most Important Company &#8211; Michael S. Malone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-intel-trinity-how-robert-noyce-gordon-moore-and-andy-grove-built-the-worlds-most-important-company-michael-s-malone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-intel-trinity-how-robert-noyce-gordon-moore-and-andy-grove-built-the-worlds-most-important-company-michael-s-malone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Based on unprecedented access to the corporation&#8217;s archives, The Intel Trinity is the first full history of Intel Corporation-the essential company of the digital age- told through the lives of the three most important figures in the company&#8217;s history: Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove. Often hailed the &#8220;most important company in the world,&#8221; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-intel-trinity-how-robert-noyce-gordon-moore-and-andy-grove-built-the-worlds-most-important-company-michael-s-malone-abridged/">The Intel Trinity : How Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove Built the World&#8217;s Most Important Company &#8211; Michael S. Malone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Based on unprecedented access to the corporation&#8217;s archives, The Intel Trinity is the first full history of Intel Corporation-the essential company of the digital age- told through the lives of the three most important figures in the company&#8217;s history: Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove.  Often hailed the &#8220;most important company in the world,&#8221; Intel remains, more than four decades after its inception, a defining company of the global digital economy. The legendary inventors of the microprocessor-the single most important product in the modern world-Intel today builds the tiny &#8220;engines&#8221; that power almost every intelligent electronic device on the planet.  But the true story of Intel is the human story of the trio of geniuses behind it. Michael S. Malone reveals how each brought different things to Intel, and at different times. Noyce, the most respected high tech figure of his generation, brought credibility (and money) to the company&#8217;s founding; Moore made Intel the world&#8217;s technological leader; and Grove, has relentlessly driven the company to ever-higher levels of success and competitiveness.<br />
                    Without any one of these figures, Intel would never have achieved its historic success; with them, Intel made possible the personal computer, Internet, telecommunications, and the personal electronics revolutions.  The Intel Trinity is not just the story of Intel&#8217;s legendary past; it also offers an analysis of the formidable challenges that lie ahead as the company struggles to maintain its dominance, its culture, and its legacy.  With eight pages of black-and-white photos.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-intel-trinity-how-robert-noyce-gordon-moore-and-andy-grove-built-the-worlds-most-important-company-michael-s-malone-abridged/">The Intel Trinity : How Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove Built the World&#8217;s Most Important Company &#8211; Michael S. Malone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You Only Have To Be Right Once : The Rise of the Instant Billionaires Behind Spotify, Airbnb, WhatsApp, and 13 Other Amazing Startups &#8211; Randall Lane, Forbes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/you-only-have-to-be-right-once-the-rise-of-the-instant-billionaires-behind-spotify-airbnb-whatsapp-and-13-other-amazing-startups-randall-lane-forbes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/you-only-have-to-be-right-once-the-rise-of-the-instant-billionaires-behind-spotify-airbnb-whatsapp-and-13-other-amazing-startups-randall-lane-forbes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE ULTIMATE INSIDER LOOK AT THE NEWEST TITANS OF TECH &#8211; AND WHAT YOU CAN LEARN FROM THEIR SUCCESS Silicon Valley&#8217;s newest billionaires are a unique and unconventional breed of entrepreneur: young, bold and taking the world by storm with their extreme speed, insatiable hunger and progressive leadership. They turn just one brilliant insight into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-only-have-to-be-right-once-the-rise-of-the-instant-billionaires-behind-spotify-airbnb-whatsapp-and-13-other-amazing-startups-randall-lane-forbes-abridged/">You Only Have To Be Right Once : The Rise of the Instant Billionaires Behind Spotify, Airbnb, WhatsApp, and 13 Other Amazing Startups &#8211; Randall Lane, Forbes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE ULTIMATE INSIDER LOOK AT THE NEWEST TITANS OF TECH &#8211; AND WHAT YOU CAN LEARN FROM THEIR SUCCESS    </p>
<p>                    Silicon Valley&#8217;s newest billionaires are a unique and unconventional breed of entrepreneur: young, bold and taking the world by storm with their extreme speed, insatiable hunger and progressive leadership. They turn just one brilliant insight into money at a rate never before seen &#8211; creating companies that, even with no revenue, garner insane valuations.    </p>
<p>                    You Only Have to Be Right Once is the first comprehensive look at the people behind the biggest companies in tech. It behind-the-scenes examinations of billionaire tech titans including Tesla&#8217;s Elon Musk, Instagram&#8217;s Kevin Systrom, Airbnb&#8217;s Brian Chesky and Snapchat co-founder Evan Spiegel &#8211; and reveals what these super-entrepreneurs say about their own success.    </p>
<p>                    Introduced, edited and updated by Forbes editor Randall Lane, this is the definitive collection of everything we can learn from these incredible game changers, and what their next moves spell for the future of business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-only-have-to-be-right-once-the-rise-of-the-instant-billionaires-behind-spotify-airbnb-whatsapp-and-13-other-amazing-startups-randall-lane-forbes-abridged/">You Only Have To Be Right Once : The Rise of the Instant Billionaires Behind Spotify, Airbnb, WhatsApp, and 13 Other Amazing Startups &#8211; Randall Lane, Forbes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Invisible Thread : The True Story of an 11-Year-Old Panhandler, a Busy Sales Executive, and an Unlikely Meeting with Destiny &#8211; Laura Schroff, Alex Tresniowski (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/an-invisible-thread-the-true-story-of-an-11-year-old-panhandler-a-busy-sales-executive-and-an-unlikely-meeting-with-destiny-laura-schroff-alex-tresniowski-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-invisible-thread-the-true-story-of-an-11-year-old-panhandler-a-busy-sales-executive-and-an-unlikely-meeting-with-destiny-laura-schroff-alex-tresniowski-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This inspirational New York Times bestseller chronicles the lifelong friendship between a busy sales executive and a disadvantaged young boy, and how both of their lives were changed by what began as one small gesture of kindness. Stopping was never part of the plan&#8230; She was a successful ad sales rep in Manhattan. He was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-invisible-thread-the-true-story-of-an-11-year-old-panhandler-a-busy-sales-executive-and-an-unlikely-meeting-with-destiny-laura-schroff-alex-tresniowski-abridged/">An Invisible Thread : The True Story of an 11-Year-Old Panhandler, a Busy Sales Executive, and an Unlikely Meeting with Destiny &#8211; Laura Schroff, Alex Tresniowski (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This inspirational New York Times bestseller chronicles the lifelong friendship between a busy sales executive and a disadvantaged young boy, and how both of their lives were changed by what began as one small gesture of kindness.     </p>
<p>                    Stopping was never part of the plan&#8230;     </p>
<p>                     She was a successful ad sales rep in Manhattan. He was a homeless, eleven-year-old panhandler on the street. He asked for spare change; she kept walking. But then something stopped her in her tracks, and she went back. And she continued to go back, again and again. They met up nearly every week for years and built an unexpected, life-changing friendship that has today spanned almost three decades.     </p>
<p>                     Whatever made me notice him on that street corner so many years ago is clearly something that cannot be extinguished, no matter how relentless the forces aligned against it. Some may call it spirit. Some may call it heart. It drew me to him, as if we were bound by some invisible, unbreakable thread. And whatever it is, it binds us still.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-invisible-thread-the-true-story-of-an-11-year-old-panhandler-a-busy-sales-executive-and-an-unlikely-meeting-with-destiny-laura-schroff-alex-tresniowski-abridged/">An Invisible Thread : The True Story of an 11-Year-Old Panhandler, a Busy Sales Executive, and an Unlikely Meeting with Destiny &#8211; Laura Schroff, Alex Tresniowski (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Howard Hughes : His Life and Madness &#8211; Donald L. Barlett, James B. Steele (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/howard-hughes-his-life-and-madness-donald-l-barlett-james-b-steele-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/howard-hughes-his-life-and-madness-donald-l-barlett-james-b-steele-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Howard Hughes has always fascinated the public with his mixture of secrecy, dashing lifestyle, and reclusiveness. This is the book that breaks through the image to get at the man. Originally published under the title Empire: The Life, Legend, and Madness of Howard Hughes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/howard-hughes-his-life-and-madness-donald-l-barlett-james-b-steele-abridged/">Howard Hughes : His Life and Madness &#8211; Donald L. Barlett, James B. Steele (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Howard Hughes has always fascinated the public with his mixture of secrecy, dashing lifestyle, and reclusiveness. This is the book that breaks through the image to get at the man. Originally published under the title Empire: The Life, Legend, and Madness of Howard Hughes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/howard-hughes-his-life-and-madness-donald-l-barlett-james-b-steele-abridged/">Howard Hughes : His Life and Madness &#8211; Donald L. Barlett, James B. Steele (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal & Public Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Moneyball meets medicine in this remarkable chronicle of one of the greatest scientific quests of our time&#8211;the groundbreaking program to answer the most essential question for humanity: how do we live and die?&#8211;and the visionary mastermind behind it. Medical doctor and economist Christopher Murray began the Global Burden of Disease studies to gain a truer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/">Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Moneyball meets medicine in this remarkable chronicle of one of the greatest scientific quests of our time&#8211;the groundbreaking program to answer the most essential question for humanity: how do we live and die?&#8211;and the visionary mastermind behind it.    </p>
<p>                    Medical doctor and economist Christopher Murray began the Global Burden of Disease studies to gain a truer understanding of how we live and how we die. While it is one of the largest scientific projects ever attempted&#8211;as breathtaking as the first moon landing or the Human Genome Project&#8211;the questions it answers are meaningful for every one of us: What are the world&#8217;s health problems? Who do they hurt? How much? Where? Why?    </p>
<p>                    Murray argues that the ideal existence isn&#8217;t simply the longest but the one lived well and with the least illness. Until we can accurately measure how people live and die, we cannot understand what makes us sick or do much to improve it. Challenging the accepted wisdom of the WHO and the UN, the charismatic and controversial health maverick has made enemies&#8211;and some influential friends, including Bill Gates who gave Murray a $100 million grant.    </p>
<p>                    In Epic Measures, journalist Jeremy N. Smith offers an intimate look at Murray and his groundbreaking work. From ranking countries&#8217; healthcare systems (the U.S. is 37th) to unearthing the shocking reality that world governments are funding developing countries at only 30% of the potential maximum efficiency when it comes to health, Epic Measures introduces a visionary leader whose unwavering determination to improve global health standards has already changed the way the world addresses issues of health and wellness, sets policy, and distributes funding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/">Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Picking up where Liar&#8217;s Poker left off (literally, in the bond dealer&#8217;s desks of Salomon Brothers) the story of Long-Term Capital Management is of a group of elite investors who believed they could beat the market and, like alchemists, create limitless wealth for themselves and their partners. Founded by John Meriweather, a notoriously confident bond [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Picking up where Liar&#8217;s Poker left off (literally, in the bond dealer&#8217;s desks of Salomon Brothers) the story of Long-Term Capital Management is of a group of elite investors who believed they could beat the market and, like alchemists, create limitless wealth for themselves and their partners.    </p>
<p>                              Founded by John Meriweather, a notoriously confident bond dealer, along with two Nobel prize winners and a floor of Wall Street&#8217;s brightest and best, Long-Term Captial Management was from the beginning hailed as a new gold standard in investing. It was to be the hedge fund to end all other hedge funds: a discreet private investment club limited to those rich enough to pony up millions.    </p>
<p>                              It became the banks&#8217; own favourite fund and from its inception achieved a run of dizzyingly spectacular returns. New investors barged each other aside to get their investment money into LTCM&#8217;s hands. But as competitors began to mimic Meriweather&#8217;s fund, he altered strategy to maintain the fund&#8217;s performance, leveraging capital with credit on a scale not fully understood and never seen before.    </p>
<p>                              When the markets in Indonesia, South America and Russia crashed in 1998 LCTM&#8217;s investments crashed with them and mountainous debts accumulated. The fund was in melt-down, and threatening to bring down into its trillion-dollar black hole a host of financial instiutions from New York to Switzerland. It&#8217;s a tale of vivid characters, overwheening ambition, and perilous drama told, in Roger Lowenstein&#8217;s hands, with brilliant style and panache.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big : Kind of the Story of My Life &#8211; Scott Adams (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-kind-of-the-story-of-my-life-scott-adams-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-kind-of-the-story-of-my-life-scott-adams-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blasting clichéd career advice, the contrarian pundit and creator of Dilbert recounts the humorous ups and downs of his career, revealing the outsized role of luck in our lives and how best to play the system. Scott Adams has likely failed at more things than anyone you&#8217;ve ever met or anyone you&#8217;ve even heard of. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-kind-of-the-story-of-my-life-scott-adams-abridged/">How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big : Kind of the Story of My Life &#8211; Scott Adams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blasting clichéd career advice, the contrarian pundit and creator of Dilbert recounts the humorous ups and downs of his career, revealing the outsized role of luck in our lives and how best to play the system.      </p>
<p>                     Scott Adams has likely failed at more things than anyone you&#8217;ve ever met or anyone you&#8217;ve even heard of. So how did he go from hapless office worker and serial failure to the creator of Dilbert, one of the world&#8217;s most famous syndicated comic strips, in just a few years? In How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big, Adams shares the game plan he&#8217;s followed since he was a teen: invite failure in, embrace it, then pick its pocket.     </p>
<p>                     No career guide can offer advice that works for everyone. As Adams explains, your best bet is to study the ways of others who made it big and try to glean some tricks and strategies that make sense for you. Adams pulls back the covers on his own unusual life and shares how he turned one failure after another&#8211;including his corporate career, his inventions, his investments, and his two restaurants&#8211;into something good and lasting. There&#8217;s a lot to learn from his personal story, and a lot of entertainment along the way. Adams discovered some unlikely truths that helped to propel him forward. For instance:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Goals are for losers. Systems are for winners.<br />
                     &#8211; &#8220;Passion&#8221; is bull. What you need is personal energy.<br />
                     &#8211; A combination of mediocre skills can make you surprisingly valuable.<br />
                     &#8211; You can manage your odds in a way that makes you look lucky to others.     </p>
<p>                     Adams hopes you can laugh at his failures while discovering some unique and helpful ideas on your own path to personal victory. As he writes: &#8220;This is a story of one person&#8217;s unlikely success within the context of scores of embarrassing failures. Was my eventual success primarily a result of talent, luck, hard work, or an accidental just-right balance of each? All I know for sure is that I pursued a conscious strategy of managing my opportunities in a way that would make it easier for luck to find me.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-kind-of-the-story-of-my-life-scott-adams-abridged/">How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big : Kind of the Story of My Life &#8211; Scott Adams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Giants : Companies That Choose to be Great Instead of Big &#8211; Bo Burlingham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/small-giants-companies-that-choose-to-be-great-instead-of-big-bo-burlingham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/small-giants-companies-that-choose-to-be-great-instead-of-big-bo-burlingham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s widely accepted in business that great companies grow their revenues and profits year after year &#8211; but bigger is not necessarily better. In Small Giants, journalist Bo Burlingham takes us deep inside fourteen remarkable privately held companies, from a brewery to a record label, that chose a different path to success. These organizations quietly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-giants-companies-that-choose-to-be-great-instead-of-big-bo-burlingham-abridged/">Small Giants : Companies That Choose to be Great Instead of Big &#8211; Bo Burlingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s widely accepted in business that great companies grow their revenues and profits year after year &#8211; but bigger is not necessarily better. In Small Giants, journalist Bo Burlingham takes us deep inside fourteen remarkable privately held companies, from a brewery to a record label, that chose a different path to success.     </p>
<p>                    These organizations quietly rejected the pressure of endless growth, deciding to focus more on satisfying business goals &#8211; being the best at what they do, creating a stimulating place to work, providing perfect customer service and making important contributions to their communities.    </p>
<p>                    But what are the magic ingredients that make these companies unique? Why and how does their approach work in such widely varying industries? And what lessons can we learn from them? A fresh, inspirational guide to business strategy, Small Giants will help any entrepeneur consider new directions to make their company great.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-giants-companies-that-choose-to-be-great-instead-of-big-bo-burlingham-abridged/">Small Giants : Companies That Choose to be Great Instead of Big &#8211; Bo Burlingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Anarchy : The Relentless Rise of the East India Company &#8211; William Dalrymple (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-anarchy-the-relentless-rise-of-the-east-india-company-william-dalrymple-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[British & Irish History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colonialism & Imperialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Naval Forces & Warfare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-anarchy-the-relentless-rise-of-the-east-india-company-william-dalrymple-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP 5 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER ONE OF BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S BEST BOOKS OF 2019 THE TIMES HISTORY BOOK OF THE YEAR FINALIST FOR THE CUNDILL HISTORY PRIZE 2020 LONGLISTED FOR THE BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION 2019 A FINANCIAL TIMES, OBSERVER, DAILY TELEGRAPH, WALL STREET JOURNAL AND TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8216;Dalrymple is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-anarchy-the-relentless-rise-of-the-east-india-company-william-dalrymple-abridged/">The Anarchy : The Relentless Rise of the East India Company &#8211; William Dalrymple (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP 5 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    ONE OF BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S BEST BOOKS OF 2019<br />
                    THE TIMES HISTORY BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    FINALIST FOR THE CUNDILL HISTORY PRIZE 2020<br />
                    LONGLISTED FOR THE BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION 2019<br />
                    A FINANCIAL TIMES, OBSERVER, DAILY TELEGRAPH, WALL STREET JOURNAL AND TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Dalrymple is a superb historian with a visceral understanding of India &#8230; A book of beauty&#8217; &#8211;  Gerard DeGroot, The Times    </p>
<p>                    In August 1765 the East India Company defeated the young Mughal emperor and forced him to establish a new administration in his richest provinces. Run by English merchants who collected taxes using a ruthless private army, this new regime saw the East India Company transform itself from an international trading corporation into something much more unusual: an aggressive colonial power in the guise of a multinational business.    </p>
<p>                      William Dalrymple tells the remarkable story of the East India Company as it has never been told before, unfolding a timely cautionary tale of the first global corporate power.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-anarchy-the-relentless-rise-of-the-east-india-company-william-dalrymple-abridged/">The Anarchy : The Relentless Rise of the East India Company &#8211; William Dalrymple (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lost and Founder : A Painfully Honest Field Guide to the Startup World &#8211; Rand Fishkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Systems Analysis & Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You won&#8217;t find a more honest, raw and helpful look into the trenches of founding a tech startup than this book&#8217; Nir Eyal, author of Hooked &#8216;Rand Fishkin is the real deal&#8217; Seth Godin, entrepreneur and author &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; Everyone knows how a startup story is supposed to go: a young, brilliant entrepreneur has an cool [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/">Lost and Founder : A Painfully Honest Field Guide to the Startup World &#8211; Rand Fishkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You won&#8217;t find a more honest, raw and helpful look into the trenches of founding a tech startup than this book&#8217; Nir Eyal, author of Hooked    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Rand Fishkin is the real deal&#8217; Seth Godin, entrepreneur and author     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    Everyone knows how a startup story is supposed to go: a young, brilliant entrepreneur has an cool idea, drops out of college, defies the doubters, overcomes all odds, makes billions and becomes the envy of the technology world.     </p>
<p>                    This is not that story.    </p>
<p>                    Rand Fishkin, the founder and former CEO of Moz, is one of the world&#8217;s leading experts on SEO. Moz is now a $45 million a year business, but Fishkin&#8217;s business and reputation took 15 years to grow, and his startup began not in a Harvard dorm room but as a mother-and-son family business that fell deeply into debt.     </p>
<p>                    Now Fishkin pulls back the curtain on tech startup mythology, exposing the ups and downs of startup life that most CEOs would rather keep secret. For instance: a minimally viable product can be destructive if you launch at the wrong moment. Growth hacking may be the buzzword du jour, but initiatives to your business can fizzle quickly. Revenue and profitability won&#8217;t protect you from layoffs. And venture capital always comes with strings attached.     </p>
<p>                    In Lost and Founder Fishkin reveals the mostly awful, sometimes awesome truth about startup culture with the transparency and humour that his hundreds of thousands of blog readers have come to love. Fishkin&#8217;s hard-won lessons are applicable to any kind of business environment and this book can help solve your problems, and make you feel less alone for having them.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is a truly courageous book. It&#8217;s one part business-building guide and two parts Indiana Jones-style adventure memoir&#8217; Chris Guillebeau, author of Side Hustle and The $100 Startup    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Rand Fishkin is like the industry friend we all wish we had &#8211; funny, warm, and refreshingly honest about the rollercoaster ride that is founding your own company&#8217; Julie Zhou, VP of Product Design at Facebook</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/">Lost and Founder : A Painfully Honest Field Guide to the Startup World &#8211; Rand Fishkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buffett : The Making of an American Capitalist &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since its hardcover publication in August of 1995, Buffett has appeared on the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, San Francisco Chronicle, Los Angeles Times, Seattle Times, Newsday and Business Week bestseller lists. Starting from scratch, simply by picking stocks and companies for investment, Warren Buffett amassed one of the epochal fortunes of the twentieth [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">Buffett : The Making of an American Capitalist &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since its hardcover publication in August of 1995, Buffett has appeared on the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, San Francisco Chronicle, Los Angeles Times, Seattle Times, Newsday and Business Week bestseller lists. Starting from scratch, simply by picking stocks and companies for investment, Warren Buffett amassed one of the epochal fortunes of the twentieth century&#8211;an astounding net worth of $10 billion, and counting. His awesome investment record has made him a cult figure popularly known for his seeming contradictions: a billionaire who has a modest lifestyle, a phenomenally successful investor who eschews the revolving-door trading of modern Wall Street, a brilliant dealmaker who cultivates a homespun aura. Journalist Roger Lowenstein draws on three years of unprecedented access to Buffett&#8217;s family, friends, and colleagues to provide the first definitive, inside account of the life and career of this American original. Buffett explains Buffett&#8217;s investment strategy&#8211;a long-term philosophy grounded in buying stock in companies that are undervalued on the market and hanging on until their worth invariably surfaces&#8211;and shows how it is a reflection of his inner self.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">Buffett : The Making of an American Capitalist &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conspiracy : A True Story of Power, Sex, and a Billionaire&#8217;s Secret Plot to Destroy a Media Empire &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2016, one of the giants of modern journalism fell: Gawker Media, infamous for saying what other outlets wouldn&#8217;t say, was sued for publishing Hulk Hogan&#8217;s sex tape, lost the case and went bust. After countless other lawsuits it seemed that Gawker had finally run out of luck. But luck had nothing to do with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Conspiracy : A True Story of Power, Sex, and a Billionaire&#8217;s Secret Plot to Destroy a Media Empire &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2016, one of the giants of modern journalism fell: Gawker Media, infamous for saying what other outlets wouldn&#8217;t say, was sued for publishing Hulk Hogan&#8217;s sex tape, lost the case and went bust. After countless other lawsuits it seemed that Gawker had finally run out of luck. But luck had nothing to do with it.     </p>
<p>                    Peter Thiel, PayPal founder and billionaire investor, had masterminded the whole thing. Still furious at an article that had outed him ten years previously, and increasingly disgusted at Gawker&#8217;s unscrupulous reporting methods, Thiel had spent nearly a decade meticulously plotting a conspiracy that would lead to the demise of Gawker and its founder, Nick Denton. After a multi-year proxy war through the Florida legal system, the settlement of $140million in favour of Hogan ended it.    </p>
<p>                    The verdict would stun the world and so would Peter&#8217;s ultimate unmasking as the man who had set it all in motion. Why had he done this? How had no one discovered it? What would this mean&#8211;for free speech? For privacy? For culture?    </p>
<p>                    In Holiday&#8217;s masterful telling of this nearly unbelievable conspiracy, informed by exclusive interviews with all the key players, this case transcends the narrative of how one billionaire took down a media empire or the current state of the free press. It&#8217;s a study in power, strategy, and one of the most wildly ambitious &#8211; and successful &#8211; secret plots in recent memory.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Conspiracy : A True Story of Power, Sex, and a Billionaire&#8217;s Secret Plot to Destroy a Media Empire &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba : The House That Jack Ma Built &#8211; Duncan Clark (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An engrossing, insider&#8217;s account of how a teacher built one of the world&#8217;s most valuable companies-rivaling Walmart and Amazon-and forever reshaped the global economy In just a decade and a half, Jack Ma, a man from modest beginnings who started out as an English teacher, founded Alibaba and built it into one of the world&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/">Alibaba : The House That Jack Ma Built &#8211; Duncan Clark (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An engrossing, insider&#8217;s account of how a teacher built one of the world&#8217;s most valuable companies-rivaling Walmart and Amazon-and forever reshaped the global economy  In just a decade and a half, Jack Ma, a man from modest beginnings who started out as an English teacher, founded Alibaba and built it into one of the world&#8217;s largest companies, an e-commerce empire on which hundreds of millions of Chinese consumers depend. In 2014, Alibaba&#8217;s $25 billion IPO was the largest global IPO in history. A Rockefeller of his time, who is courted by CEOs and presidents around the world, Jack is an icon for China&#8217;s booming private sector and the gatekeeper to hundreds of millions of middle-class consumers. Duncan Clark first met Jack in 1999 in the small apartment where Jack founded Alibaba. Granted unprecedented access to a wealth of new material, including exclusive interviews, Clark draws on his own experience as an early adviser to Alibaba as well as his two decades in China chronicling the Internet&#8217;s impact on the country to create an authoritative, compelling narrative account of Alibaba&#8217;s rise.<br />
                    How did Jack overcome his humble origins and early failures to achieve massive success with Alibaba? How did he outsmart rival entrepreneurs from both China and Silicon Valley? Can Alibaba maintain its 80 percent market share? As it forges ahead into finance and entertainment, are there limits to Alibaba&#8217;s ambitions? How does the Chinese government view its rise? Will Alibaba expand farther overseas, including into the United States?  Clark tells Alibaba&#8217;s tale in the context of China&#8217;s momentous economic and social changes, illuminating an unlikely corporate titan as never before.  Advance Praise For Alibaba  &#8220;Anybody who thinks the Chinese just copy or steal technology from the West should read this book and think again. Jack Ma is part Bill Gates, part Steve Jobs, part Larry Page, part Sergey Brin, and part Mark Zuckerberg, all rolled into one.&#8221;-Sir Martin Sorrell, CEO of WPP &#8220;Duncan Clark gets into the heart and soul of Alibaba and its founder, Jack Ma, who deftly maneuvered through the discontinuities and barriers in China to create one of the greatest companies in the world. China has thrived under the leadership of Jack Ma.<br />
                    This book is a must-read for anyone who wants to understand the present China and the heartbeat of a great entrepreneur.&#8221;-Tim Draper, founder of Draper Associates, DFJ, and Draper University  &#8220;This book provides excellent insight into the world of Jack Ma, perhaps the most famous of the leaders of the new economy in China. Duncan Clark is a real China &#8216;Old Hand,&#8217; unique in his knowledge of the Jack Ma generation. This book is definitely on the short list for those who wish to understand the Chinese economy today.&#8221;-Ken Wilcox, Chairman Emeritus, Silicon Valley Bank</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/">Alibaba : The House That Jack Ma Built &#8211; Duncan Clark (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finding My Virginity : The New Autobiography &#8211; Sir Richard Branson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/finding-my-virginity-the-new-autobiography-sir-richard-branson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/finding-my-virginity-the-new-autobiography-sir-richard-branson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>PAPERBACK EDITION FULLY UPDATED WITH TWO NEW CHAPTERS After creating 12 different billion-dollar businesses and breaking dozens of world records, wouldn&#8217;t you think you&#8217;d done it all? Not Sir Richard Branson. Having brought the Virgin brand to all corners of the globe, he&#8217;s now reaching out to the stars as he prepares to launch commercial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-my-virginity-the-new-autobiography-sir-richard-branson-abridged/">Finding My Virginity : The New Autobiography &#8211; Sir Richard Branson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>PAPERBACK EDITION FULLY UPDATED WITH TWO NEW CHAPTERS    </p>
<p>                    After creating 12 different billion-dollar businesses and breaking dozens of world records, wouldn&#8217;t you think you&#8217;d done it all?    </p>
<p>                    Not Sir Richard Branson. Having brought the Virgin brand to all corners of the globe, he&#8217;s now reaching out to the stars as he prepares to launch commercial space travel with Virgin Galactic.    </p>
<p>                    In this non-stop memoir, Richard takes you inside his whirlwind life: from reinventing his companies in the midst of the financial crisis and devastating personal losses, to tackling the planet&#8217;s biggest challenges, to the joys of becoming a &#8216;grand-dude&#8217; at 64.Discover the irrepressible spirit, ingenious vision and relentless drive that has made Richard the ultimate entrepreneur.    </p>
<p>                    The iconoclastic Virgin founder is still changing the world. Next comes outer space.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-my-virginity-the-new-autobiography-sir-richard-branson-abridged/">Finding My Virginity : The New Autobiography &#8211; Sir Richard Branson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Disrupted : Ludicrous Misadventures in the Tech Start-up Bubble &#8211; Dan Lyons (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/disrupted-ludicrous-misadventures-in-the-tech-start-up-bubble-dan-lyons-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/disrupted-ludicrous-misadventures-in-the-tech-start-up-bubble-dan-lyons-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dan Lyons was Technology Editor at Newsweek Magazine for years, a magazine writer at the top of his profession. One Friday morning he received a phone call: his job no longer existed. Fifty years old and with a wife and two young kids, Dan was unemployed and facing financial oblivion. Then an idea hit. Dan [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disrupted-ludicrous-misadventures-in-the-tech-start-up-bubble-dan-lyons-abridged/">Disrupted : Ludicrous Misadventures in the Tech Start-up Bubble &#8211; Dan Lyons (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dan Lyons was Technology Editor at Newsweek Magazine for years, a magazine writer at the top of his profession. One Friday morning he received a phone call: his job no longer existed. Fifty years old and with a wife and two young kids, Dan was unemployed and facing financial oblivion. Then an idea hit. Dan had long reported on Silicon Valley and the tech explosion. Why not join it? HubSpot, a Boston start-up, was flush with $100 million in venture capital. They offered Dan a pile of stock options for the nebulous role of &#8220;marketing fellow.&#8221; What could possibly go wrong?     </p>
<p>                     What follows is a hilarious and excoriating account of Dan&#8217;s time at the start-up and a revealing window onto the dysfunctional culture that prevails in a world flush with cash and devoid of experience. Filled with stories of meaningless jargon, teddy bears at meetings, push-up competitions and all-night parties, this uproarious tale is also a trenchant analysis of the dysfunctional start-up world, a de facto conspiracy between those who start companies and those who fund them. It is a world where bad ideas are rewarded with hefty investments, where companies blow money lavishing perks on their post-collegiate workforces, and where everybody is trying to hang on just long enough to cash out with a fortune.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/disrupted-ludicrous-misadventures-in-the-tech-start-up-bubble-dan-lyons-abridged/">Disrupted : Ludicrous Misadventures in the Tech Start-up Bubble &#8211; Dan Lyons (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019    </p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review    </p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.    </p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.    </p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.    </p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*#GIRLBOSS NETFLIX ORIGINAL OUT NOW* In this New York Times bestselling sensation, founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal Sophia Amoruso shares her story and inspires women everywhere to join the #GIRLBOSS movement. &#8216;#GIRLBOSS is more than a book . . . #GIRLBOSS is a movement&#8217; Lena Dunham &#8216;A millennial alternative to Lean In&#8217; New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/">#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*#GIRLBOSS NETFLIX ORIGINAL OUT NOW*    </p>
<p>                    In this New York Times bestselling sensation, founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal Sophia Amoruso shares her story and inspires women everywhere to join the #GIRLBOSS movement.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;#GIRLBOSS is more than a book . . . #GIRLBOSS is a movement&#8217; Lena Dunham    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A millennial alternative to Lean In&#8217; New York Magazine    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compellingly motivational read&#8217; The Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The book you need in your life&#8217; Marie Claire     </p>
<p>                    *Winner of the 2014 Goodreads Choice Award for Best Business Book*    </p>
<p>                    In the space of ten years, Sophia Amoruso has gone from high-school dropout to founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal, one of the fastest-growing retailers in the world.     </p>
<p>                    Sophia&#8217;s never been a typical executive, or a typical anything, and she&#8217;s written #GIRLBOSS for other girls like her: outsiders (and insiders) seeking a unique path to success.    </p>
<p>                    Filled with brazen wake-up calls, cunning and frank observations, and behind-the-scenes stories from Nasty Gal&#8217;s meteoric rise, #GIRLBOSS covers a lot of ground. It proves that success doesn&#8217;t come from where you went to college or how popular you were in school. Success is about trusting your instincts and following your gut, knowing which rules to follow and which to break.    </p>
<p>                    Inspiring, motivating and empowering, #GIRLBOSS will give you the kick up the ass you need to reach your potential.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/">#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moore&#8217;s Law : The Life of Gordon Moore, Silicon Valley&#8217;s Quiet Revolutionary &#8211; Arnold Thackray, David Brock, Rachel Jones (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/moores-law-the-life-of-gordon-moore-silicon-valleys-quiet-revolutionary-arnold-thackray-david-brock-rachel-jones-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic Devices & Materials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transistors]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/moores-law-the-life-of-gordon-moore-silicon-valleys-quiet-revolutionary-arnold-thackray-david-brock-rachel-jones-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Our world today,from the phone in your pocket to the car that you drive, the allure of social media to the strategy of the Pentagon,has been shaped irrevocably by the technology of silicon transistors. Year after year, for half a century, these tiny switches have enabled ever-more startling capabilities. Their incredible proliferation has altered the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moores-law-the-life-of-gordon-moore-silicon-valleys-quiet-revolutionary-arnold-thackray-david-brock-rachel-jones-abridged/">Moore&#8217;s Law : The Life of Gordon Moore, Silicon Valley&#8217;s Quiet Revolutionary &#8211; Arnold Thackray, David Brock, Rachel Jones (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Our world today,from the phone in your pocket to the car that you drive, the allure of social media to the strategy of the Pentagon,has been shaped irrevocably by the technology of silicon transistors. Year after year, for half a century, these tiny switches have enabled ever-more startling capabilities. Their incredible proliferation has altered the course of human history as dramatically as any political or social revolution. At the heart of it all has been one quiet Californian: Gordon Moore.At Fairchild Semiconductor, his seminal Silicon Valley startup, Moore,a young chemist turned electronics entrepreneur,had the defining insight: silicon transistors, and microchips made of them, could make electronics profoundly cheap and immensely powerful. Microchips could double in power, then redouble again in clockwork fashion. History has borne out this insight, which we now call  Moore&#8217;s Law&#8221;, and Moore himself, having recognized it, worked endlessly to realize his vision. With Moore&#8217;s technological leadership at Fairchild and then at his second start-up, the Intel Corporation, the law has held for fifty years. The result is profound: from the days of enormous, clunky computers of limited capability to our new era, in which computers are placed everywhere from inside of our bodies to the surface of Mars.Moore led nothing short of a revolution. In  Moore&#8217;s Law , Arnold Thackray, David C. Brock, and Rachel Jones give the authoritative account of Gordon Moore&#8217;s life and his role in the development both of Silicon Valley and the transformative technologies developed there. Told by a team of writers with unparalleled access to Moore, his family, and his contemporaries, this is the human story of man and a career that have had almost superhuman effects. The history of twentieth-century technology is littered with overblown  revolutions.&#8221;  Moore&#8217;s Law  is essential reading for anyone seeking to learn what a real revolution looks like.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moores-law-the-life-of-gordon-moore-silicon-valleys-quiet-revolutionary-arnold-thackray-david-brock-rachel-jones-abridged/">Moore&#8217;s Law : The Life of Gordon Moore, Silicon Valley&#8217;s Quiet Revolutionary &#8211; Arnold Thackray, David Brock, Rachel Jones (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film The Wolf of Wall Street is about the finance industry&#8217;s greediest adults, Kevin Roose&#8217;s Young Money is a look at those wolves as cubs&#8217; Amazon.com &#8216;Best Book of the Month&#8217; Every year, thousands of eager graduates are hired by the world&#8217;s financial giants, where they&#8217;re taught the secrets of making obscene [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/">Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film The Wolf of Wall Street is about the finance industry&#8217;s greediest adults, Kevin Roose&#8217;s Young Money is a look at those wolves as cubs&#8217; Amazon.com &#8216;Best Book of the Month&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Every year, thousands of eager graduates are hired by the world&#8217;s financial giants, where they&#8217;re taught the secrets of making obscene amounts of money &#8212; as well as how to dress, talk, date, drink, and schmooze like real financiers. Young Money is the exclusive, inside story of this well-guarded world.<br />
                    Investigative reporter Kevin Roose shadows eight rookies as they are exposed to the exhausting workloads, huge bonuses, and recreational drugs that have always characterized Wall Street life. But they experience something new, too: an industry forever changed by the massive financial collapse of 2008. And as they get their Wall Street educations, they face hard questions about morality, prestige, and the value of their work.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A great new read that doubles as a post-crash update to Michael Lewis&#8217; Liar&#8217;s Poker &#8211; Mother Jones    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fun fast read that will make you laugh out loud&#8217; Fortune Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/">Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marissa Mayer and the Fight to Save Yahoo! &#8211; Nicholas Carlson, Read by Kiff Vandenheuvel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/marissa-mayer-and-the-fight-to-save-yahoo-nicholas-carlson-read-by-kiff-vandenheuvel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/marissa-mayer-and-the-fight-to-save-yahoo-nicholas-carlson-read-by-kiff-vandenheuvel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A page-turning warts-and-all narrative about Marissa Mayer&#8217;s efforts to remake Yahoo as well as her own rise from Stanford University undergrad to CEO of a $30 billion corporation by the age of thirty-eight. When Yahoo hired star Google executive Marissa Mayer to be its CEO in 2012, employees rejoiced. They put posters on the walls [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/marissa-mayer-and-the-fight-to-save-yahoo-nicholas-carlson-read-by-kiff-vandenheuvel-abridged/">Marissa Mayer and the Fight to Save Yahoo! &#8211; Nicholas Carlson, Read by Kiff Vandenheuvel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A page-turning warts-and-all narrative about Marissa Mayer&#8217;s efforts to remake Yahoo as well as her own rise from Stanford University undergrad to CEO of a $30 billion corporation by the age of thirty-eight.    </p>
<p>                    When Yahoo hired star Google executive Marissa Mayer to be its CEO in 2012, employees rejoiced. They put posters on the walls throughout Yahoo&#8217;s California headquarters. On them was Mayer&#8217;s face and one word: hope.    </p>
<p>                    Just over a year later-on November 4, 2013-Mayer sat in front of those same employees in a huge cafeteria on Yahoo&#8217;s campus and took the beating of her life. Her hair wet and her tone defensive, Mayer read and answered a series of employee-posed questions challenging the basic elements of her plan. There was anger in the room; and behind it, a question: Was Mayer actually going to be able to do this thing?    </p>
<p>                    Nicholas Carlson&#8217;s fast-paced narrative is the inside story of Mayer&#8217;s controversial rise at Google, her desperate fight to save an Internet icon, and how Yahoo got into such awful shape in the first place.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/marissa-mayer-and-the-fight-to-save-yahoo-nicholas-carlson-read-by-kiff-vandenheuvel-abridged/">Marissa Mayer and the Fight to Save Yahoo! &#8211; Nicholas Carlson, Read by Kiff Vandenheuvel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The captivating, inside story of the woman who helmed the Washington Post during one of the most turbulent periods in the history of American media. Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Biography In this bestselling and widely acclaimed memoir, Katharine Graham, the woman who piloted the Washington Post through the scandals of the Pentagon Papers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/">Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The captivating, inside story of the woman who helmed the Washington Post during one of the most turbulent periods in the history of American media.     </p>
<p>                    Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Biography    </p>
<p>                    In this bestselling and widely acclaimed memoir, Katharine Graham, the woman who piloted the Washington Post through the scandals of the Pentagon Papers and Watergate, tells her story&#8211;one that is extraordinary both for the events it encompasses and for the courage, candor, and dignity of its telling.     </p>
<p>                     Here is the awkward child who grew up amid material wealth and emotional isolation; the young bride who watched her brilliant, charismatic husband&#8211;a confidant to John F. Kennedy and Lyndon Johnson&#8211;plunge into the mental illness that would culminate in his suicide. And here is the widow who shook off her grief and insecurity to take on a president and a pressman&#8217;s union as she entered the profane boys&#8217; club of the newspaper business.     </p>
<p>                     As timely now as ever, Personal History is an exemplary record of our history and of the woman who played such a shaping role within them, discovering her own strength and sense of self as she confronted&#8211;and mastered&#8211;the personal and professional crises of her fascinating life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/">Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Education of a Value Investor : My Transformative Quest for Wealth, Wisdom, and Enlightenment &#8211; Guy Spier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-education-of-a-value-investor-my-transformative-quest-for-wealth-wisdom-and-enlightenment-guy-spier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-education-of-a-value-investor-my-transformative-quest-for-wealth-wisdom-and-enlightenment-guy-spier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What happens when a young Wall Street investment banker spends a small fortune to have lunch with Warren Buffett? He becomes a real value investor. In this fascinating inside story, Guy Spier details his career from Harvard MBA to hedge fund manager. But the path was not so straightforward. Spier reveals his transformation from a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-a-value-investor-my-transformative-quest-for-wealth-wisdom-and-enlightenment-guy-spier-abridged/">The Education of a Value Investor : My Transformative Quest for Wealth, Wisdom, and Enlightenment &#8211; Guy Spier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What happens when a young Wall Street investment banker spends a small fortune to have lunch with Warren Buffett? He becomes a real value investor. In this fascinating inside story, Guy Spier details his career from Harvard MBA to hedge fund manager. But the path was not so straightforward. Spier reveals his transformation from a Gordon Gekko wannabe, driven by greed, to a sophisticated investor who enjoys success without selling his soul to the highest bidder. Spier&#8217;s journey is similar to the thousands that flock to Wall Street every year with their shiny new diplomas, aiming to be King of Wall Street. Yet what Guy realized just in the nick of time was that the King really lived 1,500 miles away in Omaha, Nebraska. Spier determinedly set out to create a new career in his own way. Along the way he learned some powerful lessons which include: why the right mentors and partners are critical to long term success on Wall Street; why a topnotch education can sometimes get in the way of your success; that real learning doesn&#8217;t begin until you are on your own; and how the best lessons from Warren Buffett have less to do with investing and more to do with being true to yourself.<br />
                    Spier also reveals some of his own winning investment strategies, detailing deals that were winners but also what he learned from deals that went south. Part memoir, part Wall Street advice, and part how-to, Guy Spier takes readers on a ride through Wall Street but more importantly provides those that want to take a different path with the insight, guidance, and inspiration they need to carve out their own definition of success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-a-value-investor-my-transformative-quest-for-wealth-wisdom-and-enlightenment-guy-spier-abridged/">The Education of a Value Investor : My Transformative Quest for Wealth, Wisdom, and Enlightenment &#8211; Guy Spier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lincoln On Leadership &#8211; Donald T. Phillips (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lincoln-on-leadership-donald-t-phillips-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lincoln-on-leadership-donald-t-phillips-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lincoln on Leadership is the first book to examine Abraham Lincoln&#8217;s diverse leadership abilities and how they can be applied to today&#8217;s complex world. You think you have it rough? Only ten days before Abraham Lincoln took the oath of office in 1861, the Confederate States of America seceded from the Union, taking all Federal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lincoln-on-leadership-donald-t-phillips-abridged/">Lincoln On Leadership &#8211; Donald T. Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lincoln on Leadership is the first book to examine Abraham Lincoln&#8217;s diverse leadership abilities and how they can be applied to today&#8217;s complex world.    </p>
<p>                    You think you have it rough?     </p>
<p>                    Only ten days before Abraham Lincoln took the oath of office in 1861, the Confederate States of America seceded from the Union, taking all Federal agencies, forts, and arenas within their territory. To make matters worse, Lincoln, who was elected by a minority of the popular vote, was thought of by his own advisors as nothing more than a gawky second-rate country lawyer with no leadership experience.     </p>
<p>                    What Lincoln did to become our most honored and revered president is history; now his wisdom and leadership philosophy can help you run your business. In Lincoln on Leadership you&#8217;ll discover why you should:<br />
                    Seize the initiative and never relinquish it.Wage only one war at a time.Avoid issuing order and instead request, imply, or make suggestions.Once in a while, let things slip, unbeknownst-like&#8230; and much much more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lincoln-on-leadership-donald-t-phillips-abridged/">Lincoln On Leadership &#8211; Donald T. Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>We Are the Nerds : The Birth and Tumultuous Life of REDDIT, the Internet&#8217;s Culture Laboratory &#8211; Christine Lagorio-Chafkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A gripping read&#8217; Adam Grant, bestselling author of Originals Reddit hails itself as &#8216;the front page of the Internet&#8217;. It&#8217;s the sixth most-visited website in the world &#8211; and yet, millions have no idea what it is. They should be paying attention. This definitive account of the birth and life of Reddit is perfect for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/">We Are the Nerds : The Birth and Tumultuous Life of REDDIT, the Internet&#8217;s Culture Laboratory &#8211; Christine Lagorio-Chafkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A gripping read&#8217; Adam Grant, bestselling author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    Reddit hails itself as &#8216;the front page of the Internet&#8217;. It&#8217;s the sixth most-visited website in the world &#8211; and yet, millions have no idea what it is. They should be paying attention.    </p>
<p>                    This definitive account of the birth and life of Reddit is perfect for readers of The Everything Store, Googled and The Facebook Effect.    </p>
<p>                    We Are the Nerds takes readers inside this captivating, maddening enterprise, whose army of obsessed users have been credited with everything from solving crimes and spurring millions in charitable donations to seeding alt-right fury and even landing Donald Trump in the White House. Reddit has become a mirror of the Internet itself: It has dark trenches, shiny memes, malicious trolls, and a heart-warming ability to connect people across cultures, oceans, and ideological divides.    </p>
<p>                    This is the gripping story of how Reddit&#8217;s founders, Steve Huffman and Alexis Ohanian, transformed themselves from student video-gamers into Silicon Valley millionaires as they turned their creation into an icon of the digital age. But the journey was often fraught. Reporting on Reddit for more than six years, conducting hundreds of interviews and gaining exclusive access to its founders, Christine Lagorio-Chafkin has written the definitive account of the birth and life of Reddit. Packed with revelatory details about its biggest triumphs and controversies, this inside look at Reddit includes fresh insights on the relationship between Huffman and Ohanian, staff turmoil, the tragic life of Aaron Swartz, and Reddit&#8217;s struggle to become profitable.    </p>
<p>                    In a time when we are increasingly concerned about privacy and manipulation on social platforms, We Are the Nerds reveals Reddit&#8217;s central role in the dissemination of culture and information in history&#8217;s first fully digital century. Rigorously reported and highly entertaining, We Are the Nerds explores how this unique platform has changed the way we all communicate today.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR THE BOOK:    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Incisive, witty and brilliantly written&#8217; &#8211; Emily Chang, bestselling author of Brotopia    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A triumph &#8211; a business book that reads like a page-turning novel&#8217; &#8211; James Ledbetter, author of One Nation Under Gold    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The best, grittiest, most accurate book yet about what it&#8217;s like to build a startup and a community from scratch&#8217; &#8211; John Zeratsky, bestselling author of Sprint and Make Time    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A gripping, entertaining book that is a must-read for every entrepreneur&#8217; &#8211; Daymond John, bestselling author of Rise and Grind    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Too many books on tech feel like they have been Googled together; Lagorio-Chafkin&#8217;s is rich in original reportage&#8217; &#8211; TLS</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/we-are-the-nerds-the-birth-and-tumultuous-life-of-reddit-the-internets-culture-laboratory-christine-lagorio-chafkin-abridged/">We Are the Nerds : The Birth and Tumultuous Life of REDDIT, the Internet&#8217;s Culture Laboratory &#8211; Christine Lagorio-Chafkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hit Refresh : A Memoir by Microsoft&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Satya Nadella (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hit-refresh-a-memoir-by-microsofts-ceo-satya-nadella-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hit-refresh-a-memoir-by-microsofts-ceo-satya-nadella-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Quest to Rediscover Microsoft&#8217;s Soul and Imagine a Better Future for Everyone Microsoft&#8217;s CEO tells the inside story of the company&#8217;s continuing transformation, while tracing his own journey from a childhood in India to leading some of the most significant changes of the digital era. LONGLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hit-refresh-a-memoir-by-microsofts-ceo-satya-nadella-abridged/">Hit Refresh : A Memoir by Microsoft&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Satya Nadella (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Quest to Rediscover Microsoft&#8217;s Soul and Imagine a Better Future for Everyone    </p>
<p>                                Microsoft&#8217;s CEO tells the inside story of the company&#8217;s continuing transformation, while tracing his own journey from a childhood in India to leading some of the most significant changes of the digital era.    </p>
<p>                                LONGLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD    </p>
<p>                              Satya Nadella grew up in India, studied in the US and went on to become Microsoft&#8217;s third CEO after Bill Gates and Steve Ballmer. In Hit Refresh he offers a unique view of the transformation happening inside one of the world&#8217;s most iconic tech companies, and the arrival of the most exciting and disruptive wave of technology humankind has experienced &#8211; including artificial intelligence, mixed reality, and quantum computing.    </p>
<p>                              Nadella examines how people, organisations and societies can and must transform &#8211; &#8216;hit refresh&#8217; &#8211; in their persistent quest for new energy, new ideas, and continued relevance and renewal. Yet at its core, this book is about humans, and how one of our essential qualities &#8211; empathy &#8211; will become ever more valuable in a world where technological advancement will alter the status quo as never before.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hit-refresh-a-memoir-by-microsofts-ceo-satya-nadella-abridged/">Hit Refresh : A Memoir by Microsoft&#8217;s CEO &#8211; Satya Nadella (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antiques & Collectables: Books, Manuscripts, Ephemera & Printed Matter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On the death of France&#8217;s most glorious king, Louis XIV, in 1715, few people benefited from the shift in power more than the intriguing financial genius from Edinburgh, John Law. Already notorious for killing a man in a duel and for acquiring a huge fortune from gambling, Law had proposed to the English monarch that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/">Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the death of France&#8217;s most glorious king, Louis XIV, in 1715, few people benefited from the shift in power more than the intriguing financial genius from Edinburgh, John Law. Already notorious for killing a man in a duel and for acquiring a huge fortune from gambling, Law had proposed to the English monarch that a bank be established to issue paper money with the credit based on the value of land. But Queen Anne was not about to take advice from a gambler and felon. So, in exile in Paris, he convinced the bankrupt court of Louis XV of the value of his idea.<br />
                     Law soon engineered the revival of the French economy and found himself one of the most powerful men in Europe. In August 1717, he founded the Mississippi Company, and the Court granted him the right to trade in France&#8217;s vast territory in America. The shareholders in his new trading company made such enormous profits that the term millionaire was coined to describe them. Paris was soon in a frenzy of speculation, conspiracies, and insatiable consumption. Before this first boom-and-bust cycle was complete, markets throughout Europe crashed, the mob began calling for Law&#8217;s head, and his visionary ideas about what money could do were abandoned and forgotten.<br />
                     In Millionaire,  Janet Gleeson lucidly reconstructs this epic drama where fortunes were made and lost, paupers grew rich, and lords fell into penury &#8212; and a modern fiscal philosophy was born. Her enthralling tragicomic tale reveals two great characters: John Law, with his complex personality and inscrutable motives, and money itself, whose true nature even to this day remains elusive</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/">Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Snowball : Warren Buffett and the Business of Life &#8211; Alice Schroeder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-snowball-warren-buffett-and-the-business-of-life-alice-schroeder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-snowball-warren-buffett-and-the-business-of-life-alice-schroeder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Recounting the life and times of one of the most respected men in the world, The Snowball is the most fascinating financial success story of our time. Warren Buffett, the legendary Omaha investor has never written a memoir, but finally has given Alice Schroeder unprecedented access to him and all those closest to his work, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-snowball-warren-buffett-and-the-business-of-life-alice-schroeder-abridged/">The Snowball : Warren Buffett and the Business of Life &#8211; Alice Schroeder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recounting the life and times of one of the most respected men in the world, The Snowball is the most fascinating financial success story of our time. Warren Buffett, the legendary Omaha investor has never written a memoir, but finally has given Alice Schroeder unprecedented access to him and all those closest to his work, opinions, struggles, triumphs, follies and wisdom. The result is this personally revealing and complete biography of &#8216;The Oracle of Omaha&#8217;, indispensable reading for those who wish to know the man behind the outstanding achievements.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-snowball-warren-buffett-and-the-business-of-life-alice-schroeder-abridged/">The Snowball : Warren Buffett and the Business of Life &#8211; Alice Schroeder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Becoming Steve Jobs : The evolution of a reckless upstart into a visionary leader &#8211; Brent Schlender, Rick Tetzeli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/becoming-steve-jobs-the-evolution-of-a-reckless-upstart-into-a-visionary-leader-brent-schlender-rick-tetzeli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macintosh]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/becoming-steve-jobs-the-evolution-of-a-reckless-upstart-into-a-visionary-leader-brent-schlender-rick-tetzeli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES AND #1 INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; with a new foreword by Silicon Valley legend Marc Andreessen. &#8216;For my money, a better book about Jobs than Walter Isaacson&#8217;s biography&#8217; New Yorker &#8216;A fascinating reinterpretation of the Steve Jobs story&#8217; Sunday Times We all think we know who Steve Jobs was, what made him tick, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-steve-jobs-the-evolution-of-a-reckless-upstart-into-a-visionary-leader-brent-schlender-rick-tetzeli-abridged/">Becoming Steve Jobs : The evolution of a reckless upstart into a visionary leader &#8211; Brent Schlender, Rick Tetzeli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES AND #1 INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; with a new foreword by Silicon Valley legend Marc Andreessen.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;For my money, a better book about Jobs than Walter Isaacson&#8217;s biography&#8217; New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fascinating reinterpretation of the Steve Jobs story&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    We all think we know who Steve Jobs was, what made him tick, and what made him succeed.     </p>
<p>                    Yet the single most important question about him has never been answered.     </p>
<p>                    The young, impulsive, egotistical genius was ousted in the mid-80s from the company he founded, exiled from his own kingdom and cast into the wilderness. Yet he returned a decade later to transform the ailing Apple into the most successful company the world had ever seen.     </p>
<p>                    How did this reckless upstart transform himself into a visionary business leader?     </p>
<p>                    The first comprehensive study of Jobs&#8217; career following his dismissal from Apple, written with unparalleled access and insight, BECOMING STEVE JOBS offers a startling new portrait of the most important business figure in modern history. The most intimate biography yet of Jobs, written by the journalist who knew him better than any other, BECOMING STEVE JOBS draws on recently discovered interviews that have never before seen the light of day, and answers for the first time the most pressing questions about what made this legendary business leader such a success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-steve-jobs-the-evolution-of-a-reckless-upstart-into-a-visionary-leader-brent-schlender-rick-tetzeli-abridged/">Becoming Steve Jobs : The evolution of a reckless upstart into a visionary leader &#8211; Brent Schlender, Rick Tetzeli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019 _____________________________ The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the best business books I&#8217;ve read in years.&#8217; BILL GATES<br />
                    THE #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    A SUNDAY TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR 2019<br />
                    _____________________________    </p>
<p>                    The CEO of Disney, one of Time&#8217;s most influential people of 2019, shares the ideas and values he embraced to reinvent one of the most beloved companies in the world and inspire the people who bring the magic to life.     </p>
<p>                    Robert Iger became CEO of The Walt Disney Company in 2005, during a difficult time. Morale had deteriorated, competition was intense, and technology was changing faster than at any time in the company&#8217;s history. His vision came down to three clear ideas: Recommit to the concept that quality matters, embrace technology instead of fighting it, and think bigger-think global-and turn Disney into a stronger brand in international markets.     </p>
<p>                    Fourteen years later, Disney is the largest, most respected media company in the world, counting Pixar, Marvel, Lucasfilm and 21st Century Fox among its properties. Its value is nearly five times what it was when Iger took over, and he is recognized as one of the most innovative and successful CEOs of our era.    </p>
<p>                    In The Ride of a Lifetime, Robert Iger shares the lessons he&#8217;s learned while running Disney and leading its 200,000 employees, and he explores the principles that are necessary for true leadership, including:    </p>
<p>                     Optimism. Even in the face of difficulty, an optimistic leader will find the path toward the best possible outcome and focus on that, rather than give in to pessimism and blaming.<br />
                     Courage. Leaders have to be willing to take risks and place big bets. Fear of failure destroys creativity.<br />
                     Decisiveness. All decisions, no matter how difficult, can be made on a timely basis. Indecisiveness is both wasteful and destructive to morale.<br />
                     Fairness. Treat people decently, with empathy, and be accessible to them.     </p>
<p>                    This book is about the relentless curiosity that has driven Iger for forty-five years, since the day he started as the lowliest studio grunt at ABC. It&#8217;s also about thoughtfulness and respect, and a decency-over-dollars approach that has become the bedrock of every project and partnership Iger pursues, from a deep friendship with Steve Jobs in his final years to an abiding love of the Star Wars mythology.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The ideas in this book strike me as universal&#8221; Iger writes. &#8220;Not just to the aspiring CEOs of the world, but to anyone wanting to feel less fearful, more confidently themselves, as they navigate their professional and even personal lives.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ride-of-a-lifetime-lessons-in-creative-leadership-from-15-years-as-ceo-of-the-walt-disney-company-robert-iger-abridged/">The Ride of a Lifetime : Lessons in Creative Leadership from 15 Years as CEO of the Walt Disney Company &#8211; Robert Iger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Making Of Donald Trump &#8211; David Cay Johnston (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-making-of-donald-trump-david-cay-johnston-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-making-of-donald-trump-david-cay-johnston-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER that first revealed the Russia connection The culmination of nearly 30 years of reporting on Donald Trump, this in-depth report by Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter David Cay Johnston takes a revealingly close look at the mogul&#8217;s rise to prominence &#8212; and, now, ultimate power Covering the long arc of Trump&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-making-of-donald-trump-david-cay-johnston-abridged/">The Making Of Donald Trump &#8211; David Cay Johnston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER that first revealed the Russia connection The culmination of nearly 30 years of reporting on Donald Trump, this in-depth report by Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter David Cay Johnston takes a revealingly close look at the mogul&#8217;s rise to prominence &#8212; and, now, ultimate power  Covering the long arc of Trump&#8217;s career, Johnston tells the full story of how a boy from a quiet section of Queens, NY would become an entirely new, and complex, breed of public figure. Trump is a man of great media savvy, entrepreneurial spirit, and political clout. Yet his career has been plagued by legal troubles and mounting controversy.  From the origins of his family&#8217;s fortune, to his own too-big-to-fail business empire; from his education and early career, to his whirlwind and ultimately successful presidential bid, The Making of Donald Trump provides the fullest picture yet of Trump&#8217;s extraordinary ascendency. Love him or hate him, Trump&#8217;s massive influence is undeniable, and figures as diverse as Woody Guthrie (who wrote a scathing song about Trump&#8217;s father) and Red Scare prosecutor Roy Cohn, mob bosses and high rollers, as well as the average American voter, have all been pulled into his orbit.  Drawing on decades of interviews, financial records, court documents, and public statements, David Cay Johnston, who has covered Trump longer and more closely than any other journalist working today, gives us the most in-depth look yet at the man who has shocked the world. &#8220;Provides useful, vigorously reported overviews of Mr. Trump&#8217;s life and career &#8230; Mr. Johnston, who has followed the real estate impresario for nearly three decades, offers a searing indictment of his business practices and creative accounting.&#8221;&#8211;Michiko Kakutani, The New York Times &#8220;David Cay Johnston has given us this year&#8217;s must-read Trump book.&#8221;&#8211;Lawrence O&#8217;Donnell, MSNBC&#8217;s The Last Word &#8220;Johnston devastatingly covers ground he broke open as a reporter on the Trump beat in Philadelphia and at The New York Times&#8230;The best of investigative reporting is brought to bear on a man who could potentially lead the free world.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today &#8220;Carefully fleshes out the details of Trump&#8217;s known biography&#8230;with solid documentation.&#8221;&#8211;Tampa Bay Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-making-of-donald-trump-david-cay-johnston-abridged/">The Making Of Donald Trump &#8211; David Cay Johnston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commodities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jim Paul&#8217;s meteoric rise took him from a small town in Northern Kentucky to governor of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, yet he lost it all-his fortune, his reputation, and his job-in one fatal attack of excessive economic hubris. In this honest, frank analysis, Paul and Brendan Moynihan revisit the events that led to Paul&#8217;s disastrous [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/">What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jim Paul&#8217;s meteoric rise took him from a small town in Northern Kentucky to governor of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, yet he lost it all-his fortune, his reputation, and his job-in one fatal attack of excessive economic hubris. In this honest, frank analysis, Paul and Brendan Moynihan revisit the events that led to Paul&#8217;s disastrous decision and examine the psychological factors behind bad financial practices in several economic sectors.  This book-winner of a 2014 Axiom Business Book award gold medal-begins with the unbroken string of successes that helped Paul achieve a jet-setting lifestyle and land a key spot with the Chicago Mercantile Exchange. It then describes the circumstances leading up to Paul&#8217;s $1.6 million loss and the essential lessons he learned from it-primarily that, although there are as many ways to make money in the markets as there are people participating in them, all losses come from the same few sources. Investors lose money in the markets either because of errors in their analysis or because of psychological barriers preventing the application of analysis.<br />
                    While all analytical methods have some validity and make allowances for instances in which they do not work, psychological factors can keep an investor in a losing position, causing him to abandon one method for another in order to rationalize the decisions already made. Paul and Moynihan&#8217;s cautionary tale includes strategies for avoiding loss tied to a simple framework for understanding, accepting, and dodging the dangers of investing, trading, and speculating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/">What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Losing My Virginity : How I Survived, Had Fun, and Made a Fortune Doing Business My Way &#8211; Richard Branson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/losing-my-virginity-how-i-survived-had-fun-and-made-a-fortune-doing-business-my-way-richard-branson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/losing-my-virginity-how-i-survived-had-fun-and-made-a-fortune-doing-business-my-way-richard-branson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The unusual, frequently outrageous autobiography of one of the great business geniuses of our time, Richard Branson. In little more than twenty-five years, Richard Branson spawned nearly a hundred successful ventures. From the airline business (Virgin Atlantic Airways), to music (Virgin Records and V2), to cola (Virgin Cola), and others ranging from financial services to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/losing-my-virginity-how-i-survived-had-fun-and-made-a-fortune-doing-business-my-way-richard-branson-abridged/">Losing My Virginity : How I Survived, Had Fun, and Made a Fortune Doing Business My Way &#8211; Richard Branson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The unusual, frequently outrageous autobiography of one of the great business geniuses of our time, Richard Branson.     </p>
<p>                    In little more than twenty-five years, Richard Branson spawned nearly a hundred successful ventures. From the airline business (Virgin Atlantic Airways), to music (Virgin Records and V2), to cola (Virgin Cola), and others ranging from financial services to bridal wear, Branson has a track record second to none. Many of his companies were started in the face of entrenched competition. The experts said, Don&#8217;t do it. But Branson found golden opportunities in markets in which customers have been ripped off or underserved, where confusion reigns, and the competition is complacent.     </p>
<p>                    In this stressed-out, overworked age, Richard Branson gives us a new model: a dynamic, hardworking, successful entrepreneur who lives life to the fullest. Branson has written his own rules for success, creating a group of companies with a global presence, but no central headquarters, no management hierarchy, and minimal bureaucracy. Family, friends, fun, and adventure are equally important as business in his life. Losing My Virginity is a portrait of a productive, sane, balanced life, filled with rich and colorful stories, including:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Crash-landing his hot-air balloon in the Algerian desert, yet remaining determined to have another go at being the first to circle the globe     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Signing the Sex Pistols, Janet Jackson, the Rolling Stones, Boy George, and Phil Collins     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Fighting back when British Airways took on Virgin Atlantic and successfully suing this pillar of the British business establishment     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Swimming two miles to safety during a violent storm off the coast of Mexico     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Staging a rescue flight into Baghdad before the start of the Gulf War     </p>
<p>                    And much more. Losing My Virginity is the ultimate tale of personal and business survival from a man who combines the business prowess of Bill Gates and the promotional instincts of P. T. Barnum.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/losing-my-virginity-how-i-survived-had-fun-and-made-a-fortune-doing-business-my-way-richard-branson-abridged/">Losing My Virginity : How I Survived, Had Fun, and Made a Fortune Doing Business My Way &#8211; Richard Branson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
