<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Computer Networking &amp; Communications Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/computer-networking-communications/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/computer-networking-communications/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Computer Networking &amp; Communications Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/computer-networking-communications/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Art of Social Media : Power Tips for Power Users &#8211; Guy Kawasaki, Peg Fitzpatrick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-social-media-power-tips-for-power-users-guy-kawasaki-peg-fitzpatrick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-social-media-power-tips-for-power-users-guy-kawasaki-peg-fitzpatrick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Guy Kawasaki, the bestselling author of The Art of the Start and Enchantment, The Art of Social Media is a no-nonsense guide to becoming a social media superstar. By now it&#8217;s clear that whether you&#8217;re promoting a business, a product, or yourself, social media is near the top of what will determine your success [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-social-media-power-tips-for-power-users-guy-kawasaki-peg-fitzpatrick-abridged/">The Art of Social Media : Power Tips for Power Users &#8211; Guy Kawasaki, Peg Fitzpatrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Guy Kawasaki, the bestselling author of The Art of the Start and Enchantment, The Art of Social Media is a no-nonsense guide to becoming a social media superstar.    </p>
<p>                    By now it&#8217;s clear that whether you&#8217;re promoting a business, a product, or yourself, social media is near the top of what will determine your success or failure. And there are countless pundits, authors, and consultants eager to advise you.    </p>
<p>                    But there&#8217;s no one quite like Guy Kawasaki, the legendary former chief evangelist for Apple and one of the pioneers of business blogging, tweeting, facebooking, tumbling, and much, much more. Now Guy has teamed up with his Canva colleague Peg Fitzpatrick to offer The Art of Social Media &#8211; the one essential guide you need to get the most bang for your time, effort, and money.    </p>
<p>                    With more than 100 practical tips, tricks, and insights, Guy and Peg present a ground-up strategy to produce a focused, thorough, and compelling presence on the most popular social-media platforms. They guide you through the steps of building your foundation, amassing your digital assets, going to market, optimizing your profile, attracting more followers, and effectively integrating social media and blogging.    </p>
<p>                    For beginners overwhelmed by too many choices, as well as seasoned professionals eager to improve their game, The Art of Social Media is full of tactics that have been proven to work in the real world. Or as Guy puts it, &#8220;Great Stuff, No Fluff.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Guy Kawasaki, who helped make Macintosh a household name, now runs Garage Technology Ventures, a venture-capital firm. He has held his workshop, &#8220;Boot Camp for Start-ups,&#8221; around the world. Kawasaki is the author of seven previous books, including Art of the Start, Enchantment and Rules for Revolutionaries.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-social-media-power-tips-for-power-users-guy-kawasaki-peg-fitzpatrick-abridged/">The Art of Social Media : Power Tips for Power Users &#8211; Guy Kawasaki, Peg Fitzpatrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Social Engineering : The Science of Human Hacking &#8211; Christopher Hadnagy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/social-engineering-the-science-of-human-hacking-christopher-hadnagy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Network Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Privacy & Data Protection]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/social-engineering-the-science-of-human-hacking-christopher-hadnagy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Harden the human firewall against the most current threats Social Engineering: The Science of Human Hacking reveals the craftier side of the hacker&#8217;s repertoire-why hack into something when you could just ask for access? Undetectable by firewalls and antivirus software, social engineering relies on human fault to gain access to sensitive spaces; in this book, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-engineering-the-science-of-human-hacking-christopher-hadnagy-abridged/">Social Engineering : The Science of Human Hacking &#8211; Christopher Hadnagy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Harden the human firewall against the most current threats    </p>
<p>                     Social Engineering: The Science of Human Hacking reveals the craftier side of the hacker&#8217;s repertoire-why hack into something when you could just ask for access? Undetectable by firewalls and antivirus software, social engineering relies on human fault to gain access to sensitive spaces; in this book, renowned expert Christopher Hadnagy explains the most commonly-used techniques that fool even the most robust security personnel, and shows you how these techniques have been used in the past. The way that we make decisions as humans affects everything from our emotions to our security. Hackers, since the beginning of time, have figured out ways to exploit that decision making process and get you to take an action not in your best interest. This new Second Edition has been updated with the most current methods used by sharing stories, examples, and scientific study behind how those decisions are exploited.    </p>
<p>                     Networks and systems can be hacked, but they can also be protected; when the &#8220;system&#8221; in question is a human being, there is no software to fall back on, no hardware upgrade, no code that can lock information down indefinitely. Human nature and emotion is the secret weapon of the malicious social engineering, and this book shows you how to recognize, predict, and prevent this type of manipulation by taking you inside the social engineer&#8217;s bag of tricks.    </p>
<p>                    Examine the most common social engineering tricks used to gain access<br />
                    Discover which popular techniques generally don&#8217;t work in the real world<br />
                    Examine how our understanding of the science behind emotions and decisions can be used by social engineers<br />
                    Learn how social engineering factors into some of the biggest recent headlines<br />
                    Learn how to use these skills as a professional social engineer and secure your company    </p>
<p>                    Adopt effective counter-measures to keep hackers at bay    </p>
<p>                     By working from the social engineer&#8217;s playbook, you gain the advantage of foresight that can help you protect yourself and others from even their best efforts. Social Engineering gives you the inside information you need to mount an unshakeable defense.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-engineering-the-science-of-human-hacking-christopher-hadnagy-abridged/">Social Engineering : The Science of Human Hacking &#8211; Christopher Hadnagy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Heffernan &#8220;melds the personal with the increasingly universal in a highly informative analysis of what the Internet is-and can be. A thoroughly engrossing examination of the Internet&#8217;s past, present, and future&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review) from one of the best living writers of English prose. This book makes a bold claim: The Internet is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/">Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Heffernan &#8220;melds the personal with the increasingly universal in a highly informative analysis of what the Internet is-and can be. A thoroughly engrossing examination of the Internet&#8217;s past, present, and future&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review) from one of the best living writers of English prose.    </p>
<p>                    This book makes a bold claim: The Internet is among mankind&#8217;s great masterpieces-a massive work of art. As an idea, it rivals monotheism. But its cultural potential and its societal impact often elude us. In this deep and thoughtful book, Virginia Heffernan reveals the logic and aesthetics behind the Internet, just as Susan Sontag did for photography and Marshall McLuhan did for television.    </p>
<p>                    Life online, in the highly visual, social, portable, and global incarnation rewards certain virtues. The new medium favors speed, accuracy, wit, prolificacy, and versatility, and its form and functions are changing how we perceive, experience, and understand the world. In &#8220;sumptuous writing, saturated with observations that are simultaneously personal, cultural, and strikingly original&#8221; (The New Republic), Heffernan presents &#8220;a revealing look at how the Internet continues to reshape our lives emotionally, visually, and culturally&#8221; (The Smithsonian Magazine). &#8220;Magic and Loss is an illuminating guide to the Internet&#8230;it is impossible to come away from this book without sharing some of Heffernan&#8217;s awe for this brave new world&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/">Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you an entrepreneur about to create a new web application? If you want to maximize your chances of building something customers want, this book demonstrates ways to apply and test techniques for customer development, Lean Startup, and bootstrapping. Learn how to identify and engage customers throughout the development cycle so you can focus on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/">Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you an entrepreneur about to create a new web application? If you want to maximize your chances of building something customers want, this book demonstrates ways to apply and test techniques for customer development, Lean Startup, and bootstrapping. Learn how to identify and engage customers throughout the development cycle so you can focus on building a product that people will actually buy and use. By rigorously following the techniques described in Running Lean, you can eliminate waste &#8211; whether it&#8217;s time, money, effort, or all of the above &#8211; and get your product to market quickly. Refined through the real-world experiences of dozens of startup companies, these techniques are part of Eric Ries&#8217; Lean Startup methodology. Principles covered in this book include: * Find a problem worth solving, then define a solution * Demo before building * Pricing is part of the product * Maximize for speed, learning, and focus * Build a continuous feedback loop with customers throughout the product development cycle * Right Action, Right Time * Build a path to customers from day one</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/">Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free : Laws for the Internet Age &#8211; Cory Doctorow, Foreword by Neil Gaiman, Foreword by Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Copyright Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Filled with wisdom and thought experiments and things that will mess with your mind.&#8221; &#8212; Neil Gaiman, author of The Graveyard Book and American Gods In sharply argued, fast-moving chapters, Cory Doctorow&#8217;s Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free takes on the state of copyright and creative success in the digital age. Can small artists still [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/">Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free : Laws for the Internet Age &#8211; Cory Doctorow, Foreword by Neil Gaiman, Foreword by Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Filled with wisdom and thought experiments and things that will mess with your mind.&#8221; &#8212; Neil Gaiman, author of The Graveyard Book and American Gods     </p>
<p>                    In sharply argued, fast-moving chapters, Cory Doctorow&#8217;s Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free takes on the state of copyright and creative success in the digital age. Can small artists still thrive in the Internet era? Can giant record labels avoid alienating their audiences? This is a book about the pitfalls, and the opportunities, creative industries (and individuals) are confronting today&#8211;about how the old models have failed or found new footing, and about what might soon replace them. An essential read for anyone with a stake in the future of the arts, Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free offers a vivid guide to the ways creativity and the Internet interact today, and to what might be coming next.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/">Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free : Laws for the Internet Age &#8211; Cory Doctorow, Foreword by Neil Gaiman, Foreword by Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
