<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Prints Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/prints/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/prints/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Prints Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/prints/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Tell Me More : Stories About the 12 Hardest Things I&#8217;m Learning to Say &#8211; Kelly Corrigan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tell-me-more-stories-about-the-12-hardest-things-im-learning-to-say-kelly-corrigan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Painting & Art Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prints]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tell-me-more-stories-about-the-12-hardest-things-im-learning-to-say-kelly-corrigan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A story-driven collection of essays on the twelve powerful phrases we use to sustain our relationships, from the bestselling author of Glitter and Glue and The Middle Place &#8220;Kelly Corrigan takes on all the big, difficult questions here, with great warmth and courage.&#8221;&#8211;Glennon Doyle NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tell-me-more-stories-about-the-12-hardest-things-im-learning-to-say-kelly-corrigan-abridged/">Tell Me More : Stories About the 12 Hardest Things I&#8217;m Learning to Say &#8211; Kelly Corrigan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A story-driven collection of essays on the twelve powerful phrases we use to sustain our relationships, from the bestselling author of Glitter and Glue and The Middle Place  &#8220;Kelly Corrigan takes on all the big, difficult questions here, with great warmth and courage.&#8221;&#8211;Glennon Doyle NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY REAL SIMPLE AND BUSTLE It&#8217;s a crazy idea: trying to name the phrases that make love and connection possible. But that&#8217;s just what Kelly Corrigan has set out to do here. In her New York Times bestselling memoirs,  Corrigan distilled our core relationships to their essences, showcasing a warm, easy storytelling style. Now, in Tell Me More,  she&#8217;s back with a deeply personal, unfailingly honest, and often hilarious examination of the essential phrases that turn the wheel of life.  In &#8220;I Don&#8217;t Know,&#8221; Corrigan wrestles to make peace with uncertainty, whether it&#8217;s over invitations that never came or a friend&#8217;s agonizing infertility. In &#8220;No,&#8221; she admires her mother&#8217;s ability to set boundaries and her liberating willingness to be unpopular. In &#8220;Tell Me More,&#8221; a facialist named Tish teaches her something important about listening. And in &#8220;I Was Wrong,&#8221; she comes clean about her disastrous role in a family fight&#8211;and explains why saying sorry may not be enough. With refreshing candor, a deep well of empathy, and her signature desire to understand &#8220;the thing behind the thing,&#8221; Corrigan swings between meditations on life with a preoccupied husband and two mercurial teenage daughters to profound observations on love and loss.  With the streetwise, ever-relatable voice that defines Corrigan&#8217;s work, Tell Me More is a moving and meaningful take on the power of the right words at the right moment to change everything. Praise for Tell Me More  &#8220;It is such a comfort just knowing that Kelly Corrigan exists: she is somehow both wise and self-deprecating; funny but unafraid of pain; frank but gentle. She is the sister/mother/best friend we all wish we could have&#8211;and because of this big-hearted book, we all get to.&#8221;&#8211;Ariel Levy, author of The Rules Do Not Apply  &#8220;With full-bodied humor and radical sensitivity, Kelly Corrigan transforms the mundane pain of life into a necessary spiritual text of sorts, one that reminds us that we have the right to grieve but the obligation to be grateful. This book will remind you that you are human&#8211;and of the fragile loveliness of being so.&#8221;&#8211;Lena Dunham</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tell-me-more-stories-about-the-12-hardest-things-im-learning-to-say-kelly-corrigan-abridged/">Tell Me More : Stories About the 12 Hardest Things I&#8217;m Learning to Say &#8211; Kelly Corrigan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
