<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Economic Geography Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/economic-geography/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/economic-geography/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Economic Geography Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/economic-geography/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Portfolios of the Poor : How the World&#8217;s Poor Live on $2 a Day &#8211; Daryl Collins, Jonathan Morduch, Stuart Rutherford, Orlanda Ruthven (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/portfolios-of-the-poor-how-the-worlds-poor-live-on-2-a-day-daryl-collins-jonathan-morduch-stuart-rutherford-orlanda-ruthven-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/portfolios-of-the-poor-how-the-worlds-poor-live-on-2-a-day-daryl-collins-jonathan-morduch-stuart-rutherford-orlanda-ruthven-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nearly forty percent of humanity lives on an average of two dollars a day or less. If you&#8217;ve never had to survive on an income so small, it is hard to imagine. How would you put food on the table, afford a home, and educate your children? How would you handle emergencies and old age? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/portfolios-of-the-poor-how-the-worlds-poor-live-on-2-a-day-daryl-collins-jonathan-morduch-stuart-rutherford-orlanda-ruthven-abridged/">Portfolios of the Poor : How the World&#8217;s Poor Live on $2 a Day &#8211; Daryl Collins, Jonathan Morduch, Stuart Rutherford, Orlanda Ruthven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nearly forty percent of humanity lives on an average of two dollars a day or less. If you&#8217;ve never had to survive on an income so small, it is hard to imagine. How would you put food on the table, afford a home, and educate your children? How would you handle emergencies and old age? Every day, more than a billion people around the world must answer these questions. Portfolios of the Poor is the first book to systematically explain how the poor find solutions to their everyday financial problems. The authors conducted year-long interviews with impoverished villagers and slum dwellers in Bangladesh, India, and South Africa&#8211;records that track penny by penny how specific households manage their money. The stories of these families are often surprising and inspiring. Most poor households do not live hand to mouth, spending what they earn in a desperate bid to keep afloat. Instead, they employ financial tools, many linked to informal networks and family ties. They push money into savings for reserves, squeeze money out of creditors whenever possible, run sophisticated savings clubs, and use microfinancing wherever available.<br />
                    Their experiences reveal new methods to fight poverty and ways to envision the next generation of banks for the &#8220;bottom billion.&#8221; Indispensable for those in development studies, economics, and microfinance, Portfolios of the Poor will appeal to anyone interested in knowing more about poverty and what can be done about it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/portfolios-of-the-poor-how-the-worlds-poor-live-on-2-a-day-daryl-collins-jonathan-morduch-stuart-rutherford-orlanda-ruthven-abridged/">Portfolios of the Poor : How the World&#8217;s Poor Live on $2 a Day &#8211; Daryl Collins, Jonathan Morduch, Stuart Rutherford, Orlanda Ruthven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of Poverty : Economic Possibilities for Our Time &#8211; Jeffrey D. Sachs, Foreword by Bono (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-poverty-economic-possibilities-for-our-time-jeffrey-d-sachs-foreword-by-bono-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-poverty-economic-possibilities-for-our-time-jeffrey-d-sachs-foreword-by-bono-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Book and man are brilliant, passionate, optimistic and impatient . . . Outstanding.&#8221; -The Economist The landmark exploration of economic prosperity and how the world can escape from extreme poverty for the world&#8217;s poorest citizens, from one of the world&#8217;s most renowned economists Hailed by Time as one of the world&#8217;s hundred most influential people, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-poverty-economic-possibilities-for-our-time-jeffrey-d-sachs-foreword-by-bono-abridged/">The End of Poverty : Economic Possibilities for Our Time &#8211; Jeffrey D. Sachs, Foreword by Bono (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Book and man are brilliant, passionate, optimistic and impatient . . . Outstanding.&#8221; -The Economist    </p>
<p>                    The landmark exploration of economic prosperity and how the world can escape from extreme poverty for the world&#8217;s poorest citizens, from one  of the world&#8217;s most renowned economists    </p>
<p>                     Hailed by Time as one of the world&#8217;s hundred most influential people, Jeffrey D. Sachs is renowned for his work around the globe advising economies in crisis. Now a classic of its genre, The End of Poverty distills more than thirty years of experience to offer a uniquely informed vision of the steps that can transform impoverished countries into prosperous ones. Marrying vivid storytelling with rigorous analysis, Sachs lays out a clear conceptual map of the world economy. Explaining his own work in Bolivia, Russia, India, China, and Africa, he offers an integrated set of solutions to the interwoven economic, political, environmental, and social problems that challenge the world&#8217;s poorest countries.    </p>
<p>                     Ten years after its initial publication, The End of Poverty remains an indispensible and influential work. In this 10th anniversary edition, Sachs presents an extensive new foreword assessing the progress of the past decade, the work that remains to be done, and how each of us can help. He also looks ahead across the next fifteen years to 2030, the United Nations&#8217; target date for ending extreme poverty, offering new insights and recommendations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-poverty-economic-possibilities-for-our-time-jeffrey-d-sachs-foreword-by-bono-abridged/">The End of Poverty : Economic Possibilities for Our Time &#8211; Jeffrey D. Sachs, Foreword by Bono (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An absorbing and original narrative history of American capitalism NAMED A BEST BOOK OF 2017 BY THE ECONOMIST From the days of the Mayflower and the Virginia Company, America has been a place for people to dream, invent, build, tinker, and bet the farm in pursuit of a better life. Americana takes us on a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/">Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An absorbing and original narrative history of American capitalism    </p>
<p>                    NAMED A BEST BOOK OF 2017 BY THE ECONOMIST    </p>
<p>                    From the days of the Mayflower and the Virginia Company, America has been a place for people to dream, invent, build, tinker, and bet the farm in pursuit of a better life. Americana takes us on a four-hundred-year journey of this spirit of innovation and ambition through a series of Next Big Things &#8212; the inventions, techniques, and industries that drove American history forward: from the telegraph, the railroad, guns, radio, and banking to flight, suburbia, and sneakers, culminating with the Internet and mobile technology at the turn of the twenty-first century. The result is a thrilling alternative history of modern America that reframes events, trends, and people we thought we knew through the prism of the value that, for better or for worse, this nation holds dearest: capitalism.     </p>
<p>                    In a winning, accessible style, Bhu Srinivasan boldly takes on four centuries of American enterprise, revealing the unexpected connections that link them. We learn how Andrew Carnegie&#8217;s early job as a telegraph messenger boy paved the way for his leadership of the steel empire that would make him one of the nation&#8217;s richest men; how the gunmaker Remington reinvented itself in the postwar years to sell typewriters; how the inner workings of the Mafia mirrored the trend of consolidation and regulation in more traditional business; and how a 1950s infrastructure bill triggered a series of events that produced one of America&#8217;s most enduring brands: KFC. Reliving the heady early days of Silicon Valley, we are reminded that the start-up is an idea as old as America itself.    </p>
<p>                    Entertaining, eye-opening, and sweeping in its reach, Americana is an exhilarating new work of narrative history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/">Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s going to happen to my job? That&#8217;s what an increasing number of anxious Americans are asking themselves. The US workforce, which has been one of the most productive and wealthiest in the world, is undergoing an alarming transformation. Increasing numbers of workers find themselves on shaky ground, turned into freelancers, temps and contractors. Even [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/">Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s going to happen to my job?     </p>
<p>                    That&#8217;s what an increasing number of anxious Americans are asking themselves.     </p>
<p>                    The US workforce, which has been one of the most productive and wealthiest in the world, is undergoing an alarming transformation. Increasing numbers of workers find themselves on shaky ground, turned into freelancers, temps and contractors. Even many full-time and professional jobs are experiencing this precarious shift. Within a decade, a near-majority of the 145 million employed Americans will be impacted. Add to that the steamroller of automation, robots and artificial intelligence already replacing millions of workers and projected to obsolesce millions more, and the jobs picture starts looking grim.     </p>
<p>                    Now a weird yet historic mash-up of Silicon Valley technology and Wall Street greed is thrusting upon us the latest economic fraud: the so-called sharing economy, with companies like Uber, Airbnb and TaskRabbit allegedly liberating workers to become independent and their own CEOs, hiring themselves out for ever-smaller jobs and wages while the companies profit.     </p>
<p>                    But this share the crumbs economy is just the tip of a looming iceberg that the middle class is drifting toward. Raw Deal: How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers, by veteran journalist Steven Hill, is an exposé that challenges conventional thinking, and the hype celebrating this new economy, by showing why the vision of the techno sapien leaders and their Ayn Rand libertarianism is a dead end.     </p>
<p>                    In Raw Deal, Steven Hill proposes pragmatic policy solutions to transform the US economy and its safety net and social contract, launching a new kind of deal to restore power back into the hands of American workers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/">Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Makers and Takers : How Wall Street Destroyed Main Street &#8211; Rana Foroohar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is Wall Street bad for Main Street America? A well-told exploration of why our current economy is leaving too many behind. &#8211;The New York Times In looking at the forces that shaped the 2016 presidential election, one thing is clear: much of the population believes that our economic system is rigged to enrich the privileged [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/">Makers and Takers : How Wall Street Destroyed Main Street &#8211; Rana Foroohar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is Wall Street bad for Main Street America?     </p>
<p>                    A well-told exploration of why our current economy is leaving too many behind. &#8211;The New York Times     </p>
<p>                     In looking at the forces that shaped the 2016 presidential election, one thing is clear: much of the population believes that our economic system is rigged to enrich the privileged elites at the expense of hard-working Americans. This is a belief held equally on both sides of political spectrum, and it seems only to be gaining momentum.     </p>
<p>                    A key reason, says Financial Times columnist Rana Foroohar, is the fact that Wall Street is no longer supporting Main Street businesses that create the jobs for the middle and working class. She draws on in-depth reporting and interviews at the highest rungs of business and government to show how the &#8220;financialization of America&#8221;&#8211;the phenomenon by which finance and its way of thinking have come to dominate every corner of business&#8211;is threatening the American Dream.     </p>
<p>                     Now updated with new material explaining how our corrupted financial sys­tem propelled Donald Trump to power, Makers and Takers explores the confluence of forces that has led American businesses to favor balance-sheet engineering over the actual kind, greed over growth, and short-term profits over putting people to work. From the cozy relationship between Wall Street and Washington, to a tax code designed to benefit wealthy individuals and corporations, to forty years of bad policy decisions, she shows why so many Americans have lost trust in the sys­tem, and why it matters urgently to us all.     </p>
<p>                     Through colorful stories of both &#8220;Takers,&#8221; those stifling job creation while lining their own pockets, and &#8220;Makers,&#8221; businesses serving the real economy, Foroohar shows how we can reverse these trends for a better path forward.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/">Makers and Takers : How Wall Street Destroyed Main Street &#8211; Rana Foroohar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are mass violence and catastrophes the only forces that can seriously decrease economic inequality? To judge by thousands of years of history, the answer is yes. Tracing the global history of inequality from the Stone Age to today, Walter Scheidel shows that it never dies peacefully. The Great Leveler is the first book to chart [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/">The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are mass violence and catastrophes the only forces that can seriously decrease economic inequality? To judge by thousands of years of history, the answer is yes. Tracing the global history of inequality from the Stone Age to today, Walter Scheidel shows that it never dies peacefully. The Great Leveler is the first book to chart the crucial role of violent shocks in reducing inequality over the full sweep of human history around the world. The &#8220;Four Horsemen&#8221; of leveling-mass-mobilization warfare, transformative revolutions, state collapse, and catastrophic plagues-have repeatedly destroyed the fortunes of the rich. Today, the violence that reduced inequality in the past seems to have diminished, and that is a good thing. But it casts serious doubt on the prospects for a more equal future. An essential contribution to the debate about inequality, The Great Leveler provides important new insights about why inequality is so persistent-and why it is unlikely to decline anytime soon.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/">The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
