<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Music Industry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/music-industry/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/music-industry/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Music Industry Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/music-industry/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Let Love Rule &#8211; Lenny Kravitz</title>
		<link>/let-love-rule-lenny-kravitz/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/let-love-rule-lenny-kravitz/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I see my story as a suite of songs that have a magical connection. I never understood that connection until I sat down to write. It was then that the magic started to flow.&#8217; Let Love Rule is a work of deep reflection. Lenny Kravitz looks back at his life with candor, self-scrutiny, and humour. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-love-rule-lenny-kravitz/">Let Love Rule &#8211; Lenny Kravitz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I see my story as a suite of songs that have a magical connection. I never understood that connection until I sat down to write. It was then that the magic started to flow.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    Let Love Rule is a work of deep reflection. Lenny Kravitz looks back at his life with candor, self-scrutiny, and humour. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;My life is all about opposites,&#8217; he writes. &#8216;Black and white. Jewish and Christian. The Jackson 5 and Led Zeppelin. I accepted my Gemini soul. I owned it. I adored it. Yins and yangs mingled in various parts of my heart and mind, giving me balance and fueling my curiosity and comfort.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    Let Love Rule covers a vast canvas stretching from Manhattan&#8217;s Upper East Side, Brooklyn&#8217;s Bedford-Stuyvesant, Los Angeles&#8217;s Baldwin Hills, Beverly Hills, and finally to France, England and Germany. It&#8217;s the story of a wildly creative kid who, despite tough struggles at school and extreme tension at home, finds salvation in music. We see him grow as a musician and ultimately a master songwriter, producer, and performer. </p>
<p>                    We also see Lenny&#8217;s spiritual growth-and the powerful way in which spirit informs his music. The cast of characters surrounding Lenny is extraordinary: his father, Sy, a high-powered news executive; his mother, Roxie Roker, a television star; and Lisa Bonet, the young actress who becomes his muse.</p>
<p>                    The central character, of course, is Lenny, who, despite his great aspirational energy, turns down record deal after record deal until he finds his true voice.The creation of that voice, the same voice that is able to declare &#8216;Let Love Rule&#8217; to an international audience, is the very heart of this story.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Whether recording, performing, or writing a book,&#8217; says Lenny, &#8216;my art is about listening to the inspiration inside and then sharing it with people. Art must bring the world closer together.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-love-rule-lenny-kravitz/">Let Love Rule &#8211; Lenny Kravitz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ta-Ra-Ra-Boom-De-Ay : The dodgy business of popular music &#8211; Simon Napier-Bell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ta-ra-ra-boom-de-ay-the-dodgy-business-of-popular-music-simon-napier-bell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music Reviews & Criticism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ta-ra-ra-boom-de-ay-the-dodgy-business-of-popular-music-simon-napier-bell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Legendary rock manager Simon Napier-Bell take you inside the (dodgy) world of popular music &#8211; not just a creative industry, but a business that has made people rich beyond their wildest dreams. He balances seductive anecdotes &#8211; pulling back the curtain on the gritty and absurd side of the industry &#8211; with an insightful exploration [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ta-ra-ra-boom-de-ay-the-dodgy-business-of-popular-music-simon-napier-bell-abridged/">Ta-Ra-Ra-Boom-De-Ay : The dodgy business of popular music &#8211; Simon Napier-Bell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Legendary rock manager Simon Napier-Bell take you inside the (dodgy) world of popular music &#8211; not just a creative industry, but a business that has made people rich beyond their wildest dreams. He balances seductive anecdotes &#8211; pulling back the curtain on the gritty and absurd side of the industry &#8211; with an insightful exploration of the relationship between creativity and money. This book describes the evolution of the industry from 1713 &#8211; the year parliament granted writers ownership over what they wrote &#8211; to today, when a global, 100 billion pound industry is controlled by just three major players: Sony, Universal and Warner. Inside you will uncover some little-known facts about the industry, including:     </p>
<p>                    How a formula for writing hit songs in the 1900s helped create 50,000 of the best-known songs of all time<br />
                    How infighting in the American pre-war music industry shut down traditional radio and created an opening for country music, race records and rock&#8217;n&#8217;roll<br />
                    How Jewish immigrants and black jazz musicians dancing cheek-to-cheek created a template for all popular music that followed<br />
                    How rock tours became the biggest, quickest, sleaziest and most profitable ventures the music industry has ever seen<br />
                    After reading Ta-Ra-Ra-Boom-De-Ay, you&#8217;ll never listen to music in the same way again</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ta-ra-ra-boom-de-ay-the-dodgy-business-of-popular-music-simon-napier-bell-abridged/">Ta-Ra-Ra-Boom-De-Ay : The dodgy business of popular music &#8211; Simon Napier-Bell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sonic Boom &#8211; Joel Beckerman, Tyler Gray (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sonic-boom-joel-beckerman-tyler-gray-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Acoustic & Sound Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music: Styles & Genres]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Techniques Of Music / Music Tutorials]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Music & Musicology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sonic-boom-joel-beckerman-tyler-gray-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>But sound has surprising power to influence our decisions, opinions, and actions in ways we might not even notice. Discordant ambient noise can induce anxiety; ice cream truck jingles can bring you back to your childhood. In The Sonic Boom, strategic sound consultant Joel Beckerman provides a new framework for thinking about sound effects on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sonic-boom-joel-beckerman-tyler-gray-abridged/">Sonic Boom &#8211; Joel Beckerman, Tyler Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>But sound has surprising power to influence our decisions, opinions, and actions in ways we might not even notice. Discordant ambient noise can induce anxiety; ice cream truck jingles can bring you back to your childhood. In The Sonic Boom, strategic sound consultant Joel Beckerman provides a new framework for thinking about sound effects on every aspect of our lives. You don&#8217;t need to be a musician or a composer to harness the power of sound. Whether you&#8217;re a corporate giant connecting with millions of customers or a teacher connecting with one classroom of students, the key to an effective sonic strategy is the creation of &#8220;boom moments&#8221; transcendent instants when sound connects with a listener&#8217;s emotional core.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sonic-boom-joel-beckerman-tyler-gray-abridged/">Sonic Boom &#8211; Joel Beckerman, Tyler Gray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
