<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Marxism &amp; Communism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/marxism-communism/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/marxism-communism/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Marxism &amp; Communism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/marxism-communism/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Reminiscences of the Cuban Revolutionary War &#8211; Ernesto Che Guevara</title>
		<link>/reminiscences-of-the-cuban-revolutionary-war-ernesto-che-guevara/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History: Post WW2 Conflicts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rebellions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uprisings]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reminiscences-of-the-cuban-revolutionary-war-ernesto-che-guevara/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Powerful and poetic &#8230; For anyone interested in the myth of Che Guevara &#8230; this book is essential reading&#8217; Colm Toibin, Observer &#8216;We were an army of shadows, of ghosts, walking as if to the beat of some dark psychic mechanism&#8230;&#8217; The Cuban Revolution changed the course of the twentieth century. Following years of brutal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reminiscences-of-the-cuban-revolutionary-war-ernesto-che-guevara/">Reminiscences of the Cuban Revolutionary War &#8211; Ernesto Che Guevara</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Powerful and poetic &#8230; For anyone interested in the myth of Che Guevara &#8230; this book is essential reading&#8217; Colm Toibin, Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We were an army of shadows, of ghosts, walking as if to the beat of some dark psychic mechanism&#8230;&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    The Cuban Revolution changed the course of the twentieth century. Following years of brutal tyranny and poverty, a band of idealistic young people fought against immense odds to overthrow a dictator and emerged victorious. This is the story of how they did it. Che Guevara&#8217;s classic eyewitness account chronicles the transformation of a country, and of Che himself, from troop doctor to revolutionary icon.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Che&#8217;s life is an inspiration for every human being who loves freedom&#8217; Nelson Mandela    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reminiscences-of-the-cuban-revolutionary-war-ernesto-che-guevara/">Reminiscences of the Cuban Revolutionary War &#8211; Ernesto Che Guevara</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Politically Incorrect Guide to Socialism &#8211; Kevin D Williamson</title>
		<link>/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-socialism-kevin-d-williamson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-socialism-kevin-d-williamson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stalin&#8217;s gulag, impoverished North Korea, collapsing Cuba&#8230;it&#8217;s hard to name a dogma that has failed as spectacularly as socialism. And yet leaders around the world continue to subject millions of people to this dysfunctional, violence-prone ideology. In The Politically Incorrect Guide(TM) to Socialism, Kevin Williamson reveals the fatal flaw of socialism&#8211;that efficient, complex economies simply [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-socialism-kevin-d-williamson/">The Politically Incorrect Guide to Socialism &#8211; Kevin D Williamson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stalin&#8217;s gulag, impoverished North Korea, collapsing Cuba&#8230;it&#8217;s hard to name a dogma that has failed as spectacularly as socialism. And yet leaders around the world continue to subject millions of people to this dysfunctional, violence-prone ideology. </p>
<p>                    In The Politically Incorrect Guide(TM) to Socialism, Kevin Williamson reveals the fatal flaw of socialism&#8211;that efficient, complex economies simply can&#8217;t be centrally planned. But even in America, that hasn&#8217;t stopped politicians and bureaucrats from planning, to various extents, the most vital sectors of our economy: public education, energy, and the most arrogant central-planning effort of them all, Obama&#8217;s healthcare plan. </p>
<p>                    In this provocative book, Williamson unfolds the grim history of socialism, showing how the ideology has spawned crushing poverty, devastating famines, and horrific wars. Lumbering from one crisis to the next, leaving a trail of economic devastation and environmental catastrophe, socialism has wreaked more havoc, caused more deaths, and impoverished more people than any other ideology in history&#8211;especially when you include the victims of fascism, which Williamson notes is simply a variant of socialism. </p>
<p>                    Williamson further demonstrates: </p>
<p>                    Why, contrary to popular belief, socialism in theory is no better than socialism in practice<br />
                    Why socialism can&#8217;t exist without capitalism<br />
                    How the energy powerhouse of Venezuela, under socialism, has become an economic basket case subject to rationing and blackouts<br />
                    How socialism, not British colonialism, plunged the bountiful economy of India into stagnation and dysfunction&#8211;and how capitalism is rescuing it<br />
                    Why socialism is inextricably linked to communism </p>
<p>                    If you thought socialism went into the dustbin of history with the collapse of the Soviet Union, think again. Socialism is alive and kicking, and it&#8217;s already spread further than you know.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-socialism-kevin-d-williamson/">The Politically Incorrect Guide to Socialism &#8211; Kevin D Williamson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Women Have Better Sex Under Socialism : And Other Arguments for Economic Independence &#8211; Kristen Ghodsee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-women-have-better-sex-under-socialism-and-other-arguments-for-economic-independence-kristen-ghodsee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Sexual Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-women-have-better-sex-under-socialism-and-other-arguments-for-economic-independence-kristen-ghodsee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Funny, angry, urgent. Ghodsee is going to start a revolution&#8217; Daisy Buchanan, author of The Sisterhood A witty, fiercely intelligent exploration of why capitalism is rigged against women and what we can do about it. Unregulated capitalism is bad for women. Socialism, if done properly, leads to economic independence, better labour conditions, better work/family balance [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-women-have-better-sex-under-socialism-and-other-arguments-for-economic-independence-kristen-ghodsee-abridged/">Why Women Have Better Sex Under Socialism : And Other Arguments for Economic Independence &#8211; Kristen Ghodsee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Funny, angry, urgent. Ghodsee is going to start a revolution&#8217; Daisy Buchanan, author of The Sisterhood     </p>
<p>                    A witty, fiercely intelligent exploration of why capitalism is rigged against women and what we can do about it.    </p>
<p>                    Unregulated capitalism is bad for women. Socialism, if done properly, leads to economic independence, better labour conditions, better work/family balance and, yes, even better sex.     </p>
<p>                    If you like the idea of such outcomes, then come along for an exploration of how we can change women&#8217;s lives for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-women-have-better-sex-under-socialism-and-other-arguments-for-economic-independence-kristen-ghodsee-abridged/">Why Women Have Better Sex Under Socialism : And Other Arguments for Economic Independence &#8211; Kristen Ghodsee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Communist Manifesto &#8211; Karl Marx (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/communist-manifesto-karl-marx-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/communist-manifesto-karl-marx-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Manifesto of the Communist Party (German: Manifest der Kommunistischen Partei), often referred to as The Communist Manifesto, was published on February 21, 1848, and is one of the world&#8217;s most influential political manuscripts. Commissioned by the Communist League and written by communist theorists Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels, it laid out the League&#8217;s purposes and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/communist-manifesto-karl-marx-abridged/">Communist Manifesto &#8211; Karl Marx (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Manifesto of the Communist Party (German: Manifest der Kommunistischen Partei), often referred to as The Communist Manifesto, was published on February 21, 1848, and is one of the world&#8217;s most influential political manuscripts. Commissioned by the Communist League and written by communist theorists Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels, it laid out the League&#8217;s purposes and program. It presents an analytical approach to the class struggle (historical and present) and the problems of capitalism, rather than a prediction of communism&#8217;s potential future forms.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/communist-manifesto-karl-marx-abridged/">Communist Manifesto &#8211; Karl Marx (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Socialism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Michael Newman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/socialism-a-very-short-introduction-michael-newman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/socialism-a-very-short-introduction-michael-newman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is socialism? Does it have a future, or has it become an outdated ideology in the 21st century? This Very Short Introduction considers the major theories in socialism, and explores its historical evolution from the French Revolution to the present day. Michael Newman argues that socialism has always been a diverse doctrine, while nevertheless [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/socialism-a-very-short-introduction-michael-newman-abridged/">Socialism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Michael Newman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What is socialism? Does it have a future, or has it become an outdated ideology in the 21st century?    </p>
<p>                    This Very Short Introduction considers the major theories in socialism, and explores its historical evolution from the French Revolution to the present day. Michael Newman argues that socialism has always been a diverse doctrine, while nevertheless containing a central core of interconnected values and goals: a critique of capitalism; an optimistic view of human beings; and the belief that it is possible to establish societies based on egalitarianism, social solidarity, and<br />
                    co-operation. In this new edition, he draws on case studies such as Cuba, Sweden, and Bolivia, to consider attempts to implement socialism in practice, before discussing New Left challenges to conventional notions of socialism on such questions as feminism, climate change, and direct action. Rejecting the widespread<br />
                    view that socialism is an out-dated doctrine, Newman argues that it remains ultimately relevant in today&#8217;s world.      </p>
<p>                    ABOUT THE SERIES: The Very Short Introductions series from Oxford University Press contains hundreds of titles in almost every subject area. These pocket-sized books ar the perfect way to get ahead in a new subject quickly. Our expert authors combine facts, analysis, perspective, new ideas, and enthusiasm to make interesting and challenging topics highly readable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/socialism-a-very-short-introduction-michael-newman-abridged/">Socialism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Michael Newman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The acclaimed labor lawyer and prizewinning author Thomas Geoghegan asks: where are we better off America or Europe? In an idiosyncratic, entertaining travelogue that plays on public policy, Geoghegan asks what our lives would be like if we lived them as Europeans. Sneaking out of his workaholic American life, he takes five trips where he [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/">Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The acclaimed labor lawyer and prizewinning author Thomas Geoghegan asks: where are we better off America or Europe? In an idiosyncratic, entertaining travelogue that plays on public policy, Geoghegan asks what our lives would be like if we lived them as Europeans. Sneaking out of his workaholic American life, he takes five trips where he tries to understand so-called European socialism firsthand. Though he first tries France (which has become a rhetorical stand-in for the continent as a whole in many Americans&#8217; minds), he eventually ventures into Germany to see what some call the &#8220;boring&#8221; Europe. There he finds the true &#8220;other&#8221; an economic model with more bottom-up worker control than that of any other country in the world and argues that, while we have to take Germany&#8217;s problems seriously, we also have to look seriously at how much it has achieved. Social democracy may let us live nicer lives; it also may be the only way to be globally competitive. This wry, timely book helps us understand why the European model, contrary to popular neoliberal wisdom, may thrive well into the twenty-first century without compromising its citizens&#8217; ease of living and be the best example for the United States to follow.    </p>
<p>                    Germany is more generous than the U.S.:    </p>
<p>                    The average number of paid vacation days in the U.S. is 13, versus Germany&#8217;s 35<br />
                    New mothers in the U.S. get three months of unpaid job-protected leave and only if they work for a company of 50 or more employees, while Germany mandates four months&#8217; paid leave and will pay parents 67% of their salary to stay home for up to 14 months to care for a newborn.<br />
                    U.S. life expectancy is 50th in the world, compared to Germany&#8217;s 32nd.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/">Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
