<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Disability: Social Aspects Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/disability-social-aspects/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/disability-social-aspects/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Disability: Social Aspects Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/disability-social-aspects/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Story of My Life &#8211; Helen Keller (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-story-of-my-life-helen-keller-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Disability: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-story-of-my-life-helen-keller-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When she was 19 months old, Helen Keller (1880-1968) suffered a severe illness that left her blind and deaf. Not long after, she also became mute. Her tenacious struggle to overcome these handicaps &#8212; with the help of her inspired teacher, Anne Sullivan &#8212; is one of the great stories of human courage and dedication. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-my-life-helen-keller-abridged/">The Story of My Life &#8211; Helen Keller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When she was 19 months old, Helen Keller (1880-1968) suffered a severe illness that left her blind and deaf. Not long after, she also became mute. Her tenacious struggle to overcome these handicaps &#8212; with the help of her inspired teacher, Anne Sullivan &#8212; is one of the great stories of human courage and dedication. In this classic autobiography, first published in 1903, Miss Keller recounts the first 22 years of her life, including the magical moment at the water pump when, recognizing the connection between the word &#8220;water&#8221; and the cold liquid flowing over her hand, she realized that objects had names. Subsequent experiences were equally noteworthy: her joy at eventually learning to speak, her friendships with Oliver Wendell Holmes, Edward Everett Hale and other notables, her education at Radcliffe (from which she graduated cum laude), and-underlying all-her extraordinary relationship with Miss Sullivan, who showed a remarkable genius for communicating with her eager and quick-to-learn pupil. These and many other aspects of Helen Keller&#8217;s life are presented here in clear, straightforward prose full of wonderful descriptions and imagery that would do credit to a sighted writer. Completely devoid of self-pity, yet full of love and compassion for others, this deeply moving memoir offers an unforgettable portrait of one of the outstanding women of the twentieth century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-my-life-helen-keller-abridged/">The Story of My Life &#8211; Helen Keller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crippled : Austerity and the Demonization of Disabled People &#8211; Frances Ryan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crippled-austerity-and-the-demonization-of-disabled-people-frances-ryan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Disability: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crippled-austerity-and-the-demonization-of-disabled-people-frances-ryan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In austerity Britain, disabled people have become the favourite target. From social care to the benefits system, politicians and media alike have made the case Britain&#8217;s 12 million disabled people are a drain on the public purse. In Crippled, leading commentator Frances Ryan exposes the disturbing reality, telling the story of those most affected by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crippled-austerity-and-the-demonization-of-disabled-people-frances-ryan-abridged/">Crippled : Austerity and the Demonization of Disabled People &#8211; Frances Ryan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In austerity Britain, disabled people have become the favourite target. From social care to the benefits system, politicians and media alike have made the case Britain&#8217;s 12 million disabled people are a drain on the public purse. In Crippled, leading commentator Frances Ryan exposes the disturbing reality, telling the story of those most affected by this devastating regime. This includes a paralyzed man forced to crawl down the stairs because the council wouldn&#8217;t provide accessible housing; the malnourished woman sleeping in her wheelchair; and the young girl with bipolar forced to turn to sex work to survive.     </p>
<p>                    Through these personal stories, Ryan charts how in recent years the public attitude towards disabled people has transformed from compassion to contempt: from society&#8217;s `most vulnerable&#8217; to benefit cheats. Crippled is a damning indictment of a safety net gone wrong, and a passionate demand for an end to austerity measures hitting those most in need.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crippled-austerity-and-the-demonization-of-disabled-people-frances-ryan-abridged/">Crippled : Austerity and the Demonization of Disabled People &#8211; Frances Ryan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
