<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Finance Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/finance/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/finance/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Finance Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/finance/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Intelligent Investor : The Classic Text on Value Investing &#8211; Benjamin Graham</title>
		<link>/intelligent-investor-the-classic-text-on-value-investing-benjamin-graham/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/intelligent-investor-the-classic-text-on-value-investing-benjamin-graham/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The greatest investment advisor of the twentieth century, Benjamin Graham taught and inspired people worldwide. Graham&#8217;s philosophy of `value investing`-which shields investors from substantial error and teaches them to develop long-term strategies-has made The Intelligent Investor the stock market bible ever since its original publication in 1949. Vital and indispensable, The Intelligent Investor is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/intelligent-investor-the-classic-text-on-value-investing-benjamin-graham/">Intelligent Investor : The Classic Text on Value Investing &#8211; Benjamin Graham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The greatest investment advisor of the twentieth century, Benjamin Graham taught and inspired people worldwide. Graham&#8217;s philosophy of `value investing`-which shields investors from substantial error and teaches them to develop long-term strategies-has made The Intelligent Investor the stock market bible ever since its original publication in 1949.    </p>
<p>                    Vital and indispensable, The Intelligent Investor is the most important book you will ever read on how to reach your financial goals.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/intelligent-investor-the-classic-text-on-value-investing-benjamin-graham/">Intelligent Investor : The Classic Text on Value Investing &#8211; Benjamin Graham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New Market Wizards : Conversations with America&#8217;s Top Traders &#8211; Jack D. Schwager</title>
		<link>/the-new-market-wizards-conversations-with-americas-top-traders-jack-d-schwager/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-market-wizards-conversations-with-americas-top-traders-jack-d-schwager/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The New Market Wizards, successful traders relate the financial strategies that have rocketed them to success. Asking questions that readers with an interest or involvement in the financial markets would love to pose to the financial superstars, Jack D. Schwager encourages these financial wizards to share their insights. Entertaining, informative, and invaluable, The New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-market-wizards-conversations-with-americas-top-traders-jack-d-schwager/">The New Market Wizards : Conversations with America&#8217;s Top Traders &#8211; Jack D. Schwager</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The New Market Wizards, successful traders relate the financial strategies that have rocketed them to success. Asking questions that readers with an interest or involvement in the financial markets would love to pose to the financial superstars, Jack D. Schwager encourages these financial wizards to share their insights. Entertaining, informative, and invaluable, The New Market Wizards is destined to become another Schwager classic.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-market-wizards-conversations-with-americas-top-traders-jack-d-schwager/">The New Market Wizards : Conversations with America&#8217;s Top Traders &#8211; Jack D. Schwager</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Debt : The First 5000 Years &#8211; David Graeber</title>
		<link>/debt-the-first-5000-years-david-graeber/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Laws Of Specific Jurisdictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/debt-the-first-5000-years-david-graeber/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The groundbreaking international best-seller that turns everything you think about money, debt, and society on its head&#8211;from the &#8220;brilliant, deeply original political thinker&#8221; David Graeber (Rebecca Solnit, author of Men Explain Things to Me) Before there was money, there was debt. For more than 5,000 years, since the beginnings of the first agrarian empires, humans [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/debt-the-first-5000-years-david-graeber/">Debt : The First 5000 Years &#8211; David Graeber</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The groundbreaking international best-seller that turns everything you think about money, debt, and society on its head&#8211;from the &#8220;brilliant, deeply original political thinker&#8221; David Graeber (Rebecca Solnit, author of Men Explain Things to Me) </p>
<p>                    Before there was money, there was debt. For more than 5,000 years, since the beginnings of the first agrarian empires, humans have used elaborate credit systems to buy and sell goods&#8211;that is, long before the invention of coins or cash. It is in this era that we also first encounter a society divided into debtors and creditors&#8211;which lives on in full force to this day. </p>
<p>                     So says anthropologist David Graeber in a stunning reversal of conventional wisdom. He shows that arguments about debt and debt forgiveness have been at the center of political debates from Renaissance Italy to Imperial China, as well as sparking innumerable insurrections. He also brilliantly demonstrates that the language of the ancient works of law and religion (words like &#8220;guilt,&#8221; &#8220;sin,&#8221; and &#8220;redemption&#8221;) derive in large part from ancient debates about debt, and shape even our most basic ideas of right and wrong. </p>
<p>                     We are still fighting these battles today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/debt-the-first-5000-years-david-graeber/">Debt : The First 5000 Years &#8211; David Graeber</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Panic! : The Story of Modern Financial Insanity &#8211; Michael Lewis</title>
		<link>/panic-the-story-of-modern-financial-insanity-michael-lewis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/panic-the-story-of-modern-financial-insanity-michael-lewis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Black Monday to the Asian financial crisis, from the internet bubble to mortgage meltdown, our lives are ruled by crazy cycles of euphoria and hysteria that manage to grip the world but are all-too-soon forgotten. In this unique collection of articles Michael Lewis &#8211; ex-trader and bestselling chronicler of greed and frenzy in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/panic-the-story-of-modern-financial-insanity-michael-lewis/">Panic! : The Story of Modern Financial Insanity &#8211; Michael Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Black Monday to the Asian financial crisis, from the internet bubble to mortgage meltdown, our lives are ruled by crazy cycles of euphoria and hysteria that manage to grip the world but are all-too-soon forgotten.     </p>
<p>                    In this unique collection of articles Michael Lewis &#8211; ex-trader and bestselling chronicler of greed and frenzy in the markets &#8211; casts a sceptical eye back over the most panicked-about panics of recent decades. He tells a story of boom and bust, deranged greed, outsized egos and over-inflated salaries, where the only thing that can ever be predicted is our constant inability to predict anything.     </p>
<p>                    Using contemporary accounts from commentators such as Joseph Stiglitz, Jeffrey Sachs and Paul Krugman, plus many of his own best writings, Lewis conveys the mood before each catastrophe, what it was like in the heat of the moment, how, afterwards, we tried to explain away the chaos &#8211; and then failed to learn from it before the whole process started all over again.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/panic-the-story-of-modern-financial-insanity-michael-lewis/">Panic! : The Story of Modern Financial Insanity &#8211; Michael Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review</p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.</p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.</p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.</p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>THE ENTREPRENEURIAL BIBLE TO VENTURE CAPITAL: Inside Secrets from the Leaders in the Startup Game &#8211; Andrew Romans (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-entrepreneurial-bible-to-venture-capital-inside-secrets-from-the-leaders-in-the-startup-game-andrew-romans-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-entrepreneurial-bible-to-venture-capital-inside-secrets-from-the-leaders-in-the-startup-game-andrew-romans-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>40 leading venture capitalists come together to teach entrepreneurs how to succeed with their startupThe Entrepreneurial Bible to Venture Capital is packed with invaluable advice about how to raise angel and venture capital funding, how to build value in a startup, and how to exit a company with maximum value for both founders and investors. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-entrepreneurial-bible-to-venture-capital-inside-secrets-from-the-leaders-in-the-startup-game-andrew-romans-abridged/">THE ENTREPRENEURIAL BIBLE TO VENTURE CAPITAL: Inside Secrets from the Leaders in the Startup Game &#8211; Andrew Romans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>40 leading venture capitalists come together to teach entrepreneurs how to succeed with their startupThe Entrepreneurial Bible to Venture Capital is packed with invaluable advice about how to raise angel and venture capital funding, how to build value in a startup, and how to exit a company with maximum value for both founders and investors. It guides entrepreneurs through every step in an entrepreneurial venture from the legalities of raising initial capital to knowing when to change tactics.    </p>
<p>                    Andrew Romans is the co-founder and general partner of Rubicon Venture Capital, a venture capital fund that invests in privately held technology companies and enables its investors to co-invest along side the fund on a deal-by-deal basis via innovative sidecar funds right up to IPO or M&#038;A exit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-entrepreneurial-bible-to-venture-capital-inside-secrets-from-the-leaders-in-the-startup-game-andrew-romans-abridged/">THE ENTREPRENEURIAL BIBLE TO VENTURE CAPITAL: Inside Secrets from the Leaders in the Startup Game &#8211; Andrew Romans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>STARTUP WEALTH delivers engaging interviews with early- stage investors in Google, Invisalign, ZipCar, Uber, Twilio, Localytics, and other successful and not so successful companies. Find out how an amazing IPO can result in early investors getting pennies on the dollar&#8211;or a 10x+ return. Josh Maher profiles 23 of the country&#8217;s best investors over the last [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/">Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>STARTUP WEALTH delivers engaging interviews with early- stage investors in Google, Invisalign, ZipCar, Uber, Twilio, Localytics, and other successful and not so successful companies. Find out how an amazing IPO can result in early investors getting pennies on the dollar&#8211;or a 10x+ return.    </p>
<p>                    Josh Maher profiles 23 of the country&#8217;s best investors over the last two decades by way of real-world case studies. Through revealing interviews, readers are introduced to Mark Suster, Catherine Mott, Christopher Mirabile, Brad Feld, Allan May, Joanne Wilson, and many other accomplished angel investors and venture capitalists. In these interviews you&#8217;ll learn:<br />
                     &#8211; How the best investors think about identifying companies, negotiating terms, and partnering with founders and other investors<br />
                     &#8211; How angel investing can involve many different successful approaches<br />
                     &#8211; What the best investors have learned from their largest successes and failures<br />
                     &#8211; How investors design their portfolios and work with companies to achieve the most successful results.    </p>
<p>                    STARTUP WEALTH is an insightful and useful tool for anyone seeking to make better investments, select great investors, or raise early-stage capital for their business.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;There is nothing better when it comes to learning &#8216;best practices&#8217; than hearing from successful people in the trenches. Josh&#8217;s book captures the best of the best, as they reveal both what worked and what didn&#8217;t for them as angel investors and entrepreneurs. Required reading whatever side of the investing fence you&#8217;re on!&#8221;&#8211;Gerry Langeler, Managing Director at OVP Venture Partners. Co-founder of Mentor Graphics (NASDAQ: MENT). Author of The Success Matrix and Take the Money and Run! An Insider&#8217;s Guide to Venture Capital.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/">Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge    </p>
<p>                    With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. This clear, concise, and accessible guide from two industry insiders shows you how to navigate this brave new blockchain world-and how to invest in these emerging assets to secure your financial future.    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets gives you all the tools you need:    </p>
<p>                    * An actionable framework for investigating and valuing cryptoassets     </p>
<p>                    * Portfolio management techniques to maximize returns while managing risk    </p>
<p>                    * Historical context and tips to navigate inevitable bubbles and manias    </p>
<p>                    * Practical guides to exchanges, wallets, capital market vehicles, and ICOs    </p>
<p>                    * Predictions on how blockchain technology may disrupt current portfolios    </p>
<p>                    In addition to offering smart investment strategies, this authoritative resource will help you understand how these assets were created, how they work, and how they are evolving amid the blockchain revolution. The authors define a clear and original cryptoasset taxonomy, composed of cryptocurrencies, cryptocommodities, and cryptotokens, with insights into how each subset is blending technology and markets. You&#8217;ll find a variety of methods to invest in these assets, whether through global exchanges that trade 24/7 or initial cryptoasset offerings (ICOs). By sequentially building on the concepts of each prior chapter, the book will provide you with a full understanding of the cryptoasset economy and the opportunities that await the innovative investor .    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets represent the future of money and markets. This book is your guide to that future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wait : The useful art of procrastination &#8211; Frank Partnoy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wait-the-useful-art-of-procrastination-frank-partnoy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wait-the-useful-art-of-procrastination-frank-partnoy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Warren Buffett compares stock trading to great athletes: they excel not because of fast neurological responses, but because of their ability to delay as long as possible before reacting. Successful CEOs, fire fighters, and military officers all know how to manage delay to gather as much information as possible to get the results they need. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wait-the-useful-art-of-procrastination-frank-partnoy-abridged/">Wait : The useful art of procrastination &#8211; Frank Partnoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Warren Buffett compares stock trading to great athletes: they excel not because of fast neurological responses, but because of their ability to delay as long as possible before reacting. Successful CEOs, fire fighters, and military officers all know how to manage delay to gather as much information as possible to get the results they need.    </p>
<p>                    In Wait, Frank Partnoy argues that decisions of all kinds, whether &#8216;snap&#8217; or long-term, benefit from being made at the last possible moment. The art of knowing how long you can afford to delay before committing is at the heart of many a great decision, whether in a corporate takeover or a marriage proposal. Apologies are better received if they are not rushed and people who can defer gratification are happier and more successful than those who must have everything now. Partnoy demonstrates that the ability to wait is crucial to getting the right answer and that gut instincts are often wrong.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wait-the-useful-art-of-procrastination-frank-partnoy-abridged/">Wait : The useful art of procrastination &#8211; Frank Partnoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adaptive Markets : Financial Evolution at the Speed of Thought &#8211; Andrew W. Lo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new, evolutionary explanation of markets and investor behavior Half of all Americans have money in the stock market, yet economists can&#8217;t agree on whether investors and markets are rational and efficient, as modern financial theory assumes, or irrational and inefficient, as behavioral economists believe&#8211;and as financial bubbles, crashes, and crises suggest. This is one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/">Adaptive Markets : Financial Evolution at the Speed of Thought &#8211; Andrew W. Lo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new, evolutionary explanation of markets and investor behavior  Half of all Americans have money in the stock market, yet economists can&#8217;t agree on whether investors and markets are rational and efficient, as modern financial theory assumes, or irrational and inefficient, as behavioral economists believe&#8211;and as financial bubbles, crashes, and crises suggest. This is one of the biggest debates in economics and the value or futility of investment management and financial regulation hang on the outcome. In this groundbreaking book, Andrew Lo cuts through this debate with a new framework, the Adaptive Markets Hypothesis, in which rationality and irrationality coexist. Drawing on psychology, evolutionary biology, neuroscience, artificial intelligence, and other fields, Adaptive Markets shows that the theory of market efficiency isn&#8217;t wrong but merely incomplete. When markets are unstable, investors react instinctively, creating inefficiencies for others to exploit. Lo&#8217;s new paradigm explains how financial evolution shapes behavior and markets at the speed of thought&#8211;a fact revealed by swings between stability and crisis, profit and loss, and innovation and regulation.<br />
                    A fascinating intellectual journey filled with compelling stories, Adaptive Markets starts with the origins of market efficiency and its failures, turns to the foundations of investor behavior, and concludes with practical implications&#8211;including how hedge funds have become the Galapagos Islands of finance, what really happened in the 2008 meltdown, and how we might avoid future crises. An ambitious new answer to fundamental questions in economics, Adaptive Markets is essential reading for anyone who wants to know how markets really work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/">Adaptive Markets : Financial Evolution at the Speed of Thought &#8211; Andrew W. Lo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bartering Mindset : A Mostly Forgotten Framework for Mastering Your Next Negotiation &#8211; Brian Gunia (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Specific Areas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We use money to solve our everyday problems, and it generally works well. Despite its economic benefits, however, money has a psychological downside: it trains us to think about negotiations narrow-mindedly, leading us to negotiate badly. Suggesting that we need a non-monetary mindset to negotiate better, The Bartering Mindset shows us how to look outside [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/">The Bartering Mindset : A Mostly Forgotten Framework for Mastering Your Next Negotiation &#8211; Brian Gunia (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We use money to solve our everyday problems, and it generally works well. Despite its economic benefits, however, money has a psychological downside: it trains us to think about negotiations narrow-mindedly, leading us to negotiate badly. Suggesting that we need a non-monetary mindset to negotiate better, The Bartering Mindset shows us how to look outside the monetary economy &#8211; to the bartering economies of the past, where people traded what they had for what they needed. The book argues that, because of the economic difficulties associated with bartering, barterers had to use a more sophisticated form of negotiation &#8211; a strategic approach that can make us master negotiators today.    </p>
<p>                    This book immerses readers in the assumptions made by barterers, collectively referred to as the &#8220;bartering mindset,&#8221; and then demonstrates how to apply this mindset to modern, monetary negotiations. The Bartering Mindset concludes that our individual, organizational, and social problems fester for a predictable reason: we apply a monetary mindset to our negotiations, leading to suboptimal thinking, counterproductive behaviors, and disappointing outcomes. By offering the bartering mindset as an alternative, this book will help people negotiate better and thrive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/">The Bartering Mindset : A Mostly Forgotten Framework for Mastering Your Next Negotiation &#8211; Brian Gunia (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Economist Numbers Guide : The Essentials of Business Numeracy &#8211; The Economist (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-economist-numbers-guide-the-essentials-of-business-numeracy-the-economist-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Mathematics & Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Numerical Analysis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-economist-numbers-guide-the-essentials-of-business-numeracy-the-economist-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Economist: Numbers Guide is invaluable for everyone who has to work with numbers, which in today&#8217;s commercially focused world means most managers. In addition to general advice on basic numeracy, the guide points out common errors and explains the recognized techniques for solving financial problems, analyzing information of any kind, forecasting and effective decision [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-economist-numbers-guide-the-essentials-of-business-numeracy-the-economist-abridged/">The Economist Numbers Guide : The Essentials of Business Numeracy &#8211; The Economist (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Economist: Numbers Guide is invaluable for everyone who has to work with numbers, which in today&#8217;s commercially focused world means most managers. In addition to general advice on basic numeracy, the guide points out common errors and explains the recognized techniques for solving financial problems, analyzing information of any kind, forecasting and effective decision making. Over 100 charts, graphs, tables and feature boxes highlight key points, and great emphasis is put on the all-important aspect of how you present and communicate numerical information effectively and honestly. At the back of the book is an extensive A-Z dictionary of terms covering everything from amortization to zero-sum game. Whatever your business, whatever your management role, for anyone who needs a good head for figures The Economist Numbers Guide will help you achieve your goals.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-economist-numbers-guide-the-essentials-of-business-numeracy-the-economist-abridged/">The Economist Numbers Guide : The Essentials of Business Numeracy &#8211; The Economist (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Post-Truth Business : How to Rebuild Brand Authenticity in a Distrusting World &#8211; Sean Pillot de Chenecey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-post-truth-business-how-to-rebuild-brand-authenticity-in-a-distrusting-world-sean-pillot-de-chenecey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-post-truth-business-how-to-rebuild-brand-authenticity-in-a-distrusting-world-sean-pillot-de-chenecey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FINALIST &#8211; Business Book Awards 2019 &#8211; Embracing Change Category Brands are built on trust, but in a post-truth world they&#8217;re faced with a serious challenge: so much of modern life is defined by mistrust. A shattering of the vital trust connection between brands and consumers, together with the evaporation of authenticity as a core [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-post-truth-business-how-to-rebuild-brand-authenticity-in-a-distrusting-world-sean-pillot-de-chenecey-abridged/">The Post-Truth Business : How to Rebuild Brand Authenticity in a Distrusting World &#8211; Sean Pillot de Chenecey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FINALIST &#8211; Business Book Awards 2019 &#8211; Embracing Change Category    </p>
<p>                    Brands are built on trust, but in a post-truth world they&#8217;re faced with a serious challenge: so much of modern life is defined by mistrust. A shattering of the vital trust connection between brands and consumers, together with the evaporation of authenticity as a core brand pillar, is causing enormous problems for businesses on a global scale. If a brand isn&#8217;t seen as trustworthy, then when choice is available it will be rejected in favour of one that is.    </p>
<p>                    The Post-Truth Business provides a way forward for any organization wishing to rebuild brand authenticity in a distrustful world. It explains the interconnected problems facing businesses, with important topics including:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; The impact of fake news, disinformation and the weaponizing of lies<br />
                    &#8211; The safeguarding of privacy, alongside privacy as a tradable asset<br />
                    &#8211; Why and how brands must create communication with meaning<br />
                    &#8211; The dangers of inauthentic cultural marketing activities<br />
                    &#8211; Examples of conscious capitalism and brand activism<br />
                    &#8211; Lessons in authenticity from artisans and innovators<br />
                    &#8211; National branding and reputation capital<br />
                    &#8211; Leveraging the power of &#8216;brand trust&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    The Post-Truth Business shows how to strengthen consumer engagement by closing the &#8216;brand credibility gap&#8217;. It&#8217;s packed with examples of inspiring people, brands and international campaigns from the fashion, beauty, outdoor, motor, drinks, finance, media, technology, entertainment and health sectors. Each of them demonstrates a dynamic and positive way forward.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-post-truth-business-how-to-rebuild-brand-authenticity-in-a-distrusting-world-sean-pillot-de-chenecey-abridged/">The Post-Truth Business : How to Rebuild Brand Authenticity in a Distrusting World &#8211; Sean Pillot de Chenecey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Picking up where Liar&#8217;s Poker left off (literally, in the bond dealer&#8217;s desks of Salomon Brothers) the story of Long-Term Capital Management is of a group of elite investors who believed they could beat the market and, like alchemists, create limitless wealth for themselves and their partners. Founded by John Meriweather, a notoriously confident bond [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Picking up where Liar&#8217;s Poker left off (literally, in the bond dealer&#8217;s desks of Salomon Brothers) the story of Long-Term Capital Management is of a group of elite investors who believed they could beat the market and, like alchemists, create limitless wealth for themselves and their partners.    </p>
<p>                              Founded by John Meriweather, a notoriously confident bond dealer, along with two Nobel prize winners and a floor of Wall Street&#8217;s brightest and best, Long-Term Captial Management was from the beginning hailed as a new gold standard in investing. It was to be the hedge fund to end all other hedge funds: a discreet private investment club limited to those rich enough to pony up millions.    </p>
<p>                              It became the banks&#8217; own favourite fund and from its inception achieved a run of dizzyingly spectacular returns. New investors barged each other aside to get their investment money into LTCM&#8217;s hands. But as competitors began to mimic Meriweather&#8217;s fund, he altered strategy to maintain the fund&#8217;s performance, leveraging capital with credit on a scale not fully understood and never seen before.    </p>
<p>                              When the markets in Indonesia, South America and Russia crashed in 1998 LCTM&#8217;s investments crashed with them and mountainous debts accumulated. The fund was in melt-down, and threatening to bring down into its trillion-dollar black hole a host of financial instiutions from New York to Switzerland. It&#8217;s a tale of vivid characters, overwheening ambition, and perilous drama told, in Roger Lowenstein&#8217;s hands, with brilliant style and panache.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The sharing economy&#8217;s unique customer-to-company exchange is possible because of the way in which money has evolved. These transactions have not always been as fluid as they are today, and they are likely to become even more fluid. It is therefore critical that we learn to appreciate money&#8217;s elastic nature as deeply as do Uber, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/">The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The sharing economy&#8217;s unique customer-to-company exchange is possible because of the way in which money has evolved. These transactions have not always been as fluid as they are today, and they are likely to become even more fluid. It is therefore critical that we learn to appreciate money&#8217;s elastic nature as deeply as do Uber, Airbnb, Kickstarter, and other innovators, and that we understand money&#8217;s transition from hard currencies to cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin if we are to access their cooperative potential.  The Evolution of Money illuminates this fascinating reality, focusing on the tension between currency&#8217;s real and abstract properties and advancing a vital theory of money rooted in this dual exchange. It begins with the debt tablets of Mesopotamia and follows with the development of coin money in ancient Greece and Rome, gold-backed currencies in medieval Europe, and monetary economics in Victorian England. The book ends in the digital era, with the cryptocurrencies and service providers that are making the most of money&#8217;s virtual side and that suggest a tectonic shift in what we call money.<br />
                    By building this organic time line, The Evolution of Money helps us anticipate money&#8217;s next, transformative role.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/">The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book That Still Beats the Market &#8211; Joel Greenblatt, Foreword byAndrew Tobias (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-that-still-beats-the-market-joel-greenblatt-foreword-by-andrew-tobias-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-that-still-beats-the-market-joel-greenblatt-foreword-by-andrew-tobias-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2005, Joel Greenblatt published a book that is already considered one of the classics of finance literature. In The Little Book that Beats the Market a New York Times bestseller with 300,000 copies in print Greenblatt explained how investors can outperform the popular market averages by simply and systematically applying a formula that seeks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-that-still-beats-the-market-joel-greenblatt-foreword-by-andrew-tobias-abridged/">The Little Book That Still Beats the Market &#8211; Joel Greenblatt, Foreword byAndrew Tobias (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2005, Joel Greenblatt published a book that is already considered one of the classics of finance literature. In  The Little Book that Beats the Market a  New York Times bestseller with 300,000 copies in print Greenblatt explained how investors can outperform the popular market averages by simply and systematically applying a formula that seeks out good businesses when they are available at bargain prices. Now, with a new Introduction and Afterword for 2010,  The Little Book that Still Beats the Market updates and expands upon the research findings from the original book. Included are data and analysis covering the recent financial crisis and model performance through the end of 2009. In a straightforward and accessible style, the book explores the basic principles of successful stock market investing and then reveals the author s time-tested formula that makes buying above average companies at below average prices automatic. Though the formula has been extensively tested and is a breakthrough in the academic and professional world, Greenblatt explains it using 6 th grade math, plain language and humor.<br />
                    He shows how to use his method to beat both the market and professional managers by a wide margin. You ll also learn why success eludes almost all individual and professional investors, and why the formula will continue to work even after everyone knows it.  While the formula may be simple, understanding why the formula works is the true key to success for investors. The book will take readers on a step-by-step journey so that they can learn the principles of value investing in a way that will provide them with a long term strategy that they can understand and stick with through both good and bad periods for the stock market.  As the Wall Street Journal stated about the original edition, Mr. Greenblatt says his goal was to provide advice that, while sophisticated, could be understood and followed by his five children, ages 6 to 15. They are in luck. His Little Book is one of the best, clearest guides to value investing out there.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-that-still-beats-the-market-joel-greenblatt-foreword-by-andrew-tobias-abridged/">The Little Book That Still Beats the Market &#8211; Joel Greenblatt, Foreword byAndrew Tobias (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coined : The Rich Life of Money and How Its History Has Shaped Us &#8211; Kabir Sehgal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/coined-the-rich-life-of-money-and-how-its-history-has-shaped-us-kabir-sehgal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/coined-the-rich-life-of-money-and-how-its-history-has-shaped-us-kabir-sehgal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Money isn&#8217;t just coins, bank notes or clamshells; it is more than a store of value or unit of payment. It&#8217;s an idea, a transformative player in how we view, cope, and harmonise with the world. Money isn&#8217;t just what makes the world go around; it is largely what makes each of us go around. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coined-the-rich-life-of-money-and-how-its-history-has-shaped-us-kabir-sehgal-abridged/">Coined : The Rich Life of Money and How Its History Has Shaped Us &#8211; Kabir Sehgal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Money isn&#8217;t just coins, bank notes or clamshells; it is more than a store of value or unit of payment. It&#8217;s an idea, a transformative player in how we view, cope, and harmonise with the world. Money isn&#8217;t just what makes the world go around; it is largely what makes each of us go around.    </p>
<p>                    In Coined, Kabir Sehgal travels the world while presenting a multidimensional portrait of currency through the ages. He explores the origin of exchange in the Galapagos Islands, searches for hoards of coins from an ancient civilization in Bangladesh, and learns about the art that appears on money from coin collectors in Vietnam. He takes you from the vaults beneath the Federal Reserve in New York to a beehive where pollen can be understood as a natural form of exchange. He details the birth of money, to its place in our culture, to how the obsession for it can lead to death and destruction, all the while mixing engaging and entertaining stories from the front lines of global currency exchange with extensive, thoughtful research. The story of money is rich and varied because it is our story.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coined-the-rich-life-of-money-and-how-its-history-has-shaped-us-kabir-sehgal-abridged/">Coined : The Rich Life of Money and How Its History Has Shaped Us &#8211; Kabir Sehgal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Smell a Rat : The Five Signs of Financial Fraud &#8211; Kenneth L. Fisher, Lara W. Hoffmans (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-smell-a-rat-the-five-signs-of-financial-fraud-kenneth-l-fisher-lara-w-hoffmans-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-smell-a-rat-the-five-signs-of-financial-fraud-kenneth-l-fisher-lara-w-hoffmans-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A timely guide to uncovering financial fraud 2008 and 2009 will be remembered for bear markets, a global credit crunch, and some of the largest investment scams ever. But these scams are nothing new, they&#8217;ve been repeated throughout history, and there will certainly be more to come. But the good news is fraudsters often follow [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-smell-a-rat-the-five-signs-of-financial-fraud-kenneth-l-fisher-lara-w-hoffmans-abridged/">How to Smell a Rat : The Five Signs of Financial Fraud &#8211; Kenneth L. Fisher, Lara W. Hoffmans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A timely guide to uncovering financial fraud  2008 and 2009 will be remembered for bear markets, a global credit crunch, and some of the largest investment scams ever. But these scams are nothing new, they&#8217;ve been repeated throughout history, and there will certainly be more to come. But the good news is fraudsters often follow the same basic playbook. Learn the playbook, and know how to ask the right questions, and financial fraud can be easy to detect and simple to avoid.  In How to Smell a Rat, trusted financial expert Ken Fisher provides you with an inside&#8217;s view on how to spot financial disasters before you become a part of them. Filled with in-depth insights and practical advice, this reliable resource takes an engaging look at recent and historic examples of fraudsters, how they operated, and how they can be easily avoided. Fisher also shows you the quick, identifiable features of financial frauds and arms you with the questions to ask when assessing a money manager.<br />
                    * Prepares you to identify and avoid financials cams that could instantly destroy your wealth * Contains examples that highlight how financial frauds are committed * Provides questions everyone should ask before entering any investment endeavor With How to Smell a Rat as your guide, you&#8217;ll learn how to protect your interests and assets from unnecessary losses.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-smell-a-rat-the-five-signs-of-financial-fraud-kenneth-l-fisher-lara-w-hoffmans-abridged/">How to Smell a Rat : The Five Signs of Financial Fraud &#8211; Kenneth L. Fisher, Lara W. Hoffmans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Wealth of Common Sense : Why Simplicity Trumps Complexity in Any Investment Plan &#8211; Ben Carlson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A simple guide to a smarter strategy for the individual investor A Wealth of Common Sense sheds a refreshing light on investing, and shows you how a simplicity-based framework can lead to better investment decisions. The financial market is a complex system, but that doesn&#8217;t mean it requires a complex strategy; in fact, this false [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/">A Wealth of Common Sense : Why Simplicity Trumps Complexity in Any Investment Plan &#8211; Ben Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A simple guide to a smarter strategy for the individual investor A Wealth of Common Sense sheds a refreshing light on investing, and shows you how a simplicity-based framework can lead to better investment decisions. The financial market is a complex system, but that doesn&#8217;t mean it requires a complex strategy; in fact, this false premise is the driving force behind many investors&#8217; market &#8220;mistakes.&#8221; Information is important, but understanding and perspective are the keys to better decision-making. This book describes the proper way to view the markets and your portfolio, and show you the simple strategies that make investing more profitable, less confusing, and less time-consuming. Without the burden of short-term performance benchmarks, individual investors have the advantage of focusing on the long view, and the freedom to construct the kind of portfolio that will serve their investment goals best. This book proves how complex strategies essentially waste these advantages, and provides an alternative game plan for those ready to simplify.<br />
                    Complexity is often used as a mechanism for talking investors into unnecessary purchases, when all most need is a deeper understanding of conventional options. This book explains which issues you actually should pay attention to, and which ones are simply used for an illusion of intelligence and control. * Keep up with or beat professional money managers * Exploit stock market volatility to your utmost advantage * Learn where advisors and consultants fit into smart strategy * Build a portfolio that makes sense for your particular situation You don&#8217;t have to outsmart the market if you can simply outperform it. Cut through the confusion and noise and focus on what actually matters. A Wealth of Common Sense clears the air, and gives you the insight you need to become a smarter, more successful investor.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/">A Wealth of Common Sense : Why Simplicity Trumps Complexity in Any Investment Plan &#8211; Ben Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buffett : The Making of an American Capitalist &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since its hardcover publication in August of 1995, Buffett has appeared on the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, San Francisco Chronicle, Los Angeles Times, Seattle Times, Newsday and Business Week bestseller lists. Starting from scratch, simply by picking stocks and companies for investment, Warren Buffett amassed one of the epochal fortunes of the twentieth [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">Buffett : The Making of an American Capitalist &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since its hardcover publication in August of 1995, Buffett has appeared on the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, San Francisco Chronicle, Los Angeles Times, Seattle Times, Newsday and Business Week bestseller lists. Starting from scratch, simply by picking stocks and companies for investment, Warren Buffett amassed one of the epochal fortunes of the twentieth century&#8211;an astounding net worth of $10 billion, and counting. His awesome investment record has made him a cult figure popularly known for his seeming contradictions: a billionaire who has a modest lifestyle, a phenomenally successful investor who eschews the revolving-door trading of modern Wall Street, a brilliant dealmaker who cultivates a homespun aura. Journalist Roger Lowenstein draws on three years of unprecedented access to Buffett&#8217;s family, friends, and colleagues to provide the first definitive, inside account of the life and career of this American original. Buffett explains Buffett&#8217;s investment strategy&#8211;a long-term philosophy grounded in buying stock in companies that are undervalued on the market and hanging on until their worth invariably surfaces&#8211;and shows how it is a reflection of his inner self.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">Buffett : The Making of an American Capitalist &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pricing for Profit : How to Develop a Powerful Pricing Strategy for Your Business &#8211; Peter Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/pricing-for-profit-how-to-develop-a-powerful-pricing-strategy-for-your-business-peter-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pricing-for-profit-how-to-develop-a-powerful-pricing-strategy-for-your-business-peter-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Price is the most significant factor affecting the profitability of every business, profit centre or department. When the pressure is on to perform or grow, your instinct may be to discount, undercut your competitors, cut costs and promote through price. Yet these are often the last things you should do. Pricing for Profit is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pricing-for-profit-how-to-develop-a-powerful-pricing-strategy-for-your-business-peter-hill-abridged/">Pricing for Profit : How to Develop a Powerful Pricing Strategy for Your Business &#8211; Peter Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Price is the most significant factor affecting the profitability of every business, profit centre or department. When the pressure is on to perform or grow, your instinct may be to discount, undercut your competitors, cut costs and promote through price. Yet these are often the last things you should do. Pricing for Profit is the most practical guide on pricing available. Using a firm, profit-focused framework developed running real projects for real businesses, this book shows you how by getting your pricing structures right you can make a huge difference to your bottom line. It gives business owners, managers and leaders simple, achievable pricing strategies that will deliver sustainable business growth. Can you afford to leave money on the table? If not, Pricing for Profit is the guide for you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pricing-for-profit-how-to-develop-a-powerful-pricing-strategy-for-your-business-peter-hill-abridged/">Pricing for Profit : How to Develop a Powerful Pricing Strategy for Your Business &#8211; Peter Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fanatical Prospecting : The Ultimate Guide to Opening Sales Conversations and Filling the Pipeline by Leveraging Social Selling, Telephone, Email, Text, and Cold Calling &#8211; Jeb Blount, Foreword byMike Weinberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fanatical-prospecting-the-ultimate-guide-to-opening-sales-conversations-and-filling-the-pipeline-by-leveraging-social-selling-telephone-email-text-and-cold-calling-jeb-blount-foreword-by/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fanatical-prospecting-the-ultimate-guide-to-opening-sales-conversations-and-filling-the-pipeline-by-leveraging-social-selling-telephone-email-text-and-cold-calling-jeb-blount-foreword-by/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ditch the failed sales tactics, fill your pipeline, and crush your number Fanatical Prospecting gives salespeople, sales leaders, entrepreneurs, and executives a practical, eye-opening guide that clearly explains the why and how behind the most important activity in sales and business development prospecting. The brutal fact is the number one reason for failure in sales [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fanatical-prospecting-the-ultimate-guide-to-opening-sales-conversations-and-filling-the-pipeline-by-leveraging-social-selling-telephone-email-text-and-cold-calling-jeb-blount-foreword-by/">Fanatical Prospecting : The Ultimate Guide to Opening Sales Conversations and Filling the Pipeline by Leveraging Social Selling, Telephone, Email, Text, and Cold Calling &#8211; Jeb Blount, Foreword byMike Weinberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ditch the failed sales tactics, fill your pipeline, and crush your number  Fanatical Prospecting gives salespeople, sales leaders, entrepreneurs, and executives a practical, eye-opening guide that clearly explains the why and how behind the most important activity in sales and business development prospecting.  The brutal fact is the number one reason for failure in sales is an empty pipe and the root cause of an empty pipeline is the failure to consistently prospect. By ignoring the muscle of prospecting, many otherwise competent salespeople and sales organizations consistently underperform. Step by step, Jeb Blount outlines his innovative approach to prospecting that works for real people, in the real world, with real prospects. Learn how to keep the pipeline full of qualified opportunities and avoid debilitating sales slumps by leveraging a balanced prospecting methodology across multiple prospecting channels. This book reveals the secrets, techniques, and tips of top earners.<br />
                    You ll learn: * Why the 30-Day Rule is critical for keeping the pipeline full * Why understanding the Law of Replacement is the key to avoiding sales slumps * How to leverage the Law of Familiarity to reduce prospecting friction and avoid rejection * The 5 C s of Social Selling and how to use them to get prospects to call you * How to use the simple 5 Step Telephone Framework to get more appointments fast * How to double call backs with a powerful voice mail technique * How to leverage the powerful 4 Step Email Prospecting Framework to create emails that compel prospects to respond * How to get text working for you with the 7 Step Text Message Prospecting Framework * And there is so much more! Fanatical Prospecting is filled with the high-powered strategies, techniques, and tools you need to fill your pipeline with high quality opportunities. In the most comprehensive book ever written about sales prospecting, Jeb Blount reveals the real secret to improving sales productivity and growing your income fast. You ll gain the power to blow through resistance and objections, gain more appointments, start more sales conversations, and close more sales.<br />
                    Break free from the fear and frustration that is holding you and your team back from effective and consistent prospecting. It&#8217;s time to get off the feast or famine sales roller-coaster for good!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fanatical-prospecting-the-ultimate-guide-to-opening-sales-conversations-and-filling-the-pipeline-by-leveraging-social-selling-telephone-email-text-and-cold-calling-jeb-blount-foreword-by/">Fanatical Prospecting : The Ultimate Guide to Opening Sales Conversations and Filling the Pipeline by Leveraging Social Selling, Telephone, Email, Text, and Cold Calling &#8211; Jeb Blount, Foreword byMike Weinberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investing with Impact : Why Finance is a Force for Good &#8211; Jeremy Balkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Investing with Impact: Why Finance Is a Force for Good outlines the roadmap to reinvigorating a skeptical public and demoralized financial services industry by making the case that, contrary to popular misconception, finance is not the cause of the world&#8217;s problems; in fact, it can provide the solution. Author Jeremy Balkin presents the case that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/">Investing with Impact : Why Finance is a Force for Good &#8211; Jeremy Balkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investing with Impact: Why Finance Is a Force for Good outlines the roadmap to reinvigorating a skeptical public and demoralized financial services industry by making the case that, contrary to popular misconception, finance is not the cause of the world&#8217;s problems; in fact, it can provide the solution. Author Jeremy Balkin presents the case that the finance industry can improve the state of the world by positively influencing the allocation of capital.  Investing With Impact explains the methodology of Balkin&#8217;s 6 E Paradigm, opening the toolbox to this revolutionary framework for the first time. In so doing, Balkin expands the impact investment universe, enabling mainstream capital to flow where opportunities generate positive investment returns and have demonstrable social impact.  Described by the Huffington Post as the &#8220;Anti-Wolf of Wall Street,&#8221; Balkin is challenging the status quo on Wall Street by leading the intellectual debate embracing the $1 trillion frontier impact investment market opportunity. The book demonstrates conclusively that, if we can change the culture in finance, we can change the world for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/">Investing with Impact : Why Finance is a Force for Good &#8211; Jeremy Balkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The best-selling index investing &#8220;bible&#8221; offers new information and is updated to reflect the latest market data The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the classic guide to getting smart about the market. Legendary mutual fund veteran John C. Bogle reveals his key to getting more out of investing: low-cost index funds. Bogle describes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/">The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The best-selling index investing &#8220;bible&#8221; offers new information and is updated to reflect the latest market data The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the classic guide to getting smart about the market. Legendary mutual fund veteran John C. Bogle reveals his key to getting more out of investing: low-cost index funds. Bogle describes the simplest and most effective investment strategy for building wealth over the long term: buy and hold, at very low cost, a mutual fund that tracks the S&#038;P 500 Stock Index. Such an index portfolio is the only investment that guarantees your fair share of stock market returns. This strategy is favored by Warren Buffett, who has endorsed this best selling 10th Anniversary Edition. The book shows you how to make index investing work for you and help you achieve your financial goals, cut through the hype to see what&#8217;s really in your best interest, and analyze the metrics that truly matter. You&#8217;ll gain candid insight from some of the world&#8217;s best financial minds: not only Warren Buffett, but Benjamin Graham, Paul Samuelson, Burton Malkiel, and others.<br />
                    Updated with current data and laced with two new chapters on asset allocation and retirement investing, the new Little Book of Common Sense Investing gives you a solid strategy for building your financial future. * Build a broadly diversified, low-cost portfolio without the risks of individual stocks, manager selection, and sector rotation * Forget the fads and focus on what works in the real world * Emphasize business reality over market expectations * Understand how index investing is the only game that assures your fair share of stock market returns Too many investors trade franticly, turning a winners game into a losers game, while index investing allows you to sit back and let the market do the work for you. Learn how to harness the magic of compounding returns while avoiding the tyranny of compounding costs. Bogle describes his simple method for developing rational expectations for future market returns, and what he sees coming over the next decade.  The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the guidebook to your financial future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/">The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019    </p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review    </p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.    </p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.    </p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.    </p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everyday Millionaires &#8211; Chris Hogan, Foreword byDave Ramsey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everyday-millionaires-chris-hogan-foreword-by-dave-ramsey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everyday-millionaires-chris-hogan-foreword-by-dave-ramsey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Everyday Millionaires, #1 national best-selling author Chris Hoganwill show you how ordinary people built extraordinary wealth&#8211;and how you can too. You&#8217;ll learn how millionaires live on less than they make, avoid debt, invest, are disciplined and responsible! This book is based on the largest study EVER conducted on 10,000 U.S. millionaires&#8211;and the results will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everyday-millionaires-chris-hogan-foreword-by-dave-ramsey-abridged/">Everyday Millionaires &#8211; Chris Hogan, Foreword byDave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Everyday Millionaires, #1 national best-selling author Chris Hoganwill show you how ordinary people built extraordinary wealth&#8211;and how you can too. You&#8217;ll learn how millionaires live on less than they make, avoid debt, invest, are disciplined and responsible!    </p>
<p>                    This book is based on the largest study EVER conducted on 10,000 U.S. millionaires&#8211;and the results will shock you! You&#8217;ll learn that building wealth has almost NOTHING to do with your income or your background! It doesn&#8217;t matter where you come from. It matters where you&#8217;re going.    </p>
<p>                    Most people think it takes crazy investing knowledge, a giant salary, a streak of luck, or a huge inheritance to become a millionaire. But that couldn&#8217;t be further from the truth! Here&#8217;s what you need to understand: if you&#8217;re willing to do the work&#8211;if you&#8217;ll follow the stuff we teach, if you&#8217;ll commit to our plan&#8211;then you CAN become a millionaire.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everyday-millionaires-chris-hogan-foreword-by-dave-ramsey-abridged/">Everyday Millionaires &#8211; Chris Hogan, Foreword byDave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Peers Inc : How People and Platforms are Inventing the Collaborative Economy and Reinventing Capitalism &#8211; Dina Pearlman, Robin Chase (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/peers-inc-how-people-and-platforms-are-inventing-the-collaborative-economy-and-reinventing-capitalism-dina-pearlman-robin-chase-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/peers-inc-how-people-and-platforms-are-inventing-the-collaborative-economy-and-reinventing-capitalism-dina-pearlman-robin-chase-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Robin Chase cofounded Zipcar, she not only started a business but established the foundation for one of the most important economic and social ideas of our time: the collaborative economy. With this important audiobook, she broadens our thinking about the ways in which the economy is being transformed and shows how the Peers Inc [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/peers-inc-how-people-and-platforms-are-inventing-the-collaborative-economy-and-reinventing-capitalism-dina-pearlman-robin-chase-abridged/">Peers Inc : How People and Platforms are Inventing the Collaborative Economy and Reinventing Capitalism &#8211; Dina Pearlman, Robin Chase (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Robin Chase cofounded Zipcar, she not only started a business but established the foundation for one of the most important economic and social ideas of our time: the collaborative economy. With this important audiobook, she broadens our thinking about the ways in which the economy is being transformed and shows how the Peers Inc model is changing the very nature of capitalism.     </p>
<p>                    When the best of people power is combined with the best of corporate power to form &#8220;Peers Inc&#8221; organizations, a potent creative force is released. The &#8220;Inc&#8221; in these collaborations delivers the industrial strengths of significant scale and resources, and the &#8220;Peers&#8221; bring together the individual strengths of localization, specialization, and customization, unlocking the power of the collaborative economy. When excess capacity is harnessed by the platform and diverse peers participate, a completely new dynamic is unleashed.     </p>
<p>                    In Peers Inc, Robin Chase brings her provocative insights to work, business, the economy, and the environment, showing: How focusing on excess capacity transforms the economics of what&#8217;s possible and delivers abundance to all How the new collaboration between the Inc and the Peers enables companies to grow more quickly, learn faster, and deliver smarter products and services How leveraging the Peers Inc model can address climate change with the necessary speed and scale How the Peers Inc model can help legacy companies overcome their shortening life cycle by inviting innovation and evolution Why power parity between the Peers and the Inc is a prerequisite for long-term success How platforms can be built within the existing financial system or outside of it What government can do to enhance economic possibility and protect people working in this new decentralized world</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/peers-inc-how-people-and-platforms-are-inventing-the-collaborative-economy-and-reinventing-capitalism-dina-pearlman-robin-chase-abridged/">Peers Inc : How People and Platforms are Inventing the Collaborative Economy and Reinventing Capitalism &#8211; Dina Pearlman, Robin Chase (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antiques & Collectables: Books, Manuscripts, Ephemera & Printed Matter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On the death of France&#8217;s most glorious king, Louis XIV, in 1715, few people benefited from the shift in power more than the intriguing financial genius from Edinburgh, John Law. Already notorious for killing a man in a duel and for acquiring a huge fortune from gambling, Law had proposed to the English monarch that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/">Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the death of France&#8217;s most glorious king, Louis XIV, in 1715, few people benefited from the shift in power more than the intriguing financial genius from Edinburgh, John Law. Already notorious for killing a man in a duel and for acquiring a huge fortune from gambling, Law had proposed to the English monarch that a bank be established to issue paper money with the credit based on the value of land. But Queen Anne was not about to take advice from a gambler and felon. So, in exile in Paris, he convinced the bankrupt court of Louis XV of the value of his idea.<br />
                     Law soon engineered the revival of the French economy and found himself one of the most powerful men in Europe. In August 1717, he founded the Mississippi Company, and the Court granted him the right to trade in France&#8217;s vast territory in America. The shareholders in his new trading company made such enormous profits that the term millionaire was coined to describe them. Paris was soon in a frenzy of speculation, conspiracies, and insatiable consumption. Before this first boom-and-bust cycle was complete, markets throughout Europe crashed, the mob began calling for Law&#8217;s head, and his visionary ideas about what money could do were abandoned and forgotten.<br />
                     In Millionaire,  Janet Gleeson lucidly reconstructs this epic drama where fortunes were made and lost, paupers grew rich, and lords fell into penury &#8212; and a modern fiscal philosophy was born. Her enthralling tragicomic tale reveals two great characters: John Law, with his complex personality and inscrutable motives, and money itself, whose true nature even to this day remains elusive</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/">Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Outsmarting the Crowd : A Value Investor&#8217;s Guide to Starting, Building, and Keeping a Family Fortune &#8211; Bogumil K Baranowski, Foreword byFrancois D Sicart (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/outsmarting-the-crowd-a-value-investors-guide-to-starting-building-and-keeping-a-family-fortune-bogumil-k-baranowski-foreword-by-francois-d-sicart-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/outsmarting-the-crowd-a-value-investors-guide-to-starting-building-and-keeping-a-family-fortune-bogumil-k-baranowski-foreword-by-francois-d-sicart-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WE ARE WIRED TO FAIL WITH MONEY AND INVESTING. Do You Have $1 on You? BEFORE YOU START READING, please reach for your wallet. Take out a one-dollar bill. Do you have it? Look at it, hold it up, put it in front of you. Now imagine you save $1 each month (which few do). [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsmarting-the-crowd-a-value-investors-guide-to-starting-building-and-keeping-a-family-fortune-bogumil-k-baranowski-foreword-by-francois-d-sicart-abridged/">Outsmarting the Crowd : A Value Investor&#8217;s Guide to Starting, Building, and Keeping a Family Fortune &#8211; Bogumil K Baranowski, Foreword byFrancois D Sicart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WE ARE WIRED TO FAIL WITH MONEY AND INVESTING.     </p>
<p>                    Do You Have $1 on You? BEFORE YOU START READING, please reach for your wallet. Take out a one-dollar bill. Do you have it? Look at it, hold it up, put it in front of you.    </p>
<p>                    Now imagine you save $1 each month (which few do). Imagine that your $1 earns 7% annually on average over thirty years. At the end of the thirty years you will have almost $1,200.    </p>
<p>                    Needless to say, if you put away $1,000 each month, you&#8217;d have almost $1.2 million in thirty years.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s secondary if you are just starting your family fortune&#8211;or if you already have it and want to keep it and grow it.    </p>
<p>                    If you do nothing with that dollar, inflation will eat away at its value. It will be worth less than two quarters in twenty-five years and less than a single quarter in fifty years and a nickel in one hundred years.    </p>
<p>                    Can you afford to do nothing? Do I have your attention?    </p>
<p>                    Most books misinform, or intimidate the reader, and often are not backed by real life experience.    </p>
<p>                    This book is a one of a kind, comprehensive, straightforward, and easy to follow guide to investing. It&#8217;s written by an experienced investor trained in the value investing, Buffett-Graham school of thought.    </p>
<p>                    Like no other book, it covers both the intellectual and emotional discipline needed to be a successful investor. It provides the proper philosophy, shows the path, and emphasizes the principles required to keep and grow your wealth over a lifetime.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Over more than a decade, Bogumil has assiduously assembled a set of rules from the writings and the speeches of the world&#8217;s most lastingly successful investors: these rules have become his chosen investment discipline. [&#8230;] He has written a great road map for young investors as well as a thoughtful and very readable guide to spare older neophytes the most common investment mistakes.&#8221; &#8211; Franois D. Sicart, Founder and Chairman of Tocqueville Asset Management.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Now comes his book. Obviously, Bogumil was augmenting what we were teaching him over the years about the investment process with extensive readings by the great thinkers on this subject. Unlike some of these tomes, however, Bogumil&#8217;s &#8220;Outsmarting the Crowd&#8221; is an easily digestible, common sense approach to a subject that is too often wrapped in jargon made to make it appear more difficult and less intuitive than it actually is.&#8221; &#8211; Robert W. Kleinschmidt, President, Chief Executive Officer and Chief Investment Officer of Tocqueville Asset Management.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsmarting-the-crowd-a-value-investors-guide-to-starting-building-and-keeping-a-family-fortune-bogumil-k-baranowski-foreword-by-francois-d-sicart-abridged/">Outsmarting the Crowd : A Value Investor&#8217;s Guide to Starting, Building, and Keeping a Family Fortune &#8211; Bogumil K Baranowski, Foreword byFrancois D Sicart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutionary Groups & Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. To manage the risks and spread the benefits, we have to act now, and in the interest of stakeholders everywhere&#8217; Andrew McAfee, Co-Founder, MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy, MIT, USA    </p>
<p>                    We are on the brink of the Fourth Industrial Revolution. And this one will be unlike any other in human history.    </p>
<p>                    Characterized by new technologies fusing the physical, digital and biological worlds, the Fourth Industrial Revolution will impact all disciplines, economies and industries &#8211; and it will do so at an unprecedented rate. World Economic Forum data predicts that by 2025 we will see: commercial use of nanomaterials 200 times stronger than steel and a million times thinner than human hair; the first transplant of a 3D-printed liver; 10% of all cars on US roads being driverless; and much more besides.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Industrial Revolution, Schwab outlines the key technologies driving this revolution, discusses the major impacts on governments, businesses, civil society and individuals, and offers bold ideas for what can be done to shape a better future for all.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The technologies of the Fourth Industrial Revolution are extraordinary. Leadership has to be equally extraordinary to manage the complexities of systemic change&#8217; Eric Schmidt, Technical Advisor, Alphabet, USA</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Money : Know More, Make More, Give More: Learn how to make more money and transform your life &#8211; Rob Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to get to the stage &#8211; soon &#8211; where you are truly financially independent, able to use your money in the way you&#8217;d like, and be completely confident in your ability to take care of yourself and your family? That is a universal desire, but many of us regard wealth and financial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/">Money : Know More, Make More, Give More: Learn how to make more money and transform your life &#8211; Rob Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to get to the stage &#8211; soon &#8211; where you are truly financially independent, able to use your money in the way you&#8217;d like, and be completely confident in your ability to take care of yourself and your family?     </p>
<p>                    That is a universal desire, but many of us regard wealth and financial independence as a goal which we&#8217;ll likely never achieve &#8211; there are just too many bills that need paying and there is a widespread belief that the money game is rigged. Even people who win the lottery or inherit money often seem to wind up losing it. The evidence suggests you can&#8217;t win a game that you don&#8217;t understand &#8211; even if you start out winning &#8211; because you never understood the game in the first place.    </p>
<p>                    So how can you win with money? How can you create independent wealth and hold on to it? This inspiring book by self-made multi-millionaire Rob Moore explains the rules of the game, shares simple tricks for managing money better, details how to create a plan for an ambitious future, and shows you the very best way to become a millionaire &#8211; to think and behave like one!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/">Money : Know More, Make More, Give More: Learn how to make more money and transform your life &#8211; Rob Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Other People&#8217;s Money : Masters of the Universe or Servants of the People? &#8211; John Kay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/other-peoples-money-masters-of-the-universe-or-servants-of-the-people-john-kay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/other-peoples-money-masters-of-the-universe-or-servants-of-the-people-john-kay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Orwell Prize 2016 We all depend on the finance sector. We need it to store our money, manage our payments, finance housing stock, restore infrastructure, fund retirement and support new business. But these roles comprise only a tiny sliver of the sector&#8217;s activity: the vast majority of lending is within the finance [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-peoples-money-masters-of-the-universe-or-servants-of-the-people-john-kay-abridged/">Other People&#8217;s Money : Masters of the Universe or Servants of the People? &#8211; John Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Orwell Prize 2016    </p>
<p>                    We all depend on the finance sector. We need it to store our money, manage our payments, finance housing stock, restore infrastructure, fund retirement and support new business. But these roles comprise only a tiny sliver of the sector&#8217;s activity: the vast majority of lending is within the finance sector. So what is it all for?  What is the purpose of this activity?  And why is it so profitable?    </p>
<p>                    John Kay, a distinguished economist with wide experience of the financial sector, argues that the industry&#8217;s perceived profitability is partly illusory, and partly an appropriation of wealth created elsewhere &#8211; of other people&#8217;s money. The financial sector, he shows, has grown too large, detached itself from ordinary business and everyday life, and has become an industry that mostly trades with itself, talks to itself, and judges itself by reference to standards which it has itself generated. And the outside world has itself adopted those standards, bailing out financial institutions that have failed all of us through greed and mismanagement.      </p>
<p>                    We need finance, but today we have far too much of a good thing. In Other People&#8217;s Money John Kay shows in his inimitable style what has gone wrong in the dark heart of finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-peoples-money-masters-of-the-universe-or-servants-of-the-people-john-kay-abridged/">Other People&#8217;s Money : Masters of the Universe or Servants of the People? &#8211; John Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
