<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>History: Specific Events &amp; Topics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/history-specific-events-topics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/history-specific-events-topics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>History: Specific Events &amp; Topics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/history-specific-events-topics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>A Year at the Chateau : As seen on the hit Channel 4 show &#8211; Dick Strawbridge</title>
		<link>/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Home Renovation & Extension]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV Tie-in Humour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE ENTERTAINING AND HEARTWARMING SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER. Like many couples, Dick and Angel had long dreamed of living in France, but where others might settle for a modest bolthole in the French countryside, the Strawbridges fell in love with a 19th-century fairytale chateau, complete with 45 rooms, seven outbuildings, 12 acres of land and its [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/">A Year at the Chateau : As seen on the hit Channel 4 show &#8211; Dick Strawbridge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE ENTERTAINING AND HEARTWARMING SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER.</p>
<p>                    Like many couples, Dick and Angel had long dreamed of living in France, but where others might settle for a modest bolthole in the French countryside, the Strawbridges fell in love with a 19th-century fairytale chateau, complete with 45 rooms, seven outbuildings, 12 acres of land and its own moat.</p>
<p>                    Throwing caution to the wind, Dick and Angel swapped their two-bedroom flat in East London for an abandoned and derelict castle in the heart of the Loire valley and embarked on the adventure of a lifetime with their two young children Arthur and Dorothy.</p>
<p>                    Sharing their full journey for the first time, A Year at the Chateau follows Dick and Angel from when they first moved to France in the depths of winter and found bedrooms infested with flies, turrets inhabited by bats, the wind rattling through cracked windows, and just one working toilet, which flushed into the moat, through to the monumental efforts that went into readying the chateau for their unforgettable wedding and their incredibly special first Christmas.</p>
<p>                    Along the way we&#8217;ll read glorious descriptions of rural life in France, with charming characters, delicious food and wonderful seasonal produce, together with the extraordinary list of renovations and restorations Dick and Angel completed, many of which were never shown on TV.</p>
<p>                    As warm and entertaining as their much-loved show, A Year at the Chateau is a truly irresistible story of adventure and heart, epic ambitions and a huge amount of hard graft.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-year-at-the-chateau-as-seen-on-the-hit-channel-4-show-dick-strawbridge/">A Year at the Chateau : As seen on the hit Channel 4 show &#8211; Dick Strawbridge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food    </p>
<p>                    There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; whole grains are healthy, whole grains are a disaster; eat everything in moderation; eat only certain foods&#8212;and on and on. In 100 Million Years of Food, biological anthropologist Stephen Le explains how cuisines of different cultures are a result of centuries of evolution, finely tuned to our biology and surroundings. Today many cultures have strayed from their ancestral diets, relying instead on mass-produced food often made with chemicals that may be contributing to a rise in so-called Western diseases, such as cancer, heart disease, and obesity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Colour : Travels Through the Paintbox &#8211; Victoria Finlay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/colour-travels-through-the-paintbox-victoria-finlay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paintings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/colour-travels-through-the-paintbox-victoria-finlay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A rare and wonderful book&#8230; I could not be more enthusiastic.&#8217; Simon Winchester &#8216;A treasure trove of human history and obsession&#8230;the breadth of research and insight is dazzling.&#8217; Glasgow Herald Colour unlocks the history of the colours of the rainbow, and reveals how paints came to be invented, discovered, traded and used. This remarkable and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/colour-travels-through-the-paintbox-victoria-finlay-abridged/">Colour : Travels Through the Paintbox &#8211; Victoria Finlay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A rare and wonderful book&#8230; I could not be more enthusiastic.&#8217; Simon Winchester    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A treasure trove of human history and obsession&#8230;the breadth of research and insight is dazzling.&#8217; Glasgow Herald    </p>
<p>                    Colour unlocks the history of the colours of the rainbow, and reveals how paints came to be invented, discovered, traded and used. This remarkable and beautifully written book, part travelogue part narrative history, remembers a time when red paint was really the colour of blood, when orange was the poison pigment, blue as expensive as gold, and yellow made from the urine of cows force-fed with mangoes. It looks at how green was carried by yaks along the silk road, and how an entire nation was founded on the colour purple.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A highly companionable guide, adventurous and romantic&#8217; Independent on Sunday    </p>
<p>                    Exciting, richly informative, and always surprising, Colour lifts the lid on the historical palette and unearths an astonishing wealth of stories about the quest for colours, and our efforts to understand them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/colour-travels-through-the-paintbox-victoria-finlay-abridged/">Colour : Travels Through the Paintbox &#8211; Victoria Finlay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Doubt : A History &#8211; Jennifer Hecht (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/doubt-a-history-jennifer-hecht-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Epistemology & Theory Of Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy, From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/doubt-a-history-jennifer-hecht-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the tradition of grand sweeping histories such as From Dawn To Decadence, The Structure of Scientific Revolutions, and A History of God, Hecht champions doubt and questioning as one of the great and noble, if unheralded, intellectual traditions that distinguish the Western mind especially-from Socrates to Galileo and Darwin to Wittgenstein and Hawking. This [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/doubt-a-history-jennifer-hecht-abridged/">Doubt : A History &#8211; Jennifer Hecht (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the tradition of grand sweeping histories such as From Dawn To Decadence, The Structure of Scientific Revolutions, and A History of God, Hecht champions doubt and questioning as one of the great and noble, if unheralded, intellectual traditions that distinguish the Western mind especially-from Socrates to Galileo and Darwin to Wittgenstein and Hawking. This is an account of the world&#8217;s greatest &#8216;intellectual virtuosos, &#8216; who are also humanity&#8217;s greatest doubters and disbelievers, from the ancient Greek philosophers, Jesus, and the Eastern religions, to modern secular equivalents Marx, Freud and Darwin&#8211;and their attempts to reconcile the seeming meaninglessness of the universe with the human need for meaning,     </p>
<p>                    This remarkable book ranges from the early Greeks, Hebrew figures such as Job and Ecclesiastes, Eastern critical wisdom, Roman stoicism, Jesus as a man of doubt, Gnosticism and Christian mystics, medieval Islamic, Jewish and Christian skeptics, secularism, the rise of science, modern and contemporary critical thinkers such as Schopenhauer, Darwin, Marx, Freud, Nietzsche, the existentialists.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/doubt-a-history-jennifer-hecht-abridged/">Doubt : A History &#8211; Jennifer Hecht (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Personality Brokers : The Strange History of Myers-Briggs and the Birth of Personality Testing &#8211; Merve Emre (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-personality-brokers-the-strange-history-of-myers-briggs-and-the-birth-of-personality-testing-merve-emre-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-personality-brokers-the-strange-history-of-myers-briggs-and-the-birth-of-personality-testing-merve-emre-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An unprecedented history of the personality test conceived a century ago by a mother and her daughter&#8211;fiction writers with no formal training in psychology&#8211;and how it insinuated itself into our boardrooms, classrooms, and beyond. The basis for the HBO Max documentary, Persona The Myers-Briggs Type Indicator is the most popular personality test in the world. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personality-brokers-the-strange-history-of-myers-briggs-and-the-birth-of-personality-testing-merve-emre-abridged/">The Personality Brokers : The Strange History of Myers-Briggs and the Birth of Personality Testing &#8211; Merve Emre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An unprecedented history of the personality test conceived a century ago by a mother and her daughter&#8211;fiction writers with no formal training in psychology&#8211;and how it insinuated itself into our boardrooms, classrooms, and beyond. The basis for the HBO Max documentary, Persona    </p>
<p>                    The Myers-Briggs Type Indicator is the most popular personality test in the world. It is used regularly by Fortune 500 companies, universities, hospitals, churches, and the military. Its language of personality types&#8211;extraversion and introversion, sensing and intuiting, thinking and feeling, judging and perceiving&#8211;has inspired television shows, online dating platforms, and Buzzfeed quizzes. Yet despite the test&#8217;s widespread adoption, experts in the field of psychometric testing, a $2 billion industry, have struggled to validate its results&#8211;no less account for its success. How did Myers-Briggs, a homegrown multiple choice questionnaire, infiltrate our workplaces, our relationships, our Internet, our lives?     </p>
<p>                    First conceived in the 1920s by the mother-daughter team of Katherine Briggs and Isabel Briggs Myers, a pair of devoted homemakers, novelists, and amateur psychoanalysts, Myers-Briggs was designed to bring the gospel of Carl Jung to the masses. But it would take on a life entirely its own, reaching from the smoke-filled boardrooms of mid-century New York to Berkeley, California, where it was administered to some of the twentieth century&#8217;s greatest creative minds. It would travel across the world to London, Zurich, Cape Town, Melbourne, and Tokyo, until it could be found just as easily in elementary schools, nunneries, and wellness retreats as in shadowy political consultancies and on social networks.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing from original reporting and never-before-published documents, The Personality Brokers takes a critical look at the personality indicator that became a cultural icon. Along the way it examines nothing less than the definition of the self&#8211;our attempts to grasp, categorize, and quantify our personalities. Surprising and absorbing, the book, like the test at its heart, considers the timeless question: What makes you, you?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personality-brokers-the-strange-history-of-myers-briggs-and-the-birth-of-personality-testing-merve-emre-abridged/">The Personality Brokers : The Strange History of Myers-Briggs and the Birth of Personality Testing &#8211; Merve Emre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
