<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Manufacturing Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/manufacturing-industries/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/manufacturing-industries/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Manufacturing Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/manufacturing-industries/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Reinventing the Product : How to Transform your Business and Create Value in the Digital Age &#8211; Eric Schaeffer, David Sovie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reinventing-the-product-how-to-transform-your-business-and-create-value-in-the-digital-age-eric-schaeffer-david-sovie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reinventing-the-product-how-to-transform-your-business-and-create-value-in-the-digital-age-eric-schaeffer-david-sovie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Create the personalized and compelling experiences that today&#8217;s customers expect by harnessing AI and digital technologies to create smart connected products, with this cutting-edge guide from senior leaders at Accenture. Digital technology is both friend and foe: highly disruptive, yet it cannot be ignored. As traditional products transform into smart connected products faster than ever [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reinventing-the-product-how-to-transform-your-business-and-create-value-in-the-digital-age-eric-schaeffer-david-sovie-abridged/">Reinventing the Product : How to Transform your Business and Create Value in the Digital Age &#8211; Eric Schaeffer, David Sovie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Create the personalized and compelling experiences that today&#8217;s customers expect by harnessing AI and digital technologies to create smart connected products, with this cutting-edge guide from senior leaders at Accenture.      </p>
<p>                    Digital technology is both friend and foe: highly disruptive, yet it cannot be ignored. As traditional products transform into smart connected products faster than ever before, companies that fail to make use of it now put themselves in the firing line for disintermediation or even eradication.     </p>
<p>                    However, digital technology is also the biggest opportunity for product-making businesses to create the next generation of goods in the marketplace. In Reinventing the Product, Eric Schaeffer and David Sovie, both Senior Managing Directors at Accenture, show how this reinvention is made possible, to deliver truly intelligent, and often even autonomous, products.     </p>
<p>                    Reinventing the Product makes the case for companies to rethink their product strategy, innovation and engineering processes, including:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; How to harness the opportunities of AI and digital technologies, such as IoT sensors, blockchain, advanced analytics, cloud and edge computing<br />
                    &#8211; Practical advice on transforming their entire culture to build the future of successful &#8216;living products&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Features case studies from global organizations such as Faurecia, Signify, Symmons and Haier and interviews with thought leaders from top companies including Amazon, ABB, Tesla, Samsung and Google    </p>
<p>                    This book provides the only advice any product-making company needs as it embarks on, or accelerates, its digitization journey.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reinventing-the-product-how-to-transform-your-business-and-create-value-in-the-digital-age-eric-schaeffer-david-sovie-abridged/">Reinventing the Product : How to Transform your Business and Create Value in the Digital Age &#8211; Eric Schaeffer, David Sovie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Race : The Global Quest for the Car of the Future &#8211; Levi Tillemann (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-great-race-the-global-quest-for-the-car-of-the-future-levi-tillemann-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automotive Technology & Trades]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motor Cars]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Road & Motor Vehicles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Road Vehicle Manufacturing Industry]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-race-the-global-quest-for-the-car-of-the-future-levi-tillemann-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Great Race recounts the exciting story of a century-long battle among automakers for market share, profit, and technological dominance&#8211;and the thrilling race to build the car of the future. The world&#8217;s great manufacturing juggernaut&#8211;the $3 trillion automotive industry&#8211;is in the throes of a revolution. Its future will include cars Henry Ford and Karl Benz [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-race-the-global-quest-for-the-car-of-the-future-levi-tillemann-abridged/">The Great Race : The Global Quest for the Car of the Future &#8211; Levi Tillemann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Great Race recounts the exciting story of a century-long battle among automakers for market share, profit, and technological dominance&#8211;and the thrilling race to build the car of the future.     </p>
<p>                    The world&#8217;s great manufacturing juggernaut&#8211;the $3 trillion automotive industry&#8211;is in the throes of a revolution. Its future will include cars Henry Ford and Karl Benz could scarcely imagine. They will drive themselves, won&#8217;t consume oil, and will come in radical shapes and sizes. But the path to that future is fraught. The top contenders are two traditional manufacturing giants, the US and Japan, and a newcomer, China.     </p>
<p>                    Team America has a powerful and little-known weapon in its arsenal: a small group of technology buffs and regulators from California. The story of why and how these men and women could shape the future&#8211;how you move, how you work, how you live on Earth&#8211;is an unexpected tale filled with unforgettable characters: a scorned chemistry professor, a South African visionary who went for broke, an ambitious Chinese ex-pat, a quixotic Japanese nuclear engineer, and a string of billion-dollar wagers by governments and corporations.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;To explain the scramble for the next-generation auto&#8211;and the roles played in that race by governments, auto makers, venture capitalists, environmentalists, and private inventors&#8211;comes Levi Tillemann&#8217;s The Great Race&#8230;Mr. Tillemann seems ideally cast to guide us through the big ideas percolating in the world&#8217;s far-flung workshops and labs&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal). His account is incisive and riveting, explaining how America bounced back in this global contest and what it will take to command the industrial future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-race-the-global-quest-for-the-car-of-the-future-levi-tillemann-abridged/">The Great Race : The Global Quest for the Car of the Future &#8211; Levi Tillemann (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fabricated : The New World of 3D Printing &#8211; Hod Lipson, Melba Kurman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3D Graphics & Modelling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fabricated tells the story of 3D printers, humble manufacturing machines that are bursting out of the factory and into schools, kitchens, hospitals, even onto the fashion catwalk. Fabricated describes our emerging world of printable products, where people design and 3D print their own creations as easily as they edit an online document. A 3D printer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/">Fabricated : The New World of 3D Printing &#8211; Hod Lipson, Melba Kurman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fabricated tells the story of 3D printers, humble manufacturing machines that are bursting out of the factory and into schools, kitchens, hospitals, even onto the fashion catwalk. Fabricated describes our emerging world of printable products, where people design and 3D print their own creations as easily as they edit an online document. A 3D printer transforms digital information into a physical object by carrying out instructions from an electronic design file, or &#8216;blueprint.&#8217; Guided by a design file, a 3D printer lays down layer after layer of a raw material to &#8216;print&#8217; out an object. That&#8217;s not the whole story, however. The magic happens when you plug a 3D printer into today s mind-boggling digital technologies. Add to that the Internet, tiny, low cost electronic circuitry, radical advances in materials science and biotech and voila! The result is an explosion of technological and social innovation. Fabricated takes the reader onto a rich and fulfilling journey that explores how 3D printing is poised to impact nearly every part of our lives.<br />
                    Aimed at people who enjoy books on business strategy, popular science and novel technology, Fabricated will provide readers with practical and imaginative insights to the question &#8216;how will this technology change my life?&#8217; Based on hundreds of hours of research and dozens of interviews with experts from a broad range of industries, Fabricated offers readers an informative, engaging and fast-paced introduction to 3D printing now and in the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/">Fabricated : The New World of 3D Printing &#8211; Hod Lipson, Melba Kurman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Intel Trinity : How Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove Built the World&#8217;s Most Important Company &#8211; Michael S. Malone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-intel-trinity-how-robert-noyce-gordon-moore-and-andy-grove-built-the-worlds-most-important-company-michael-s-malone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-intel-trinity-how-robert-noyce-gordon-moore-and-andy-grove-built-the-worlds-most-important-company-michael-s-malone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Based on unprecedented access to the corporation&#8217;s archives, The Intel Trinity is the first full history of Intel Corporation-the essential company of the digital age- told through the lives of the three most important figures in the company&#8217;s history: Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove. Often hailed the &#8220;most important company in the world,&#8221; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-intel-trinity-how-robert-noyce-gordon-moore-and-andy-grove-built-the-worlds-most-important-company-michael-s-malone-abridged/">The Intel Trinity : How Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove Built the World&#8217;s Most Important Company &#8211; Michael S. Malone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Based on unprecedented access to the corporation&#8217;s archives, The Intel Trinity is the first full history of Intel Corporation-the essential company of the digital age- told through the lives of the three most important figures in the company&#8217;s history: Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove.  Often hailed the &#8220;most important company in the world,&#8221; Intel remains, more than four decades after its inception, a defining company of the global digital economy. The legendary inventors of the microprocessor-the single most important product in the modern world-Intel today builds the tiny &#8220;engines&#8221; that power almost every intelligent electronic device on the planet.  But the true story of Intel is the human story of the trio of geniuses behind it. Michael S. Malone reveals how each brought different things to Intel, and at different times. Noyce, the most respected high tech figure of his generation, brought credibility (and money) to the company&#8217;s founding; Moore made Intel the world&#8217;s technological leader; and Grove, has relentlessly driven the company to ever-higher levels of success and competitiveness.<br />
                    Without any one of these figures, Intel would never have achieved its historic success; with them, Intel made possible the personal computer, Internet, telecommunications, and the personal electronics revolutions.  The Intel Trinity is not just the story of Intel&#8217;s legendary past; it also offers an analysis of the formidable challenges that lie ahead as the company struggles to maintain its dominance, its culture, and its legacy.  With eight pages of black-and-white photos.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-intel-trinity-how-robert-noyce-gordon-moore-and-andy-grove-built-the-worlds-most-important-company-michael-s-malone-abridged/">The Intel Trinity : How Robert Noyce, Gordon Moore, and Andy Grove Built the World&#8217;s Most Important Company &#8211; Michael S. Malone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Autonomy : The Quest to Build the Driverless Car-And How It Will Reshape Our World &#8211; Lawrence D. Burns, Christopher Shulgan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automotive Technology & Trades]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Road Vehicle Manufacturing Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transport Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An automotive and tech world insider investigates the quest to develop and perfect the driverless car&#8211;an innovation that promises to be the most disruptive change to our way of life since the smartphone We stand on the brink of a technological revolution. Soon, few of us will own our own automobiles and instead will get [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/">Autonomy : The Quest to Build the Driverless Car-And How It Will Reshape Our World &#8211; Lawrence D. Burns, Christopher Shulgan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An automotive and tech world insider investigates the quest to develop and perfect the driverless car&#8211;an innovation that promises to be the most disruptive change to our way of life since the smartphone    </p>
<p>                    We stand on the brink of a technological revolution. Soon, few of us will own our own automobiles and instead will get around in driverless electric vehicles that we summon with the touch of an app. We will be liberated from driving, prevent over 90% of car crashes, provide freedom of mobility to the elderly and disabled, and decrease our dependence on fossil fuels.     </p>
<p>                    Autonomy is the story of the maverick engineers and computer nerds who are creating the revolution. Longtime advisor to the Google Self-Driving Car team and former GM research and development chief Lawrence D. Burns provides the perfectly-timed history of how we arrived at this point, in a character-driven and heavily reported account of the unlikely thinkers who accomplished what billion-dollar automakers never dared.    </p>
<p>                    Beginning with the way 9/11 spurred the U.S. government to set a million-dollar prize for a series of off-road robot races in the Mojave Desert up to the early 2016 stampede to develop driverless technology, Autonomy is a page-turner that represents a chronicle of the past, diagnosis of the present, and prediction of the future&#8211;the ultimate guide to understanding the driverless car and navigating the revolution it sparks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/">Autonomy : The Quest to Build the Driverless Car-And How It Will Reshape Our World &#8211; Lawrence D. Burns, Christopher Shulgan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper : How Innovation Keeps Proving the Catastrophists Wrong &#8211; Robert Bryce (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/smaller-faster-lighter-denser-cheaper-how-innovation-keeps-proving-the-catastrophists-wrong-robert-bryce-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nanotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/smaller-faster-lighter-denser-cheaper-how-innovation-keeps-proving-the-catastrophists-wrong-robert-bryce-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the face of today&#8217;s environmental and economic challenges, doomsayers preach that the only way to stave off disaster is for humans to reverse course: to de-industrialize, re-localize, ban the use of modern energy sources, and forswear prosperity. But in this provocative and optimistic rebuke to the catastrophists, Robert Bryce shows how innovation and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smaller-faster-lighter-denser-cheaper-how-innovation-keeps-proving-the-catastrophists-wrong-robert-bryce-abridged/">Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper : How Innovation Keeps Proving the Catastrophists Wrong &#8211; Robert Bryce (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the face of today&#8217;s environmental and economic challenges, doomsayers preach that the only way to stave off disaster is for humans to reverse course: to de-industrialize, re-localize, ban the use of modern energy sources, and forswear prosperity. But in this provocative and optimistic rebuke to the catastrophists, Robert Bryce shows how innovation and the inexorable human desire to make things Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper is providing consumers with Cheaper and more abundant energy, Faster computing, Lighter vehicles, and myriad other goods. That same desire is fostering unprecedented prosperity, greater liberty, and yes, better environmental protection.Utilizing on-the-ground reporting from Ottawa to Panama City and Pittsburgh to Bakersfield, Bryce shows how we have, for centuries, been pushing for Smaller Faster solutions to our problems. From the vacuum tube, mass-produced fertilizer, and the printing press to mobile phones, nanotech, and advanced drill rigs, Bryce demonstrates how cutting-edge companies and breakthrough technologies have created a world in which people are living longer, freer, healthier, lives than at any time in human history.The push toward Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper is happening across multiple sectors. Bryce profiles innovative individuals and companies, from long-established ones like Ford and Intel to upstarts like Aquion Energy and Khan Academy. And he zeroes in on the energy industry, proving that the future belongs to the high power density sources that can provide the enormous quantities of energy the world demands.The tools we need to save the planet aren&#8217;t to be found in the technologies or lifestyles of the past. Nor must we sacrifice prosperity and human progress to ensure our survival. The catastrophists have been wrong since the days of Thomas Malthus. This is the time to embrace the innovators and businesses all over the world who are making things Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smaller-faster-lighter-denser-cheaper-how-innovation-keeps-proving-the-catastrophists-wrong-robert-bryce-abridged/">Smaller Faster Lighter Denser Cheaper : How Innovation Keeps Proving the Catastrophists Wrong &#8211; Robert Bryce (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Machine That Changed the World &#8211; James P. Womack, Daniel T. Jones, Daniel Roos (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-machine-that-changed-the-world-james-p-womack-daniel-t-jones-daniel-roos-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-machine-that-changed-the-world-james-p-womack-daniel-t-jones-daniel-roos-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When James Womack, Daniel Jones, and Daniel Roos wrote THE MACHINE THAT CHANGED THE WORLD in 1990, Japanese automakers, and Toyota in particular, were making a strong showing by applying the principles of lean production. However, the full power of lean principles was unproven, and they had not been applied outside of the auto industry. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-machine-that-changed-the-world-james-p-womack-daniel-t-jones-daniel-roos-abridged/">The Machine That Changed the World &#8211; James P. Womack, Daniel T. Jones, Daniel Roos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When James Womack, Daniel Jones, and Daniel Roos wrote THE MACHINE THAT CHANGED THE WORLD in 1990, Japanese automakers, and Toyota in particular, were making a strong showing by applying the principles of lean production. However, the full power of lean principles was unproven, and they had not been applied outside of the auto industry. Today, the power of lean production has been conclusively proved by Toyota&#8217;s unparalleled success, and the concepts have been widely applied in many industries. Based on MIT&#8217;s pioneering global study of industrial competition, THE MACHINE THAT CHANGED THE WORLD offers a groundbreaking analysis of the entire lean business system, including product development, supplier management, sales, service, and production &#8211; an analysis even more relevant today as GM and Ford struggle to survive and a wide range of British abd American companies embrace lean production. A new Foreword by the authors brings the story up to date and details how their predictions were right. As a result, this reissue of a classic is as insightful and instructive today as when it was first published.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-machine-that-changed-the-world-james-p-womack-daniel-t-jones-daniel-roos-abridged/">The Machine That Changed the World &#8211; James P. Womack, Daniel T. Jones, Daniel Roos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*#GIRLBOSS NETFLIX ORIGINAL OUT NOW* In this New York Times bestselling sensation, founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal Sophia Amoruso shares her story and inspires women everywhere to join the #GIRLBOSS movement. &#8216;#GIRLBOSS is more than a book . . . #GIRLBOSS is a movement&#8217; Lena Dunham &#8216;A millennial alternative to Lean In&#8217; New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/">#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*#GIRLBOSS NETFLIX ORIGINAL OUT NOW*    </p>
<p>                    In this New York Times bestselling sensation, founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal Sophia Amoruso shares her story and inspires women everywhere to join the #GIRLBOSS movement.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;#GIRLBOSS is more than a book . . . #GIRLBOSS is a movement&#8217; Lena Dunham    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A millennial alternative to Lean In&#8217; New York Magazine    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compellingly motivational read&#8217; The Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The book you need in your life&#8217; Marie Claire     </p>
<p>                    *Winner of the 2014 Goodreads Choice Award for Best Business Book*    </p>
<p>                    In the space of ten years, Sophia Amoruso has gone from high-school dropout to founder and Executive Chairman of Nasty Gal, one of the fastest-growing retailers in the world.     </p>
<p>                    Sophia&#8217;s never been a typical executive, or a typical anything, and she&#8217;s written #GIRLBOSS for other girls like her: outsiders (and insiders) seeking a unique path to success.    </p>
<p>                    Filled with brazen wake-up calls, cunning and frank observations, and behind-the-scenes stories from Nasty Gal&#8217;s meteoric rise, #GIRLBOSS covers a lot of ground. It proves that success doesn&#8217;t come from where you went to college or how popular you were in school. Success is about trusting your instincts and following your gut, knowing which rules to follow and which to break.    </p>
<p>                    Inspiring, motivating and empowering, #GIRLBOSS will give you the kick up the ass you need to reach your potential.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girlboss-sophia-amoruso-abridged/">#Girlboss &#8211; Sophia Amoruso (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Golden Thread : How Fabric Changed History &#8211; Kassia St Clair (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-golden-thread-how-fabric-changed-history-kassia-st-clair-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History: From c 1960]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fashion & Textiles: Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Earliest Times To Present Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrialisation & Industrial History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Needlework & Fabric Crafts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Textile Artworks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Textile Design & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Textile Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-golden-thread-how-fabric-changed-history-kassia-st-clair-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** A RADIO 4 BOOK OF THE WEEK ** &#8216;Fascinating . . . The history of the world through the eye of a needle . . . I recommend this book to anyone&#8217; THE SPECTATOR &#8216;A charming, absorbing and history that takes us on a journey from the silk roads to sportswear, from ruffs to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-golden-thread-how-fabric-changed-history-kassia-st-clair-abridged/">The Golden Thread : How Fabric Changed History &#8211; Kassia St Clair (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** A RADIO 4 BOOK OF THE WEEK **    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating . . . The history of the world through the eye of a needle . . . I recommend this book to anyone&#8217; THE SPECTATOR<br />
                    &#8216;A charming, absorbing and history that takes us on a journey from the silk roads to sportswear, from ruffs to spacesuits . . . I devoured this quietly feminist book&#8217; SUNDAY TIMES<br />
                    &#8216;Joyful and beautiful&#8217; NATURE<br />
                    &#8216;Will make you rethink your relationship with fabric&#8217; ELLE DECORATION    </p>
<p>                    All textiles begin with a twist. From colourful 30,000-year old threads found on the floor of a Georgian cave to what the linen wrappings of Tutankhamun&#8217;s mummy actually meant; from the Silk Roads to the woollen sails that helped the Vikings reach America 700 years before Columbus; from the lace ruffs that infuriated the puritans to the Indian calicoes and chintzes that powered the Industrial Revolution, our continuing reinvention of cloth tells fascinating stories of human ingenuity.     </p>
<p>                    When we talk of lives hanging by a thread, being interwoven, or part of the social fabric, we are part of a tradition that stretches back many thousands of years. Fabric has allowed us to achieve extraordinary things and survive in unlikely places, and this book shows you how &#8212; and why.    </p>
<p>                    With a cast that includes Chinese empresses, Richard the Lionheart and Bing Crosby, Kassia St Clair takes us on the run with escaped slaves, climbing the slopes of Everest and moonwalking with astronauts. Running like a bright line through history, The Golden Thread offers an unforgettable adventure through our past, present and future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-golden-thread-how-fabric-changed-history-kassia-st-clair-abridged/">The Golden Thread : How Fabric Changed History &#8211; Kassia St Clair (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epidemiology & Medical Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmacology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated with bonus material, including a new foreword and afterword with new research, this New York Times bestseller is essential reading for a time when mental health is constantly in the news. In this astonishing and startling book, award-winning science and history writer Robert Whitaker investigates a medical mystery: Why has the number of disabled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/">Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated with bonus material, including a new foreword and afterword with new research, this New York Times bestseller is essential reading for a time when mental health is constantly in the news.     </p>
<p>                    In this astonishing and startling book, award-winning science and history writer Robert Whitaker investigates a medical mystery: Why has the number of disabled mentally ill in the United States tripled over the past two decades?     </p>
<p>                    Interwoven with Whitaker&#8217;s groundbreaking analysis of the merits of psychiatric medications are the personal stories of children and adults swept up in this epidemic. As Anatomy of an Epidemic reveals, other societies have begun to alter their use of psychiatric medications and are now reporting much improved outcomes . . . so why can&#8217;t such change happen here in the United States? Why have the results from these long-term studies&#8211;all of which point to the same startling conclusion&#8211;been kept from the public?     </p>
<p>                    Our nation has been hit by an epidemic of disabling mental illness, and yet, as Anatomy of an Epidemic reveals, the medical blueprints for curbing that epidemic have already been drawn up.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Anatomy of an Epidemic     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The timing of Robert Whitaker&#8217;s Anatomy of an Epidemic, a comprehensive and highly readable history of psychiatry in the United States, couldn&#8217;t be better.&#8221;&#8211;Salon     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Anatomy of an Epidemic offers some answers, charting controversial ground with mystery-novel pacing.&#8221;&#8211;TIME     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Lucid, pointed and important, Anatomy of an Epidemic should be required reading for anyone considering extended use of psychiatric medicine. Whitaker is at the height of his powers.&#8221; &#8211;Greg Critser, author of Generation Rx</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/">Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Hillbilly Elegy and Strangers in Their Own Land *A New York Post Must-Read Book* *A Newsweek Best New Book* *One of The Week&#8217;s 20 Books to Read in 2017* *One of Bustle&#8217;s 16 Best Nonfiction Books Coming in February 2017* *Best Non-Fiction/2017 Books by the Banks* The Wall Street Journal: A devastating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/">Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Hillbilly Elegy and Strangers in Their Own Land     </p>
<p>                    *A New York Post Must-Read Book*<br />
                    *A Newsweek Best New Book*<br />
                    *One of The Week&#8217;s 20 Books to Read in 2017*<br />
                    *One of Bustle&#8217;s 16 Best Nonfiction Books Coming in February 2017*<br />
                    *Best Non-Fiction/2017 Books by the Banks*     </p>
<p>                    The Wall Street Journal: A devastating portrait&#8230;For anyone wondering why swing-state America voted against the establishment in 2016, Mr. Alexander supplies plenty of answers.      </p>
<p>                    Laura Miller, Slate: This book hunts bigger game. Reads like an odd&#8211;and oddly satisfying&#8211;fusion of George Packer&#8217;s The Unwinding and one of Michael Lewis&#8217; real-life financial thrillers.     </p>
<p>                    The New Yorker: Does a remarkable job.     </p>
<p>                    Beth Macy, author of Factory Man: This book should be required reading for people trying to understand Trumpism, inequality, and the sad state of a needlessly wrecked rural America. I wish I had written it.      </p>
<p>                    In 1947, Forbes magazine declared Lancaster, Ohio the epitome of the all-American town. Today it is damaged, discouraged, and fighting for its future. In Glass House, journalist Brian Alexander uses the story of one town to show how seeds sown 35 years ago have sprouted to give us Trumpism, inequality, and an eroding national cohesion.     </p>
<p>                    The Anchor Hocking Glass Company, once the world&#8217;s largest maker of glass tableware, was the base on which Lancaster&#8217;s society was built. As Glass House unfolds, bankruptcy looms. With access to the company and its leaders, and Lancaster&#8217;s citizens, Alexander shows how financial engineering took hold in the 1980s, accelerated in the 21st Century, and wrecked the company. We follow CEO Sam Solomon, an African-American leading the nearly all-white town&#8217;s biggest private employer, as he tries to rescue the company from the New York private equity firm that hired him. Meanwhile, Alexander goes behind the scenes, entwined with the lives of residents as they wrestle with heroin, politics, high-interest lenders, low wage jobs, technology, and the new demands of American life: people like Brian Gossett, the fourth generation to work at Anchor Hocking; Joe Piccolo, first-time director of the annual music festival who discovers the town relies on him, and it, for salvation; Jason Roach, who police believed may have been Lancaster&#8217;s biggest drug dealer; and Eric Brown, a local football hero-turned-cop who comes to realize that he can never arrest Lancaster&#8217;s real problems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/">Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The One Device : The Secret History of the iPhone &#8211; Brian Merchant (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-one-device-the-secret-history-of-the-iphone-brian-merchant-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hi-tech Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phone Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-one-device-the-secret-history-of-the-iphone-brian-merchant-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The secret history of the invention that changed everything and became the most profitable product in the world. Odds are that as you read this, an iPhone is within reach. But before Steve Jobs introduced us to &#8216;the one device&#8217;, as he called it, a mobile phone was merely what you used to make calls [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-one-device-the-secret-history-of-the-iphone-brian-merchant-abridged/">The One Device : The Secret History of the iPhone &#8211; Brian Merchant (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The secret history of the invention that changed everything and became the most profitable product in the world.    </p>
<p>                    Odds are that as you read this, an iPhone is within reach. But before Steve Jobs introduced us to &#8216;the one device&#8217;, as he called it, a mobile phone was merely what you used to make calls on the go.    </p>
<p>                    How did the iPhone transform our world and turn Apple into the most valuable company ever? Veteran technology journalist Brian Merchant reveals the inside story you won&#8217;t hear from Cupertino &#8211; based on his exclusive interviews with the engineers, inventors and developers who guided every stage of the iPhone&#8217;s creation.    </p>
<p>                    This deep dive takes you from inside 1 Infinite Loop to nineteenth-century France to WWII America, from the driest place on earth to a Kenyan pit of toxic e-waste, and even deep inside Shenzhen&#8217;s notorious &#8216;suicide factories&#8217;. It&#8217;s a first-hand look at how the cutting-edge tech that makes the world work &#8211; touch screens, motion trackers and even AI &#8211; made its way into our pockets.    </p>
<p>                    The One Device is a road map for design and engineering genius, an anthropology of the modern age and an unprecedented view into one of the most secretive companies in history. This is the untold account, ten years in the making, of the device that changed everything.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-one-device-the-secret-history-of-the-iphone-brian-merchant-abridged/">The One Device : The Secret History of the iPhone &#8211; Brian Merchant (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Empire of Cotton : A New History of Global Capitalism &#8211; Sven Beckert (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colonialism & Imperialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Textile Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE 2015 BANCROFT PRIZE WINNER OF THE 2015 PHILIP TAFT PRIZE FINALIST FOR THE 2015 PULITZER PRIZE FOR HISTORY SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2015 CUNDHILL PRIZE IN HISTORICAL LITERATURE Economist BOOKS OF THE YEAR 2015 &#8216;Knowledgeable and stunning&#8217; Orhan Pamuk &#8216;A masterpiece of the historian&#8217;s craft&#8217; The Nation For about 900 years, from 1000 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/">Empire of Cotton : A New History of Global Capitalism &#8211; Sven Beckert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE 2015 BANCROFT PRIZE<br />
                    WINNER OF THE 2015 PHILIP TAFT PRIZE<br />
                    FINALIST FOR THE 2015 PULITZER PRIZE FOR HISTORY<br />
                    SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2015 CUNDHILL PRIZE IN HISTORICAL LITERATURE<br />
                    Economist BOOKS OF THE YEAR 2015    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Knowledgeable and stunning&#8217; Orhan Pamuk     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A masterpiece of the historian&#8217;s craft&#8217; The Nation    </p>
<p>                    For about 900 years, from 1000 to 1900, cotton was the world&#8217;s most important manufacturing industry. It remains a vast business &#8211; if all the cotton bales produced in 2013 had been stacked on top of each other they would have made a somewhat unstable tower 40,000 miles high.      </p>
<p>                    Sven Beckert&#8217;s superb new book is a history of the overwhelming role played by cotton in dictating the shape of our world. It is both a gripping narrative and a brilliant case history of how the world works.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/">Empire of Cotton : A New History of Global Capitalism &#8211; Sven Beckert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
