<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Historical Fiction Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/historical-fiction/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/historical-fiction/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Historical Fiction Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/historical-fiction/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Tattooist of Auschwitz : the heart-breaking and unforgettable international bestseller &#8211; Heather Morris</title>
		<link>/the-tattooist-of-auschwitz-the-heart-breaking-and-unforgettable-international-bestseller-heather-morris/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tattooist-of-auschwitz-the-heart-breaking-and-unforgettable-international-bestseller-heather-morris/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the bestselling books of the 21st century with over 6 million copies sold. Don&#8217;t miss the conclusion to The Tattooist of Auschwitz Trilogy, Three Sisters. Available now. I tattooed a number on her arm. She tattooed her name on my heart. In 1942, Lale Sokolov arrived in Auschwitz-Birkenau. He was given the job [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tattooist-of-auschwitz-the-heart-breaking-and-unforgettable-international-bestseller-heather-morris/">The Tattooist of Auschwitz : the heart-breaking and unforgettable international bestseller &#8211; Heather Morris</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the bestselling books of the 21st century with over 6 million copies sold.</p>
<p>Don&#8217;t miss the conclusion to The Tattooist of Auschwitz Trilogy, Three Sisters. Available now.</p>
<p>I tattooed a number on her arm. She tattooed her name on my heart.</p>
<p>In 1942, Lale Sokolov arrived in Auschwitz-Birkenau. He was given the  job   of tattooing the prisoners marked for survival &#8211; scratching  numbers  into  his fellow victims&#8217; arms in indelible ink to create what  would  become  one of the most potent symbols of the Holocaust.</p>
<p>Waiting   in line  to be tattooed, terrified and shaking, was a young girl. For   Lale &#8211; a  dandy, a jack-the-lad, a bit of a chancer &#8211; it was love at   first sight.  And he was determined not only to survive himself, but to   ensure this  woman, Gita, did, too.</p>
<p>So begins one of the most   life-affirming,  courageous, unforgettable and human stories of the   Holocaust: the love  story of the tattooist of Auschwitz.</p>
<p>Discover Cilka&#8217;s Journey, the incredible bestselling sequel to The Tattooist of Auschwitz. Out now.</p>
<p>&#8212;&#8211;</p>
<p>&#8216;Extraordinary &#8211; moving, confronting and uplifting . . . I recommend it unreservedly&#8217; Greame Simsion</p>
<p>&#8216;A moving and ultimately uplifting story of love, loyalties and friendship amidst the horrors of war . . . It&#8217;s a triumph.&#8217; Jill Mansell</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tattooist-of-auschwitz-the-heart-breaking-and-unforgettable-international-bestseller-heather-morris/">The Tattooist of Auschwitz : the heart-breaking and unforgettable international bestseller &#8211; Heather Morris</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Corruption of Blood &#8211; Ambrose Parry</title>
		<link>/a-corruption-of-blood-ambrose-parry/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Adventure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-corruption-of-blood-ambrose-parry/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Raven and Fisher Mystery: Book 3 Edinburgh, 1850. This city will bleed you dry. Dr Will Raven is a man seldom shocked by human remains, but even he is disturbed by the contents of a package washed up at the Port of Leith. Stranger still, a man Raven has long detested is pleading for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-corruption-of-blood-ambrose-parry/">A Corruption of Blood &#8211; Ambrose Parry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Raven and Fisher Mystery: Book 3    </p>
<p>                    Edinburgh, 1850. This city will bleed you dry.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Will Raven is a man seldom shocked by human remains, but even he is disturbed by the contents of a package washed up at the Port of Leith. Stranger still, a man Raven has long detested is pleading for his help to escape the hangman.    </p>
<p>                    Back in the townhouse of Dr James Simpson, Sarah Fisher has set her sights on learning to practise medicine. Almost everyone seems intent on dissuading her from this ambition, but when word reaches her that a woman has recently obtained a medical degree despite her gender, Sarah decides to seek her out.    </p>
<p>                    Raven&#8217;s efforts to prove his former adversary&#8217;s innocence are failing and he desperately needs Sarah&#8217;s help. Putting their feelings for one another aside, their investigations take them to both extremes of Edinburgh&#8217;s social divide, where they discover that wealth and status cannot alter a fate written in the blood.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-corruption-of-blood-ambrose-parry/">A Corruption of Blood &#8211; Ambrose Parry</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</title>
		<link>/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A heartbreaking story of love and loss, based on a true story OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD THE NO.1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WINNER OF GOODREADS CHOICE AWARDS 2017 BEST HISTORICAL FICTION AWARD *************************** Memphis, Tennessee, 1939 Twelve-year-old Rill Foss and her four younger siblings live a magical life aboard their family&#8217;s Mississippi River shantyboat. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/">Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A heartbreaking story of love and loss, based on a true story </p>
<p>                    OVER ONE MILLION COPIES SOLD</p>
<p>                    THE NO.1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    WINNER OF GOODREADS CHOICE AWARDS 2017 BEST HISTORICAL FICTION AWARD</p>
<p>                    ***************************</p>
<p>                    Memphis, Tennessee, 1939</p>
<p>                    Twelve-year-old Rill Foss and her four younger siblings live a magical life aboard their family&#8217;s Mississippi River shantyboat. But when their father must rush their mother to the hospital one stormy night, Rill is left in charge, until strangers arrive in force. Wrenched from all that is familiar and thrown into a Tennessee Children&#8217;s Home Society orphanage, the Foss children are assured that they will soon be returned to their parents &#8211; but they quickly realize the dark truth&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Aiken, South Carolina, present day</p>
<p>                    Born into wealth and privilege, Avery Stafford seems to have it all: a successful career, a handsome fiance, and a lavish wedding on the horizon. But when Avery returns home to help her father weather a health crisis, a chance encounter leaves her with uncomfortable questions and compels her to take a journey through her family&#8217;s long-hidden history, on a path that will ultimately lead either to devastation or to redemption.</p>
<p>                    *********************</p>
<p>                    Based on one of America&#8217;s most notorious real-life scandals, in which Georgia Tann, director of a Memphis-based adoption organization, kidnapped and sold poor children to wealthy families all over the country, Before We Were Yours is a riveting, wrenching and ultimately uplifting global bestseller. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A tale of enduring power&#8217; Paula McLain</p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is impossible not to get swept up in this near-perfect novel&#8217; Huffington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/before-we-were-yours-a-heartbreaking-read-based-on-a-real-life-story-lisa-wingate/">Before We Were Yours : a heartbreaking read based on a real-life story &#8211; Lisa Wingate</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>City of Girls : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Elizabeth Gilbert</title>
		<link>/city-of-girls-the-sunday-times-bestseller-elizabeth-gilbert/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/city-of-girls-the-sunday-times-bestseller-elizabeth-gilbert/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER &#8216;Stunning&#8217; Lisa Taddeo, author of THREE WOMEN &#8216;Warm and wise&#8217; Stephanie Merritt, Observer &#8216;Glamorous, sexy, compelling&#8217; Dolly Alderton, Sunday Times &#8216;I fell in love with Vivian from page one&#8217; Daisy Buchanan &#8216;An education in love, and an iridescent delight&#8217; Rowan Pelling, Spectator New York, 1940. Young, glamorous and inseparable, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/city-of-girls-the-sunday-times-bestseller-elizabeth-gilbert/">City of Girls : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Elizabeth Gilbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Stunning&#8217; Lisa Taddeo, author of THREE WOMEN<br />
                    &#8216;Warm and wise&#8217; Stephanie Merritt, Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Glamorous, sexy, compelling&#8217; Dolly Alderton, Sunday Times<br />
                    &#8216;I fell in love with Vivian from page one&#8217; Daisy Buchanan<br />
                    &#8216;An education in love, and an iridescent delight&#8217; Rowan Pelling, Spectator</p>
<p>                    New York, 1940. Young, glamorous and inseparable, Vivian and Celia are chasing trouble from one end of the city to the other. But there is risk in all this play &#8211; that&#8217;s what makes it so fun, and so dangerous. Sometimes, the world may feel like it&#8217;s ending, but for Vivian and Celia, life is just beginning.</p>
<p>                    City of Girls is about daring to break conventions and follow your desires: a celebration of glamour, resilience, growing up, and the joys of female friendship &#8211; and about the freedom that comes from finding a place you truly belong.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/city-of-girls-the-sunday-times-bestseller-elizabeth-gilbert/">City of Girls : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Elizabeth Gilbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thirteen Moons &#8211; Charles Frazier</title>
		<link>/thirteen-moons-charles-frazier/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thirteen-moons-charles-frazier/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>At the age of twelve, under the Wind Moon, Will is given a horse, a key, and a map, and sent alone into the Indian Nation to run a trading post as a bound boy. It is during this time that he grows into a man, learning, as he does, of the raw power it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirteen-moons-charles-frazier/">Thirteen Moons &#8211; Charles Frazier</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At the age of twelve, under the Wind Moon, Will is given a horse, a key, and a map, and sent alone into the Indian Nation to run a trading post as a bound boy. It is during this time that he grows into a man, learning, as he does, of the raw power it takes to create a life, to find a home. In a card game with a white Indian named Featherstone, Will wins &#8211; for a brief moment &#8211; a mysterious girl named Claire, and his passion and desire for her spans this novel. As Will&#8217;s destiny intertwines with the fate of the Cherokee Indians, including a Cherokee Chief named Bear, he learns how to fight and survive in the face of both nature and men, and eventually, under the Corn Tassle Moon, Will begins the fight against Washington City to preserve the Cherokee&#8217;s homeland and culture. And he will come to know the truth behind his belief that &#8216;only desire trumps time&#8217;.     </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly imagined, written with great power and beauty by a master of American fiction, Thirteen Moons is a stunning novel about a man&#8217;s passion for a woman, and how loss, longing and love can shape a man&#8217;s destiny over the many moons of a life.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirteen-moons-charles-frazier/">Thirteen Moons &#8211; Charles Frazier</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Tournament &#8211; Matthew Reilly</title>
		<link>/the-tournament-matthew-reilly/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Adventure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tournament-matthew-reilly/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A tale of murder, passion and intrigue set in the majestic city of Constantinople. From global superstar Matthew Reilly comes this gripping historical thriller . . . * * * * * A PRINCESS IN DANGER England, 1546. A young Princess Elizabeth is in a dangerous position as her older siblings jostle for the throne. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tournament-matthew-reilly/">The Tournament &#8211; Matthew Reilly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A tale of murder, passion and intrigue set in the majestic city of Constantinople.</p>
<p>                    From global superstar Matthew Reilly comes this gripping historical thriller . . . </p>
<p>                    * * * * *</p>
<p>                    A PRINCESS IN DANGER<br />
                    England, 1546. A young Princess Elizabeth is in a dangerous position as her older siblings jostle for the throne.</p>
<p>                    A TOURNAMENT UNLIKE ANY OTHER<br />
                    Roger Ascham, Elizabeth&#8217;s teacher and mentor, is determined to keep her safe. So when he receives an unusual invitation from the Sultan in Constantinople, asking him to take part in the greatest chess tournament the world has ever seen, he resolves to take the princess with him.</p>
<p>                    A DEVASTATING SECRET<br />
                    But death stalks the streets of the glittering Ottoman capital &#8211; a cardinal has been found mutilated. Ascham is asked to investigate, but as he and Elizabeth delve deeper, they uncover a secret that marks the young Princess for life. And a darkness that defines the queen she will become.</p>
<p>                    * * * * * </p>
<p>                    READERS LOVE THE TOURNAMENT</p>
<p>                    &#8216;So full of intrigue, it kept me reading late into the night&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An amazing book. Thrills, spills, twists and turns&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Action, adventure, history . . . A read that you cannot put down&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Totally unputdownable . . . Magic stuff!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Another blinding read&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tournament-matthew-reilly/">The Tournament &#8211; Matthew Reilly</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Girl With a Pearl Earring &#8211; Tracy Chevalier</title>
		<link>/girl-with-a-pearl-earring-tracy-chevalier/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girl-with-a-pearl-earring-tracy-chevalier/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>OVER FIVE MILLION COPIES SOLD WORLDWIDE &#8216;A phenomenon&#8217; Jessie Burton &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;Truly magical&#8217; Guardian Those eyes are fixed on someone. But who? What is she thinking as she stares out from one of the world&#8217;s best-loved paintings? Johannes Vermeer can spot exceptional beauty. When servant girl Griet catches his eye, she soon becomes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-with-a-pearl-earring-tracy-chevalier/">Girl With a Pearl Earring &#8211; Tracy Chevalier</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OVER FIVE MILLION COPIES SOLD WORLDWIDE</p>
<p>                                &#8216;A phenomenon&#8217; Jessie Burton</p>
<p>                                &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                                &#8216;Truly magical&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                              Those eyes are fixed on someone. But who? What is she thinking as she stares out from one of the world&#8217;s best-loved paintings?</p>
<p>                              Johannes Vermeer can spot exceptional beauty. When servant girl Griet catches his eye, she soon becomes both student and muse. But then he gives her his wife&#8217;s pearl earrings to wear for a portrait, and a scandal erupts that could threaten Griet&#8217;s future&#8230;</p>
<p>                                Vivid and captivating, this timeless modern classic has become a successful film and an international bestseller, with over 5 million copies sold around the world; now with a new introduction by the author.</p>
<p>                              &#8216;A veritable work of art&#8230; one of those rare novels where all the decisions made by the author appear inevitable and right&#8217; Rose Tremain</p>
<p>                              &#8216;Timeless, delicate and as exquisitely measured as one of Vermeer&#8217;s paintings. Tense yet perfectly-paced and filled with the beauty of life&#8217;s colours, Girl with the Pearl Earring is a masterpiece in its own right. Just a phenomenon. I will hold this novel close for the rest of my life&#8217; Jessie Burton, author of The Minaturist</p>
<p>                              &#8216;If ever a novel rightly deserves its &#8220;five millions copies sold&#8221; achievement, it is this dazzling little masterpiece &#8230; Absolute magic&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                              &#8216;A portrait of radiance&#8230;Tracy Chevalier brings the real artist Vermeer and a fictional muse to life in a jewel of a novel&#8217; Time</p>
<p>                              &#8216;Chevalier doesn&#8217;t put a foot wrong in this triumphant work &#8230; It is a beautifully written tale that mirrors the elegance of the painting that inspired it&#8217; Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>                              &#8216;A wonderful novel, mysterious, steeped in atmosphere, deeply revealing about the process of painting&#8230;truly magical&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                              &#8216;It is no wonder that this beautifully-written story has sold more than five million copies and been made into a successful film. An absolute triumph&#8217; Woman&#8217;s Weekly</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-with-a-pearl-earring-tracy-chevalier/">Girl With a Pearl Earring &#8211; Tracy Chevalier</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Aquitaine Progression : A Novel &#8211; Robert Ludlum</title>
		<link>/the-aquitaine-progression-a-novel-robert-ludlum/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-aquitaine-progression-a-novel-robert-ludlum/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Geneva, American lawyer Joel Converse meets a man he hasn&#8217;t seen in twenty years, a covert operative who dies violently at his feet, whispering words that hand Converse a staggering legacy of death: &#8220;The generals . . . they&#8217;re back . . . Aquitaine!&#8221; Suddenly Converse is running for his life, alone with the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-aquitaine-progression-a-novel-robert-ludlum/">The Aquitaine Progression : A Novel &#8211; Robert Ludlum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Geneva, American lawyer Joel Converse meets a man he hasn&#8217;t seen in twenty years, a covert operative who dies violently at his feet, whispering words that hand Converse a staggering legacy of death: &#8220;The generals . . . they&#8217;re back . . . Aquitaine!&#8221; Suddenly Converse is running for his life, alone with the world&#8217;s most shattering secret. Pursued by anonymous executioners to the dark corners of Europe, he is forced to play a game of survival by blood rules he thought he&#8217;d long left behind. One by one, he traces each thread of a lethal progression to the heart of every major government, a network of coordinated global violence that no one believes possible&#8211;no one but Converse and the woman he once loved and lost, the only two people on earth who can wrest the world from the iron grasp of Aquitaine.     </p>
<p>                     Praise for Robert Ludlum and The Aquitaine Progression    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;You won&#8217;t be able to put it down. (Don&#8217;t ever begin a Ludlum novel if you have to go to work the next day).&#8221;&#8211;Chicago Sun-Times     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Ludlum at his best.&#8221;&#8211;Publishers Weekly    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-aquitaine-progression-a-novel-robert-ludlum/">The Aquitaine Progression : A Novel &#8211; Robert Ludlum</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deacon King Kong : Barack Obama Favourite Read &#038; Oprah&#8217;s Book Club Pick &#8211; James McBride</title>
		<link>/deacon-king-kong-barack-obama-favourite-read-oprahs-book-club-pick-james-mcbride/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deacon-king-kong-barack-obama-favourite-read-oprahs-book-club-pick-james-mcbride/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AND OPRAH&#8217;S BOOK CLUB PICK CHOSEN BY BARACK OBAMA AS A FAVOURITE READ TOP TEN BOOKS OF THE YEAR, NEW YORK TIMES &#038; WASHINGTON POST &#8216;Brilliantly imagined, larger than life, a tragicomedic epic of intertwined lives.&#8217; JOYCE CAROL OATES &#8216;Deeply felt, beautifully written and profoundly humane.&#8217; JUNOT DIAZ, New York Times [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deacon-king-kong-barack-obama-favourite-read-oprahs-book-club-pick-james-mcbride/">Deacon King Kong : Barack Obama Favourite Read &#038; Oprah&#8217;s Book Club Pick &#8211; James McBride</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AND OPRAH&#8217;S BOOK CLUB PICK<br />
                      CHOSEN BY BARACK OBAMA AS A FAVOURITE READ<br />
                      TOP TEN BOOKS OF THE YEAR, NEW YORK TIMES &#038; WASHINGTON POST</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brilliantly imagined, larger than life, a tragicomedic epic of intertwined lives.&#8217; JOYCE CAROL OATES</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Deeply felt, beautifully written and profoundly humane.&#8217; JUNOT DIAZ, New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>                    The year is 1969. In a housing project in south Brooklyn, a shambling old church deacon called Sportcoat shoots &#8211; for no apparent reason &#8211; the local drug-dealer who used to be part of the church&#8217;s baseball team. The repercussions of that moment draw in the whole community, from Sportcoat&#8217;s best friend &#8211; Hot Sausage &#8211; to the local Italian mobsters, the police (corrupt and otherwise), and the stalwart ladies of the Five Ends Baptist Church.</p>
<p>                    DEACON KING KONG is a book about a community under threat, about the ways people pull together in an age when the old rules are being rewritten. It is very funny in places, and heartbreaking in others. From a prize-winning storyteller, this New York Times bestseller shows us that not all secrets are meant to be hidden, and that the communities we build are fragile but vital.<br />
                    ______________________<br />
                    From the winner of a National Book Award and author of the bestselling memoir,The Color of Water, and The Good Lord Bird, a TV series starring Ethan Hawke</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A hilarious, pitch-perfect comedy set in the Brooklyn projects of the late 1960s. This alone may qualify it as one of the year&#8217;s best novels.&#8217; The Washington Post</p>
<p>                    What Goodreads readers are saying:</p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;Deacon King Kong is one of those novels whose brilliance sneaks up on you. I haven&#8217;t been this pleasantly surprised by a book in a while.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;I do believe I just finished one of my all time favorite books. I loved every minute spent with Sportcoat and his community. A good old fashioned yarn shot through with truth, spirit, and humor. I LOVED it!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;This book was a balm for my soul, a portrait of a black church community circa 1969 with sweet characters (well, most of them), interconnections that stretch back decades, and a plot with more than one mystery at its heart.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;&#8221;Deacon&#8221; has the texture of folk lore and fable mixed with the unexpected rhythms of jazz and the noisy streets of late 1960s Brooklyn.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;The ending was one of those where you clutch your heart and want to hug the book (or your Kindle).&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deacon-king-kong-barack-obama-favourite-read-oprahs-book-club-pick-james-mcbride/">Deacon King Kong : Barack Obama Favourite Read &#038; Oprah&#8217;s Book Club Pick &#8211; James McBride</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Nickel Boys : Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Fiction 2020 &#8211; Colson Whitehead</title>
		<link>/the-nickel-boys-winner-of-the-pulitzer-prize-for-fiction-2020-colson-whitehead/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-nickel-boys-winner-of-the-pulitzer-prize-for-fiction-2020-colson-whitehead/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE PULITZER PRIZE FOR FICTION 2020 WINNER OF THE ORWELL PRIZE FOR POLITICAL FICTION 2020 Winner of the Library of Congress Prize for American Fiction 2020 Time #1 Novel of the Year 2019 ________________________________________________________________________ Author of The Underground Railroad, Colson Whitehead brilliantly dramatizes another strand of American history through the story of two [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-nickel-boys-winner-of-the-pulitzer-prize-for-fiction-2020-colson-whitehead/">The Nickel Boys : Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Fiction 2020 &#8211; Colson Whitehead</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE PULITZER PRIZE FOR FICTION 2020</p>
<p>                    WINNER OF THE ORWELL PRIZE FOR POLITICAL FICTION 2020</p>
<p>                    Winner of the Library of Congress Prize for American Fiction 2020</p>
<p>                    Time #1 Novel of the Year 2019</p>
<p>                    ________________________________________________________________________</p>
<p>                    Author of The Underground Railroad, Colson Whitehead brilliantly dramatizes another strand of American history through the story of two boys sentenced to a hellish reform school in 1960s Florida.</p>
<p>                    Elwood Curtis has taken the words of Dr Martin Luther King to heart: he is as good as anyone. Abandoned by his parents, brought up by his loving, strict and clear-sighted grandmother, Elwood is about to enroll in the local black college. But given the time and the place, one innocent mistake is enough to destroy his future, and so Elwood arrives at The Nickel Academy, which claims to provide &#8216;physical, intellectual and moral training&#8217; which will equip its inmates to become &#8216;honorable and honest men&#8217;.</p>
<p>                    In reality, the Nickel Academy is a chamber of horrors, where physical, emotional and sexual abuse is rife, where corrupt officials and tradesmen do a brisk trade in supplies intended for the school, and where any boy who resists is likely to disappear &#8216;out back&#8217;. Stunned to find himself in this vicious environment, Elwood tries to hold on to Dr King&#8217;s ringing assertion, &#8216;Throw us in jail, and we will still love you.&#8217; But Elwood&#8217;s fellow inmate and new friend Turner thinks Elwood is naive and worse; the world is crooked, and the only way to survive is to emulate the cruelty and cynicism of their oppressors.</p>
<p>                    The tension between Elwood&#8217;s idealism and Turner&#8217;s skepticism leads to a decision which will have decades-long repercussions.</p>
<p>                    Based on the history of a real reform school in Florida that operated for one hundred and eleven years and warped and destroyed the lives of thousands of children, The Nickel Boys is a devastating, driven narrative by a great American novelist whose work is essential to understanding the current reality of the United States.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;If greatness is excellence sustained over time, then without question, Whitehead is one of the greatest of his generation. In fact, figuring his age, acclaim, productivity and consistency, he is one of the greatest American writers alive&#8217; Time</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A commanding triumph&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Every chapter hits its mark&#8217; New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-nickel-boys-winner-of-the-pulitzer-prize-for-fiction-2020-colson-whitehead/">The Nickel Boys : Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Fiction 2020 &#8211; Colson Whitehead</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exodus : A Novel of Israel &#8211; Leon Uris</title>
		<link>/exodus-a-novel-of-israel-leon-uris/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bible Readings]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious & Spiritual Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Selections & Meditations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/exodus-a-novel-of-israel-leon-uris/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Passionate summary of the inhuman treatment of the Jewish people in Europe, of the exodus in the nineteenth and twentieth centuries to Palestine, and of the triumphant founding of the new Israel.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Exodus is an international publishing phenomenon&#8211;the towering novel of the twentieth century&#8217;s most dramatic geopolitical event. Leon Uris magnificently portrays [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/exodus-a-novel-of-israel-leon-uris/">Exodus : A Novel of Israel &#8211; Leon Uris</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Passionate summary of the inhuman treatment of the Jewish people in Europe, of the exodus in the nineteenth and twentieth centuries to Palestine, and of the triumphant founding of the new Israel.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times     </p>
<p>                    Exodus is an international publishing phenomenon&#8211;the towering novel of the twentieth century&#8217;s most dramatic geopolitical event. Leon Uris magnificently portrays the birth of a new nation in the midst of enemies&#8211;the beginning of an earthshaking struggle for power. Here is the tale that swept the world with its fury: the story of an American nurse, an Israeli freedom fighter caught up in a glorious, heartbreaking, triumphant era. Here is Exodus&#8211;one of the great bestselling novels of all time.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/exodus-a-novel-of-israel-leon-uris/">Exodus : A Novel of Israel &#8211; Leon Uris</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Miniaturist &#8211; Jessie Burton</title>
		<link>/the-miniaturist-jessie-burton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-miniaturist-jessie-burton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER There is nothing hidden that will not be revealed &#8230;On an autumn day in 1686, eighteen-year-old Nella Oortman knocks at the door of a grand house in the wealthiest quarter of Amsterdam. She has come from the country to begin a new life as the wife of illustrious merchant [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-miniaturist-jessie-burton/">The Miniaturist &#8211; Jessie Burton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER There is nothing hidden that will not be revealed &#8230;On an autumn day in 1686, eighteen-year-old Nella Oortman knocks at the door of a grand house in the wealthiest quarter of Amsterdam. She has come from the country to begin a new life as the wife of illustrious merchant trader Johannes Brandt, but instead she is met by his sharp-tongued sister, Marin. Only later does Johannes appear and present her with an extraordinary wedding gift: a cabinet-sized replica of their home. It is to be furnished by an elusive miniaturist, whose tiny creations mirror their real-life counterparts in unexpected ways &#8230;Nella is at first mystified by the closed world of the Brandt household, but as she uncovers its secrets she realizes the escalating dangers that await them all. Does the miniaturist hold their fate in her hands? And will she be the key to their salvation or the architect of their downfall? Beautiful, intoxicating and filled with heart-pounding suspense, Jessie Burton&#8217;s magnificent debut novel The Miniaturist is a story of love and obsession, betrayal and retribution, appearance and truth.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-miniaturist-jessie-burton/">The Miniaturist &#8211; Jessie Burton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret Life of Bees : The stunning multi-million bestselling novel about a young girl&#8217;s journey; poignant, uplifting and unforgettable &#8211; Sue Monk Kidd</title>
		<link>/the-secret-life-of-bees-the-stunning-multi-million-bestselling-novel-about-a-young-girls-journey-poignant-uplifting-and-unforgettable-sue-monk-kidd/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-life-of-bees-the-stunning-multi-million-bestselling-novel-about-a-young-girls-journey-poignant-uplifting-and-unforgettable-sue-monk-kidd/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DON&#8217;T MISS THE EXTRAORDINARY NEW NOVEL FROM SUE MONK KIDD, THE BOOK OF LONGINGS &#8211; PUBLISHED ON 21ST APRIL 2020, AND AVAILABLE TO PRE-ORDER NOW The Secret Life of Bees: The multi-million-copy bestselling novel about a young girl&#8217;s journey towards healing and the transforming power of love, from the award-winning author of The Invention of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-bees-the-stunning-multi-million-bestselling-novel-about-a-young-girls-journey-poignant-uplifting-and-unforgettable-sue-monk-kidd/">The Secret Life of Bees : The stunning multi-million bestselling novel about a young girl&#8217;s journey; poignant, uplifting and unforgettable &#8211; Sue Monk Kidd</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DON&#8217;T MISS THE EXTRAORDINARY  NEW NOVEL FROM SUE MONK KIDD, THE BOOK OF LONGINGS &#8211; PUBLISHED ON 21ST APRIL 2020, AND AVAILABLE TO PRE-ORDER NOW</p>
<p>                    The Secret Life of Bees: The multi-million-copy bestselling novel about a young girl&#8217;s journey towards healing and the transforming power of love, from the award-winning author of The Invention of Wings. </p>
<p>                    Lily has grown up believing she accidentally killed her mother when she was four years old. Now, at fourteen, she yearns for forgiveness and a mother&#8217;s love. Living on a peach farm in South Carolina with her harsh and unforgiving father, she has only one friend, Rosaleen, a black servant.</p>
<p>                    When racial tension explodes one summer afternoon, and Rosaleen is arrested and beaten, Lily chooses to flee with her. Fugitives from justice, the pair follow a trail left by the woman who died ten years before. Finding sanctuary in the home of three beekeeping sisters, Lily starts a journey as much about her understanding of the world as about the mystery surrounding her mother. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A wonderful book, by turns sad, full of incident and shot through with grown-up magic reminiscent of Joanne Harris&#8217; Daily Telegraph</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Charming, funny, moving&#8217; The Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderfully written, powerful, poignant&#8230;read it&#8217; Joanna Trollope</p>
<p>                    What readers are saying about The Secret Life of Bees:</p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the most poignant and heart tugging books I have ever read&#8217; Amazon reviewer, 5 stars</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Emotional and heart-breaking, yet full of hope and love. I laughed and cried equally through the book. This wonderful book will stay with me for a long time to come&#8217; Amazon reviewer, 5 stars</p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the best books I&#8217;ve read in a while. Touching, well-written, beautiful, full of expression, insightful&#8217; Goodreads reviewer, 5 stars </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A beautifully written masterpiece. I loved the writing, the descriptions, the humour sprinkled through the story. There was sadness and love, hope and forgiveness. I highly recommend this book&#8217; Goodreads reviewer, 5 stars</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-life-of-bees-the-stunning-multi-million-bestselling-novel-about-a-young-girls-journey-poignant-uplifting-and-unforgettable-sue-monk-kidd/">The Secret Life of Bees : The stunning multi-million bestselling novel about a young girl&#8217;s journey; poignant, uplifting and unforgettable &#8211; Sue Monk Kidd</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bedlam Stacks : From the internationally bestselling author of The Watchmaker of Filigree Street &#8211; Natasha Pulley</title>
		<link>/the-bedlam-stacks-from-the-internationally-bestselling-author-of-the-watchmaker-of-filigree-street-natasha-pulley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Adventure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bedlam-stacks-from-the-internationally-bestselling-author-of-the-watchmaker-of-filigree-street-natasha-pulley/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE ROYAL SOCIETY OF LITERATURE&#8217;S ENCORE AWARD 2018 LONGLISTED FOR THE WALTER SCOTT PRIZE 2018 &#8216;A sheer fantastical delight&#8217; The Times &#8216;Epic&#8217; New York Times &#8216;An immense treat&#8217; Observer Books of the Year &#8216;A fast-paced adventure story&#8217; i &#8216;Magical&#8217; Sunday Express In uncharted Peru, the holy town of Bedlam stands at the edge [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bedlam-stacks-from-the-internationally-bestselling-author-of-the-watchmaker-of-filigree-street-natasha-pulley/">The Bedlam Stacks : From the internationally bestselling author of The Watchmaker of Filigree Street &#8211; Natasha Pulley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE ROYAL SOCIETY OF LITERATURE&#8217;S ENCORE AWARD 2018<br />
                    LONGLISTED FOR THE WALTER SCOTT PRIZE 2018</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A sheer fantastical delight&#8217; The Times<br />
                    &#8216;Epic&#8217; New York Times<br />
                    &#8216;An immense treat&#8217; Observer Books of the Year<br />
                    &#8216;A fast-paced adventure story&#8217; i<br />
                    &#8216;Magical&#8217; Sunday Express</p>
<p>                    In uncharted Peru, the holy town of Bedlam stands at the edge of a mysterious forest. Deep within are cinchona trees, whose bark yields the only known treatment for malaria.</p>
<p>                    In 1859, across the Pacific, India is ravaged by the disease. In desperation, the India Office dispatches the injured expeditionary Merrick Tremayne to Bedlam, under orders to return with cinchona cuttings. But there he meets Raphael, an enigmatic priest who is the key to a secret which will prove more valuable than they could ever have imagined.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bedlam-stacks-from-the-internationally-bestselling-author-of-the-watchmaker-of-filigree-street-natasha-pulley/">The Bedlam Stacks : From the internationally bestselling author of The Watchmaker of Filigree Street &#8211; Natasha Pulley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Circe : The No. 1 Bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles &#8211; Madeline Miller</title>
		<link>/circe-the-no-1-bestseller-from-the-author-of-the-song-of-achilles-madeline-miller/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Myth & Legend Told As Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/circe-the-no-1-bestseller-from-the-author-of-the-song-of-achilles-madeline-miller/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The international Number One bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles, shortlisted for the Women&#8217;s Prize for Fiction Woman. Witch. Myth. Mortal. Outcast. Lover. Destroyer. Survivor. CIRCE. In the house of Helios, god of the sun and mightiest of the Titans, a daughter is born. Circe is a strange child &#8211; not powerful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/circe-the-no-1-bestseller-from-the-author-of-the-song-of-achilles-madeline-miller/">Circe : The No. 1 Bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles &#8211; Madeline Miller</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The international Number One bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles, shortlisted for the Women&#8217;s Prize for Fiction</p>
<p>                    Woman. Witch. Myth. Mortal. Outcast. Lover. Destroyer. Survivor. CIRCE.</p>
<p>                     In the house of Helios, god of the sun and mightiest of the Titans, a daughter is born. Circe is a strange child &#8211; not powerful and terrible, like her father, nor gorgeous and mercenary like her mother. Scorned and rejected, Circe grows up in the shadows, at home in neither the world of gods or mortals. But Circe has a dark power of her own: witchcraft. When her gift threatens the gods, she is banished to the island of Aiaia where she hones her occult craft, casting spells, gathering strange herbs and taming wild beasts. Yet a woman who stands alone will never be left in peace for long &#8211; and among her island&#8217;s guests is an unexpected visitor: the mortal Odysseus, for whom Circe will risk everything. </p>
<p>                     So Circe sets forth her tale, a vivid, mesmerizing epic of family rivalry, love and loss &#8211; the defiant, inextinguishable song of woman burning hot and bright through the darkness of a man&#8217;s world.</p>
<p>                    THE NUMBER ONE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER </p>
<p>                    CHOSEN AS A BOOK OF THE YEAR BY THE GUARDIAN, TELEGRAPH, SUNDAY TELEGRAPH, I PAPER, SUNDAY EXPRESS, IRISH TIMES, TIMES LITERARY SUPPLEMENT, AMAZON, AUDIBLE, BUZZFEED, REFINERY 29, WASHINGTON POST, BOSTON GLOBE, SEATTLE TIMES, TIME MAGAZINE, NEWSWEEK, PEOPLE, ENTERTAINMENT WEEKLY, KIRKUS, PUBLISHERS WEEKLY AND GOODREADS</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/circe-the-no-1-bestseller-from-the-author-of-the-song-of-achilles-madeline-miller/">Circe : The No. 1 Bestseller from the author of The Song of Achilles &#8211; Madeline Miller</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Original Miss Honeyford &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/the-original-miss-honeyford-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-original-miss-honeyford-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Miss Honeyford was sour on romance, but she had been duly dispatched to London to save the family fortune by hunting forand securinga wealthy husband and thereby proving her role as a loving, if not entirely dutiful, daughter. Honoraria obeyed. But if she was reluctantly willing to surrender her hand, this beautiful young lady who [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-original-miss-honeyford-m-c-beaton/">The Original Miss Honeyford &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Miss Honeyford was sour on romance, but she had been duly dispatched to London to save the family fortune by hunting forand securinga wealthy husband and thereby proving her role as a loving, if not entirely dutiful, daughter. Honoraria obeyed. But if she was reluctantly willing to surrender her hand, this beautiful young lady who could ride, shoot, and argue with any man was not about to lose her head or her heart to any of the dismal cads and lads of the marriage mart.     </p>
<p>                    First she met the arrogantly attractive Lord Alistair Stewart, who treated her infuriatingly like a little girl. And then she met the skillfully seductive Lord Channington, who treated her intoxicatingly like the desirable full-grown woman that she was. But now that she had a choice, which role would she choose and just how much risk was she willing to run?    </p>
<p>                    The Regency series brings us heroines of style, grace, and determinationwomen who are not afraid to use their smarts to seek the stature or standing they feel they need. They may come from humble beginnings or not, but what these heroines share is an unmatched determination that leaves us turning page after page as we follow them in their dance.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-original-miss-honeyford-m-c-beaton/">The Original Miss Honeyford &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>War God: Nights of the Witch : War God Trilogy Book One &#8211; Graham Hancock</title>
		<link>/war-god-nights-of-the-witch-war-god-trilogy-book-one-graham-hancock/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/war-god-nights-of-the-witch-war-god-trilogy-book-one-graham-hancock/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A young girl called Tozi stands at the bottom of a pyramid, waiting to be led to the top where her heart will be cut out&#8230; Pepillo, a Spanish orphan who serves a sadistic Dominican friar, is aboard the Spanish fleet as it sails towards Mexico&#8230; This is the epic story of the clash of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/war-god-nights-of-the-witch-war-god-trilogy-book-one-graham-hancock/">War God: Nights of the Witch : War God Trilogy Book One &#8211; Graham Hancock</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A young girl called Tozi stands at the bottom of a pyramid, waiting to be led to the top where her heart will be cut out&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Pepillo, a Spanish orphan who serves a sadistic Dominican friar, is aboard the Spanish fleet as it sails towards Mexico&#8230;</p>
<p>                    This is the epic story of the clash of two empires, two armies and two gods of war. Five hundred desperate adventurers are about to pit themselves against the most brutal armies of the ancient Americas, armies hundreds of thousands strong. </p>
<p>                    This is a war of gods and men. Dark powers that work behind the scenes of history show their hand as the prophecy of the return of Quetzalcoatl is fulfilled with the arrival of Cortes. The Aztec ruler Moctezuma fights to maintain the demands of the war god Huitzilopochtli for human sacrifice. The Spanish Inquisition is planning an even greater blood-letting. </p>
<p>                    Caught up in the headlong collision between two gods of war are Tozi, Pepillo and the beautiful Malinal whose hatred of Moctezuma runs so deep she will sell out her own land and people to destroy him.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/war-god-nights-of-the-witch-war-god-trilogy-book-one-graham-hancock/">War God: Nights of the Witch : War God Trilogy Book One &#8211; Graham Hancock</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sweet Masquerade &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/sweet-masquerade-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sweet-masquerade-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The tenth Earl of Berham does not know what to do. An attractive thirty-two-year-old bachelor, he has been appointed guardian of the young Freddie Armstrong, the eighteen-year-old grandson of his late father&#8217;s dear friend. That&#8217;s bad enough. Then he discovers that the boy is really a girl! It is against all convention and against his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sweet-masquerade-m-c-beaton/">Sweet Masquerade &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The tenth Earl of Berham does not know what to do. An attractive thirty-two-year-old bachelor, he has been appointed guardian of the young Freddie Armstrong, the eighteen-year-old grandson of his late father&#8217;s dear friend. That&#8217;s bad enough. Then he discovers that the boy is really a girl! It is against all convention and against his personal code to keep a young lady concealed in his own home. He must find a solution.    </p>
<p>                    The earl&#8217;s frequent visitor, Lady Clarissa Rennenord, heartily agrees&#8211;but for less noble reasons. Lady Clarissa hopes to snare the earl in marriage and does not want any competition. She recommends that Freddie be sent to a seminary. No one but Lady Rennenord knows what a horrid place it is&#8211;and no one, including Lady Rennenord, expects Freddie to escape. Now Freddie is back, and the earl finds her presence unsettling in more ways than one.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sweet-masquerade-m-c-beaton/">Sweet Masquerade &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Back in Society &#8211; M C Beaton</title>
		<link>/back-in-society-m-c-beaton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/back-in-society-m-c-beaton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Life is finally looking up for the poor relations. The Prince of Wales&#8217; coat of arms gleams over the hotel entrance. All but one of the rooms are filled by the open-handed Prince Hugo and his entourage. The owners have taken on a new partner, Mr. Jason Davy, a popular actor. Even curmudgeonly Sir Philip [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/back-in-society-m-c-beaton/">Back in Society &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Life is finally looking up for the poor relations. The Prince of Wales&#8217; coat of arms gleams over the hotel entrance. All but one of the rooms are filled by the open-handed Prince Hugo and his entourage. The owners have taken on a new partner, Mr. Jason Davy, a popular actor. Even curmudgeonly Sir Philip hasn&#8217;t uttered anything loathsome for days. They have finally reached a position comfortable enough to allow them to consider offers to buy the hotel.    </p>
<p>                    The poor relations&#8217; hard-earned success, however, is in stark contrast to the plight of their latest guest, Lady Jane Fremney. The slight, beautiful youngest daughter of the Earl of Durby has been cast out of her family for refusing to marry the man her father has chosen. Lonely and bankrupt, Lady Jane has decided to commit suicide. But when Miss Tonks uncovers her plans, the poor relations go into action again to rescue Lady Jane from suicide, her father, and her intended husband.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/back-in-society-m-c-beaton/">Back in Society &#8211; M C Beaton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Egyptian : A Novel &#8211; Mika Waltari</title>
		<link>/egyptian-a-novel-mika-waltari/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Adventure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/egyptian-a-novel-mika-waltari/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>First published in the United States in 1949 and widely condemned as obscene, The Egyptian outsold every other novel published that year, and remains a classic; readers worldwide have testified to its life-changing power. It is a full-bodied re-creation of a largely forgotten era in the world s history: the Egypt of the 14th century [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/egyptian-a-novel-mika-waltari/">Egyptian : A Novel &#8211; Mika Waltari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First published in the United States in 1949 and widely condemned as obscene, The Egyptian outsold every other novel published that year, and remains a classic; readers worldwide have testified to its life-changing power. It is a full-bodied re-creation of a largely forgotten era in the world s history: the Egypt of the 14th century B.C.E., when pharaohs and gods contended with the near-collapse of history s greatest empire. This epic tale encompasses the whole of the then-known world, from Babylon to Crete, from Thebes to Jerusalem, while centering around one unforgettable figure: Sinuhe, a man of mysterious origins who rises from the depths of degradation to become personal physician to Pharaoh Akhnaton.<br />
                    &#8221;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/egyptian-a-novel-mika-waltari/">Egyptian : A Novel &#8211; Mika Waltari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An Officer and a Spy : The gripping Richard and Judy Book Club favourite &#8211; Robert Harris</title>
		<link>/an-officer-and-a-spy-the-gripping-richard-and-judy-book-club-favourite-robert-harris/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-officer-and-a-spy-the-gripping-richard-and-judy-book-club-favourite-robert-harris/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>National Book Awards Popular Fiction Book of the Year 2013 They lied to protect their country. He told the truth to save it. A gripping historical thriller from the bestselling author of FATHERLAND. January 1895. On a freezing morning in the heart of Paris, an army officer, Georges Picquart, witnesses a convicted spy, Captain Alfred [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-officer-and-a-spy-the-gripping-richard-and-judy-book-club-favourite-robert-harris/">An Officer and a Spy : The gripping Richard and Judy Book Club favourite &#8211; Robert Harris</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>National Book Awards Popular Fiction Book of the Year 2013</p>
<p>                    They lied to protect their country. He told the truth to save it. A gripping historical thriller from the bestselling author of FATHERLAND.</p>
<p>                    January 1895. On a freezing morning in the heart of Paris, an army officer, Georges Picquart, witnesses a convicted spy, Captain Alfred Dreyfus, being publicly humiliated in front of twenty thousand spectators baying &#8216;Death to the Jew!&#8217;</p>
<p>                    The officer is rewarded with promotion: Picquart is made the French army&#8217;s youngest colonel and put in command of &#8216;the Statistical Section&#8217; &#8211; the shadowy intelligence unit that tracked down Dreyfus.</p>
<p>                    The spy, meanwhile, is given a punishment of medieval cruelty: Dreyfus is shipped off to a lifetime of solitary confinement on Devil&#8217;s Island &#8211; unable to speak to anyone, not even his guards, his case seems closed forever.</p>
<p>                    But gradually Picquart comes to believe there is something rotten at the heart of the Statistical Section. When he discovers another German spy operating on French soil, his superiors are oddly reluctant to pursue it. Despite official warnings, Picquart persists, and soon the officer and the spy are in the same predicament&#8230;</p>
<p>                    Narrated by Picquart, An Officer and a Spy is a compelling recreation of a scandal that became the most famous miscarriage of justice in history. Compelling, too, are the echoes for our modern world: an intelligence agency gone rogue, justice corrupted in the name of national security, a newspaper witch-hunt of a persecuted minority, and the age-old instinct of those in power to cover-up their crimes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-officer-and-a-spy-the-gripping-richard-and-judy-book-club-favourite-robert-harris/">An Officer and a Spy : The gripping Richard and Judy Book Club favourite &#8211; Robert Harris</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Muse &#8211; Jessie Burton</title>
		<link>/the-muse-jessie-burton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-muse-jessie-burton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times Number One Bestseller and Richard and Judy Book Club selection. Seductive, exhilarating and suspenseful, The Muse is an unforgettable novel about aspiration and identity, love and obsession, authenticity and deception &#8211; a masterpiece from Jessie Burton, the million-copy bestselling author of The Miniaturist. A picture hides a thousand words . . . [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-muse-jessie-burton/">The Muse &#8211; Jessie Burton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times Number One Bestseller and Richard and Judy Book Club selection.</p>
<p>                    Seductive, exhilarating and suspenseful, The Muse is an unforgettable novel about aspiration and identity, love and obsession, authenticity and deception &#8211; a masterpiece from Jessie Burton, the million-copy bestselling author of The Miniaturist.</p>
<p>                    A picture hides a thousand words . . .</p>
<p>                    On a hot July day in 1967, Odelle Bastien climbs the stone steps of the Skelton gallery in London, knowing that her life is about to change forever. Having struggled to find her place in the city since she arrived from Trinidad five years ago, she has been offered a job as a typist under the tutelage of the glamorous and enigmatic Marjorie Quick. But though Quick takes Odelle into her confidence, and unlocks a potential she didn&#8217;t know she had, she remains a mystery &#8211; no more so than when a lost masterpiece with a secret history is delivered to the gallery.</p>
<p>                    The truth about the painting lies in 1936 and a large house in rural Spain, where Olive Schloss, the daughter of a renowned art dealer, is harbouring ambitions of her own. Into this fragile paradise come artist and revolutionary Isaac Robles and his half-sister Teresa, who immediately insinuate themselves into the Schloss family, with explosive and devastating consequences . . .</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Those who loved The Miniaturist will find here all the cliffhangers, twists and heart-stopping revelations they expected, and in two evocative settings . . . as a study of female creativity, it triumphs&#8217; &#8211; Daily Telegraph</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-muse-jessie-burton/">The Muse &#8211; Jessie Burton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Winter of the World : Book Two of the Century Trilogy &#8211; Ken Follett</title>
		<link>/winter-of-the-world-book-two-of-the-century-trilogy-ken-follett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/winter-of-the-world-book-two-of-the-century-trilogy-ken-follett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;This book is truly epic. . . . The reader will probably wish there was a thousand more pages.&#8221; -The Huffington Post Picking up where Fall of Giants, the first novel in the extraordinary Century Trilogy, left off, Winter of the World follows its five interrelated families-American, German, Russian, English, and Welsh-through a time of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/winter-of-the-world-book-two-of-the-century-trilogy-ken-follett/">Winter of the World : Book Two of the Century Trilogy &#8211; Ken Follett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;This book is truly epic. . . . The reader will probably wish there was a thousand more pages.&#8221; -The Huffington Post    </p>
<p>                    Picking up where Fall of Giants, the first novel in the extraordinary Century Trilogy, left off, Winter of the World follows its five interrelated families-American, German, Russian, English, and Welsh-through a time of enormous social, political, and economic turmoil, beginning with the rise of the Third Reich, through the great dramas of World War II, and into the beginning of the long Cold War.    </p>
<p>                     Carla von Ulrich, born of German and English parents, finds her life engulfed by the Nazi tide until daring to commit a deed of great courage and heartbreak . . . . American brothers Woody and Chuck Dewar, each with a secret, take separate paths to momentous events, one in Washington, the other in the bloody jungles of the Pacific . . . . English student Lloyd Williams discovers in the crucible of the Spanish Civil War that he must fight Communism just as hard as Fascism . . . . Daisy Peshkov, a driven social climber, cares only for popularity and the fast set until war transforms her life, while her cousin Volodya carves out a position in Soviet intelligence that will affect not only this war but also the war to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/winter-of-the-world-book-two-of-the-century-trilogy-ken-follett/">Winter of the World : Book Two of the Century Trilogy &#8211; Ken Follett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Wonder &#8211; Emma Donoghue</title>
		<link>/the-wonder-emma-donoghue/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wonder-emma-donoghue/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An eleven-year-old girl stops eating, but remains miraculously alive and well. A nurse, sent to investigate whether she is a fraud, meets a journalist hungry for a story . . . Set in the Irish Midlands in the 1850s, Emma Donoghue&#8217;s The Wonder &#8211; inspired by numerous European and North American cases of &#8216;fasting girls&#8217; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wonder-emma-donoghue/">The Wonder &#8211; Emma Donoghue</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An eleven-year-old girl stops eating, but remains miraculously alive and well. A nurse, sent to investigate whether she is a fraud, meets a journalist hungry for a story . . .    </p>
<p>                    Set in the Irish Midlands in the 1850s, Emma Donoghue&#8217;s The Wonder &#8211; inspired by numerous European and North American cases of &#8216;fasting girls&#8217; between the sixteenth century and the twentieth &#8211; is a psychological thriller about a child&#8217;s murder threatening to happen in slow motion before our eyes. Pitting all the seductions of fundamentalism against sense and love, it is a searing examination of what nourishes us, body and soul.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wonder-emma-donoghue/">The Wonder &#8211; Emma Donoghue</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Empty Throne &#8211; Bernard Cornwell</title>
		<link>/the-empty-throne-bernard-cornwell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-empty-throne-bernard-cornwell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The eighth book in the epic and bestselling series that has gripped millions. A hero will be forged from this broken land. As seen on Netflix and BBC around the world. In the battle for power, there can be only one ruler. The ruler of Mercia is dying, leaving no apparent heir. His wife is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-empty-throne-bernard-cornwell/">The Empty Throne &#8211; Bernard Cornwell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The eighth book in the epic and bestselling series that has gripped millions.</p>
<p>                              A hero will be forged from this broken land.<br />
                              As seen on Netflix and BBC around the world.</p>
<p>                              In the battle for power, there can be only one ruler.</p>
<p>                              The ruler of Mercia is dying, leaving no apparent heir. His wife is a born leader, but no woman has ever ruled over an English kingdom. And she is without her greatest warrior and champion, Uhtred of Bebbanburg.</p>
<p>                              An empty throne leaves the kingdom exposed to rival West Saxons and to the Vikings, who are on a bloody rampage once more.</p>
<p>                              A hero is needed, a hero who has been in battle all his life, who can destroy the double threat to Mercia. A hero who will ultimately decide the fate of a nation&#8230;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-empty-throne-bernard-cornwell/">The Empty Throne &#8211; Bernard Cornwell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Poppy Wife : A Novel of the Great War &#8211; Caroline Scott</title>
		<link>/the-poppy-wife-a-novel-of-the-great-war-caroline-scott/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 1 Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-poppy-wife-a-novel-of-the-great-war-caroline-scott/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A beautifully evocative reminder of what it means to come back from war and to face the age-old question of whether it is better to have survived or to have died. Highly recommended.&#8221;&#8211;Library Journal, starred review In the tradition of Jennifer Robson and Hazel Gaynor, this unforgettable debut novel is a sweeping tale of forbidden [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-poppy-wife-a-novel-of-the-great-war-caroline-scott/">The Poppy Wife : A Novel of the Great War &#8211; Caroline Scott</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A beautifully evocative reminder of what it means to come back from war and to face the age-old question of whether it is better to have survived or to have died. Highly recommended.&#8221;&#8211;Library Journal, starred review</p>
<p>                    In the tradition of Jennifer Robson and Hazel Gaynor, this unforgettable debut novel is a sweeping tale of forbidden love, profound loss, and the startling truth of the broken families left behind in the wake of World War I.</p>
<p>                    1921. Survivors of the Great War are desperately trying to piece together the fragments of their broken lives. While many have been reunited with their loved ones, Edie&#8217;s husband Francis has not come home. Francis is presumed to have been killed in action, but Edie believes he might still be alive.</p>
<p>                    Harry, Francis&#8217;s brother, was there the day Francis was wounded. He was certain it was a fatal wound&#8211;that he saw his brother die&#8211;but as time passes, Harry begins questioning his memory of what happened. Could Francis, like many soldiers, merely be lost and confused somewhere? Hired by grieving families, Harry returns to the Western Front to photograph gravesites. As he travels through battle-scarred France and Belgium gathering news for British wives and mothers, he searches for evidence of Francis.</p>
<p>                    When Edie receives a mysterious photograph of Francis, she is more convinced than ever he might still be alive. And so, she embarks on a journey in the hope of finding some trace of her husband. Is he truly gone? And if he isn&#8217;t, then why hasn&#8217;t he come home? </p>
<p>                    As Harry and Edie&#8217;s paths converge, they get closer to the truth about Francis and, as they do, are faced with the life-changing impact of the answers they discover. </p>
<p>                    Artful and incredibly moving, The Poppy Wife tells the unforgettable story of the soldiers lost amid the chaos and ruins, and those who were desperate to find them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-poppy-wife-a-novel-of-the-great-war-caroline-scott/">The Poppy Wife : A Novel of the Great War &#8211; Caroline Scott</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Shaman : Number 2 in series &#8211; Noah Gordon</title>
		<link>/shaman-number-2-in-series-noah-gordon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/shaman-number-2-in-series-noah-gordon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Robert Jeremy Cole, the legendary doctor and hero of THE PHYSICIAN, left an enduring legacy. From the eleventh century on, the eldest son in each generation of the Cole family has borne the same first name and middle initial and many of these men have followed the medical profession. A few have been blessed with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shaman-number-2-in-series-noah-gordon/">Shaman : Number 2 in series &#8211; Noah Gordon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Robert Jeremy Cole, the legendary doctor and hero of THE PHYSICIAN, left an enduring legacy. From the eleventh century on, the eldest son in each generation of the Cole family has borne the same first name and middle initial and many of these men have followed the medical profession. A few have been blessed with their ancestor&#8217;s diagnostic skill and the &#8216;sixth sense&#8217; they call The Gift, the ability to know instinctively when death is impending.<br />
                             The tragedy of Rob J.&#8217;s life is the deafness of his son, Robert Jefferson Cole, who is called Shaman by everyone who knows him. Shaman&#8217;s life is difficult. First, he must learn to speak so that he can take his place in the hearing world, and then he must fight against the prejudices of a society where physical differences matter. As Shaman struggles to achieve his identity, the Coles, along with the rest of America, are drawn into the conflict between the North and the South.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/shaman-number-2-in-series-noah-gordon/">Shaman : Number 2 in series &#8211; Noah Gordon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conqueror (Conqueror, Book 5) &#8211; Conn Iggulden</title>
		<link>/conqueror-conqueror-book-5-conn-iggulden/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/conqueror-conqueror-book-5-conn-iggulden/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The one and only Conn Iggulden takes on the story of the mighty Kublai Khan. An epic tale of a great and heroic mind; his action-packed rule; and how in conquering one-fifth of the world&#8217;s inhabited land, he changed the course of history forever. A scholar who conquered an empire larger than those of Alexander [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conqueror-conqueror-book-5-conn-iggulden/">Conqueror (Conqueror, Book 5) &#8211; Conn Iggulden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The one and only Conn Iggulden takes on the story of the mighty Kublai Khan. An epic tale of a great and heroic mind; his action-packed rule; and how in conquering one-fifth of the world&#8217;s inhabited land, he changed the course of history forever. A scholar who conquered an empire larger than those of Alexander or Caesar. A warrior who would rule a fifth of the world with strength and wisdom. A man who betrayed a brother to protect a nation. From a young scholar to one of history&#8217;s most powerful warriors, Conqueror tells the story of Kublai Khan &#8211; an extraordinary man who should be remembered alongside Julius Caesar, Alexander the Great and Napoleon Bonaparte as one of the greatest conquerors the world has ever known. It should have been a golden age, with an empire to dwarf the lands won by the mighty Genghis Khan. Instead, the vast Mongol nation is slowly losing ground, swallowed whole by their most ancient enemy. A new generation has arisen, yet the long shadow of the Great Khan still hangs over them all &#8230;Kublai dreams of an empire stretching from sea to sea. But to see it built, this scholar must first learn the art of war.<br />
                    He must take his nation&#8217;s warriors to the ends of the known world. And when he is weary, when he is wounded, he must face his own brothers in bloody civil war.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conqueror-conqueror-book-5-conn-iggulden/">Conqueror (Conqueror, Book 5) &#8211; Conn Iggulden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Yiddish Policemen&#8217;s Union &#8211; Michael Chabon</title>
		<link>/the-yiddish-policemens-union-michael-chabon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-yiddish-policemens-union-michael-chabon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The brilliantly original new novel from Michael Chabon, author of THE ADVENTURES OF KAVALIER &#038; CLAY and WONDER BOYS. What if, as Franklin Roosevelt once proposed, Alaska &#8211; and not Israel &#8211; had become the homeland for the Jews after the Second World War? In Michael Chabon&#8217;s Yiddish-speaking &#8216;Alyeska&#8217;, Orthodox gangs in side-curls and knee [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-yiddish-policemens-union-michael-chabon/">The Yiddish Policemen&#8217;s Union &#8211; Michael Chabon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The brilliantly original new novel from Michael Chabon, author of THE ADVENTURES OF KAVALIER &#038; CLAY and WONDER BOYS.    </p>
<p>                              What if, as Franklin Roosevelt once proposed, Alaska &#8211; and not Israel &#8211; had become the homeland for the Jews after the Second World War? In Michael Chabon&#8217;s Yiddish-speaking &#8216;Alyeska&#8217;, Orthodox gangs in side-curls and knee breeches roam the streets of Sitka, where Detective Meyer Landsman discovers the corpse of a heroin-addled chess prodigy in the flophouse Meyer calls home. Marionette strings stretch back to the hands of charismatic Rebbe Gold, leader of a sect that seems to have drawn its mission statement from the Cosa Nostra. Meyer is determined to unsnarl the meaning behind the murder. Even if that means surrendering his badge and his dignity to the chief of Sitka&#8217;s homicide unit &#8211; his fearsome ex-wife Bina.    </p>
<p>                              A novel of colossal ambition and heart, THE YIDDISH POLICEMEN&#8217;S UNION interweaves a homage to the stylish menace of 1940s film noir with a bittersweet fable of identity, home and faith.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-yiddish-policemens-union-michael-chabon/">The Yiddish Policemen&#8217;s Union &#8211; Michael Chabon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Terror : A Novel &#8211; Dan Simmons</title>
		<link>/the-terror-a-novel-dan-simmons/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-terror-a-novel-dan-simmons/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dan Simmons writes with the salty grace and precision of Patrick O&#8217;Brian. But in piling supernatural nightmare upon historical nightmare, layering mystery upon mystery, he has produced a turbocharged vision of popular doom.&#8221; -Men&#8217;s JournalGreeted with excited critical praise, this extraordinary novel-inspired by the true story of two ice ships that disappeared in the Arctic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-terror-a-novel-dan-simmons/">The Terror : A Novel &#8211; Dan Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dan Simmons writes with the salty grace and precision of Patrick O&#8217;Brian. But in piling supernatural nightmare upon historical nightmare, layering mystery upon mystery, he has produced a turbocharged vision of popular doom.&#8221; -Men&#8217;s JournalGreeted with excited critical praise, this extraordinary novel-inspired by the true story of two ice ships that disappeared in the Arctic Circle during an 1845 expedition-swells with the heart-stopping suspense and heroic adventure that have won Dan Simmons praise as &#8220;a writer who not only makes big promises but keeps them&#8221; (Seattle Post-Intelligencer). THE TERROR chills readers to the core.&#8221;Brutal, relentless, yet oddly uplifting, THE TERROR is a masterfully chilling work.&#8221; -Entertainment Weekly&#8221;In the hands of a lesser writer than Dan Simmons, THE TERROR might well have dissolved into a series of frigid days and three-dog nights. But Simmons is too good a writer to ignore the real gold in his story-its beleaguered cast.&#8221; -Bookpage&#8221;Guaranteed to have readers pulling their covers up to their noses, THE TERROR will make for a blood-freezing, bedtime read this winter-and any season thereafter.&#8221; -Pages    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-terror-a-novel-dan-simmons/">The Terror : A Novel &#8211; Dan Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Colorado Christmas &#8211; William W. Johnstone, J.A. Johnstone</title>
		<link>/a-colorado-christmas-william-w-johnstone-j-a-johnstone/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Westerns]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-colorado-christmas-william-w-johnstone-j-a-johnstone/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FOR THE JENSEN FAMILY, DANGER IS MERELY ANOTHER HOLIDAY TRADITION. At the Sugarloaf Ranch, Smoke and Sally Jensen prepare to welcome Preacher home for the holidays&#8211;unaware that their friend is trailed by a storm full of trouble. On a mission of vengeance, an old trapper is rescued by Ace and Chance Jensen from ruthless outlaws&#8211;and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-colorado-christmas-william-w-johnstone-j-a-johnstone/">A Colorado Christmas &#8211; William W. Johnstone, J.A. Johnstone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FOR THE JENSEN FAMILY, DANGER IS MERELY ANOTHER HOLIDAY TRADITION.  At the Sugarloaf Ranch, Smoke and Sally Jensen prepare to welcome Preacher home for the holidays&#8211;unaware that their friend is trailed by a storm full of trouble.  On a mission of vengeance, an old trapper is rescued by Ace and Chance Jensen from ruthless outlaws&#8211;and wanted by a driven bounty hunter named Luke Jensen.  And, just released from prison, a criminal mastermind assembles a vicious gang of cutthroats to extract his final revenge against his enemy&#8211;the sheriff of Big Rock, Colorado . . .  With a snowstorm brewing, a community in jeopardy, and a showdown ready to explode, these courageous pioneers are brought together by fate and fury to forge peace on earth. But they&#8217;re going to have to fight for it. With guns. With grit. With glory. Because this Christmas, the greatest gift of all is . . . staying alive.  RAVE FOR A ROCKY MOUNTAIN CHRISTMAS!  &#8220;An absorbing tale of Christmas with a side of magic . . . An exciting visit to the old west of gunfights and cattle drives. Four stars!&#8221;<br />
                     &#8212; RT Book Reviews     </p>
<p>                     Live Free. Read Hard.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-colorado-christmas-william-w-johnstone-j-a-johnstone/">A Colorado Christmas &#8211; William W. Johnstone, J.A. Johnstone</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Longbourn : The unputdownable Richard and Judy pick &#8211; Jo Baker</title>
		<link>/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Romance Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER A RICHARD AND JUDY BOOKCLUB PICK &#8216;Utterly engrossing&#8217; Guardian It is wash-day for the housemaids at Longbourn House, and Sarah&#8217;s hands are chapped and raw. Domestic life below stairs, ruled with a tender heart and an iron will by Mrs Hill the housekeeper, is about to be disturbed by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/">Longbourn : The unputdownable Richard and Judy pick &#8211; Jo Baker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER<br />
                    A RICHARD AND JUDY BOOKCLUB PICK<br />
                    &#8216;Utterly engrossing&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    It is wash-day for the housemaids at Longbourn House, and Sarah&#8217;s hands are chapped and raw. Domestic life below stairs, ruled with a tender heart and an iron will by Mrs Hill the housekeeper, is about to be disturbed by the arrival of a new footman, bearing secrets and the scent of the sea.    </p>
<p>                    What readers are saying:    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A novel to be savoured&#8217;<br />
                    &#8216;Highly recommended&#8217;<br />
                    &#8216;Very enjoyable exploration of the background to Pride and Prejudice&#8217;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/longbourn-the-unputdownable-richard-and-judy-pick-jo-baker/">Longbourn : The unputdownable Richard and Judy pick &#8211; Jo Baker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
