<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Political Structure &amp; Processes Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/political-structure-processes/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/political-structure-processes/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Political Structure &amp; Processes Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/political-structure-processes/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</title>
		<link>/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR </p>
<p>                     When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch a cable news network in 1996, American politics and media changed forever. With a remarkable level of detail and insight, Vanity Fair magazine reporter Gabriel Sherman puts Ailes&#8217;s unique genius on display, along with the outsize personalities&#8211;Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Sean Hannity, Megyn Kelly, Sarah Palin, Karl Rove, Glenn Beck, Mike Huckabee, Gretchen Carlson, Bill Shine, and others&#8211;who have helped Fox News play a defining role in the great social and political controversies of the past two decades. From the Clinton-Lewinsky scandal to the Bush-Gore recount, from the war in Iraq to the Tea Party attack on the Obama presidency, Roger Ailes developed an unrivaled power to sway the national agenda. Even more, he became the indispensable figure in conservative America and the man any Republican politician with presidential aspirations had to court. </p>
<p>                     How did this man become the master strategist of our political landscape? In revelatory detail, Sherman chronicles the rise of Ailes, a frail kid from an Ohio factory town who, through sheer willpower, the flair of a showman, fierce corporate politicking, and a profound understanding of the priorities of middle America, built the most influential television news empire of our time. </p>
<p>                     Drawing on hundreds of interviews with Fox News insiders past and present, Sherman documents Ailes&#8217;s tactical acuity as he battled the press, business rivals, and countless real and perceived enemies inside and outside Fox. Sherman takes us inside the morning meetings in which Ailes and other high-level executives strategized Fox&#8217;s presentation of the news to advance Ailes&#8217;s political agenda; provides behind-the-scenes details of Ailes&#8217;s crucial role as finder and shaper of talent, including his sometimes rocky relationships with Fox News stars such as O&#8217;Reilly, Hannity, and Carlson; and probes Ailes&#8217;s fraught partnership with his equally brash and mercurial boss, Rupert Murdoch. </p>
<p>                     Roger Ailes&#8217;s life is a story worthy of Citizen Kane. Featuring an afterword about Ailes&#8217;s epic downfall during the extraordinary 2016 election, The Loudest Voice in the Room is an extraordinary feat of reportage with a compelling human drama at its heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Leap in the Dark : The Struggle to Create the American Republic &#8211; John Ferling</title>
		<link>/a-leap-in-the-dark-the-struggle-to-create-the-american-republic-john-ferling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-leap-in-the-dark-the-struggle-to-create-the-american-republic-john-ferling/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It was an age of fascinating leaders and difficult choices, of grand ideas eloquently expressed and of epic conflicts bitterly fought. Now comes a brilliant portrait of the American Revolution, one that is compelling in its prose, fascinating in its details, and provocative in its fresh interpretations. John Ferling has shown himself to be an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-leap-in-the-dark-the-struggle-to-create-the-american-republic-john-ferling/">A Leap in the Dark : The Struggle to Create the American Republic &#8211; John Ferling</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It was an age of fascinating leaders and difficult choices, of grand ideas eloquently expressed and of epic conflicts bitterly fought. Now comes a brilliant portrait of the American Revolution, one that is compelling in its prose, fascinating in its details, and provocative in its fresh interpretations. John Ferling has shown himself to be an insightful  historian of our Revolution, and an unusually skillful  writer. A Leap in the Dark is his masterpiece,<br />
                    work that provokes, enlightens, and entertains in full measure.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-leap-in-the-dark-the-struggle-to-create-the-american-republic-john-ferling/">A Leap in the Dark : The Struggle to Create the American Republic &#8211; John Ferling</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rise and Fall of the Great Powers : Economic Change and Military Conflict from 1500 to 2000 &#8211; Paul Kennedy</title>
		<link>/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-great-powers-economic-change-and-military-conflict-from-1500-to-2000-paul-kennedy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-great-powers-economic-change-and-military-conflict-from-1500-to-2000-paul-kennedy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>About national and international power in the &#34;modern&#34; or Post Renaissance period. Explains how the various powers have risen and fallen over the 5 centuries since the formation of the &#34;new monarchies&#34; in W. Europe.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-great-powers-economic-change-and-military-conflict-from-1500-to-2000-paul-kennedy/">The Rise and Fall of the Great Powers : Economic Change and Military Conflict from 1500 to 2000 &#8211; Paul Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>About national and international power in the &quot;modern&quot; or Post Renaissance period. Explains how the various powers have risen and fallen over the 5 centuries since the formation of the &quot;new monarchies&quot; in W. Europe.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-great-powers-economic-change-and-military-conflict-from-1500-to-2000-paul-kennedy/">The Rise and Fall of the Great Powers : Economic Change and Military Conflict from 1500 to 2000 &#8211; Paul Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</title>
		<link>/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Economic and other outcomes differ vastly among individuals, groups, and nations. Many explanations have been offered for the differences. Some believe that those with less fortunate outcomes are victims of genetics. Others believe that those who are less fortunate are victims of the more fortunate. Discrimination and Disparities gathers a wide array of empirical evidence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/">Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Economic and other outcomes differ vastly among individuals, groups, and nations. Many explanations have been offered for the differences. Some believe that those with less fortunate outcomes are victims of genetics. Others believe that those who are less fortunate are victims of the more fortunate.    </p>
<p>                    Discrimination and Disparities gathers a wide array of empirical evidence to challenge the idea that different economic outcomes can be explained by any one factor, be it discrimination, exploitation, or genetics. This revised and enlarged edition also analyzes the human consequences of the prevailing social vision of these disparities and the policies based on that vision&#8211;from educational disasters to widespread crime and violence.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/">Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It Was All a Lie : How the Republican Party Became Donald Trump &#8211; Stuart Stevens</title>
		<link>/it-was-all-a-lie-how-the-republican-party-became-donald-trump-stuart-stevens/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/it-was-all-a-lie-how-the-republican-party-became-donald-trump-stuart-stevens/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER In his bare-knuckles account, Stevens confesses to the reader that the entire apparatus of his Republican Party is built on a pack of lies&#8230; This reckoning inspired Stevens to publish this blistering, tell-all history&#8230; Although this book will be a hard read for any committed conservatives, they would do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-was-all-a-lie-how-the-republican-party-became-donald-trump-stuart-stevens/">It Was All a Lie : How the Republican Party Became Donald Trump &#8211; Stuart Stevens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER </p>
<p>                    In his bare-knuckles account, Stevens confesses to the reader that the entire apparatus of his Republican Party is built on a pack of lies&#8230; This reckoning inspired Stevens to publish this blistering, tell-all history&#8230; Although this book will be a hard read for any committed conservatives, they would do well to ponder it.<br />
                    &#8211;Julian E. Zelizer, The New York Times </p>
<p>                    From the most successful Republican political operative of his generation, a searing, unflinching, and deeply personal exposé of how his party became what it is today </p>
<p>                    Stuart Stevens spent decades electing Republicans at every level, from presidents to senators to local officials. He knows the GOP as intimately as anyone in America, and in this new book he offers a devastating portrait of a party that has lost its moral and political compass. </p>
<p>                    This is not a book about how Donald J. Trump hijacked the Republican Party and changed it into something else. Stevens shows how Trump is in fact the natural outcome of five decades of hypocrisy and self-delusion, dating all the way back to the civil rights legislation of the early 1960s. Stevens shows how racism has always lurked in the modern GOP&#8217;s DNA, from Goldwater&#8217;s opposition to desegregation to Ronald Reagan&#8217;s welfare queens and states&#8217; rights rhetoric. He gives an insider&#8217;s account of the rank hypocrisy of the party&#8217;s claims to embody family values, and shows how the party&#8217;s vaunted commitment to fiscal responsibility has been a charade since the 1980s. When a party stands for nothing, he argues, it is only natural that it will be taken over by the loudest and angriest voices in the room. </p>
<p>                    It Was All a Lie is not just an indictment of the Republican Party, but a candid and often lacerating mea culpa. Stevens is not asking for pity or forgiveness; he is simply telling us what he has seen firsthand. He helped to create the modern party that kneels before a morally bankrupt con man and now he wants nothing more than to see what it has become burned to the ground.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/it-was-all-a-lie-how-the-republican-party-became-donald-trump-stuart-stevens/">It Was All a Lie : How the Republican Party Became Donald Trump &#8211; Stuart Stevens</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</title>
		<link>/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER** In twenty-one bite-sized lessons, Yuval Noah Harari explores what it means to be human in an age of bewilderment. &#8217;21 Lessons is, simply put, a crucial book&#8217; Adam Kay How can we protect ourselves from nuclear war, ecological cataclysms and technological disruptions? What can we do about the epidemic of fake [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/">21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER**</p>
<p>                    In twenty-one bite-sized lessons, Yuval Noah Harari explores what it means to be human in an age of bewilderment. </p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                              &#8217;21 Lessons is, simply put, a crucial book&#8217; Adam Kay</p>
<p>                    How can we protect ourselves from nuclear war, ecological cataclysms and technological disruptions? What can we do about the epidemic of fake news or the threat of terrorism? What should we teach our children? </p>
<p>                    Yuval Noah Harari takes us on a thrilling journey through today&#8217;s most urgent issues. The golden thread running through his exhilarating new book is the challenge of maintaining our collective and individual focus in the face of constant and disorienting change.</p>
<p>                    Are we still capable of understanding the world we have created?</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating&#8230; compelling&#8230; [Harari] has teed up a crucial global conversation about how to take on the problems of the 21st century&#8217; Bill Gates, New York Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Truly mind-expanding&#8230; Ultra-topical&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/">21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</title>
		<link>/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019 Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump. The 2016 election was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019</p>
<p>                    Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump.</p>
<p>                    The 2016 election was a watershed for the United States. But, as Tim Alberta explains in American Carnage, to understand Trump&#8217;s victory is to view him not as the creator of this era of polarization and bruising partisanship, but rather as its most manifest consequence.</p>
<p>                    American Carnage is the story of a president&#8217;s rise based on a country&#8217;s evolution and a party&#8217;s collapse. As George W. Bush left office with record-low approval ratings and Barack Obama led a Democratic takeover of Washington, Republicans faced a moment of reckoning: They had no vision, no generation of new leaders, and no energy in the party&#8217;s base. Yet Obama&#8217;s forceful pursuit of his progressive agenda, coupled with the nation&#8217;s rapidly changing cultural and demographic landscape, lit a fire under the right, returning Republicans to power and inviting a bloody struggle for the party&#8217;s identity in the post-Bush era. The factions that emerged-one led by absolutists like Jim Jordan and Ted Cruz, the other led by pragmatists like John Boehner and Mitch McConnell-engaged in a series of devastating internecine clashes and attempted coups for control. With the GOP&#8217;s internal fissures rendering it legislatively impotent, and that impotence fueling a growing resentment toward the political class and its institutions, the stage was set for an outsider to crash the party. When Trump descended a gilded escalator to announce his run in the summer of 2015, the candidate had met the moment.</p>
<p>                    Only by viewing Trump as the culmination of a decade-long civil war inside the Republican Party-and of the parallel sense of cultural, socioeconomic, and technological disruption during that period-can we appreciate how he won the White House and consider the fundamental questions at the center of America&#8217;s current turmoil. How did a party obsessed with the national debt vote for trillion-dollar deficits and record-setting spending increases? How did the party of compassionate conservatism become the party of Muslim bans and walls? How did the party of family values elect a thrice-divorced philanderer? And, most important, how long can such a party survive?</p>
<p>                     Loaded with exclusive reporting and based off hundreds of interviews-including with key players such as President Trump, Paul Ryan, Ted Cruz, John Boehner, Mitch McConnell, Jim DeMint, and Reince Priebus, and many others-American Carnage takes us behind the scenes of this tumultuous period as we&#8217;ve never seen it before and establishes Tim Alberta as the premier chronicler of this political era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Revolt : Inside the Populist Coalition Reshaping American Politics &#8211; Salena Zito</title>
		<link>/the-great-revolt-inside-the-populist-coalition-reshaping-american-politics-salena-zito/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-revolt-inside-the-populist-coalition-reshaping-american-politics-salena-zito/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A CNN political analyst and a Republican strategist reframe the discussion of the &#8220;Trump voter&#8221; to answer the question, What&#8217;s next? NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY FOREIGN AFFAIRS &#8211; &#8220;Unlike most retellings of the 2016 election, The Great Revolt provides a cohesive, non-wild-eyed argument about where the Republican Party could [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-revolt-inside-the-populist-coalition-reshaping-american-politics-salena-zito/">The Great Revolt : Inside the Populist Coalition Reshaping American Politics &#8211; Salena Zito</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A CNN political analyst and a Republican strategist reframe the discussion of the &#8220;Trump voter&#8221; to answer the question, What&#8217;s next?</p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY FOREIGN AFFAIRS &#8211; &#8220;Unlike most retellings of the 2016 election, The Great Revolt provides a cohesive, non-wild-eyed argument about where the Republican Party could be headed.&#8221;&#8211;The Atlantic </p>
<p>                    Political experts were wrong about the 2016 election and they continue to blow it, predicting the coming demise of the president without pausing to consider the durability of the winds that swept him into office. </p>
<p>                    Salena Zito and Brad Todd have traveled over 27,000 miles of country roads to interview more than three hundred Trump voters in ten swing counties. What emerges is a portrait of a group of citizens who span job descriptions, income brackets, education levels, and party allegiances, united by their desire to be part of a movement larger than themselves. They want to put pragmatism before ideology and localism before globalism, and demand the respect they deserve from Washington. </p>
<p>                    The 2016 election signaled a realignment in American politics that will outlast any one president. Zito and Todd reframe the discussion of the &#8220;Trump voter&#8221; to answer the question, What&#8217;s next?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-revolt-inside-the-populist-coalition-reshaping-american-politics-salena-zito/">The Great Revolt : Inside the Populist Coalition Reshaping American Politics &#8211; Salena Zito</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Power : Why outsiders are winning, institutions are failing, and how the rest of us can keep up in the age of mass participation &#8211; Jeremy Heimans, Henry Timms (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/new-power-why-outsiders-are-winning-institutions-are-failing-and-how-the-rest-of-us-can-keep-up-in-the-age-of-mass-participation-jeremy-heimans-henry-timms-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/new-power-why-outsiders-are-winning-institutions-are-failing-and-how-the-rest-of-us-can-keep-up-in-the-age-of-mass-participation-jeremy-heimans-henry-timms-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For most of human history the rules of power were clear: power was something to be seized, and then jealously guarded. Under this &#8216;Old Power&#8217; we lived in a world of rulers and subjects. Now, we all sense that something has changed. From #MeToo to Harvey Weinstein; Corbyn to Trump; from YouTube sensations to darker [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-power-why-outsiders-are-winning-institutions-are-failing-and-how-the-rest-of-us-can-keep-up-in-the-age-of-mass-participation-jeremy-heimans-henry-timms-abridged/">New Power : Why outsiders are winning, institutions are failing, and how the rest of us can keep up in the age of mass participation &#8211; Jeremy Heimans, Henry Timms (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For most of human history the rules of power were clear: power was something to be seized, and then jealously guarded. Under this &#8216;Old Power&#8217; we lived in a world of rulers and subjects.    </p>
<p>                    Now, we all sense that something has changed. From #MeToo to Harvey Weinstein; Corbyn to Trump; from YouTube sensations to darker phenomena such as the emergence of ISIS &#8211; in our new hyper-connected world, ideas and movements can spread and flourish with astonishing force and speed.    </p>
<p>                    In New Power, Jeremy Heimans and Henry Timms confront the biggest story of our age and trace how New Power is the key to understanding where we are and will prosper in the 21st Century.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on examples from business, politics, popular culture and social justice, as well as case studies of organisations like LEGO and TED, they explain the forces that are changing the course of our age.    </p>
<p>                    In a world increasingly shaped by New Power, this book will show you how to shape your future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/new-power-why-outsiders-are-winning-institutions-are-failing-and-how-the-rest-of-us-can-keep-up-in-the-age-of-mass-participation-jeremy-heimans-henry-timms-abridged/">New Power : Why outsiders are winning, institutions are failing, and how the rest of us can keep up in the age of mass participation &#8211; Jeremy Heimans, Henry Timms (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Imagined Communities : Reflections on the Origin and Spread of Nationalism &#8211; Benedict Anderson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/imagined-communities-reflections-on-the-origin-and-spread-of-nationalism-benedict-anderson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nationalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/imagined-communities-reflections-on-the-origin-and-spread-of-nationalism-benedict-anderson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What are the imagined communities that compel men to kill or to die for an idea of a nation? This notion of nationhood had its origins in the founding of the Americas, but was then adopted and transformed by populist movements in nineteenth-century Europe. It became the rallying cry for anti-Imperialism as well as the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/imagined-communities-reflections-on-the-origin-and-spread-of-nationalism-benedict-anderson-abridged/">Imagined Communities : Reflections on the Origin and Spread of Nationalism &#8211; Benedict Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What are the imagined communities that compel men to kill or to die for an idea of a nation? This notion of nationhood had its origins in the founding of the Americas, but was then adopted and transformed by populist movements in nineteenth-century Europe. It became the rallying cry for anti-Imperialism as well as the abiding explanation for colonialism. In this scintillating, groundbreaking work of intellectual history Anderson explores how ideas are formed and reformulated at every level, from high politics to popular culture, and the way that they can make people do extraordinary things. In the twenty-first century, these debates on the nature of the nation state are even more urgent. As new nations rise, vying for influence, and old empires decline, we must understand who we are as a community in the face of history, and change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/imagined-communities-reflections-on-the-origin-and-spread-of-nationalism-benedict-anderson-abridged/">Imagined Communities : Reflections on the Origin and Spread of Nationalism &#8211; Benedict Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A First-Rate Madness : Uncovering the Links Between Leadership and Mental Illness &#8211; Nassir Ghaemi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-first-rate-madness-uncovering-the-links-between-leadership-and-mental-illness-nassir-ghaemi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-first-rate-madness-uncovering-the-links-between-leadership-and-mental-illness-nassir-ghaemi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestseller is a myth-shattering exploration of the powerful connections between mental illness and leadership. Historians have long puzzled over the apparent mental instability of great and terrible leaders alike: Napoleon, Lincoln, Churchill, Hitler, and others. In A First-Rate Madness, Nassir Ghaemi, director of the Mood Disorders Programme at Tufts Medical Center, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-first-rate-madness-uncovering-the-links-between-leadership-and-mental-illness-nassir-ghaemi-abridged/">A First-Rate Madness : Uncovering the Links Between Leadership and Mental Illness &#8211; Nassir Ghaemi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestseller is a myth-shattering exploration of the powerful connections between mental illness and leadership.    </p>
<p>                    Historians have long puzzled over the apparent mental instability of great and terrible leaders alike: Napoleon, Lincoln, Churchill, Hitler, and others. In A First-Rate Madness, Nassir Ghaemi, director of the Mood Disorders Programme at Tufts Medical Center, offers and sets forth a controversial, compelling thesis: the very qualities that mark those with mood disorders also make for the best leaders in times of crisis.     </p>
<p>                    From the importance of Lincoln&#8217;s &#8220;depressive realism&#8221; to the lacklustre leadership of exceedingly sane men as Neville Chamberlain, A First-Rate Madness overturns many of our most cherished perceptions about greatness and the mind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-first-rate-madness-uncovering-the-links-between-leadership-and-mental-illness-nassir-ghaemi-abridged/">A First-Rate Madness : Uncovering the Links Between Leadership and Mental Illness &#8211; Nassir Ghaemi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colonialism & Imperialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historiography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National Liberation & Independence, Post-colonialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The seminal work that has redefined our understanding of colonialism and empire, with a preface by the author &#8216;Stimulating, elegant and pugnacious&#8217; Observer &#8216;Magisterial&#8217; Terry Eagleton In this highly-acclaimed work, Edward Said surveys the history and nature of Western attitudes towards the East, considering orientalism as a powerful European ideological creation &#8211; a way for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/">Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The seminal work that has redefined our  understanding of colonialism and empire, with a preface by the author    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Stimulating, elegant and pugnacious&#8217; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Magisterial&#8217; Terry Eagleton    </p>
<p>                    In this  highly-acclaimed work, Edward Said surveys the history and nature of  Western attitudes towards the East, considering orientalism as a  powerful European ideological creation &#8211; a way for writers, philosophers  and colonial administrators to deal with the &#8216;otherness&#8217; of eastern  culture, customs and beliefs. He traces this view through the writings  of Homer, Nerval and Flaubert, Disraeli and Kipling, whose imaginative  depictions have greatly contributed to the West&#8217;s romantic and exotic  picture of the Orient. Drawing on his own experiences as an Arab  Palestinian living in the West, Said examines how these ideas can be a  reflection of European imperialism and racism.<br />
                    &#8216;Beautifully patterned and passionately argued&#8217;<br />
                    New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Very exciting &#8230; his case is not merely persuasive, but conclusive&#8217;<br />
                    John Leonard, New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/">Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blueprint for Revolution : How to Use Rice Pudding, Lego Men, and Other Nonviolent Techniques to Galvanize Communities, Overthrow Dictators, or Simply Change the World &#8211; Srdja Popovic, Matthew Miller (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blueprint-for-revolution-how-to-use-rice-pudding-lego-men-and-other-nonviolent-techniques-to-galvanize-communities-overthrow-dictators-or-simply-change-the-world-srdja-popovic-matthew-miller/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blueprint-for-revolution-how-to-use-rice-pudding-lego-men-and-other-nonviolent-techniques-to-galvanize-communities-overthrow-dictators-or-simply-change-the-world-srdja-popovic-matthew-miller/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An urgent and accessible handbook for peaceful protesters, activists, and community organizers&#8211;anyone trying to defend their rights, hold their government accountable, or change the world Blueprint for Revolution will teach you how to &#8211; make oppression backfire by playing your opponents&#8217; strongest card against them &#8211; identify the &#8220;almighty pillars of power&#8221; in order to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blueprint-for-revolution-how-to-use-rice-pudding-lego-men-and-other-nonviolent-techniques-to-galvanize-communities-overthrow-dictators-or-simply-change-the-world-srdja-popovic-matthew-miller/">Blueprint for Revolution : How to Use Rice Pudding, Lego Men, and Other Nonviolent Techniques to Galvanize Communities, Overthrow Dictators, or Simply Change the World &#8211; Srdja Popovic, Matthew Miller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An urgent and accessible handbook for peaceful protesters, activists, and community organizers&#8211;anyone trying to defend their rights, hold their government accountable, or change the world  Blueprint for Revolution will teach you how to<br />
                     &#8211; make oppression backfire by playing your opponents&#8217; strongest card against them<br />
                     &#8211; identify the &#8220;almighty pillars of power&#8221; in order to shift the balance of control<br />
                     &#8211; dream big, but start small: learn how to pick battles you can win<br />
                     &#8211; listen to what people actually care about in order to incorporate their needs into your revolutionary vision<br />
                     &#8211; master the art of compromise to bring together even the most disparate groups<br />
                     &#8211; recognize your allies and view your enemies as potential partners<br />
                     &#8211; use humor to make yourself heard, defuse potentially violent situations, and &#8220;laugh your way to victory&#8221;  Praise for Blueprint for Revolution &#8220;The title is no exaggeration. Otpor&#8217;s methods . . . have been adopted by democracy movements around the world. The Egyptian opposition used them to topple Hosni Mubarak. In Lebanon, the Serbs helped the Cedar Revolution extricate the country from Syrian control. In Maldives, their methods were the key to overthrowing a dictator who had held power for thirty years. In many other countries, people have used what Canvas teaches to accomplish other political goals, such as fighting corruption or protecting the environment.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times &#8220;A clear, well-constructed, and easily applicable set of principles for any David facing any Goliath (sans slingshot, of course) . . . By the end of Blueprint,  the idea that a punch is no match for a punch line feels like anything but a joke.&#8221;&#8211;The Boston Globe &#8220;An entertaining primer on the theory and practice of peaceful protest.&#8221;&#8211;The Guardian  &#8220;With this wonderful book, Srdja Popovic is inspiring ordinary people facing injustice and oppression to use this tool kit to challenge their oppressors and create something much better. When I was growing up, we dreamed that young people could bring down those who misused their power and create a more just and democratic society. For Srdja Popovic, living in Belgrade in 1998, this same dream was potentially a much more dangerous idea. But with an extraordinarily courageous group of students that formed Otpor!, Srdja used imagination, invention, cunning, and lots of humor to create a movement that not only succeeded in toppling the brutal dictator Slobodan Milosevic but has become a blueprint for nonviolent revolution around the world. Srdja rules!&#8221;&#8211;Peter Gabriel  &#8220;Blueprint for Revolution is not only a spirited guide to changing the world but a breakthrough in the annals of advice for those who seek justice and democracy. It asks (and not heavy-handedly): As long as you want to change the world, why not do it joyfully? It&#8217;s not just funny. It&#8217;s seriously funny. No joke.&#8221;&#8211;Todd Gitlin, author of The Sixties and Occupy Nation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blueprint-for-revolution-how-to-use-rice-pudding-lego-men-and-other-nonviolent-techniques-to-galvanize-communities-overthrow-dictators-or-simply-change-the-world-srdja-popovic-matthew-miller/">Blueprint for Revolution : How to Use Rice Pudding, Lego Men, and Other Nonviolent Techniques to Galvanize Communities, Overthrow Dictators, or Simply Change the World &#8211; Srdja Popovic, Matthew Miller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Progress : Ten Reasons to Look Forward to the Future &#8211; Johan Norberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Book of the Year for The Economist and the Observer Our world seems to be collapsing. The daily news cycle reports the deterioration: divisive politics across the Western world, racism, poverty, war, inequality, hunger. While politicians, journalists and activists from all sides talk about the damage done, Johan Norberg offers an illuminating and heartening [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/">Progress : Ten Reasons to Look Forward to the Future &#8211; Johan Norberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Book of the Year for The Economist and the Observer    </p>
<p>                    Our world seems to be collapsing. The daily news cycle reports the deterioration: divisive politics across the Western world, racism, poverty, war, inequality, hunger. While politicians, journalists and activists from all sides talk about the damage done, Johan Norberg offers an illuminating and heartening analysis of just how far we have come in tackling the greatest problems facing humanity. In the face of fear-mongering, darkness and division, the facts are unequivocal: the golden age is now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/">Progress : Ten Reasons to Look Forward to the Future &#8211; Johan Norberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dangerously Sleepy : Overworked Americans and the Cult of Manly Wakefulness &#8211; Alan Derickson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dangerously-sleepy-overworked-americans-and-the-cult-of-manly-wakefulness-alan-derickson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dangerously-sleepy-overworked-americans-and-the-cult-of-manly-wakefulness-alan-derickson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Workers in the United States are losing sleep. In the global economy a growing number of employees hold jobs-often more than one at once-with unpredictable hours. Even before the rise of the twenty-four-hour workplace, the relationship between sleep and industry was problematic: sleep is frequently cast as an enemy or a weakness, while constant productivity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dangerously-sleepy-overworked-americans-and-the-cult-of-manly-wakefulness-alan-derickson-abridged/">Dangerously Sleepy : Overworked Americans and the Cult of Manly Wakefulness &#8211; Alan Derickson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Workers in the United States are losing sleep. In the global economy a growing number of employees hold jobs-often more than one at once-with unpredictable hours. Even before the rise of the twenty-four-hour workplace, the relationship between sleep and industry was problematic: sleep is frequently cast as an enemy or a weakness, while constant productivity and flexibility are glorified at the expense of health and safety.    </p>
<p>                    Dangerously Sleepy is the first book to track the longtime association of overwork and sleep deprivation from the nineteenth century to the present. Health and labor historian Alan Derickson charts the cultural and political forces behind the overvaluation-and masculinization-of wakefulness in the United States. Since the nineteenth century, men at all levels of society have toiled around the clock by necessity: steel workers coped with rotating shifts, Pullman porters grappled with ever-changing timetables and unrelenting on-call status, and long-haul truckers dealt with chaotic life on the road. But the dangerous realities of exhaustion were minimized and even glamorized when the entrepreneurial drive of public figures such as Thomas Edison and Donald Trump encouraged American men to deny biological need in the name of success. For workers, resisting sleep became a challenge of masculine strength.    </p>
<p>                    This lucid history of the wakeful work ethic suggests that for millions of American men and women, untenable work schedules have been the main factor leading to sleep loss, newer ailments such as shift work sleep disorder, and related morbidity and mortality. Dangerously Sleepy places these public health problems in historical context.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dangerously-sleepy-overworked-americans-and-the-cult-of-manly-wakefulness-alan-derickson-abridged/">Dangerously Sleepy : Overworked Americans and the Cult of Manly Wakefulness &#8211; Alan Derickson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An unburdening, a witness statement and a thriller all at the same time &#8230; electrifying.&#8217; The Times I have to assume that there is a very real chance that Putin or members of his regime will have me killed some day. If I&#8217;m killed, you will know who did it. When my enemies read this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/">Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An unburdening, a witness statement and a thriller all at the same time &#8230; electrifying.&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    I have to assume that there is a very real chance that Putin or members of his regime will have me killed some day. If I&#8217;m killed, you will know who did it. When my enemies read this book, they will know that you know.    </p>
<p>                    A Sunday Times and New York Times bestseller. A true-life thriller by one of Putin&#8217;s Most Wanted.    </p>
<p>                    In November 2009, the young lawyer Sergei Magnitsky was beaten to death by eight police officers in a freezing cell in a Moscow prison. His crime? Testifying against Russian officials who were involved in a conspiracy to steal $230 million of taxes.    </p>
<p>                    Red Notice is a searing expose of the whitewash of this imprisonment and murder. The killing hasn&#8217;t been investigated. It hasn&#8217;t been punished. Bill Browder is still campaigning for justice for his late lawyer and friend. This is his explosive journey from the heady world of finance in New York and London in the 1990s, through battles with ruthless oligarchs in turbulent post-Soviet Union Moscow, to the shadowy heart of the Kremlin.    </p>
<p>                    With fraud, bribery, corruption and torture exposed at every turn, Red Notice is a shocking political roller-coaster.<br />
                    __________________    </p>
<p>                    Reads like a classic thriller, with an everyman hero alone and in danger in a hostile foreign city &#8230; but it&#8217;s all true, and it&#8217;s a story that needs to be told.&#8217; Lee Child    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A shocking true-life thriller.&#8217; Tom Stoppard    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A riveting account&#8230; it is a powerful story and Browder tells it skilfully.&#8217; The Washington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/">Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brazillionaires : The Godfathers of Modern Brazil &#8211; Alex Cuadros (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brazillionaires-the-godfathers-of-modern-brazil-alex-cuadros-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brazillionaires-the-godfathers-of-modern-brazil-alex-cuadros-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the Financial Times Business Book of the Year Award Wealth and power on the trail of the super-rich In 2012, Brazilian tycoon Eike Batista was the eighth richest man in the world, his $30bn fortune built on Brazil&#8217;s incredible natural resources. By the middle of 2013 he had lost it all, engulfed in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brazillionaires-the-godfathers-of-modern-brazil-alex-cuadros-abridged/">Brazillionaires : The Godfathers of Modern Brazil &#8211; Alex Cuadros (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the Financial Times  Business Book of the Year Award     </p>
<p>                    Wealth and power on the trail of the super-rich    </p>
<p>                    In 2012, Brazilian tycoon Eike Batista was the eighth richest man in the world, his $30bn fortune built on Brazil&#8217;s incredible natural resources. By the middle of 2013 he had lost it all, engulfed in scandal.    </p>
<p>                    Brazillionaires is a fast-paced account of Batista&#8217;s rise and fall: a story of helicopter flights, beach-front penthouses and high-speed car crashes. Along the way, it tells the parallel story of Brazil itself, a country caught in the cycle of boom and bust, renewed hope and dashed promise; a country where the hyper-rich are at the heart of the economy &#8211; and where their wealth can buy immense political power.    </p>
<p>                    Stefan Zweig said in 1941 that Brazil was the country of the future; Brazilians joke that it always will be. Today, rampant corruption and endemic inequality threaten to derail the new Brazilian Dream. The brazillionaires are the key to understanding that dream; through them Brazillionaires tells the story of their country&#8217;s past, present and future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brazillionaires-the-godfathers-of-modern-brazil-alex-cuadros-abridged/">Brazillionaires : The Godfathers of Modern Brazil &#8211; Alex Cuadros (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Connection is a story of political skullduggery unprecedented in American history. It weaves together tales of international intrigue, cyber espionage, and superpower rivalry. After US-Russia relations soured, as Vladimir Putin moved to reassert Russian strength on the global stage, Moscow trained its best hackers on US political targets and exploited Julian Assange and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/">Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Connection is a story of political skullduggery unprecedented in American history. It weaves together tales of international intrigue, cyber espionage, and superpower rivalry. After US-Russia relations soured, as Vladimir Putin moved to reassert Russian strength on the global stage, Moscow trained its best hackers on US political targets and exploited Julian Assange and Wikileaks to disseminate information that could affect the 2016 election.     </p>
<p>                    The Russians were wildly successful and the great break-in of 2016 was no &#8220;third rate burglary.&#8221; It was far more sophisticated and sinister &#8212; a brazen act of political espionage designed to interfere with American democracy, and at the end of the day, Trump, the candidate with business ties to Russia, won. And millions of Americans were left wondering, what the hell happened?    </p>
<p>                    This story of high-tech spying and multiple political feuds will be told against the backdrop of Donald Trump and his strange relationship with Putin, and his inner circle of advisers with profitable ties to Russia, most notably Michael Flynn and Paul Manafort.    </p>
<p>                    The Russian Connection will chronicle and examine all these bizarre events and relationships, explain the stakes, and seek to answer one of the biggest questions in American politics: How and why did a foreign government infiltrate the country&#8217;s political process and implant its tentacles in Washington?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/">Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Senator Bernie Sanders explains where he comes from. He describes in detail how, after cutting his teeth in the Civil Rights movement, Sanders helped build an extraordinary grassroots political movement in Vermont, making it possible for him to become the first independent elected to the U.S. House of Representatives in forty years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/">Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Senator Bernie Sanders explains where he comes from. He describes in detail how, after cutting his teeth in the Civil Rights movement, Sanders helped build an extraordinary grassroots political movement in Vermont, making it possible for him to become the first independent elected to the U.S. House of Representatives in forty years and now the longest-serving independent in U.S. political history. An extensive afterword by The Nation&#8217;s National Affairs correspondent John Nichols continues the story with Sanders&#8217;s entrance into the Senate, the drama of the 2016 Democratic Primary, his ongoing resistance to Trump, and the thrilling launch of his 2020 bid for the White House. A new foreword by Nina Turner, former president of Our Revolution and co-chair of the Sanders for President campaign, provides a rare glimpse of Bernie as a person. Outsider in the White House tells the story of a passionate and principled political life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsider-in-the-white-house-bernie-sanders-abridged/">Outsider in the White House &#8211; Bernie Sanders (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bully Pulpit : Theodore Roosevelt, William Howard Taft, and the Golden Age of Journalism &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bully-pulpit-theodore-roosevelt-william-howard-taft-and-the-golden-age-of-journalism-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bully-pulpit-theodore-roosevelt-william-howard-taft-and-the-golden-age-of-journalism-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the Best Books of the Year as chosen by The New York Times, The Washington Post, The Economist, Time, USA TODAY, Christian Science Monitor, and more. &#8220;A tale so gripping that one questions the need for fiction when real life is so plump with drama and intrigue&#8221; (Associated Press). Doris Kearns Goodwin&#8217;s The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bully-pulpit-theodore-roosevelt-william-howard-taft-and-the-golden-age-of-journalism-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/">The Bully Pulpit : Theodore Roosevelt, William Howard Taft, and the Golden Age of Journalism &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the Best Books of the Year as chosen by The New York Times, The Washington Post, The Economist, Time, USA TODAY, Christian Science Monitor, and more. &#8220;A tale so gripping that one questions the need for fiction when real life is so plump with drama and intrigue&#8221; (Associated Press).     </p>
<p>                    Doris Kearns Goodwin&#8217;s The Bully Pulpit is a dynamic history of the first decade of the Progressive era, that tumultuous time when the nation was coming unseamed and reform was in the air.     </p>
<p>                    The story is told through the intense friendship of Theodore Roosevelt and William Howard Taft&#8211;a close relationship that strengthens both men before it ruptures in 1912, when they engage in a brutal fight for the presidential nomination that divides their wives, their children, and their closest friends, while crippling the progressive wing of the Republican Party, causing Democrat Woodrow Wilson to be elected, and changing the country&#8217;s history.     </p>
<p>                    The Bully Pulpit is also the story of the muckraking press, which arouses the spirit of reform that helps Roosevelt push the government to shed its laissez-faire attitude toward robber barons, corrupt politicians, and corporate exploiters of our natural resources. The muckrakers are portrayed through the greatest group of journalists ever assembled at one magazine&#8211;Ida Tarbell, Ray Stannard Baker, Lincoln Steffens, and William Allen White&#8211;teamed under the mercurial genius of publisher S.S. McClure.     </p>
<p>                    Goodwin&#8217;s narrative is founded upon a wealth of primary materials. The correspondence of more than four hundred letters between Roosevelt and Taft begins in their early thirties and ends only months before Roosevelt&#8217;s death. Edith Roosevelt and Nellie Taft kept diaries. The muckrakers wrote hundreds of letters to one another, kept journals, and wrote their memoirs. The letters of Captain Archie Butt, who served as a personal aide to both Roosevelt and Taft, provide an intimate view of both men.     </p>
<p>                    The Bully Pulpit, like Goodwin&#8217;s brilliant chronicles of the Civil War and World War II, exquisitely demonstrates her distinctive ability to combine scholarly rigor with accessibility. It is a major work of history&#8211;an examination of leadership in a rare moment of activism and reform that brought the country closer to its founding ideals.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bully-pulpit-theodore-roosevelt-william-howard-taft-and-the-golden-age-of-journalism-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/">The Bully Pulpit : Theodore Roosevelt, William Howard Taft, and the Golden Age of Journalism &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Anarchy : The Relentless Rise of the East India Company &#8211; William Dalrymple (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-anarchy-the-relentless-rise-of-the-east-india-company-william-dalrymple-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[British & Irish History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colonialism & Imperialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Naval Forces & Warfare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-anarchy-the-relentless-rise-of-the-east-india-company-william-dalrymple-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP 5 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER ONE OF BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S BEST BOOKS OF 2019 THE TIMES HISTORY BOOK OF THE YEAR FINALIST FOR THE CUNDILL HISTORY PRIZE 2020 LONGLISTED FOR THE BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION 2019 A FINANCIAL TIMES, OBSERVER, DAILY TELEGRAPH, WALL STREET JOURNAL AND TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8216;Dalrymple is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-anarchy-the-relentless-rise-of-the-east-india-company-william-dalrymple-abridged/">The Anarchy : The Relentless Rise of the East India Company &#8211; William Dalrymple (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP 5 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    ONE OF BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S BEST BOOKS OF 2019<br />
                    THE TIMES HISTORY BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    FINALIST FOR THE CUNDILL HISTORY PRIZE 2020<br />
                    LONGLISTED FOR THE BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION 2019<br />
                    A FINANCIAL TIMES, OBSERVER, DAILY TELEGRAPH, WALL STREET JOURNAL AND TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Dalrymple is a superb historian with a visceral understanding of India &#8230; A book of beauty&#8217; &#8211;  Gerard DeGroot, The Times    </p>
<p>                    In August 1765 the East India Company defeated the young Mughal emperor and forced him to establish a new administration in his richest provinces. Run by English merchants who collected taxes using a ruthless private army, this new regime saw the East India Company transform itself from an international trading corporation into something much more unusual: an aggressive colonial power in the guise of a multinational business.    </p>
<p>                      William Dalrymple tells the remarkable story of the East India Company as it has never been told before, unfolding a timely cautionary tale of the first global corporate power.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-anarchy-the-relentless-rise-of-the-east-india-company-william-dalrymple-abridged/">The Anarchy : The Relentless Rise of the East India Company &#8211; William Dalrymple (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Accidental Presidents : Eight Men Who Changed America &#8211; Jared Cohen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestselling &#8220;deep dive into the terms of eight former presidents is chock-full of political hijinks-and deja vu&#8221; (Vanity Fair) and provides a fascinating look at the men who came to the office without being elected to it, showing how each affected the nation and world. The strength and prestige of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/">Accidental Presidents : Eight Men Who Changed America &#8211; Jared Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestselling &#8220;deep dive into the terms of eight former presidents is chock-full of political hijinks-and deja vu&#8221; (Vanity Fair) and provides a fascinating look at the men who came to the office without being elected to it, showing how each affected the nation and world.    </p>
<p>                    The strength and prestige of the American presidency has waxed and waned since George Washington. Eight men have succeeded to the presidency when the incumbent died in office. In one way or another they vastly changed our history. Only Theodore Roosevelt would have been elected in his own right. Only TR, Truman, Coolidge, and LBJ were re-elected.    </p>
<p>                    John Tyler succeeded William Henry Harrison who died 30 days into his term. He was kicked out of his party and became the first president threatened with impeachment. Millard Fillmore succeeded esteemed General Zachary Taylor. He immediately sacked the entire cabinet and delayed an inevitable Civil War by standing with Henry Clay&#8217;s compromise of 1850. Andrew Johnson, who succeeded our greatest president, sided with remnants of the Confederacy in Reconstruction. Chester Arthur, the embodiment of the spoils system, was so reviled as James Garfield&#8217;s successor that he had to defend himself against plotting Garfield&#8217;s assassination; but he reformed the civil service. Theodore Roosevelt broke up the trusts. Calvin Coolidge silently cooled down the Harding scandals and preserved the White House for the Republican Herbert Hoover and the Great Depression. Harry Truman surprised everybody when he succeeded the great FDR and proved an able and accomplished president. Lyndon B. Johnson was named to deliver Texas electorally. He led the nation forward on Civil Rights but failed on Vietnam.    </p>
<p>                    Accidental Presidents shows that &#8220;history unfolds in death as well as in life&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal) and adds immeasurably to our understanding of the power and limits of the American presidency in critical times.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/">Accidental Presidents : Eight Men Who Changed America &#8211; Jared Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stronger Together &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, Tim Kaine (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For more than a year, Hillary Clinton has laid out an ambitious agenda to improve the lives of the American people and make the country stronger and safer. Stronger Together presents that agenda in full, relating stories from the American people and outlining the Clinton/Kaine campaign&#8217;s plans on everything from apprenticeships to the Zika virus, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/">Stronger Together &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, Tim Kaine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For more than a year, Hillary Clinton has laid out an ambitious agenda to improve the lives of the American people and make the country stronger and safer. Stronger Together presents that agenda in full, relating stories from the American people and outlining the Clinton/Kaine campaign&#8217;s plans on everything from apprenticeships to the Zika virus, including:<br />
                     -Building an economy that works for everyone.<br />
                     -Making investment in good-paying jobs, including infrastructure, manufacturing, clean energy and small business.<br />
                     -Making debt-free college a reality and tackling the student debt crisis.<br />
                     -A course of action to defeat global terrorist networks and support allies.<br />
                     -Breaking down the barriers that hold Americans back by reforming a broken immigration system, ending mass incarceration, protecting voting rights, and fixing the campaign finance system.<br />
                     -Putting families first through universal, affordable health care; paid family and medical leave, and affordable child care.<br />
                        Stronger Together offers specific solutions and a bold vision for building a more perfect union.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stronger-together-hillary-rodham-clinton-tim-kaine-abridged/">Stronger Together &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton, Tim Kaine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amusing Ourselves to Death : Public Discourse in the Age of Show Business &#8211; Neil Postman, Introduction by Andrew Postman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/amusing-ourselves-to-death-public-discourse-in-the-age-of-show-business-neil-postman-introduction-by-andrew-postman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/amusing-ourselves-to-death-public-discourse-in-the-age-of-show-business-neil-postman-introduction-by-andrew-postman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What happens when media and politics become forms of entertainment? As our world begins to look more and more like Orwell&#8217;s 1984, Neil&#8217;s Postman&#8217;s essential guide to the modern media is more relevant than ever. It&#8217;s unlikely that Trump has ever read Amusing Ourselves to Death, but his ascent would not have surprised Postman.&#8221; -CNN [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/amusing-ourselves-to-death-public-discourse-in-the-age-of-show-business-neil-postman-introduction-by-andrew-postman-abridged/">Amusing Ourselves to Death : Public Discourse in the Age of Show Business &#8211; Neil Postman, Introduction by Andrew Postman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What happens when media and politics become forms of entertainment? As our world begins to look more and more like Orwell&#8217;s 1984, Neil&#8217;s Postman&#8217;s essential guide to the modern media is more relevant than ever.     </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s unlikely that Trump has ever read Amusing Ourselves to Death, but his ascent would not have surprised Postman.&#8221; -CNN     </p>
<p>                    Originally published in 1985, Neil Postman&#8217;s groundbreaking polemic about the corrosive effects of television on our politics and public discourse has been hailed as a twenty-first-century book published in the twentieth century. Now, with television joined by more sophisticated electronic media&#8211;from the Internet to cell phones to DVDs&#8211;it has taken on even greater significance. Amusing Ourselves to Death is a prophetic look at what happens when politics, journalism, education, and even religion become subject to the demands of entertainment. It is also a blueprint for regaining control of our media, so that they can serve our highest goals.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A brilliant, powerful, and important book. This is an indictment that Postman has laid down and, so far as I can see, an irrefutable one.&#8221; -Jonathan Yardley, The Washington Post Book World</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/amusing-ourselves-to-death-public-discourse-in-the-age-of-show-business-neil-postman-introduction-by-andrew-postman-abridged/">Amusing Ourselves to Death : Public Discourse in the Age of Show Business &#8211; Neil Postman, Introduction by Andrew Postman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Age of Propaganda &#8211; Anthony Pratkanis, Elliot Aronson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/age-of-propaganda-anthony-pratkanis-elliot-aronson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dance & Other Performing Arts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/age-of-propaganda-anthony-pratkanis-elliot-aronson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Americans create 57% of the world&#8217;s advertising while representing only 6% of its population; half of our waking hours are spent immersed in the mass media. Persuasion has always been integral to the democratic process, but increasingly, thoughtful discussion is being replaced with simplistic soundbites and manipulative messages. Drawing on the history of propaganda as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-propaganda-anthony-pratkanis-elliot-aronson-abridged/">Age of Propaganda &#8211; Anthony Pratkanis, Elliot Aronson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Americans create 57% of the world&#8217;s advertising while representing only 6% of its population; half of our waking hours are spent immersed in the mass media. Persuasion has always been integral to the democratic process, but increasingly, thoughtful discussion is being replaced with simplistic soundbites and manipulative messages.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the history of propaganda as well as on contemporary research in social psychology, Age of Propaganda shows how the tactics used by political campaigners, sales agents, advertisers, televangelists, demagogues, and others often take advantage of our emotions by appealing to our deepest fears and most irrational hopes, creating a distorted vision of the world we live in.     </p>
<p>                    This revised and updated edition includes coverage of the Clinton/Lewinsky scandal, recent election campaigns, talk radio, teen suicide, U.F.O. abductions, the Columbine shootings, and novel propaganda tactics based on hypocrisy and false allegations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-propaganda-anthony-pratkanis-elliot-aronson-abridged/">Age of Propaganda &#8211; Anthony Pratkanis, Elliot Aronson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Black Jacobins : Toussaint L&#8217;Ouverture and the San Domingo Revolution &#8211; C.L.R. James (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-black-jacobins-toussaint-louverture-and-the-san-domingo-revolution-c-l-r-james-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-black-jacobins-toussaint-louverture-and-the-san-domingo-revolution-c-l-r-james-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A classic and impassioned account of the first revolution in the Third World. This powerful, intensely dramatic book is the definitive account of the Haitian Revolution of 1794-1803, a revolution that began in the wake of the Bastille but became the model for the Third World liberation movements from Africa to Cuba. It is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-black-jacobins-toussaint-louverture-and-the-san-domingo-revolution-c-l-r-james-abridged/">The Black Jacobins : Toussaint L&#8217;Ouverture and the San Domingo Revolution &#8211; C.L.R. James (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A classic and impassioned account of the first revolution in the Third World.     </p>
<p>                    This powerful, intensely dramatic book is the definitive account of the Haitian Revolution of 1794-1803, a revolution that began in the wake of the Bastille but became the model for the Third World liberation movements from Africa to Cuba. It is the story of the French colony of San Domingo, a place where the brutality of master toward slave was commonplace and ingeniously refined. And it is the story of a barely literate slave named Toussaint L&#8217;Ouverture, who led the black people of San Domingo in a successful struggle against successive invasions by overwhelming French, Spanish, and English forces and in the process helped form the first independent nation in the Caribbean.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-black-jacobins-toussaint-louverture-and-the-san-domingo-revolution-c-l-r-james-abridged/">The Black Jacobins : Toussaint L&#8217;Ouverture and the San Domingo Revolution &#8211; C.L.R. James (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future is History : How Totalitarianism Reclaimed Russia &#8211; Masha Gessen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-future-is-history-how-totalitarianism-reclaimed-russia-masha-gessen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-future-is-history-how-totalitarianism-reclaimed-russia-masha-gessen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Future is History Masha Gessen follows the lives of four Russians, born as the Soviet Union crumbled, at what promised to be the dawn of democracy. Each came of age with unprecedented expectations, some as the children or grandchildren of the very architects of the new Russia, each with newfound aspirations of their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-is-history-how-totalitarianism-reclaimed-russia-masha-gessen-abridged/">The Future is History : How Totalitarianism Reclaimed Russia &#8211; Masha Gessen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Future is History Masha Gessen follows the lives of four Russians, born as the Soviet Union crumbled, at what promised to be the dawn of democracy. Each came of age with unprecedented expectations, some as the children or grandchildren of the very architects of the new Russia, each with newfound aspirations of their own &#8211; as entrepreneurs, activists, thinkers and writers, sexual and social beings. Gessen charts their paths not only against the machinations of the regime that would seek to crush them all (censorship, intimidation, violence) but also against the war it waged on understanding itself, ensuring the unobstructed emergence of the old Soviet order in the form of today&#8217;s terrifying and seemingly unstoppable mafia state. The Future is History is a powerful and urgent cautionary tale by contemporary Russia&#8217;s most fearless inquisitor.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-is-history-how-totalitarianism-reclaimed-russia-masha-gessen-abridged/">The Future is History : How Totalitarianism Reclaimed Russia &#8211; Masha Gessen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Prime Ministers We Never Had : Success and Failure from Butler to Corbyn &#8211; Steve Richards (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-prime-ministers-we-never-had-success-and-failure-from-butler-to-corbyn-steve-richards-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-prime-ministers-we-never-had-success-and-failure-from-butler-to-corbyn-steve-richards-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BOOK OF THE YEAR, The Times, Guardian and Prospect Was Harold Wilson a bigger figure than Denis Healey? Was John Major more &#8216;prime ministerial&#8217; than Michael Heseltine? Would David Miliband have become prime minister if it were not for his brother Ed? Would Ed have become prime minister if it were not for David? How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-prime-ministers-we-never-had-success-and-failure-from-butler-to-corbyn-steve-richards-abridged/">The Prime Ministers We Never Had : Success and Failure from Butler to Corbyn &#8211; Steve Richards (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BOOK OF THE YEAR, The Times, Guardian and Prospect    </p>
<p>                    Was Harold Wilson a bigger figure than Denis Healey? Was John Major more &#8216;prime ministerial&#8217; than Michael Heseltine? Would David Miliband have become prime minister if it were not for his brother Ed? Would Ed have become prime minister if it were not for David? How close did Jeremy Corbyn come to being prime minister?     </p>
<p>                    In this piercing and original study, journalist and commentator Steve Richards looks at eleven prime ministers we never had, examining what made each of these illustrious figures unique and why they failed to make the final leap to the very top. Combining astute insights into the demands of leadership with compelling historical analysis, this fascinating exploration of failure and success sheds new light on some of the most compelling characters in British public life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-prime-ministers-we-never-had-success-and-failure-from-butler-to-corbyn-steve-richards-abridged/">The Prime Ministers We Never Had : Success and Failure from Butler to Corbyn &#8211; Steve Richards (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Propaganda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semiotics / Semiology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to the usual image of the press as cantankerous, obstinate, and ubiquitous in its search for truth, Edward Herman and Noam Chomsky depict how an underlying elite consensus largely structures all facets of the news. They skilfully dissect the way in which the marketplace and the economics of publishing significantly shape the news. They [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/">Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to the usual image of the press as cantankerous, obstinate, and ubiquitous in its search for truth, Edward Herman and Noam Chomsky depict how an underlying elite consensus largely structures all facets of the news. They skilfully dissect the way in which the marketplace and the economics of publishing significantly shape the news. They reveal how issues are framed and topics chosen, and contrast the double standards underlying accounts of free elections, a free press, and governmental repression between Nicaragua and El Salvador; between the Russian invasion of Afghanistan and the American invasion of Vietnam; between the genocide in Cambodia under a pro-American government and genocide under Pol Pot. What emerges from this groundbreaking work is an account of just how propagandistic our mass media are, and how we can learn to read them and see their function in a radically new way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/">Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Yes We (Still) Can : Politics in the age of Obama, Twitter and Trump &#8211; Dan Pfeiffer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/yes-we-still-can-politics-in-the-age-of-obama-twitter-and-trump-dan-pfeiffer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/yes-we-still-can-politics-in-the-age-of-obama-twitter-and-trump-dan-pfeiffer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Barack Obama was the breath of fresh air the Democrats didn&#8217;t even realise they needed. Running on a platform of hope, change and progress, he won his first term with a decisive landslide, completely rewriting the rules of politics. So how did we go from Obama to Trump &#8211; and how can the Democrats turn [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/yes-we-still-can-politics-in-the-age-of-obama-twitter-and-trump-dan-pfeiffer-abridged/">Yes We (Still) Can : Politics in the age of Obama, Twitter and Trump &#8211; Dan Pfeiffer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Barack Obama was the breath of fresh air the Democrats didn&#8217;t even realise they needed. Running on a platform of hope, change and progress, he won his first term with a decisive landslide, completely rewriting the rules of politics.    </p>
<p>                    So how did we go from Obama to Trump &#8211; and how can the Democrats turn the tide? Once his communications director, and now co-host of Pod Save America, Dan Pfeiffer was at Obama&#8217;s side through two presidential elections and six years in the White House. Offering up surreal stories from behind the scenes, Pfeiffer explains how Obama navigated the forces that propelled Trump to power, and metes out critical wisdom on how the Democrats can reverse the country&#8217;s fate.    </p>
<p>                    A funny, thoughtful and humble account of Pfeiffer&#8217;s time on the front line of politics, Yes We (Still) Can is not just a memoir but an action plan for those who still dare to hope for change &#8211; and for the end of the Trump era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/yes-we-still-can-politics-in-the-age-of-obama-twitter-and-trump-dan-pfeiffer-abridged/">Yes We (Still) Can : Politics in the age of Obama, Twitter and Trump &#8211; Dan Pfeiffer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Be Right : &#8230; in a world gone wrong &#8211; James O&#8217;Brien (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Speaking Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The voice of reason in a world that won&#8217;t shut up. The Sunday Times Bestseller Winner of the Parliamentary Book Awards Every day, James O&#8217;Brien listens to people blaming hard-working immigrants for stealing their jobs while scrounging benefits, and pointing their fingers at the EU and feminists for destroying Britain. But what makes James&#8217;s daily [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/">How To Be Right : &#8230; in a world gone wrong &#8211; James O&#8217;Brien (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The voice of reason in a world that won&#8217;t shut up.    </p>
<p>                    The Sunday Times Bestseller<br />
                    Winner of the Parliamentary Book Awards    </p>
<p>                    Every day, James O&#8217;Brien listens to people blaming hard-working immigrants for stealing their jobs while scrounging benefits, and pointing their fingers at the EU and feminists for destroying Britain. But what makes James&#8217;s daily LBC show such essential listening &#8211; and has made James a standout social media star &#8211; is the incisive way he punctures their assumptions and dismantles their arguments live on air, every single morning.    </p>
<p>                    In the bestselling How To Be Right, James provides a hilarious and invigorating guide to talking to people with unchallenged opinions. With chapters on every lightning-rod issue, James shows how people have been fooled into thinking the way they do, and in each case outlines the key questions to ask to reveal fallacies, inconsistencies and double standards.    </p>
<p>                    If you ever get cornered by ardent Brexiteers, Daily Mail disciples or corporate cronies, this book is your conversation survival guide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/">How To Be Right : &#8230; in a world gone wrong &#8211; James O&#8217;Brien (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s going to happen to my job? That&#8217;s what an increasing number of anxious Americans are asking themselves. The US workforce, which has been one of the most productive and wealthiest in the world, is undergoing an alarming transformation. Increasing numbers of workers find themselves on shaky ground, turned into freelancers, temps and contractors. Even [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/">Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s going to happen to my job?     </p>
<p>                    That&#8217;s what an increasing number of anxious Americans are asking themselves.     </p>
<p>                    The US workforce, which has been one of the most productive and wealthiest in the world, is undergoing an alarming transformation. Increasing numbers of workers find themselves on shaky ground, turned into freelancers, temps and contractors. Even many full-time and professional jobs are experiencing this precarious shift. Within a decade, a near-majority of the 145 million employed Americans will be impacted. Add to that the steamroller of automation, robots and artificial intelligence already replacing millions of workers and projected to obsolesce millions more, and the jobs picture starts looking grim.     </p>
<p>                    Now a weird yet historic mash-up of Silicon Valley technology and Wall Street greed is thrusting upon us the latest economic fraud: the so-called sharing economy, with companies like Uber, Airbnb and TaskRabbit allegedly liberating workers to become independent and their own CEOs, hiring themselves out for ever-smaller jobs and wages while the companies profit.     </p>
<p>                    But this share the crumbs economy is just the tip of a looming iceberg that the middle class is drifting toward. Raw Deal: How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers, by veteran journalist Steven Hill, is an exposé that challenges conventional thinking, and the hype celebrating this new economy, by showing why the vision of the techno sapien leaders and their Ayn Rand libertarianism is a dead end.     </p>
<p>                    In Raw Deal, Steven Hill proposes pragmatic policy solutions to transform the US economy and its safety net and social contract, launching a new kind of deal to restore power back into the hands of American workers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raw-deal-how-the-uber-economy-and-runaway-capitalism-are-screwing-american-workers-steven-hill-abridged/">Raw Deal : How the Uber Economy and Runaway Capitalism Are Screwing American Workers &#8211; Steven Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Strangers In Their Own Land : Anger and Mourning on the American Right &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/strangers-in-their-own-land-anger-and-mourning-on-the-american-right-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/strangers-in-their-own-land-anger-and-mourning-on-the-american-right-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Strangers in Their Own Land, the renowned sociologist Arlie Hochschild embarks on a thought-provoking journey from her liberal hometown of Berkeley, California, deep into Louisiana bayou country &#8211; a stronghold of the conservative right. As she gets to know people who strongly oppose many of the ideas she famously champions, Hochschild nevertheless finds common [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strangers-in-their-own-land-anger-and-mourning-on-the-american-right-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">Strangers In Their Own Land : Anger and Mourning on the American Right &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Strangers in Their Own Land, the renowned sociologist Arlie Hochschild embarks on a thought-provoking journey from her liberal hometown of Berkeley, California, deep into Louisiana bayou country &#8211; a stronghold of the conservative right. As she gets to know people who strongly oppose many of the ideas she famously champions, Hochschild nevertheless finds common ground and quickly warms to the people she meets, people whose concerns are actually ones that all Americans share: the desire for community, the embrace of family, and hopes for their children.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/strangers-in-their-own-land-anger-and-mourning-on-the-american-right-arlie-russell-hochschild-abridged/">Strangers In Their Own Land : Anger and Mourning on the American Right &#8211; Arlie Russell Hochschild (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lincoln On Leadership &#8211; Donald T. Phillips (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lincoln-on-leadership-donald-t-phillips-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lincoln-on-leadership-donald-t-phillips-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lincoln on Leadership is the first book to examine Abraham Lincoln&#8217;s diverse leadership abilities and how they can be applied to today&#8217;s complex world. You think you have it rough? Only ten days before Abraham Lincoln took the oath of office in 1861, the Confederate States of America seceded from the Union, taking all Federal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lincoln-on-leadership-donald-t-phillips-abridged/">Lincoln On Leadership &#8211; Donald T. Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lincoln on Leadership is the first book to examine Abraham Lincoln&#8217;s diverse leadership abilities and how they can be applied to today&#8217;s complex world.    </p>
<p>                    You think you have it rough?     </p>
<p>                    Only ten days before Abraham Lincoln took the oath of office in 1861, the Confederate States of America seceded from the Union, taking all Federal agencies, forts, and arenas within their territory. To make matters worse, Lincoln, who was elected by a minority of the popular vote, was thought of by his own advisors as nothing more than a gawky second-rate country lawyer with no leadership experience.     </p>
<p>                    What Lincoln did to become our most honored and revered president is history; now his wisdom and leadership philosophy can help you run your business. In Lincoln on Leadership you&#8217;ll discover why you should:<br />
                    Seize the initiative and never relinquish it.Wage only one war at a time.Avoid issuing order and instead request, imply, or make suggestions.Once in a while, let things slip, unbeknownst-like&#8230; and much much more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lincoln-on-leadership-donald-t-phillips-abridged/">Lincoln On Leadership &#8211; Donald T. Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Common Sense &#8211; Thomas Paine (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Among the most influential authors and reformers of his age, Thomas Paine (1737-1809) was born in England but went on to play an important role in both the American and French Revolutions. In 1774, he emigrated to America where, for a time, he helped to edit the Pennsylvania Magazine. On January 10, 1776, he published [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/">Common Sense &#8211; Thomas Paine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Among the most influential authors and reformers of his age, Thomas Paine (1737-1809) was born in England but went on to play an important role in both the American and French Revolutions. In 1774, he emigrated to America where, for a time, he helped to edit the Pennsylvania Magazine. On January 10, 1776, he published his pamphlet Common Sense,  a persuasive argument for the colonies&#8217; political and economic separation from Britain.<br />
                    Common Sense cites the evils of monarchy, accuses the British government of inflicting economic and social injustices upon the colonies, and points to the absurdity of an island attempting to rule a continent. Credited by George Washington as having changed the minds of many of his countrymen, the document sold over 500,000 copies within a few months.<br />
                    Today, Common Sense remains a landmark document in the struggle for freedom, distinguished not only by Paine&#8217;s ideas but also by its clear and passionate presentation. Designed to ignite public opinion against autocratic rule, the pamphlet offered a careful balance between imagination and judgment, and appropriate language and expression to fit the subject. It immediately found a receptive audience, heartened Washington&#8217;s despondent army, and foreshadowed much of the phrasing and substance of the Declaration of Independence.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/">Common Sense &#8211; Thomas Paine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the 2018 Waterstones Book of the Year Winner at the 2018 Parliamentary Book Awards Longlisted for the Orwell Prize, 2019 ____________ &#8220;A really good book&#8230; Well-structured and well-written.&#8221; Observer &#8220;Well written and incisive.&#8221; The Times &#8220;Vital and compelling.&#8221; New Statesman In an era when politicians are responsible for the Brexit logjam and embroiled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/">Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the 2018 Waterstones Book of the Year<br />
                    Winner at the 2018 Parliamentary Book Awards<br />
                    Longlisted for the Orwell Prize, 2019<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A really good book&#8230;  Well-structured and well-written.&#8221; Observer<br />
                    &#8220;Well written and incisive.&#8221; The Times<br />
                    &#8220;Vital and compelling.&#8221; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    In an era when politicians are responsible for the Brexit logjam and embroiled in sexual-harassment and expenses scandals, it&#8217;s no wonder we&#8217;ve lost our faith in government. Every year, they introduce new legislation that doesn&#8217;t do what it sets out to achieve &#8211; often with terrible financial and human costs. But, with some notable exceptions, they are decent, hard-working people, doing a hugely difficult and demanding job. In this searching examination of our political class, award-winning journalist Isabel Hardman investigates the strange and demanding world of Westminster, and asks why we end up with representatives we no longer trust &#8211; and how might faith be restored.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/">Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019 Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump. The 2016 election was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019    </p>
<p>                    Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump.    </p>
<p>                    The 2016 election was a watershed for the United States. But, as Tim Alberta explains in American Carnage, to understand Trump&#8217;s victory is to view him not as the creator of this era of polarization and bruising partisanship, but rather as its most manifest consequence.    </p>
<p>                    American Carnage is the story of a president&#8217;s rise based on a country&#8217;s evolution and a party&#8217;s collapse. As George W. Bush left office with record-low approval ratings and Barack Obama led a Democratic takeover of Washington, Republicans faced a moment of reckoning: They had no vision, no generation of new leaders, and no energy in the party&#8217;s base. Yet Obama&#8217;s forceful pursuit of his progressive agenda, coupled with the nation&#8217;s rapidly changing cultural and demographic landscape, lit a fire under the right, returning Republicans to power and inviting a bloody struggle for the party&#8217;s identity in the post-Bush era. The factions that emerged-one led by absolutists like Jim Jordan and Ted Cruz, the other led by pragmatists like John Boehner and Mitch McConnell-engaged in a series of devastating internecine clashes and attempted coups for control. With the GOP&#8217;s internal fissures rendering it legislatively impotent, and that impotence fueling a growing resentment toward the political class and its institutions, the stage was set for an outsider to crash the party. When Trump descended a gilded escalator to announce his run in the summer of 2015, the candidate had met the moment.    </p>
<p>                    Only by viewing Trump as the culmination of a decade-long civil war inside the Republican Party-and of the parallel sense of cultural, socioeconomic, and technological disruption during that period-can we appreciate how he won the White House and consider the fundamental questions at the center of America&#8217;s current turmoil. How did a party obsessed with the national debt vote for trillion-dollar deficits and record-setting spending increases? How did the party of compassionate conservatism become the party of Muslim bans and walls? How did the party of family values elect a thrice-divorced philanderer? And, most important, how long can such a party survive?    </p>
<p>                     Loaded with exclusive reporting and based off hundreds of interviews-including with key players such as President Trump, Paul Ryan, Ted Cruz, John Boehner, Mitch McConnell, Jim DeMint, and Reince Priebus, and many others-American Carnage takes us behind the scenes of this tumultuous period as we&#8217;ve never seen it before and establishes Tim Alberta as the premier chronicler of this political era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Empire of Cotton : A New History of Global Capitalism &#8211; Sven Beckert (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colonialism & Imperialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Textile Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE 2015 BANCROFT PRIZE WINNER OF THE 2015 PHILIP TAFT PRIZE FINALIST FOR THE 2015 PULITZER PRIZE FOR HISTORY SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2015 CUNDHILL PRIZE IN HISTORICAL LITERATURE Economist BOOKS OF THE YEAR 2015 &#8216;Knowledgeable and stunning&#8217; Orhan Pamuk &#8216;A masterpiece of the historian&#8217;s craft&#8217; The Nation For about 900 years, from 1000 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/">Empire of Cotton : A New History of Global Capitalism &#8211; Sven Beckert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE 2015 BANCROFT PRIZE<br />
                    WINNER OF THE 2015 PHILIP TAFT PRIZE<br />
                    FINALIST FOR THE 2015 PULITZER PRIZE FOR HISTORY<br />
                    SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2015 CUNDHILL PRIZE IN HISTORICAL LITERATURE<br />
                    Economist BOOKS OF THE YEAR 2015    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Knowledgeable and stunning&#8217; Orhan Pamuk     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A masterpiece of the historian&#8217;s craft&#8217; The Nation    </p>
<p>                    For about 900 years, from 1000 to 1900, cotton was the world&#8217;s most important manufacturing industry. It remains a vast business &#8211; if all the cotton bales produced in 2013 had been stacked on top of each other they would have made a somewhat unstable tower 40,000 miles high.      </p>
<p>                    Sven Beckert&#8217;s superb new book is a history of the overwhelming role played by cotton in dictating the shape of our world. It is both a gripping narrative and a brilliant case history of how the world works.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/">Empire of Cotton : A New History of Global Capitalism &#8211; Sven Beckert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations & Safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Burnham has real intellectual courage, and writes about real issues.&#8217; &#8211; George Orwell Burnham&#8217;s claim was that capitalism was dead, but that it was being replaced not by socialism, but a new economic system he called &#8220;managerialism&#8221;; rule by managers. Written in 1941, this is the book that theorised how the world was moving into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/">The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Burnham has real intellectual courage, and writes about real issues.&#8217; &#8211; George Orwell    </p>
<p>                    Burnham&#8217;s claim was that capitalism was dead, but that it was being replaced not by socialism, but a new economic system he called &#8220;managerialism&#8221;; rule by managers.    </p>
<p>                    Written in 1941, this is the book that theorised how the world was moving into the hands of the &#8216;managers&#8217;. Burnham explains how Capitalism had virtually lost its control, and would be displaced not by labour, nor by socialism, but by the rule of administartors in business and in government.    </p>
<p>                    This revolution, he posited, is as broad as the world and as comprehensive as human society, asking &#8220;Why is &#8216;totalitarianism&#8217; not the issue?&#8221; &#8220;Can civilization be destroyed?&#8221; And &#8220;Why is the New Deal something bigger than Roosevelt can handle?&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    In a volume extraordinary for its dispassionate handling of those and other fundamental questions, James Burnham explores fully the implications of the managerial revolution.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/">The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Autobiography of Malcolm X &#8211; Alex Haley, Malcolm X, Introduction by Paul Gilroy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-autobiography-of-malcolm-x-alex-haley-malcolm-x-introduction-by-paul-gilroy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-autobiography-of-malcolm-x-alex-haley-malcolm-x-introduction-by-paul-gilroy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Malcolm X&#8217;s The Autobiography of Malcolm X was written in collaboration with Alex Haley, author of Roots, and includes an introduction by Paul Gilroy, author of The Black Atlantic, in Penguin Modern Classics. From hustling, drug addiction and armed violence in America&#8217;s black ghettos Malcolm X turned, in a dramatic prison conversion, to the puritanical [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-autobiography-of-malcolm-x-alex-haley-malcolm-x-introduction-by-paul-gilroy-abridged/">The Autobiography of Malcolm X &#8211; Alex Haley, Malcolm X, Introduction by Paul Gilroy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Malcolm X&#8217;s The Autobiography of Malcolm X was written in collaboration with Alex Haley, author of Roots, and includes an introduction by Paul Gilroy, author of The Black Atlantic, in Penguin Modern Classics.    </p>
<p>                    From hustling, drug addiction and armed violence in America&#8217;s black ghettos Malcolm X turned, in a dramatic prison conversion, to the puritanical fervour of the Black Muslims. As their spokesman he became identified in the white press as a terrifying teacher of race hatred; but to his direct audience, the oppressed American blacks, he brought hope and self-respect. This autobiography (written with Alex Haley) reveals his quick-witted integrity, usually obscured by batteries of frenzied headlines, and the fierce idealism which led him to reject both liberal hypocrisies and black racialism.    </p>
<p>                    Vilified by his critics as an anti-white demagogue, Malcolm X gave a voice to unheard African-Americans, bringing them pride, hope and fearlessness, and remains an inspirational and controversial figure.    </p>
<p>                    Malcolm X (1925-65), born Malcolm Little in Omaha, and also known as El-Hajj Malik El-Shabazz, lost both his parents at a young age. Leaving school early, he soon became part of Harlem&#8217;s underworld, and in 1946 he was sentenced to ten years&#8217; imprisonment. It was in prison that Malcolm X converted to Islam. Paroled in 1952, he became an outspoken defender of Muslim doctrines, formed the Organization of Afro-American Unity in 1963, and had received considerable publicity by the time of his assassination in 1965.    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed The Autobiography of Malcolm X, you might like Nelson Mandela&#8217;s No Easy Walk to Freedom, also available in Penguin Modern Classics.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This extraordinary autobiography is a brilliant, painful, important book&#8217;<br />
                    The New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-autobiography-of-malcolm-x-alex-haley-malcolm-x-introduction-by-paul-gilroy-abridged/">The Autobiography of Malcolm X &#8211; Alex Haley, Malcolm X, Introduction by Paul Gilroy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Leadership Jazz &#8211; Revised Edition : The Essential Elements of a Great Leader &#8211; Max De Pree (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/leadership-jazz-revised-edition-the-essential-elements-of-a-great-leader-max-de-pree-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/leadership-jazz-revised-edition-the-essential-elements-of-a-great-leader-max-de-pree-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since it was first published to wide acclaim in 1992, the bestselling Leadership Jazz has firmly placed itself among the great business classics. Former President Bill Clinton called it &#8220;astonishing,&#8221; and the late Peter Drucker advised, &#8220;Read this slowly. This book is wisdom in action.&#8221; Now updated for first time in well over a decade, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leadership-jazz-revised-edition-the-essential-elements-of-a-great-leader-max-de-pree-abridged/">Leadership Jazz &#8211; Revised Edition : The Essential Elements of a Great Leader &#8211; Max De Pree (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since it was first published to wide acclaim in 1992, the bestselling Leadership Jazz has firmly placed itself among the great business classics. Former President Bill Clinton called it &#8220;astonishing,&#8221; and the late Peter Drucker advised, &#8220;Read this slowly. This book is wisdom in action.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Now updated for first time in well over a decade, this powerful book reveals why today, more than ever, leadership is more an art than a science. Today&#8217;s best leaders, De Pree says, are attuned to the needs and ideas of their followers, and even step aside at times to be followers themselves. Filled with insightful stories from De Pree&#8217;s experience as the chairman of Herman Miller and from people he&#8217;s met along the way, Leadership Jazz reveals how to:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Hold people accountable and give them space to reach their potential<br />
                    &#8211; See the needs of employees and those of the company as the same<br />
                    &#8211; Inspire change and innovation<br />
                    &#8211; Work effectively with creative people     </p>
<p>                    Complete with an extensive new introduction from De Pree on why his philosophy is more relevant now than ever before, Leadership Jazz gives you an entirely new way to look at the difficult job of leader.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/leadership-jazz-revised-edition-the-essential-elements-of-a-great-leader-max-de-pree-abridged/">Leadership Jazz &#8211; Revised Edition : The Essential Elements of a Great Leader &#8211; Max De Pree (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
