<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900 Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/modern-history-to-20th-century-c-1700-to-c-1900/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/modern-history-to-20th-century-c-1700-to-c-1900/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900 Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/modern-history-to-20th-century-c-1700-to-c-1900/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>American Dialogue : The Founders and Us &#8211; Joseph J. Ellis</title>
		<link>/american-dialogue-the-founders-and-us-joseph-j-ellis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rebellions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uprisings]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-dialogue-the-founders-and-us-joseph-j-ellis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The award-winning author of Founding Brothers and The Quartet now gives us a deeply insightful examination of the relevance of the views of George Washington, Thomas Jefferson, James Madison, and John Adams to some of the most divisive issues in America today. The story of history is a ceaseless conversation between past and present, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-dialogue-the-founders-and-us-joseph-j-ellis/">American Dialogue : The Founders and Us &#8211; Joseph J. Ellis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The award-winning author of Founding Brothers and The Quartet now gives us a deeply insightful examination of the relevance of the views of George Washington, Thomas Jefferson, James Madison, and John Adams to some of the most divisive issues in America today.     </p>
<p>                    The story of history is a ceaseless conversation between past and present, and in American Dialogue Joseph J. Ellis focuses the conversation on the often-asked question What would the Founding Fathers think? He examines four of our most seminal historical figures through the prism of particular topics, using the perspective of the present to shed light on their views and, in turn, to make clear how their now centuries-old ideas illuminate the disturbing impasse of today&#8217;s political conflicts. He discusses Jefferson and the issue of racism, Adams and the specter of economic inequality, Washington and American imperialism, Madison and the doctrine of original intent. Through these juxtapositions&#8211;and in his hallmark dramatic and compelling narrative voice&#8211;Ellis illuminates the obstacles and pitfalls paralyzing contemporary discussions of these fundamentally important issues.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-dialogue-the-founders-and-us-joseph-j-ellis/">American Dialogue : The Founders and Us &#8211; Joseph J. Ellis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Leap in the Dark : The Struggle to Create the American Republic &#8211; John Ferling</title>
		<link>/a-leap-in-the-dark-the-struggle-to-create-the-american-republic-john-ferling/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-leap-in-the-dark-the-struggle-to-create-the-american-republic-john-ferling/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It was an age of fascinating leaders and difficult choices, of grand ideas eloquently expressed and of epic conflicts bitterly fought. Now comes a brilliant portrait of the American Revolution, one that is compelling in its prose, fascinating in its details, and provocative in its fresh interpretations. John Ferling has shown himself to be an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-leap-in-the-dark-the-struggle-to-create-the-american-republic-john-ferling/">A Leap in the Dark : The Struggle to Create the American Republic &#8211; John Ferling</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It was an age of fascinating leaders and difficult choices, of grand ideas eloquently expressed and of epic conflicts bitterly fought. Now comes a brilliant portrait of the American Revolution, one that is compelling in its prose, fascinating in its details, and provocative in its fresh interpretations. John Ferling has shown himself to be an insightful  historian of our Revolution, and an unusually skillful  writer. A Leap in the Dark is his masterpiece,<br />
                    work that provokes, enlightens, and entertains in full measure.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-leap-in-the-dark-the-struggle-to-create-the-american-republic-john-ferling/">A Leap in the Dark : The Struggle to Create the American Republic &#8211; John Ferling</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Victoria: The Queen : An Intimate Biography of the Woman who Ruled an Empire &#8211; Julia Baird</title>
		<link>/victoria-the-queen-an-intimate-biography-of-the-woman-who-ruled-an-empire-julia-baird/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Royalty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/victoria-the-queen-an-intimate-biography-of-the-woman-who-ruled-an-empire-julia-baird/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY JANET MASLIN, THE NEW YORK TIMES &#8216;Victoria the Queen, Julia Baird&#8217;s exquisitely wrought and meticulously researched biography, brushes the dusty myth off this extraordinary monarch&#8217; The New York Times Book Review (Editor&#8217;s Choice). The true story for fans of the hit ITV drama series Victoria [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/victoria-the-queen-an-intimate-biography-of-the-woman-who-ruled-an-empire-julia-baird/">Victoria: The Queen : An Intimate Biography of the Woman who Ruled an Empire &#8211; Julia Baird</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY JANET MASLIN, THE NEW YORK TIMES</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Victoria the Queen, Julia Baird&#8217;s exquisitely wrought and meticulously researched biography, brushes the dusty myth off this extraordinary monarch&#8217; The New York Times Book Review (Editor&#8217;s Choice).</p>
<p>                    The true story for fans of the hit ITV drama series Victoria starring Jenna Coleman, this page-turning biography reveals the real woman behind the myth: a bold, glamorous, unbreakable queen. Drawing on previously unpublished papers, this stunning book is a story of love and heartbreak, of devotion and grief, of strength and resilience.</p>
<p>                    When Victoria was born, in 1819, the world was a very different place. Revolution would begin to threaten many of Europe&#8217;s monarchies in the coming decades. In Britain, a generation of royals had indulged their whims at the public&#8217;s expense, and republican sentiment was growing. The Industrial Revolution was transforming the landscape, and the British Empire was commanding ever larger parts of the globe. Born into a world where woman were often powerless, during a century roiling with change, Victoria went on to rule the most powerful country on earth with a decisive hand.</p>
<p>                    Fifth in line to the throne at the time of her birth, Victoria was an ordinary woman thrust into an extraordinary role. As a girl, she defied her mother&#8217;s meddling and an adviser&#8217;s bullying, forging an iron will of her own. As a teenage queen, she eagerly grasped the crown and relished the freedom it brought her. At twenty years old, she fell passionately in love with Prince Albert of Saxe-Coburg and Gotha, eventually giving birth to nine children. She loved sex and delighted in power. She was outspoken with her ministers, overstepping boundaries and asserting her opinions. After the death of her adored Albert, she began a controversial, intimate relationship with her servant John Brown. She survived eight assassination attempts over the course of her lifetime. And as science, technology, and democracy were dramatically reshaping the world, Victoria was a symbol of steadfastness and security-queen of a quarter of the world&#8217;s population at the height of the British Empire&#8217;s reach.</p>
<p>                    Drawing on sources that include revelations about Victoria&#8217;s relationship with John Brown, Julia Baird brings vividly to life the fascinating story of a woman who struggled with so many of the things we do today: balancing work and family, raising children, navigating marital strife, losing parents, combating anxiety and self-doubt, finding an identity, searching for meaning. This sweeping, page-turning biography gives us the real woman behind the myth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/victoria-the-queen-an-intimate-biography-of-the-woman-who-ruled-an-empire-julia-baird/">Victoria: The Queen : An Intimate Biography of the Woman who Ruled an Empire &#8211; Julia Baird</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond</title>
		<link>/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A riveting and illuminating tour of how nations deal with crises &#8211; which might hopefully help humanity as a whole deal with our present global crisis&#8217; YUVAL NOAH HARARI, author of SAPIENS ** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Author of the landmark international bestsellers Guns, Germs and Steel and Collapse, Jared Diamond has transformed our understanding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond/">Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A riveting and illuminating tour of how nations deal with crises &#8211; which might hopefully help humanity as a whole deal with our present global crisis&#8217; YUVAL NOAH HARARI, author of SAPIENS </p>
<p>                    ** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** </p>
<p>                    Author of the landmark international bestsellers Guns, Germs and Steel and Collapse, Jared Diamond has transformed our understanding of what makes civilizations rise and fall. Now, at a time when crises are erupting around the world, heexplores what makes certain nations resilient, and reveals the factors that influence how nations and individuals can respond to enormous challenges. </p>
<p>                    In a riveting journey into the recent past, he traces how six distinctive modern nations &#8211; Finland, Chile, Indonesia, Japan, Germany and Australia &#8211; have survived defining catastrophes, and identifies patterns in their recovery. Looking ahead, he investigates the risk that the United States and other countries, faced by grave threat, are set on a course towards catastrophe. </p>
<p>                    Adding a rich psychological dimension to the in-depth history, geography, biology and anthropology that underpin all of Diamond&#8217;s writing, Upheaval is epic in scope, but also his most personal book yet.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating &#8230; I finished the book even more optimistic about our ability to solve problems than I started&#8217; BILL GATES</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Jared Diamond does it again: another rich, original and fascinating chapter in the human saga &#8211; with vital lessons for our difficult times&#8217; STEVEN PINKER</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond/">Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Benjamin Franklin : An American Life &#8211; Walter Isaacson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/benjamin-franklin-an-american-life-walter-isaacson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dictionaries Of Biography (Who's Who)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/benjamin-franklin-an-american-life-walter-isaacson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>During his 84-year life Benjamin Franklin was America&#8217;s best scientist, inventor, publisher, business strategist, diplomat, and writer. He was also one of its most practical political thinkers. America&#8217;s first great publicist, he carefully crafted his own persona, portrayed it in public and polished it for posterity. In this riveting new biography Walter Isaacson provides readers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/benjamin-franklin-an-american-life-walter-isaacson-abridged/">Benjamin Franklin : An American Life &#8211; Walter Isaacson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>During his 84-year life Benjamin Franklin was America&#8217;s best scientist, inventor, publisher, business strategist, diplomat, and writer. He was also one of its most practical political thinkers. America&#8217;s first great publicist, he carefully crafted his own persona, portrayed it in public and polished it for posterity. In this riveting new biography Walter Isaacson provides readers with a full portrait of Franklin&#8217;s public and private life &#8211; his loyal but neglected wife, his bastard son with whom he broke over going to war with England, his endless replacement families and his many amorous, but probably unconsummated, liaisons. But this is not just a biography of Benjamin Franklin but rather a fascinating look at American and European political history at that time. Isaacson examines the run up to the Revolutionary War, the intimate relations between Britain, France and the colonies and the decisive events that led to America&#8217;s independence. Just as David McCullough brought life to the historic figure of John Adams, Isaacson portrays Franklin in the flesh, showing readers how this radical man helped define America&#8217;s national character and personality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/benjamin-franklin-an-american-life-walter-isaacson-abridged/">Benjamin Franklin : An American Life &#8211; Walter Isaacson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Napoleon&#8217;S Buttons : How 17 Molecules Changed History &#8211; Penny Le Couteur, Jay Burreson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum & Theoretical Chemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Napoleon&#8217;s Buttons is the fascinating account of seventeen groups of molecules that have greatly influenced the course of history. These molecules provided the impetus for early exploration, and made possible the voyages of discovery that ensued. The molecules resulted in grand feats of engineering and spurred advances in medicine and law; they determined what we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/">Napoleon&#8217;S Buttons : How 17 Molecules Changed History &#8211; Penny Le Couteur, Jay Burreson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Napoleon&#8217;s Buttons is the fascinating account of seventeen groups of molecules that have greatly influenced the course of history. These molecules provided the impetus for early exploration, and made possible the voyages of discovery that ensued. The molecules resulted in grand feats of engineering and spurred advances in medicine and law; they determined what we now eat, drink, and wear. A change as small as the position of an atom can lead to enormous alterations in the properties of a substance-which, in turn, can result in great historical shifts.     </p>
<p>                     With lively prose and an eye for colorful and unusual details, Le Couteur and Burreson offer a novel way to understand the shaping of civilization and the workings of our contemporary world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/">Napoleon&#8217;S Buttons : How 17 Molecules Changed History &#8211; Penny Le Couteur, Jay Burreson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A First-Rate Madness : Uncovering the Links Between Leadership and Mental Illness &#8211; Nassir Ghaemi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-first-rate-madness-uncovering-the-links-between-leadership-and-mental-illness-nassir-ghaemi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-first-rate-madness-uncovering-the-links-between-leadership-and-mental-illness-nassir-ghaemi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestseller is a myth-shattering exploration of the powerful connections between mental illness and leadership. Historians have long puzzled over the apparent mental instability of great and terrible leaders alike: Napoleon, Lincoln, Churchill, Hitler, and others. In A First-Rate Madness, Nassir Ghaemi, director of the Mood Disorders Programme at Tufts Medical Center, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-first-rate-madness-uncovering-the-links-between-leadership-and-mental-illness-nassir-ghaemi-abridged/">A First-Rate Madness : Uncovering the Links Between Leadership and Mental Illness &#8211; Nassir Ghaemi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestseller is a myth-shattering exploration of the powerful connections between mental illness and leadership.    </p>
<p>                    Historians have long puzzled over the apparent mental instability of great and terrible leaders alike: Napoleon, Lincoln, Churchill, Hitler, and others. In A First-Rate Madness, Nassir Ghaemi, director of the Mood Disorders Programme at Tufts Medical Center, offers and sets forth a controversial, compelling thesis: the very qualities that mark those with mood disorders also make for the best leaders in times of crisis.     </p>
<p>                    From the importance of Lincoln&#8217;s &#8220;depressive realism&#8221; to the lacklustre leadership of exceedingly sane men as Neville Chamberlain, A First-Rate Madness overturns many of our most cherished perceptions about greatness and the mind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-first-rate-madness-uncovering-the-links-between-leadership-and-mental-illness-nassir-ghaemi-abridged/">A First-Rate Madness : Uncovering the Links Between Leadership and Mental Illness &#8211; Nassir Ghaemi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Devil in the White City : Murder, Magic, and Madness at the Fair that Changed America &#8211; Erik Larson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The true tale of the 1893 World&#8217;s Fair in Chicago and the cunning serial killer who used the magic and majesty of the fair to lure his victims to their death. &#8220;Relentlessly fuses history and entertainment to give this nonfiction book the dramatic effect of a novel &#8230;. It doesn&#8217;t [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/">The Devil in the White City : Murder, Magic, and Madness at the Fair that Changed America &#8211; Erik Larson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The true tale of the 1893 World&#8217;s Fair in Chicago and the cunning serial killer who used the magic and majesty of the fair to lure his victims to their death.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Relentlessly fuses history and entertainment to give this nonfiction book the dramatic effect of a novel &#8230;. It doesn&#8217;t hurt that this truth is stranger than fiction.&#8221; &#8211;The New York Times     </p>
<p>                    Combining meticulous research with nail-biting storytelling, Erik Larson has crafted a narrative with all the wonder of newly discovered history and the thrills of the best fiction.    </p>
<p>                    Two men, each handsome and unusually adept at his chosen work, embodied an element of the great dynamic that characterized America&#8217;s rush toward the twentieth century. The architect was Daniel Hudson Burnham, the fair&#8217;s brilliant director of works and the builder of many of the country&#8217;s most important structures, including the Flatiron Building in New York and Union Station in Washington, D.C. The murderer was Henry H. Holmes, a young doctor who, in a malign parody of the White City, built his &#8220;World&#8217;s Fair Hotel&#8221; just west of the fairgrounds&#8211;a torture palace complete with dissection table, gas chamber, and 3,000-degree crematorium.     </p>
<p>                    Burnham overcame tremendous obstacles and tragedies as he organized the talents of Frederick Law Olmsted, Charles McKim, Louis Sullivan, and others to transform swampy Jackson Park into the White City, while Holmes used the attraction of the great fair and his own satanic charms to lure scores of young women to their deaths. What makes the story all the more chilling is that Holmes really lived, walking the grounds of that dream city by the lake.     </p>
<p>                    The Devil in the White City draws the reader into the enchantment of the Guilded Age, made all the more appealing by a supporting cast of real-life characters, including Buffalo Bill, Theodore Dreiser, Susan B. Anthony, Thomas Edison, Archduke Francis Ferdinand, and others. Erik Larson&#8217;s gifts as a storyteller are magnificently displayed in this rich narrative of the master builder, the killer, and the great fair that obsessed them both.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/">The Devil in the White City : Murder, Magic, and Madness at the Fair that Changed America &#8211; Erik Larson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Biography of Loneliness : The History of an Emotion &#8211; Fay Bound Alberti (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Language]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite 21st-century fears of an &#8216;epidemic&#8217; of loneliness, its history has been sorely neglected. A Biography of Loneliness offers a radically new interpretation of loneliness as an emotional language and experience. Using letters and diaries, philosophical tracts, political discussions, and medical literature from the eighteenth century to the present, historian of the emotions Fay Bound [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/">A Biography of Loneliness : The History of an Emotion &#8211; Fay Bound Alberti (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Despite 21st-century fears of an &#8216;epidemic&#8217; of loneliness, its history has been sorely neglected. A Biography of Loneliness offers a radically new interpretation of loneliness as an emotional language and experience. Using letters and diaries, philosophical tracts, political discussions, and medical literature from the eighteenth century to the present, historian of the emotions Fay Bound Alberti argues that loneliness is not an ahistorical, universal<br />
                    phenomenon. It is, in fact, a modern emotion: before 1800, its language did not exist. And where loneliness is identified, it is not always bad, but a complex emotional state that differs according to class, gender, ethnicity and experience.    </p>
<p>                    Looking at informative case studies such as Sylvia Plath, Queen Victoria, and Virginia Woolf, A Biography of Loneliness charts the emergence of loneliness as a modern and embodied emotional state.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-biography-of-loneliness-the-history-of-an-emotion-fay-bound-alberti-abridged/">A Biography of Loneliness : The History of an Emotion &#8211; Fay Bound Alberti (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An absorbing and original narrative history of American capitalism NAMED A BEST BOOK OF 2017 BY THE ECONOMIST From the days of the Mayflower and the Virginia Company, America has been a place for people to dream, invent, build, tinker, and bet the farm in pursuit of a better life. Americana takes us on a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/">Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An absorbing and original narrative history of American capitalism    </p>
<p>                    NAMED A BEST BOOK OF 2017 BY THE ECONOMIST    </p>
<p>                    From the days of the Mayflower and the Virginia Company, America has been a place for people to dream, invent, build, tinker, and bet the farm in pursuit of a better life. Americana takes us on a four-hundred-year journey of this spirit of innovation and ambition through a series of Next Big Things &#8212; the inventions, techniques, and industries that drove American history forward: from the telegraph, the railroad, guns, radio, and banking to flight, suburbia, and sneakers, culminating with the Internet and mobile technology at the turn of the twenty-first century. The result is a thrilling alternative history of modern America that reframes events, trends, and people we thought we knew through the prism of the value that, for better or for worse, this nation holds dearest: capitalism.     </p>
<p>                    In a winning, accessible style, Bhu Srinivasan boldly takes on four centuries of American enterprise, revealing the unexpected connections that link them. We learn how Andrew Carnegie&#8217;s early job as a telegraph messenger boy paved the way for his leadership of the steel empire that would make him one of the nation&#8217;s richest men; how the gunmaker Remington reinvented itself in the postwar years to sell typewriters; how the inner workings of the Mafia mirrored the trend of consolidation and regulation in more traditional business; and how a 1950s infrastructure bill triggered a series of events that produced one of America&#8217;s most enduring brands: KFC. Reliving the heady early days of Silicon Valley, we are reminded that the start-up is an idea as old as America itself.    </p>
<p>                    Entertaining, eye-opening, and sweeping in its reach, Americana is an exhilarating new work of narrative history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/">Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Anarchy : The Relentless Rise of the East India Company &#8211; William Dalrymple (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-anarchy-the-relentless-rise-of-the-east-india-company-william-dalrymple-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[British & Irish History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colonialism & Imperialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Naval Forces & Warfare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-anarchy-the-relentless-rise-of-the-east-india-company-william-dalrymple-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP 5 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER ONE OF BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S BEST BOOKS OF 2019 THE TIMES HISTORY BOOK OF THE YEAR FINALIST FOR THE CUNDILL HISTORY PRIZE 2020 LONGLISTED FOR THE BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION 2019 A FINANCIAL TIMES, OBSERVER, DAILY TELEGRAPH, WALL STREET JOURNAL AND TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8216;Dalrymple is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-anarchy-the-relentless-rise-of-the-east-india-company-william-dalrymple-abridged/">The Anarchy : The Relentless Rise of the East India Company &#8211; William Dalrymple (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP 5 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    ONE OF BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S BEST BOOKS OF 2019<br />
                    THE TIMES HISTORY BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    FINALIST FOR THE CUNDILL HISTORY PRIZE 2020<br />
                    LONGLISTED FOR THE BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION 2019<br />
                    A FINANCIAL TIMES, OBSERVER, DAILY TELEGRAPH, WALL STREET JOURNAL AND TIMES BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Dalrymple is a superb historian with a visceral understanding of India &#8230; A book of beauty&#8217; &#8211;  Gerard DeGroot, The Times    </p>
<p>                    In August 1765 the East India Company defeated the young Mughal emperor and forced him to establish a new administration in his richest provinces. Run by English merchants who collected taxes using a ruthless private army, this new regime saw the East India Company transform itself from an international trading corporation into something much more unusual: an aggressive colonial power in the guise of a multinational business.    </p>
<p>                      William Dalrymple tells the remarkable story of the East India Company as it has never been told before, unfolding a timely cautionary tale of the first global corporate power.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-anarchy-the-relentless-rise-of-the-east-india-company-william-dalrymple-abridged/">The Anarchy : The Relentless Rise of the East India Company &#8211; William Dalrymple (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team of Rivals : The Political Genius of Abraham Lincoln &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/team-of-rivals-the-political-genius-of-abraham-lincoln-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/team-of-rivals-the-political-genius-of-abraham-lincoln-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling and prize-winning study of one of the most legendary American Presidents in history, Team of Rivals by Doris Kearns Goodwin is the book that inspired Barack Obama in his presidency. When Barack Obama was asked which book he could not live without in the White House, his answer was instant: Team of Rivals. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/team-of-rivals-the-political-genius-of-abraham-lincoln-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/">Team of Rivals : The Political Genius of Abraham Lincoln &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling and prize-winning study of one of the most legendary American Presidents in history, Team of Rivals by Doris Kearns Goodwin is the book that inspired Barack Obama in his presidency.    </p>
<p>                    When Barack Obama was asked which book he could not live without in the White House, his answer was instant: Team of Rivals. This monumental and brilliant work has given Obama the model for his presidency, showing how Abraham Lincoln saved America by appointing his fiercest rival to key cabinet positions. As well as a thrilling piece of narrative history, it&#8217;s an inspiring study of one of the greatest leaders the world has ever seen.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A wonderful book . . . a remarkable study in leadership&#8217; Barack Obama    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A portrait of Lincoln as a virtuosic politician and managerial genius&#8217; The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I have not enjoyed a history book as much for years&#8217; Robert Harris    </p>
<p>                    Doris Kearns Goodwin is the doyenne of US presidential historians, and one of the most acclaimed non-fiction authors in the world. Her works include Lyndon Johnson and the American Dream, The Fitzgeralds and the Kennedys: An American Saga, and No Ordinary Time: Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt, for which she won the Pulitzer Prize for History in 1995.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/team-of-rivals-the-political-genius-of-abraham-lincoln-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/">Team of Rivals : The Political Genius of Abraham Lincoln &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Black Jacobins : Toussaint L&#8217;Ouverture and the San Domingo Revolution &#8211; C.L.R. James (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-black-jacobins-toussaint-louverture-and-the-san-domingo-revolution-c-l-r-james-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-black-jacobins-toussaint-louverture-and-the-san-domingo-revolution-c-l-r-james-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A classic and impassioned account of the first revolution in the Third World. This powerful, intensely dramatic book is the definitive account of the Haitian Revolution of 1794-1803, a revolution that began in the wake of the Bastille but became the model for the Third World liberation movements from Africa to Cuba. It is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-black-jacobins-toussaint-louverture-and-the-san-domingo-revolution-c-l-r-james-abridged/">The Black Jacobins : Toussaint L&#8217;Ouverture and the San Domingo Revolution &#8211; C.L.R. James (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A classic and impassioned account of the first revolution in the Third World.     </p>
<p>                    This powerful, intensely dramatic book is the definitive account of the Haitian Revolution of 1794-1803, a revolution that began in the wake of the Bastille but became the model for the Third World liberation movements from Africa to Cuba. It is the story of the French colony of San Domingo, a place where the brutality of master toward slave was commonplace and ingeniously refined. And it is the story of a barely literate slave named Toussaint L&#8217;Ouverture, who led the black people of San Domingo in a successful struggle against successive invasions by overwhelming French, Spanish, and English forces and in the process helped form the first independent nation in the Caribbean.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-black-jacobins-toussaint-louverture-and-the-san-domingo-revolution-c-l-r-james-abridged/">The Black Jacobins : Toussaint L&#8217;Ouverture and the San Domingo Revolution &#8211; C.L.R. James (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The First Conspiracy : The Secret Plot to Kill George Washington &#8211; Brad Meltzer, Josh Mensch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-first-conspiracy-the-secret-plot-to-kill-george-washington-brad-meltzer-josh-mensch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-first-conspiracy-the-secret-plot-to-kill-george-washington-brad-meltzer-josh-mensch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Taking place during the most critical period of our nation&#8217;s birth, The First Conspiracy tells a remarkable and previously untold piece of American history that not only reveals George Washington&#8217;s character, but also illuminates the origins of America&#8217;s counterintelligence movement that led to the modern day CIA. In 1776, an elite group of soldiers were [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-first-conspiracy-the-secret-plot-to-kill-george-washington-brad-meltzer-josh-mensch-abridged/">The First Conspiracy : The Secret Plot to Kill George Washington &#8211; Brad Meltzer, Josh Mensch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Taking place during the most critical period of our nation&#8217;s birth, The First Conspiracy tells a remarkable and previously untold piece of American history that not only reveals George Washington&#8217;s character, but also illuminates the origins of America&#8217;s counterintelligence movement that led to the modern day CIA.     </p>
<p>                    In 1776, an elite group of soldiers were handpicked to serve as George Washington&#8217;s bodyguards. Washington trusted them; relied on them. But unbeknownst to Washington, some of them were part of a treasonous plan. In the months leading up to the Revolutionary War, these traitorous soldiers, along with the Governor of New York, William Tryon, and Mayor David Mathews, launched a deadly plot against the most important member of the military: George Washington himself.     </p>
<p>                    This is the story of the secret plot and how it was revealed. It is a story of leaders, liars, counterfeiters, and jailhouse confessors. It also shows just how hard the battle was for George Washington and how close America was to losing the Revolutionary War.     </p>
<p>                    In this historical page-turner, New York Times bestselling author Brad Meltzer teams up with American history writer and documentary television producer, Josh Mensch to unravel the shocking true story behind what has previously been a footnote in the pages of history. Drawing on extensive research, Meltzer and Mensch capture in riveting detail how George Washington not only defeated the most powerful military force in the world, but also uncovered the secret plot against him in the tumultuous days leading up to July 4, 1776.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for The First Conspiracy:     </p>
<p>                    This is American history at its finest, a gripping story of spies, killers, counterfeiters, traitors and a mysterious prostitute who may or may not have even existed. Anyone with an interest in American history will love this book. &#8211;Douglas Preston, #1 bestselling author of The Lost City of the Monkey God     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A wonderful book about leadership and it shows why George Washington and his moral lessons are just as vital today. What a book. You&#8217;ll love it.&#8221; &#8211;former president George H.W. Bush</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-first-conspiracy-the-secret-plot-to-kill-george-washington-brad-meltzer-josh-mensch-abridged/">The First Conspiracy : The Secret Plot to Kill George Washington &#8211; Brad Meltzer, Josh Mensch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Palestine : A Four Thousand Year History &#8211; Nur Masalha (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ancient History: To C 500 CE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Exegesis & Hermeneutics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Higher & Further Education, Tertiary Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Earliest Times To Present Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This rich and magisterial work traces Palestine&#8217;s millennia-old heritage, uncovering cultures and societies of astounding depth and complexity that stretch back to the very beginnings of recorded history. Starting with the earliest references in Egyptian and Assyrian texts, Nur Masalha explores how Palestine and its Palestinian identity have evolved over thousands of years, from the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/">Palestine : A Four Thousand Year History &#8211; Nur Masalha (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This rich and magisterial work traces Palestine&#8217;s millennia-old heritage, uncovering cultures and societies of astounding depth and complexity that stretch back to the very beginnings of recorded history.    </p>
<p>                    Starting with the earliest references in Egyptian and Assyrian texts, Nur Masalha explores how Palestine and its Palestinian identity have evolved over thousands of years, from the Bronze Age to the present day. Drawing on a rich body of sources and the latest archaeological evidence, Masalha shows how Palestine&#8217;s multicultural past has been distorted and mythologised by Biblical lore and the Israel-Palestinian conflict.    </p>
<p>                    In the process, Masalha reveals that the concept of Palestine, contrary to accepted belief, is not a modern invention or one constructed in opposition to Israel, but rooted firmly in ancient past. Palestine represents the authoritative account of the country&#8217;s history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/palestine-a-four-thousand-year-history-nur-masalha-abridged/">Palestine : A Four Thousand Year History &#8211; Nur Masalha (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Napoleonic Wars]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutions, Uprisings, Rebellions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Napoleonic triumph of a book, irresistibly galloping with the momentum of a cavalry charge&#8217; Simon Sebag Montefiore &#8216;Simply dynamite&#8217; Bernard Cornwell From Andrew Roberts, author of the bestsellers The Storm of War and Churchill: Walking with Destiny, this is the definitive modern biography of Napoleon. Napoleon Bonaparte lived one of the most extraordinary of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/">Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Napoleonic triumph of a book, irresistibly galloping with the  momentum of a cavalry charge&#8217;   Simon Sebag Montefiore<br />
                    &#8216;Simply dynamite&#8217; Bernard Cornwell    </p>
<p>                    From Andrew Roberts, author of the bestsellers The Storm of War and Churchill: Walking with Destiny, this is the definitive modern biography of Napoleon.    </p>
<p>                    Napoleon Bonaparte lived one of the most extraordinary of all human lives. In the space of just twenty years, from October 1795 when as a young artillery captain he cleared the streets of Paris of insurrectionists, to his final defeat at the (horribly mismanaged) battle of Waterloo in June 1815, Napoleon transformed France and Europe. After seizing power in a coup d&#8217;etat he ended the corruption and incompetence into which the Revolution had descended. In a series of dazzling battles he reinvented the art of warfare; in peace, he completely remade the laws of France, modernised her systems of education and administration, and presided over a flourishing of the beautiful &#8216;Empire style&#8217; in the arts. The impossibility of defeating his most persistent enemy, Great Britain, led him to make draining and ultimately fatal expeditions into Spain and Russia, where half a million Frenchmen died and his Empire began to unravel.    </p>
<p>                    More than any other modern biographer, Andrew Roberts conveys Napoleon&#8217;s tremendous energy, both physical and intellectual, and the attractiveness of his personality, even to his enemies. He has walked 53 of Napoleon&#8217;s 60 battlefields, and has absorbed the gigantic new French edition of Napoleon&#8217;s letters, which allows a complete re-evaluation of this exceptional man. He overturns many received opinions, including the myth of a great romance with Josephine: she took a lover immediately after their marriage, and, as Roberts shows, he had three times as many mistresses as he acknowledged.    </p>
<p>                    Of the climactic Battle of Leipzig in 1813, as the fighting closed around them, a French sergeant-major wrote, &#8216;No-one who has not experienced it can have any idea of the enthusiasm that burst forth among the half-starved, exhausted soldiers when the Emperor was there in person. If all were demoralised and he appeared, his presence was like an electric shock. All shouted &#8220;Vive l&#8217;Empereur!&#8221; and everyone charged blindly into the fire.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    The reader of this biography will understand why this was so.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/">Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antiques & Collectables: Books, Manuscripts, Ephemera & Printed Matter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On the death of France&#8217;s most glorious king, Louis XIV, in 1715, few people benefited from the shift in power more than the intriguing financial genius from Edinburgh, John Law. Already notorious for killing a man in a duel and for acquiring a huge fortune from gambling, Law had proposed to the English monarch that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/">Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the death of France&#8217;s most glorious king, Louis XIV, in 1715, few people benefited from the shift in power more than the intriguing financial genius from Edinburgh, John Law. Already notorious for killing a man in a duel and for acquiring a huge fortune from gambling, Law had proposed to the English monarch that a bank be established to issue paper money with the credit based on the value of land. But Queen Anne was not about to take advice from a gambler and felon. So, in exile in Paris, he convinced the bankrupt court of Louis XV of the value of his idea.<br />
                     Law soon engineered the revival of the French economy and found himself one of the most powerful men in Europe. In August 1717, he founded the Mississippi Company, and the Court granted him the right to trade in France&#8217;s vast territory in America. The shareholders in his new trading company made such enormous profits that the term millionaire was coined to describe them. Paris was soon in a frenzy of speculation, conspiracies, and insatiable consumption. Before this first boom-and-bust cycle was complete, markets throughout Europe crashed, the mob began calling for Law&#8217;s head, and his visionary ideas about what money could do were abandoned and forgotten.<br />
                     In Millionaire,  Janet Gleeson lucidly reconstructs this epic drama where fortunes were made and lost, paupers grew rich, and lords fell into penury &#8212; and a modern fiscal philosophy was born. Her enthralling tragicomic tale reveals two great characters: John Law, with his complex personality and inscrutable motives, and money itself, whose true nature even to this day remains elusive</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/">Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A riveting and illuminating tour of how nations deal with crises &#8211; which might hopefully help humanity as a whole deal with our present global crisis&#8217; YUVAL NOAH HARARI, author of SAPIENS ** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Author of the landmark international bestsellers Guns, Germs and Steel and Collapse, Jared Diamond has transformed our understanding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond-abridged/">Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A riveting and illuminating tour of how nations deal with crises &#8211; which might hopefully help humanity as a whole deal with our present global crisis&#8217; YUVAL NOAH HARARI, author of SAPIENS     </p>
<p>                    ** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**     </p>
<p>                    Author of the landmark international bestsellers Guns, Germs and Steel and Collapse, Jared Diamond has transformed our understanding of what makes civilizations rise and fall. Now, at a time when crises are erupting around the world, heexplores what makes certain nations resilient, and reveals the factors that influence how nations and individuals can respond to enormous challenges.     </p>
<p>                    In a riveting journey into the recent past, he traces how six distinctive modern nations &#8211; Finland, Chile, Indonesia, Japan, Germany and Australia &#8211; have survived defining catastrophes, and identifies patterns in their recovery. Looking ahead, he investigates the risk that the United States and other countries, faced by grave threat, are set on a course towards catastrophe.     </p>
<p>                    Adding a rich psychological dimension to the in-depth history, geography, biology and anthropology that underpin all of Diamond&#8217;s writing, Upheaval is epic in scope, but also his most personal book yet.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating &#8230; I finished the book even more optimistic about our ability to solve problems than I started&#8217; BILL GATES    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Jared Diamond does it again: another rich, original and fascinating chapter in the human saga &#8211; with vital lessons for our difficult times&#8217; STEVEN PINKER</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond-abridged/">Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
