<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Semantics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/semantics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/semantics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Semantics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/semantics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Wired for Story : The Writer&#8217;s Guide to Using Brain Science to Hook Readers from the Very First Sentence &#8211; Lisa Cron (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wired-for-story-the-writers-guide-to-using-brain-science-to-hook-readers-from-the-very-first-sentence-lisa-cron-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing Skills]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wired-for-story-the-writers-guide-to-using-brain-science-to-hook-readers-from-the-very-first-sentence-lisa-cron-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This guide reveals how writers can utilize cognitive storytelling strategies to craft stories that ignite readers&#8217; brains and captivate them through each plot element. Imagine knowing what the brain craves from every tale it encounters, what fuels the success of any great story, and what keeps readers transfixed. Wired for Story reveals these cognitive secrets&#8211;and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wired-for-story-the-writers-guide-to-using-brain-science-to-hook-readers-from-the-very-first-sentence-lisa-cron-abridged/">Wired for Story : The Writer&#8217;s Guide to Using Brain Science to Hook Readers from the Very First Sentence &#8211; Lisa Cron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This guide reveals how writers can utilize cognitive storytelling strategies to craft stories that ignite readers&#8217; brains and captivate them through each plot element.     </p>
<p>                    Imagine knowing what the brain craves from every tale it encounters, what fuels the success of any great story, and what keeps readers transfixed. Wired for Story reveals these cognitive secrets&#8211;and it&#8217;s a game-changer for anyone who has ever set pen to paper.     </p>
<p>                    The vast majority of writing advice focuses on &#8220;writing well&#8221; as if it were the same as telling a great story. This is exactly where many aspiring writers fail&#8211;they strive for beautiful metaphors, authentic dialogue, and interesting characters, losing sight of the one thing that every engaging story must do: ignite the brain&#8217;s hardwired desire to learn what happens next. When writers tap into the evolutionary purpose of story and electrify our curiosity, it triggers a delicious dopamine rush that tells us to pay attention. Without it, even the most perfect prose won&#8217;t hold anyone&#8217;s interest.     </p>
<p>                    Backed by recent breakthroughs in neuroscience as well as examples from novels, screenplays, and short stories, Wired for Story offers a revolutionary look at story as the brain experiences it. Each chapter zeroes in on an aspect of the brain, its corresponding revelation about story, and the way to apply it to your storytelling right now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wired-for-story-the-writers-guide-to-using-brain-science-to-hook-readers-from-the-very-first-sentence-lisa-cron-abridged/">Wired for Story : The Writer&#8217;s Guide to Using Brain Science to Hook Readers from the Very First Sentence &#8211; Lisa Cron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Don&#8217;t Buy It : The Trouble with Talking Nonsense about the Economy &#8211; Anat Shenker-Osorio (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After everything that&#8217;s happened, how is it possible that conservatives still win debates about the economy? Time and again the right wins over voters by claiming that their solutions are only common sense, even as their tired policies of budgetary sacrifice and corporate plunder both create and prolong economic disaster. Why does the electorate keep [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/">Don&#8217;t Buy It : The Trouble with Talking Nonsense about the Economy &#8211; Anat Shenker-Osorio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After everything that&#8217;s happened, how is it possible that conservatives still win debates about the economy? Time and again the right wins over voters by claiming that their solutions are only common sense, even as their tired policies of budgetary sacrifice and corporate plunder both create and prolong economic disaster. Why does the electorate keep buying what they&#8217;re selling? According to political communications expert Anat Shenker-Osorio, it&#8217;s all about language,and not just theirs, but ours.In  Don&#8217;t Buy It  Shenker-Osorio diagnoses our economic discourse as stricken with faulty messages, deceptive personification, and, worst of all, a barely coherent concept of what the economy actually is. Opening up the business section of most newspapers or flipping on cable news unleashes an onslaught of economic doomsaying that treats the economy as an ungovernable force of nature. Alternately, by calling the economy  unhealthy&#8221; or  recovering&#8221; as we so often do, we unconsciously give it the status of a living being. No wonder Americans become willing to submit to any indignity required to keep the economy happy. Tread lightly, we can&#8217;t risk irritating the economy!Cutting through conservative myth-making, messaging muddles, and destructive misinformation, Shenker-Osorio suggests a new way to win the most important arguments of our day. The left doesn&#8217;t have to self-destruct every time matters economic come to the fore,there are metaphors and frames that can win, and Shenker-Osorio shows what they are and how to use them. Don&#8217;t Buy It  is a vital handbook for seizing victory in the economic debate. In the end, it convincingly shows that radically altering our politics and policies for the better is a matter of first changing the conversation,literally.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dont-buy-it-the-trouble-with-talking-nonsense-about-the-economy-anat-shenker-osorio-abridged/">Don&#8217;t Buy It : The Trouble with Talking Nonsense about the Economy &#8211; Anat Shenker-Osorio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Words Like Loaded Pistols &#8211; Sam Leith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/words-like-loaded-pistols-sam-leith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/words-like-loaded-pistols-sam-leith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Words Like Loaded Pistols, Sam Leith traces the art of persuasion, beginning in ancient Syracuse and taking us on detours as varied and fascinating as Elizabethan England, Milton&#8217;s Satanic realm, the Springfield of Abraham Lincoln and the Springfield of Homer Simpson. He explains how language has been used by the great heroes of rhetoric [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/words-like-loaded-pistols-sam-leith-abridged/">Words Like Loaded Pistols &#8211; Sam Leith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Words Like Loaded Pistols, Sam Leith traces the art of persuasion, beginning in ancient Syracuse and taking us on detours as varied and fascinating as Elizabethan England, Milton&#8217;s Satanic realm, the Springfield of Abraham Lincoln and the Springfield of Homer Simpson. He explains how language has been used by the great heroes of rhetoric (such as Cicero and Martin Luther King Jr.), as well as some villains (like Adolf Hitler and Richard Nixon.) Words Like Loaded Pistols is a primer to rhetoric&#8217;s key techniques; you&#8217;ll find out how to build your own memory-palace; you&#8217;ll be introduced to the Three Musketeers: Ethos, Pathos and Logos; and you&#8217;ll learn how to use chiasmus with confidence and occultation without thinking about it. Most importantly of all, you will discover that rhetoric is useful, relevant &#8212; and absolutely nothing to be afraid of.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/words-like-loaded-pistols-sam-leith-abridged/">Words Like Loaded Pistols &#8211; Sam Leith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Language Intelligence : Lessons on persuasion from Jesus, Shakespeare, Lincoln, and Lady Gaga &#8211; Joseph J Romm (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/language-intelligence-lessons-on-persuasion-from-jesus-shakespeare-lincoln-and-lady-gaga-joseph-j-romm-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/language-intelligence-lessons-on-persuasion-from-jesus-shakespeare-lincoln-and-lady-gaga-joseph-j-romm-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Romm, one of Rolling Stone magazine&#8217;s top &#8220;100 Agents of Change,&#8221; has focused his talents on helping us all to increase our Language Intelligence and to better understand the art of persuasion. Romm demonstrates that you don&#8217;t have to be an expert to vastly improve your ability to communicate. He has pulled together the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/language-intelligence-lessons-on-persuasion-from-jesus-shakespeare-lincoln-and-lady-gaga-joseph-j-romm-abridged/">Language Intelligence : Lessons on persuasion from Jesus, Shakespeare, Lincoln, and Lady Gaga &#8211; Joseph J Romm (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Joseph Romm, one of Rolling Stone magazine&#8217;s top &#8220;100 Agents of Change,&#8221; has focused his talents on helping us all to increase our Language Intelligence and to better understand the art of persuasion.     </p>
<p>                     Romm demonstrates that you don&#8217;t have to be an expert to vastly improve your ability to communicate. He has pulled together the secrets of the greatest communicators in history to show how you can apply these tools to your writing, speaking, blogging &#8211; even your Tweeting. The book also looks at the language intelligence of President Obama and Governor Romney.     </p>
<p>                     Nothing could be more relevant in 2012 as Americans prepare to make vital choices in the upcoming elections. Language Intelligence not only will prepare you to be a much more memorable and persuasive communicator, it will also help you to understand the tricks of the trade used &#8212; and misused &#8212; by candidates on the stump.     </p>
<p>                     With a few easily digestible and memorable concepts, Language Intelligence also offers readers an indispensible roadmap for today&#8217;s political and pop culture landscape. &#8220;For anyone who seeks to understand why Lady Gaga&#8217;s music has become a global phenomena or how to avoid &#8216;Etch-a-Sketch&#8217; moments, this book is for you,&#8221; said Romm.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/language-intelligence-lessons-on-persuasion-from-jesus-shakespeare-lincoln-and-lady-gaga-joseph-j-romm-abridged/">Language Intelligence : Lessons on persuasion from Jesus, Shakespeare, Lincoln, and Lady Gaga &#8211; Joseph J Romm (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Are We Yelling? : The Art of Productive Disagreement &#8211; Buster Benson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-are-we-yelling-the-art-of-productive-disagreement-buster-benson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues & Debates]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-are-we-yelling-the-art-of-productive-disagreement-buster-benson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is a life-changing book. Read it three times and then give a copy to anyone you care about. It will make things better&#8217; &#8211; Seth Godin, author of This is Marketing &#8216;All you need is Buster Benson. His methods are instantly actionable, [and] his writing is funny and relatable&#8217; &#8211; Adam Grant, author of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-are-we-yelling-the-art-of-productive-disagreement-buster-benson-abridged/">Why Are We Yelling? : The Art of Productive Disagreement &#8211; Buster Benson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is a life-changing book. Read it three times and then give a copy to anyone you care about. It will make things better&#8217; &#8211; Seth Godin, author of This is Marketing    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;All you need is Buster Benson. His methods are instantly actionable, [and] his writing is funny and relatable&#8217; &#8211; Adam Grant, author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    Why Are We Yelling is Buster Benson&#8217;s essential guide to having more honest and constructive arguments.    </p>
<p>                    The way we argue is broken. Whether it&#8217;s about Brexit, the existence of ghosts, the best burger in the city or who&#8217;s allowed to sit in your favourite chair, we end up digging our heels in and yelling at one another or choosing to avoid heated topics entirely. There has to be a better way.    </p>
<p>                    Buster Benson, a Silicon Valley entrepreneur with two decades of experience facilitating hard conversations at some of the biggest tech companies in the world, recommends eight things to try in order to make disagreements more productive. By applying these eight new habits, we can flip frustrating, unproductive disagreements into ones that bear fruit and bring people closer together.    </p>
<p>                    In this book you&#8217;ll master practical skills to make your disagreements more productive by:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Understanding four ways of disagreeing that are more valuable than simply &#8216;winning&#8217; the argument<br />
                    &#8211; Identifying the kind of argument you&#8217;re having so you know how best to negotiate it<br />
                    &#8211; Articulating the best possible version of your opponent&#8217;s argument before attacking it    </p>
<p>                    With this toolkit we can explore more possibilities and perspectives in the world, simply because we&#8217;ll no longer be afraid to wade into scary topics of conversation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-are-we-yelling-the-art-of-productive-disagreement-buster-benson-abridged/">Why Are We Yelling? : The Art of Productive Disagreement &#8211; Buster Benson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
