<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation &amp; Visualisation Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/mind-body-spirit-meditation-visualisation/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/mind-body-spirit-meditation-visualisation/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation &amp; Visualisation Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/mind-body-spirit-meditation-visualisation/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Success Through Stillness : Meditation Made Simple &#8211; Russell Simmons, With Chris Morrow</title>
		<link>/success-through-stillness-meditation-made-simple-russell-simmons-with-chris-morrow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/success-through-stillness-meditation-made-simple-russell-simmons-with-chris-morrow/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Master entrepreneur, original hip-hop mogul, and New York Times bestselling author Russell Simmons shares the most fundamental key to success&#8211;meditation&#8211;and guides readers to use stillness as a powerful tool to access their potential. In the New York Times bestseller Super Rich, Russell Simmons proved that to be rich is more than just having money in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/success-through-stillness-meditation-made-simple-russell-simmons-with-chris-morrow/">Success Through Stillness : Meditation Made Simple &#8211; Russell Simmons, With Chris Morrow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Master entrepreneur, original hip-hop mogul, and New York Times bestselling author Russell Simmons shares the most fundamental key to success&#8211;meditation&#8211;and guides readers to use stillness as a powerful tool to access their potential.     </p>
<p>                    In the New York Times bestseller Super Rich, Russell Simmons proved that to be rich is more than just having money in the bank&#8211;wealth is about balance, joy, and conscientious living.     </p>
<p>                    In Success Through Stillness, Simmons shows the connection between inner peace and outward success through interviews with other successful leaders in various industries, and how learning to be still has been instrumental in his own career. Simmons attributes his meditation practice with changing his life for the better and says that there is no &#8220;bad&#8221; way to meditate, only different forms for different people.     </p>
<p>                    In this highly anticipated new book, Russell Simmons guides readers into finding greater clarity and focus, and explains how to be healthier in both mind and body. Simmons breaks down what he&#8217;s learned from masters of meditation into a guide that is accessible to those unfamiliar with the practice.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/success-through-stillness-meditation-made-simple-russell-simmons-with-chris-morrow/">Success Through Stillness : Meditation Made Simple &#8211; Russell Simmons, With Chris Morrow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Analyze People : Persuasion, and Dark Psychology &#8211; 3 Books in 1 &#8211; How to Recognize The Signs Of a Toxic Person Manipulating You, and The Best Defense Against It &#8211; James W Williams</title>
		<link>/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanistic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neuro Linguistic Programming (NLP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dark Psychology Series Complete 3 Book Compilation This book includes: How to Analyze People: Dark Psychology &#8211; Dark Secrets to Analyze and Influence Anyone Using Body Language, Human Psychology, Subliminal Persuasion and NLP Persuasion: Dark Psychology &#8211; How People are Influencing You to Do What They Want Using Manipulation, NLP, and Subliminal Persuasion Dark Psychology: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/">How to Analyze People : Persuasion, and Dark Psychology &#8211; 3 Books in 1 &#8211; How to Recognize The Signs Of a Toxic Person Manipulating You, and The Best Defense Against It &#8211; James W Williams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dark Psychology Series Complete 3 Book Compilation    </p>
<p>                    This book includes: How to Analyze People: Dark Psychology &#8211; Dark Secrets to Analyze and Influence Anyone Using Body Language, Human Psychology, Subliminal Persuasion and NLP<br />
                    Persuasion: Dark Psychology &#8211; How People are Influencing You to Do What They Want Using Manipulation, NLP, and Subliminal Persuasion<br />
                    Dark Psychology: The Practical Uses and Best Defenses of Psychological Warfare in Everyday Life &#8211; How to Detect and Defend Against Manipulation, Deception, Dark Persuasion, and Covert NLP    </p>
<p>                    If you&#8217;re tired of being manipulated, whether you&#8217;re being tricked into doing things you don&#8217;t want, or others are taking advantage of you, there are ways to stop manipulation and persuasion in its tracks.    </p>
<p>                    In this book, you will get a groundwork for what different types of persuasion and manipulation might be. You will learn the process of how people use these tactics to their advantage.    </p>
<p>                    The first half of the book will discuss what makes up an individual. The way you use your body, the words that you choose to speak, and the way that they were raised all play important roles in what makes an individual. You will also have to look at your own self and pick out all of these unique things that make them different from everyone else as well.    </p>
<p>                    There are psychological studies that back up the idea of certain methods of persuasion, such as NLP tactics, that prove that anyone has the power to persuade others.    </p>
<p>                    Inside this book, you will discover: WhatDark Psychologyis and how it&#8217;s used to control people.How to plant different emotional seeds that will grow in people&#8217;s mindsHow to use words to steer people however you likeHow to identify and work with different types of people like contrarians and control freaks.The jobs/roles in society that you are most likely to be manipulated inThe language of the subconsciousThedirty trickslovers and family members use to control their victims.How to analyze different personality typesMind-blowing tricks for manipulationMagic words for influencing othersA step-by-step guide on influencing others with NLPForbidden secrets of dark psychologyCase studies showcasing how much damage a master manipulator can do.And much more&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Although there are many differences among people, there are also many things that make us the same. In order to better analyze and understand those around you, it&#8217;s crucial to find those things that we do connect on, and the things that bring us together rather than the things that tear us apart.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s important when reading this book to remember that not all manipulation is bad. In the first book of this boxset, it is emphasized that those who might be manipulating you might also be taking advantage of you.    </p>
<p>                    When reading this book, you should remember that manipulation is a tool, much like a hammer. You can either use that hammer to destroy everything around you, or you could alternatively use that hammer to create something organic, something new.    </p>
<p>                    This book will take you first through the discovery and analyzation of those around you, and then it will provide different ways that you can persuade them.    </p>
<p>                    The only thing you need before starting this book is the willingness to change. You might have to confront some of your darkest issues, and you might have to put yourself through future scenarios that elicit a feeling of discomfort. In the end, however, you&#8217;ll find yourself to be much more self-aware and independent.Click &#8220;Add to Cart&#8221; nowand learn how to defend against dark psychology and keep your mind and life in control.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/">How to Analyze People : Persuasion, and Dark Psychology &#8211; 3 Books in 1 &#8211; How to Recognize The Signs Of a Toxic Person Manipulating You, and The Best Defense Against It &#8211; James W Williams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chicken Soup for the Soul Happily Ever After : Fun and Heartwarming Stories About Finding and Enjoying Your Mate &#8211; Amy Kaechele, Fred Stella, Compiled by JACK CANFIELD, Compiled by Mark Victor Hansen, Compiled by Amy Newmark</title>
		<link>/chicken-soup-for-the-soul-happily-ever-after-fun-and-heartwarming-stories-about-finding-and-enjoying-your-mate-amy-kaechele-fred-stella-compiled-by-jack-canfield-compiled-by-mark-vict/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chicken-soup-for-the-soul-happily-ever-after-fun-and-heartwarming-stories-about-finding-and-enjoying-your-mate-amy-kaechele-fred-stella-compiled-by-jack-canfield-compiled-by-mark-vict/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dating and courtship, romance, love, and marriage are favorite Chicken Soup topics. Women, and even men, love to listen to true stories about how it happened for other people. This audiobook includes the 101 best stories on love and marriage chosen from a wide variety of past Chicken Soup books. These heartwarming stories will inspire [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chicken-soup-for-the-soul-happily-ever-after-fun-and-heartwarming-stories-about-finding-and-enjoying-your-mate-amy-kaechele-fred-stella-compiled-by-jack-canfield-compiled-by-mark-vict/">Chicken Soup for the Soul Happily Ever After : Fun and Heartwarming Stories About Finding and Enjoying Your Mate &#8211; Amy Kaechele, Fred Stella, Compiled by JACK CANFIELD, Compiled by Mark Victor Hansen, Compiled by Amy Newmark</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dating and courtship, romance, love, and marriage are favorite Chicken Soup topics. Women, and even men, love to listen to true stories about how it happened for other people. This audiobook includes the 101 best stories on love and marriage chosen from a wide variety of past Chicken Soup books. These heartwarming stories will inspire and amuse listeners, whether they are just starting to date, are newly wed, or are veterans of a long marriage.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chicken-soup-for-the-soul-happily-ever-after-fun-and-heartwarming-stories-about-finding-and-enjoying-your-mate-amy-kaechele-fred-stella-compiled-by-jack-canfield-compiled-by-mark-vict/">Chicken Soup for the Soul Happily Ever After : Fun and Heartwarming Stories About Finding and Enjoying Your Mate &#8211; Amy Kaechele, Fred Stella, Compiled by JACK CANFIELD, Compiled by Mark Victor Hansen, Compiled by Amy Newmark</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mindful Athlete : Secrets to Peak Performance &#8211; George Mumford (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-mindful-athlete-secrets-to-peak-performance-george-mumford-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mindful-athlete-secrets-to-peak-performance-george-mumford-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;George helped me understand the art of mindfulness. To be neither distracted or focused, rigid or flexible, passive or aggressive. I learned just to be. &#8211;Kobe Bryant Michael Jordan credits George Mumford with transforming his on-court leadership of the Bulls, helping Jordan lead the team to six NBA championships. Mumford also helped Kobe Bryant, Andrew [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mindful-athlete-secrets-to-peak-performance-george-mumford-abridged/">The Mindful Athlete : Secrets to Peak Performance &#8211; George Mumford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;George helped me understand the art of mindfulness. To be neither distracted or focused, rigid or flexible, passive or aggressive. I learned just to be. &#8211;Kobe Bryant    </p>
<p>                    Michael Jordan credits George Mumford with transforming his on-court leadership of the Bulls, helping Jordan lead the team to six NBA championships. Mumford also helped Kobe Bryant, Andrew Bynum, and Lamar Odom and countless other NBA players turn around their games. A widely respected public speaker and coach, Mumford is sharing his own story and the strategies that have made these athletes into stars in The Mindful Athlete: The Secret to Pure Performance. His proven, gentle but groundbreaking mindfulness techniques can transform the performance of anyone with a goal, be they an Olympian, weekend warrior, executive, hacker, or artist.     </p>
<p>                    When Michael Jordan left the Chicago Bulls to play baseball in 1993, the team was in crisis. Coach Phil Jackson, a long-time mindfulness practitioner, contacted Dr. Kabat-Zinn to find someone who could teach mindfulness techniques to the struggling team&#8211;someone who would have credibility and could speak the language of his players. Kabat-Zinn led Jackson to Mumford and their partnership began. Mumford has worked with Jackson and each of the eleven teams he coached to become NBA champions. His roster of champion clients has since blossomed way beyond basketball to include corporate executives, Olympians, and athletes in many different sports.     </p>
<p>                    With a charismatic teaching style that combines techniques of engaged mindfulness with lessons from popular culture icons such as Yoda, Indiana Jones, and Bruce Lee, Mumford tells illuminating stories about his larger than life clients. His writing is down-to-earth and easy to understand and apply. The Mindful Athlete is an engrossing story and an invaluable resource for anyone looking to elevate their game, no matter what the pursuit, and includes a foreword by Phil Jackson.     </p>
<p>                    Self-consciousness is when you&#8217;re focused on how you&#8217;re doing instead of what you&#8217;re doing. We have to learn how to push and challenge ourselves, but not in an insensitive way. Honing your performance really comes down to being comfortable with being uncomfortable.&#8211;George Mumford</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mindful-athlete-secrets-to-peak-performance-george-mumford-abridged/">The Mindful Athlete : Secrets to Peak Performance &#8211; George Mumford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mindsight : The New Science of Personal Transformation &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mindsight-the-new-science-of-personal-transformation-daniel-j-siegel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mindsight-the-new-science-of-personal-transformation-daniel-j-siegel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a pioneer in the field of mental health comes a groundbreaking book on the healing power of mindsight, the potent skill that allows you to make positive changes in your brain-and in your life. Foreword by Daniel Goleman, author of Emotional Intelligence &#8211; Is there a memory that torments you, or an irrational fear [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindsight-the-new-science-of-personal-transformation-daniel-j-siegel-abridged/">Mindsight : The New Science of Personal Transformation &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a pioneer in the field of mental health comes a groundbreaking book on the healing power of mindsight, the potent skill that allows you to make positive changes in your brain-and in your life.     </p>
<p>                    Foreword by Daniel Goleman, author of Emotional Intelligence     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Is there a memory that torments you, or an irrational fear you can&#8217;t shake?<br />
                    &#8211; Do you sometimes become unreasonably angry or upset and find it hard to calm down?<br />
                    &#8211; Do you ever wonder why you can&#8217;t stop behaving the way you do, no matter how hard you try?<br />
                    &#8211; Are you and your child (or parent, partner, or boss) locked in a seemingly inevitable pattern of conflict?     </p>
<p>                    What if you could escape traps like these and live a fuller, richer, happier life? This isn&#8217;t mere speculation but the result of twenty-five years of careful hands-on clinical work by Daniel J. Siegel, M.D. A Harvard-trained physician, Dr. Siegel is one of the revolutionary global innovators in the integration of brain science into the practice of psychotherapy. Using case histories from his practice, he shows how, by following the proper steps, nearly everyone can learn how to focus their attention on the internal world of the mind in a way that will literally change the wiring and architecture of their brain.     </p>
<p>                    Through his synthesis of a broad range of scientific research with applications to everyday life, Dr. Siegel has developed novel approaches that have helped hundreds of patients. And now he has written the first book that will help all of us understand the potential we have to create our own lives. Showing us mindsight in action, Dr. Siegel describes     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; a sixteen-year-old boy with bipolar disorder who uses meditation and other techniques instead of drugs to calm the emotional storms that made him suicidal<br />
                    &#8211; a woman paralyzed by anxiety, who uses mindsight to discover, in an unconscious memory of a childhood accident, the source of her dread<br />
                    &#8211; a physician-the author himself-who pays attention to his intuition, which he experiences as a vague, uneasy feeling in my belly, a gnawing restlessness in my heart and my gut, and tracks down a patient who could have gone deaf because of an inaccurately written prescription for an ear infection<br />
                    &#8211; a twelve-year-old girl with OCD who learns a meditation that is like watching myself from outside myself and, using a form of internal dialogue, is able to stop the compulsive behaviors that have been tormenting her     </p>
<p>                    These and many other extraordinary stories illustrate how mindsight can help us master our emotions, heal our relationships, and reach our fullest potential.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindsight-the-new-science-of-personal-transformation-daniel-j-siegel-abridged/">Mindsight : The New Science of Personal Transformation &#8211; Daniel J. Siegel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ikigai : The Japanese secret to a long and happy life &#8211; Hector Garcia, Francesc Miralles (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ikigai-the-japanese-secret-to-a-long-and-happy-life-hector-garcia-francesc-miralles-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ikigai-the-japanese-secret-to-a-long-and-happy-life-hector-garcia-francesc-miralles-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER We all have an ikigai. It&#8217;s the Japanese word for &#8216;a reason to live&#8217; or &#8216;a reason to jump out of bed in the morning&#8217;. It&#8217;s the place where your needs, desires, ambitions, and satisfaction meet. A place of balance. Small wonder that finding your ikigai is closely linked to living longer. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ikigai-the-japanese-secret-to-a-long-and-happy-life-hector-garcia-francesc-miralles-abridged/">Ikigai : The Japanese secret to a long and happy life &#8211; Hector Garcia, Francesc Miralles (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    We all have an ikigai.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s the Japanese word for &#8216;a reason to live&#8217; or &#8216;a reason to jump out of bed in the morning&#8217;.     </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s the place where your needs, desires, ambitions, and satisfaction meet. A place of balance. Small wonder that finding your ikigai is closely linked to living longer.    </p>
<p>                    Finding your ikigai is easier than you might think. This book will help you work out what your own ikigai really is, and equip you to change your life. You have a purpose in this world: your skills, your interests, your desires and your history have made you the perfect candidate for something. All you have to do is find it.    </p>
<p>                    Do that, and you can make every single day of your life joyful and meaningful.<br />
                    ______________________________<br />
                    &#8216;I read it and it&#8217;s bewitched me ever since. I&#8217;m spellbound.&#8217;<br />
                    Chris Evans    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A refreshingly simple recipe for happiness.&#8217; Stylist    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ikigai gently unlocks simple secrets we can all use to live long, meaningful, happy lives. Warm, patient, and kind, this book pulls you gently along your own journey rather than pushing you from behind.&#8217; Neil Pasricha, bestselling author of The Happiness Equation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ikigai-the-japanese-secret-to-a-long-and-happy-life-hector-garcia-francesc-miralles-abridged/">Ikigai : The Japanese secret to a long and happy life &#8211; Hector Garcia, Francesc Miralles (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do Breathe : Calm Your Mind. Find Focus. Get Stuff Done &#8211; Michael Townsend Williams (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-breathe-calm-your-mind-find-focus-get-stuff-done-michael-townsend-williams-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-breathe-calm-your-mind-find-focus-get-stuff-done-michael-townsend-williams-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When you get the right balance in life you can do amazing things: create, perform, lead a team, build a great company, raise a family. But so often the scales tip and we feel overwhelmed and stressed. Michael Townsend Williams, an adman turned yoga teacher and mindfulness coach, is an advocate of welldoing leading a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-breathe-calm-your-mind-find-focus-get-stuff-done-michael-townsend-williams-abridged/">Do Breathe : Calm Your Mind. Find Focus. Get Stuff Done &#8211; Michael Townsend Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When you get the right balance in life you can do amazing things: create, perform, lead a team, build a great company, raise a family. But so often the scales tip and we feel overwhelmed and stressed.  Michael Townsend Williams, an adman turned yoga teacher and mindfulness coach, is an advocate of  welldoing    leading a busy and productive life, but not at the expense of our health and wellbeing. And key to this? Our breath.  The crucial link between mind and body, our breath reflects what we re dealing with at any given moment. It tells us when we re out of our depth.  With simple breathing exercises and elements from yoga, meditation and mindfulness, Do Breathe will help you to: -Reduce stress and increase productivity -Improve focus and work flow -Cultivate new good habits and drop the bad -Build courage and resilience.  Why not breathe yourself better?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-breathe-calm-your-mind-find-focus-get-stuff-done-michael-townsend-williams-abridged/">Do Breathe : Calm Your Mind. Find Focus. Get Stuff Done &#8211; Michael Townsend Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Miracle Morning : The 6 Habits That Will Transform Your Life Before 8AM &#8211; Hal Elrod (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-miracle-morning-the-6-habits-that-will-transform-your-life-before-8am-hal-elrod-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-miracle-morning-the-6-habits-that-will-transform-your-life-before-8am-hal-elrod-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s being widely regarded as &#8220;one of the most life changing books ever written&#8221; may be the simplest approach to achieving everything you&#8217;ve ever wanted, and faster than you ever thought possible &#8216;Hal Elrod is a genius and his book The Miracle Morning has been magical in my life&#8217; Robert Kiyosaki, bestselling author of Rich [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-miracle-morning-the-6-habits-that-will-transform-your-life-before-8am-hal-elrod-abridged/">The Miracle Morning : The 6 Habits That Will Transform Your Life Before 8AM &#8211; Hal Elrod (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s being widely regarded as &#8220;one of the most life changing books ever written&#8221; may be the simplest approach to achieving everything you&#8217;ve ever wanted, and faster than you ever thought possible    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Hal Elrod is a genius and his book The Miracle Morning has been magical in my life&#8217; Robert Kiyosaki, bestselling author of Rich Dad Poor Dad     </p>
<p>                    What if you could wake up tomorrow and any &#8211; or EVERY &#8211; area of your life was beginning to transform? What would you change? The Miracle Morning is already transforming the lives of tens of thousands of people around the world by showing them how to wake up each day with more ENERGY, MOTIVATION, and FOCUS to take your life to the next level. It&#8217;s been right here in front of us all along, but this book has finally brought it to life.     </p>
<p>                    Are you ready? The next chapter of YOUR life-the most extraordinary life you&#8217;ve ever imagined-is about to begin. It&#8217;s time to WAKE UP to your full potential&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Every once in a while, you read a book that changes the way you look at life, but it is so rare to find a book that changes the way you live your life&#8217; Tim Sanders, New York Times bestselling author of The Likeability Factor     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;To read The Miracle Morning is to give yourself the gift of waking up each day to your full potential. It&#8217;s time to stop putting off creating the life you want and deserve to live. Read this book and find out how&#8217; Dr Ivan Misner, CEO and Founder of BNI (R)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-miracle-morning-the-6-habits-that-will-transform-your-life-before-8am-hal-elrod-abridged/">The Miracle Morning : The 6 Habits That Will Transform Your Life Before 8AM &#8211; Hal Elrod (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zen: The Art of Simple Living &#8211; Shunmyo Masuno, Illustrated by Harry Goldhawk, Illustrated by Zanna Goldhawk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Worship, Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feng Shui]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zen Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Be more Zen in 2022 with this little book of 100 tips and activities to soothe the soul &#8216;Brings the spirit of Zen Buddhism to everyday life . . . 100 snack-size Zen activities you can do daily to add more calm to your life&#8217; Daily Telegraph _______ Zen is the perfect antidote to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/">Zen: The Art of Simple Living &#8211; Shunmyo Masuno, Illustrated by Harry Goldhawk, Illustrated by Zanna Goldhawk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Be more Zen in 2022 with this little book of 100 tips and activities to soothe the soul    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brings the spirit of Zen Buddhism to everyday life . . . 100 snack-size Zen activities you can do daily to add more calm to your life&#8217; Daily Telegraph<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    Zen is the perfect antidote to the stress and uncertainty of modern life . . .    </p>
<p>                    In clear, practical and easy to follow lessons &#8211; one a day for 100 days &#8211; renowned Buddhist monk Shunmyo Masuno draws on centuries of wisdom to show you how to apply the essence of Zen to modern life.    </p>
<p>                    You will learn how to exhale deeply to eliminate negative emotions, to arrange your house simply to clear your thinking, to line up your shoes at night to bring order to your mind, to plant a single flower and watch it grow, to worry less about what you cannot control, and so much more . . .    </p>
<p>                    You will even make time to think about nothing at all.    </p>
<p>                    Simplify your life with the art of Zen, and learn how to feel more relaxed, fulfilled, and with a renewed sense of peace.<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Full of the simplest yet richest rituals to adopt in order to live a long and happy life, this book of wisdom is a soothing balm of peace for anyone living in the busy modern world&#8217; Psychologies    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Does for mental clutter what Marie Kondo has done for household clutter&#8217; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This little treasure needs to be at every bedside&#8217; llan Lokos, author of Through the Flames, Patience, and Pocket Peace    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Zen: The Art of Simple Living makes the wisdom of the Buddha radically accessible&#8217; Dzogchen Ponlop Rinpoche, author of Emotional Rescue and Rebel Buddha</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/">Zen: The Art of Simple Living &#8211; Shunmyo Masuno, Illustrated by Harry Goldhawk, Illustrated by Zanna Goldhawk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Start Where You Are : How to Accept Yourself and Others &#8211; Pema Choedroen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/start-where-you-are-how-to-accept-yourself-and-others-pema-choedroen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/start-where-you-are-how-to-accept-yourself-and-others-pema-choedroen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Start Where You Are is an indispensable handbook for cultivating fearlessness and awakening a compassionate heart, from bestselling author Pema Choedroen. With insight and humour, she presents down-to-earth guidance on how to make friends with ourselves and develop genuine compassion towards others. This book shows how we can &#8216;start where we are&#8217; by embracing rather [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/start-where-you-are-how-to-accept-yourself-and-others-pema-choedroen-abridged/">Start Where You Are : How to Accept Yourself and Others &#8211; Pema Choedroen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Start Where You Are is an indispensable handbook for cultivating fearlessness and awakening a compassionate heart, from bestselling author Pema Choedroen. With insight and humour, she presents down-to-earth guidance on how to make friends with ourselves and develop genuine compassion towards others.    </p>
<p>                              This book shows how we can &#8216;start where we are&#8217; by embracing rather than denying the painful aspects of our lives.    </p>
<p>                              Pema Choedroen frames her teachings on compassion around fifty-nine traditional Tibetan Buddhist maxims, or slogans, such as: &#8216;Always apply a joyful state of mind&#8217;, &#8216;Always meditate on whatever provokes resentment&#8217; and &#8216;Be grateful to everyone&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                              Working with these slogans and through the practice of meditation, Start Where You Are shows how we can all develop the courage to work with our own inner pain and discover joy, well-being and confidence.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/start-where-you-are-how-to-accept-yourself-and-others-pema-choedroen-abridged/">Start Where You Are : How to Accept Yourself and Others &#8211; Pema Choedroen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unplug : A Simple Guide to Meditation for Busy Sceptics and Modern Soul Seekers &#8211; Suze Yalof Schwartz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unplug-a-simple-guide-to-meditation-for-busy-sceptics-and-modern-soul-seekers-suze-yalof-schwartz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unplug-a-simple-guide-to-meditation-for-busy-sceptics-and-modern-soul-seekers-suze-yalof-schwartz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unplug is the book I wish I had when I first started meditating. Simple, smart, and inspirational, it provides concrete tools you can use to live a more fulfilling, happier, and yes, more productive life&#8217; Arianna Huffington THE MODERN GUIDE TO MEDITATION FOR BUSY PEOPLE Unplug is the modern, minimalist guide to meditation for busy [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unplug-a-simple-guide-to-meditation-for-busy-sceptics-and-modern-soul-seekers-suze-yalof-schwartz-abridged/">Unplug : A Simple Guide to Meditation for Busy Sceptics and Modern Soul Seekers &#8211; Suze Yalof Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unplug is the book I wish I had when I first started meditating. Simple, smart, and inspirational, it provides concrete tools you can use to live a more fulfilling, happier, and yes, more productive life&#8217;  Arianna Huffington    </p>
<p>                    THE MODERN GUIDE TO MEDITATION FOR BUSY PEOPLE    </p>
<p>                    Unplug is the modern, minimalist guide to meditation for busy people. Whether you&#8217;re a Fortune 500 CEO or someone bogged down with a never ending to-do list, Suze Yalof-Schwartz shows that you can get more done &#8211; and do it better &#8211; by consciously unplugging for just a few minutes each day.    </p>
<p>                    This revolutionary book brilliantly simplifies the art of meditation and reveals the life-changing benefits you will experience, from improved memory and a more positive outlook to a reduction in anxiety and stress.    </p>
<p>                    Through easy techniques and tips for incorporating meditation into your daily life, Unplug shows you that everyone can meditate, even if &#8211; especially if &#8211; you believe you think too much, have no time, can&#8217;t sit still or that it&#8217;s just &#8216;not you&#8217;.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unplug-a-simple-guide-to-meditation-for-busy-sceptics-and-modern-soul-seekers-suze-yalof-schwartz-abridged/">Unplug : A Simple Guide to Meditation for Busy Sceptics and Modern Soul Seekers &#8211; Suze Yalof Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Code of the Extraordinary Mind : 10 Unconventional Laws to Redefine Your Life and Succeed on Your Own Terms &#8211; Vishen Lakhiani (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-code-of-the-extraordinary-mind-10-unconventional-laws-to-redefine-your-life-and-succeed-on-your-own-terms-vishen-lakhiani-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-code-of-the-extraordinary-mind-10-unconventional-laws-to-redefine-your-life-and-succeed-on-your-own-terms-vishen-lakhiani-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; What if everything we think we know about how the world works&#8211;our ideas of love, education, spirituality, work, happiness, and love&#8211;are based on Brules (bullsh*t rules) that get passed from generation to generation and are long past their expiration date? This book teaches you to think like some of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-code-of-the-extraordinary-mind-10-unconventional-laws-to-redefine-your-life-and-succeed-on-your-own-terms-vishen-lakhiani-abridged/">The Code of the Extraordinary Mind : 10 Unconventional Laws to Redefine Your Life and Succeed on Your Own Terms &#8211; Vishen Lakhiani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; What if everything we think we know about how the world works&#8211;our ideas of love, education, spirituality, work, happiness, and love&#8211;are based on Brules (bullsh*t rules) that get passed from generation to generation and are long past their expiration date?     </p>
<p>                    This book teaches you to think like some of the greatest non-conformist minds of our era, to question, challenge, hack, and create new rules for YOUR life so you can define success on your own terms.     </p>
<p>                    The Code of the Extraordinary Mind is a blueprint of laws to break us free from the shackles of an ordinary life. It makes a case that everything we know about the world is shaped by conditioning and habit. And thus, most people live their lives based on limiting rules and outdated beliefs about pretty much everything&#8211;love, work, money, parenting, sex, health, and more&#8211;which they inherit and pass on from generation to generation.     </p>
<p>                    But what if you could remove these outdated ideas and start anew? What would your life look like if you could forget the rules of the past, and redefine what happiness, purpose, and success mean for you?     </p>
<p>                    Not Just a Book, but a Movement<br />
                    Blending computational thinking, integral theory, modern spirituality, evolutionary biology, and humor, personal growth entrepreneur Vishen Lakhiani provides a revolutionary 10-point framework for understanding and enhancing the human self. You will learn about bending reality. You will learn how to apply unique models like consciousness engineering to help you learn and grow at speeds like never before.You will learn to make a dent in the universe and discover your quest. This framework is based on Lakhiani&#8217;s personal experiences, the 5 million people he&#8217;s reached through Mindvalley, and 200 hours of interviews and questions posed to incredible minds, including Elon Musk, Richard Branson, Peter Diamandis, Ken Wilber, Dean Kamen, Arianna Huffington, Michael Beckwith, and other legendary leaders.     </p>
<p>                    In a unique fusion of cutting-edge ideas, personal stories, irreverence, and a brilliant teaching style, Lakhiani reveals the 10 powerful laws that form a step-by-step process that you can apply to life to shed years of struggle and elevate yourself to exceptional new heights.     </p>
<p>                    The 10 Laws to an Extraordinary Life<br />
                    This book challenges conventional ideas of relationships, goal-setting, mindfulness, happiness, and meaning. In a unique fusion of cutting-edge ideas, personal stories, and humorous irreverence, and not to mention, humor and napkin diagrams,  this framework combines computational thinking with personal growth to provide a powerful framework for re-coding yourself&#8211;and replacing old, limiting models that hold you back with new, empowering beliefs and behaviors that set you on the path toward an extraordinary life. A life of more happiness and achievement than you might have dared to dream possible.     </p>
<p>                    Once you discover the code, you will question your limits and realize that there are none. Step into a new understanding of the world around you and your place in it, and find yourself operating at a new, extraordinary level in every way&#8230;happiness, purpose, fulfilment, and love.     </p>
<p>                    This Book Is a Living, Breathing Manifesto That Goes Beyond a Traditional Publication<br />
                    For those who want more, The Code of the Extraordinary Mind connects to a full on immersive experience including ways for you to dive into particular chapters to unlock additional videos or training and connect with each other and the author to learn via peer-to-peer learning networks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-code-of-the-extraordinary-mind-10-unconventional-laws-to-redefine-your-life-and-succeed-on-your-own-terms-vishen-lakhiani-abridged/">The Code of the Extraordinary Mind : 10 Unconventional Laws to Redefine Your Life and Succeed on Your Own Terms &#8211; Vishen Lakhiani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Altered Traits : Science Reveals How Meditation Changes Your Mind, Brain, and Body &#8211; Daniel Goleman, Richard J. Davidson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/altered-traits-science-reveals-how-meditation-changes-your-mind-brain-and-body-daniel-goleman-richard-j-davidson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/altered-traits-science-reveals-how-meditation-changes-your-mind-brain-and-body-daniel-goleman-richard-j-davidson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two New York Times-bestselling authors unveil new research showing what meditation can really do for the brain. In the last twenty years, meditation and mindfulness have gone from being kind of cool to becoming an omnipresent Band-Aid for fixing everything from your weight to your relationship to your achievement level. Unveiling here the kind of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/altered-traits-science-reveals-how-meditation-changes-your-mind-brain-and-body-daniel-goleman-richard-j-davidson-abridged/">Altered Traits : Science Reveals How Meditation Changes Your Mind, Brain, and Body &#8211; Daniel Goleman, Richard J. Davidson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two New York Times-bestselling authors unveil new research showing what meditation can really do for the brain.     </p>
<p>                     In the last twenty years, meditation and mindfulness have gone from being kind of cool to becoming an omnipresent Band-Aid for fixing everything from your weight to your relationship to your achievement level. Unveiling here the kind of cutting-edge research that has made them giants in their fields, Daniel Goleman and Richard Davidson show us the truth about what meditation can really do for us, as well as exactly how to get the most out of it.     </p>
<p>                    Sweeping away common misconceptions and neuromythology to open readers&#8217; eyes to the ways data has been distorted to sell mind-training methods, the authors demonstrate that beyond the pleasant states mental exercises can produce, the real payoffs are the lasting personality traits that can result. But short daily doses will not get us to the highest level of lasting positive change&#8211;even if we continue for years&#8211;without specific additions. More than sheer hours, we need smart practice, including crucial ingredients such as targeted feedback from a master teacher and a more spacious, less attached view of the self, all of which are missing in widespread versions of mind training. The authors also reveal the latest data from Davidson&#8217;s own lab that point to a new methodology for developing a broader array of mind-training methods with larger implications for how we can derive the greatest benefits from the practice.     </p>
<p>                    Exciting, compelling, and grounded in new research, this is one of those rare books that has the power to change us at the deepest level.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/altered-traits-science-reveals-how-meditation-changes-your-mind-brain-and-body-daniel-goleman-richard-j-davidson-abridged/">Altered Traits : Science Reveals How Meditation Changes Your Mind, Brain, and Body &#8211; Daniel Goleman, Richard J. Davidson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crafts & Hobbies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**From the author of the international bestseller The Little Book of Hygge &#8211; over one million copies sold** Lykke (Luu-kah) (n): Happiness Meik Wiking is the CEO of the world&#8217;s only Happiness Research Institute in Copenhagen. His job is to travel around the world, seeking out the happiest people and uncovering what they do differently. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/">The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**From the author of the international bestseller The Little Book of Hygge  &#8211; over one million copies sold**    </p>
<p>                    Lykke (Luu-kah) (n): Happiness    </p>
<p>                    Meik Wiking is the CEO of the world&#8217;s only Happiness Research Institute in Copenhagen. His job is to travel around the world, seeking out the happiest people and uncovering what they do differently. In The Little Book of Lykke, he reveals what he has found.    </p>
<p>                    This captivating read features case studies from Bhutan to Australia, South Korea to Canada, France to Denmark, taking the reader on a happiness treasure hunt. Written in the same warm tone as Meik&#8217;s phenomenal bestseller The Little Book of Hygge, this easy-to-understand book will change the way you think about how you relate to your neighbours, the rituals around cooking and eating dinner, and when to book your next holiday &#8211; and is guaranteed to put a smile on your face.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is a happy book about happiness, written with a twinkle and packaged with Danish style&#8217; (John Helliwell, Economist and Editor of the World Happiness Report)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/">The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conscious : A Brief Guide to the Fundamental Mystery of the Mind &#8211; Annaka Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/conscious-a-brief-guide-to-the-fundamental-mystery-of-the-mind-annaka-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conscious & Unconscious]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance, C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/conscious-a-brief-guide-to-the-fundamental-mystery-of-the-mind-annaka-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8220;If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how you have the capacity to wonder, some fascinating insights await you in these pages.&#8221; &#8211;Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of Originals As concise and enlightening as Seven Brief Lessons on Physics and Astrophysics for People in a Hurry, this mind-expanding dive into the mystery [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conscious-a-brief-guide-to-the-fundamental-mystery-of-the-mind-annaka-harris-abridged/">Conscious : A Brief Guide to the Fundamental Mystery of the Mind &#8211; Annaka Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how you have the capacity to wonder, some fascinating insights await you in these pages.&#8221; &#8211;Adam Grant, New York Times bestselling author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    As concise and enlightening as Seven Brief Lessons on Physics and Astrophysics for People in a Hurry, this mind-expanding dive into the mystery of consciousness is an illuminating meditation on the self, free will, and felt experience.    </p>
<p>                    What is consciousness? How does it arise? And why does it exist? We take our experience of being in the world for granted. But the very existence of consciousness raises profound questions: Why would any collection of matter in the universe be conscious? How are we able to think about this? And why should we?    </p>
<p>                    In this wonderfully accessible book, Annaka Harris guides us through the evolving definitions, philosophies, and scientific findings that probe our limited understanding of consciousness. Where does it reside, and what gives rise to it? Could it be an illusion, or a universal property of all matter? As we try to understand consciousness, we must grapple with how to define it and, in the age of artificial intelligence, who or what might possess it.     </p>
<p>                    Conscious offers lively and challenging arguments that alter our ideas about consciousness-allowing us to think freely about it for ourselves, if indeed we can.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conscious-a-brief-guide-to-the-fundamental-mystery-of-the-mind-annaka-harris-abridged/">Conscious : A Brief Guide to the Fundamental Mystery of the Mind &#8211; Annaka Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A New Earth : The life-changing follow up to The Power of Now. &#8216;My No.1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans &#8211; Eckhart Tolle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>LIFE-CHANGING&#8217; CAROLINE HINNES Learn to harness the strength of mindfulness and positivity to change your life with Eckhart Tolle THE BOOK THAT INSPIRED THE CHART-TOPPING PODCAST OPRAH &#038; ECKHART TOLLE: A NEW EARTH ____________ Are you ready to change your life? In Eckhart Tolle&#8217;s ground-breaking book, he gives you the spiritual framework to: &#8211; Understand [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/">A New Earth : The life-changing follow up to The Power of Now. &#8216;My No.1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans &#8211; Eckhart Tolle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LIFE-CHANGING&#8217; CAROLINE HINNES    </p>
<p>                    Learn to harness the strength of mindfulness and positivity to change your life with Eckhart Tolle    </p>
<p>                    THE BOOK THAT INSPIRED THE CHART-TOPPING PODCAST OPRAH &#038; ECKHART TOLLE: A NEW EARTH<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    Are you ready to change your life?    </p>
<p>                    In Eckhart Tolle&#8217;s ground-breaking book, he gives you the spiritual framework to:<br />
                    &#8211; Understand yourself better<br />
                    &#8211; Manage, manifest and achieve your goals<br />
                    &#8211; Reach your full potential<br />
                    &#8211; Channel conflict into something positive<br />
                    &#8211; Change negative habits<br />
                    &#8211; Live in the moment    </p>
<p>                    Open your mind and follow Tolle&#8217;s guidance to happiness and health in the modern world.<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A wake up call for the entire planet. A New Earth helps us to stop creating our own suffering and obsessing over the past and what the future might be and to put ourselves in the now&#8217; Oprah Winfrey    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;My No. 1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans, Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;m gonna have to listen to [this podcast] several times! Too good!&#8217; Fearne Cotton on the &#8216;Oprah and Eckhart Tolle: A New Earth&#8217; podcast    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book changed my life. It&#8217;s a brilliant and very practical spiritual guide that teaches the way to inner peace: how to live in the moment and get beyond the ego&#8217; Santa Montefiore, bestselling author of The Secret Hours</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/">A New Earth : The life-changing follow up to The Power of Now. &#8216;My No.1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans &#8211; Eckhart Tolle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thoughts Without A Thinker : Psychotherapy from a Buddhist Perspective &#8211; Mark Epstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thoughts-without-a-thinker-psychotherapy-from-a-buddhist-perspective-mark-epstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thoughts-without-a-thinker-psychotherapy-from-a-buddhist-perspective-mark-epstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The line between psychology and spirituality has blurred, as clinicians, their patients, and religious seekers explore new perspectives on the self. A landmark contribution to the field of psychoanalysis, Thoughts Without a Thinker describes the unique psychological contributions offered by the teachings of Buddhism. Drawing upon his own experiences as a psychotherapist and meditator, New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thoughts-without-a-thinker-psychotherapy-from-a-buddhist-perspective-mark-epstein-abridged/">Thoughts Without A Thinker : Psychotherapy from a Buddhist Perspective &#8211; Mark Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The line between psychology and spirituality has blurred, as clinicians, their patients, and religious seekers explore new perspectives on the self. A landmark contribution to the field of psychoanalysis,  Thoughts Without a Thinker  describes the unique psychological contributions offered by the teachings of Buddhism. Drawing upon his own experiences as a psychotherapist and meditator, New York-based psychiatrist Mark Epstein lays out the path to meditation-inspired healing, and offers a revolutionary new understanding of what constitutes a healthy emotional life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thoughts-without-a-thinker-psychotherapy-from-a-buddhist-perspective-mark-epstein-abridged/">Thoughts Without A Thinker : Psychotherapy from a Buddhist Perspective &#8211; Mark Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Life-Changing Power of Sophrology : A practical guide to reducing stress and living up to your full potential &#8211; Dominique Antiglio (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-life-changing-power-of-sophrology-a-practical-guide-to-reducing-stress-and-living-up-to-your-full-potential-dominique-antiglio-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-life-changing-power-of-sophrology-a-practical-guide-to-reducing-stress-and-living-up-to-your-full-potential-dominique-antiglio-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical sophrology guide to reducing stress and living up to your full potential. &#8216;I like Antiglio. She is calming.&#8217; &#8211; The Times Sophrology is a unique stress management and personal development technique to help you relax, feel confident and cope with life&#8217;s ups and downs. It is a straightforward method combining relaxation, breathing, body [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-life-changing-power-of-sophrology-a-practical-guide-to-reducing-stress-and-living-up-to-your-full-potential-dominique-antiglio-abridged/">The Life-Changing Power of Sophrology : A practical guide to reducing stress and living up to your full potential &#8211; Dominique Antiglio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical sophrology guide to reducing stress and living up to your full potential.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I like Antiglio. She is calming.&#8217; &#8211; The Times     </p>
<p>                    Sophrology is a unique stress management and personal development technique to help you relax, feel confident and cope with life&#8217;s ups and downs. It is a straightforward method combining relaxation, breathing, body awareness and visualisation into a step by step practice and it has the power to radically transform your life.     </p>
<p>                    Sophrology is already extremely popular on the continent. Elite athletes, CEOs and pop stars, among others, have used the techniques to dramatically improve their professional performance and reach a state of balance. It is also used in schools, as well as in the workplace, to enhance wellbeing.     </p>
<p>                    Dominique Antiglio, a globally sought-after and highly praised sophrologist, guides you through the key exercises to manage stress, improve your sleep, prepare for events, boost your confidence and positively transform your daily life. By learning the basics of sophrology, you will feel happier and discover inner strength and resilience you never knew you had.     </p>
<p>                    Featuring practical tips, case studies and 13 audio downloads, this leading book on sophrology is a must-have self-help resource.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The simplest, most natural way of calming and focusing our lives lies in front of our noses, breathing. This book will transform all our lives if we follow its helpful suggestions.&#8217; &#8211; Sir Anthony Seldon    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Sophrology looks set to be the &#8230; answer to all our problems&#8217; &#8211; The Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Sophrology is big news in the wellness world.&#8217; &#8211; ELLE    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;You&#8217;ve heard of mindfulness, now meet its dynamic young cousin sophrology&#8217; &#8211; The Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-life-changing-power-of-sophrology-a-practical-guide-to-reducing-stress-and-living-up-to-your-full-potential-dominique-antiglio-abridged/">The Life-Changing Power of Sophrology : A practical guide to reducing stress and living up to your full potential &#8211; Dominique Antiglio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics & Communications Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phones: Consumer/user Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is your phone the first thing you reach for when you wake up? And the last thing you see before you sleep? Do you find the hours slip away as you idly scroll through your social media timeline? In short, are you addicted to your phone? If so, How to Break Up with Your Phone [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/">How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is your phone the first thing you reach for when you wake up? And the  last thing you see before you sleep? Do you find the hours slip away as  you idly scroll through your social media timeline?     </p>
<p>                     In short, are you addicted to your phone? If so, How to Break Up with Your Phone is here to help.     </p>
<p>                     How to Break Up With Your Phone  is a smart, practical and useful plan to help you conquer your mobile  phone addiction in just 30 days &#8211; and take back your life in the  process.     </p>
<p>                    Recent studies have shown that spending extended time  on our phones affects our ability to form new memories, think deeply,  focus and absorb information, and the hormones triggered every time we  hear our phones buzz both add to our stress levels and are the hallmark  signs of addiction. In How to Break Up with Your Phone,  award-winning science journalist Catherine Price explores the effects  that our constant connectivity is having on our brains, bodies,  relationships, and society at large and asks, how much time do you really want to spend on your phone?     </p>
<p>                    Over  the course of 30 days, Catherine will guide you through an  easy-to-follow plan that enables you to identify your goals, priorities  and bad habits, tidy your apps, prune your email, and take time away.  Lastly, you will create a new, healthier relationship with your phone  and establish habits and routines to ensure this new relationship  sticks.     </p>
<p>                    You don&#8217;t have to give up your phone forever; instead  you will be more mindful not only of how you use your phone, but also  about how you choose to spend the precious moments of your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/">How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Miracle Of Mindfulness : The Classic Guide to Meditation by the World&#8217;s Most Revered Master &#8211; Thich Nhat Hanh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-miracle-of-mindfulness-the-classic-guide-to-meditation-by-the-worlds-most-revered-master-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Worship, Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-miracle-of-mindfulness-the-classic-guide-to-meditation-by-the-worlds-most-revered-master-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this beautifully written book, Buddhist monk and Nobel Peace Prize nominee Thich Nhat Hanh explains how to acquire the skills of mindfulness. Once we have these skills, we can slow our lives down and discover how to live in the moment &#8211; even simple acts like washing the dishes or drinking a cup of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-miracle-of-mindfulness-the-classic-guide-to-meditation-by-the-worlds-most-revered-master-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/">The Miracle Of Mindfulness : The Classic Guide to Meditation by the World&#8217;s Most Revered Master &#8211; Thich Nhat Hanh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this beautifully written book, Buddhist monk and Nobel Peace Prize nominee Thich Nhat Hanh explains how to acquire the skills of mindfulness. Once we have these skills, we can slow our lives down and discover how to live in the moment &#8211; even simple acts like washing the dishes or drinking a cup of tea may be transformed into acts of meditation.    </p>
<p>                    Thich Nhat Hanh&#8217;s gentle anecdotes and practical exercises help us to arrive at greater self-understanding and peacefulness, whether we are beginners or advanced students. Irrespective of our particular religious beliefs, we can begin to reap the immense benefits that meditation has been scientifically proven to offer. We can all learn how to be mindful and experience the miracle of mindfulness for ourselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-miracle-of-mindfulness-the-classic-guide-to-meditation-by-the-worlds-most-revered-master-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/">The Miracle Of Mindfulness : The Classic Guide to Meditation by the World&#8217;s Most Revered Master &#8211; Thich Nhat Hanh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Emotional Agility : Get Unstuck, Embrace Change and Thrive in Work and Life &#8211; Susan David (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Perfect for lovers of Quiet and The Power of Now, Emotional Agility shares a new way of relating to yourself and the world around you Every day we speak around 16,000 words &#8211; but inside minds we create tens of thousands more. Thoughts such as &#8216;I&#8217;m not spending enough time with my children&#8217; or &#8216;I&#8217;m [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david-abridged/">Emotional Agility : Get Unstuck, Embrace Change and Thrive in Work and Life &#8211; Susan David (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Perfect for lovers of Quiet and The Power of Now, Emotional Agility shares a new way of relating to yourself and the world around you    </p>
<p>                     Every day we speak around 16,000 words &#8211; but inside minds we create tens of thousands more.     </p>
<p>                    Thoughts such as &#8216;I&#8217;m not spending enough time with my children&#8217; or &#8216;I&#8217;m not good enough to present my work&#8217; can seem to be unshakeable facts. In reality, they&#8217;re the judgemental opinions of our inner voice.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on more than twenty years of academic research and her own experiences, Susan David PhD, a psychologist and faculty member at Harvard Medical School, has pioneered a new way to make peace with our inner self, achieve our most valued goals and live life to the fullest.    </p>
<p>                     Become aware of your true nature, learn to face your emotions with acceptance and generosity, act according to your deepest values, and flourish.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Essential reading&#8217; Susan Cain, author of Quiet    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A practical, science-backed guide to looking inward and living intentionally&#8217; Arianna Huffington, author of The Sleep Revolution    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An accessible, reader-friendly voyage. Emotional Agility can be helpful to anyone.&#8217; Daniel Goleman, author of Emotional Intelligence</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/emotional-agility-get-unstuck-embrace-change-and-thrive-in-work-and-life-susan-david-abridged/">Emotional Agility : Get Unstuck, Embrace Change and Thrive in Work and Life &#8211; Susan David (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fully Present : The Science, Art, and Practice of Mindfulness &#8211; Diana Winston, Susan Smalley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fully-present-the-science-art-and-practice-of-mindfulness-diana-winston-susan-smalley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fully-present-the-science-art-and-practice-of-mindfulness-diana-winston-susan-smalley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mindfulness,the art of paying attention with an open and curious mind to present-moment experiences,has attracted ever-growing interest and tens of thousands of practitioners, who have come to the discipline from both within and outside the Buddhist tradition. In Fully Present, leading mindfulness researchers and educators Dr. Sue Smalley and Diana Winston provide an all-in-one guide [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fully-present-the-science-art-and-practice-of-mindfulness-diana-winston-susan-smalley-abridged/">Fully Present : The Science, Art, and Practice of Mindfulness &#8211; Diana Winston, Susan Smalley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mindfulness,the art of paying attention with an open and curious mind to present-moment experiences,has attracted ever-growing interest and tens of thousands of practitioners, who have come to the discipline from both within and outside the Buddhist tradition. In Fully Present, leading mindfulness researchers and educators Dr. Sue Smalley and Diana Winston provide an all-in-one guide for anyone interested in bringing mindfulness to daily life as a means of enhancing well-being. Fully Present provides both a scientific explanation for how mindfulness positively and powerfully affects the brain and the body as well as practical guidance to develop both a practice and mindfulness in daily living, not only through meditation but also during daily experiences, such as waiting in line at the supermarket, exercising, or facing difficult news.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fully-present-the-science-art-and-practice-of-mindfulness-diana-winston-susan-smalley-abridged/">Fully Present : The Science, Art, and Practice of Mindfulness &#8211; Diana Winston, Susan Smalley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>10% Happier : How I Tamed the Voice in My Head, Reduced Stress Without Losing My Edge, and Found Self-Help That Actually Works &#8211; A True Story &#8211; Dan Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/10-happier-how-i-tamed-the-voice-in-my-head-reduced-stress-without-losing-my-edge-and-found-self-help-that-actually-works-a-true-story-dan-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/10-happier-how-i-tamed-the-voice-in-my-head-reduced-stress-without-losing-my-edge-and-found-self-help-that-actually-works-a-true-story-dan-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*As heard on the Tim Ferriss Show podcast* #1 New York Times bestseller and winner of the 2014 &#8216;Inspirational Memoir&#8217; category at the Living Now book awards. 10% HAPPIER is a spiritual book written for &#8211; and by &#8211; someone who would otherwise never read a spiritual book. This fifth anniversary edition features a new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/10-happier-how-i-tamed-the-voice-in-my-head-reduced-stress-without-losing-my-edge-and-found-self-help-that-actually-works-a-true-story-dan-harris-abridged/">10% Happier : How I Tamed the Voice in My Head, Reduced Stress Without Losing My Edge, and Found Self-Help That Actually Works &#8211; A True Story &#8211; Dan Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*As heard on the Tim Ferriss Show podcast*    </p>
<p>                    #1 New York Times bestseller and winner of the 2014 &#8216;Inspirational Memoir&#8217; category at the Living Now book awards.    </p>
<p>                    10% HAPPIER is a spiritual book written for &#8211; and by &#8211; someone who would otherwise never read a spiritual book. This fifth anniversary edition features a new preface and new guided meditations from his favourite teachers, including Joseph Goldstein and Sharon Salzberg.    </p>
<p>                    After having a nationally televised panic attack, Harris knew he had to make some changes. A lifelong non-believer, he found himself on a bizarre adventure and realised that the sources of his problems was the very thing he always thought was his greatest asset: the incessant, insatiable voice in his head, which had propelled him through the ranks of a hyper-competitive business, but had also led him to make the profoundly stupid decisions that provoked his on-air freak-out.     </p>
<p>                    What happened next was completely unforeseen. Through a strange series of events &#8211; Harris stumbled upon something that helped him tame the voice in his head: meditation. At first, he was deeply suspicious, but when confronted with mounting scientific evidence that just a few minutes a day can literally rewire the brain for focus, happiness and reduced reactivity, Harris took a deep dive. He became a daily meditator, and even found himself on a ten-day, silent meditation retreat.    </p>
<p>                    10% Happier is a narrative account of Dan&#8217;s conversion amid the harried and decidedly non-Zen world of the newsroom and concludes with a section for the beginner on how to get started.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I loved it&#8217; &#8211; Ruby Wax    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A wonderful book and excellent advice.&#8217; &#8211; Andy Puddicombe, founder of Headspace    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An enormously smart, clear-eyed, brave-hearted, and quite a personal look at the benefits of meditation&#8217; &#8211; Elizabeth Gilbert, author of Eat Pray Love</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/10-happier-how-i-tamed-the-voice-in-my-head-reduced-stress-without-losing-my-edge-and-found-self-help-that-actually-works-a-true-story-dan-harris-abridged/">10% Happier : How I Tamed the Voice in My Head, Reduced Stress Without Losing My Edge, and Found Self-Help That Actually Works &#8211; A True Story &#8211; Dan Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Real Love : The Art of Mindful Connection &#8211; Sharon Salzberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/real-love-the-art-of-mindful-connection-sharon-salzberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/real-love-the-art-of-mindful-connection-sharon-salzberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Real Love, one of the world&#8217;s leading authorities on love tells us how to find it, how to nurture it, how to honor it-and most of all how to rethink it &#8230; This book has the power to set your heart at peace.&#8217; -Susan Cain, author of Quiet What is love? Sharon Salzberg believes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/real-love-the-art-of-mindful-connection-sharon-salzberg-abridged/">Real Love : The Art of Mindful Connection &#8211; Sharon Salzberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Real Love, one of the world&#8217;s leading authorities on love tells us how to find it, how to nurture it, how to honor it-and most of all how to rethink it &#8230; This book has the power to set your heart at peace.&#8217; -Susan Cain, author of Quiet    </p>
<p>                    What is love? Sharon Salzberg believes that love is a powerful healing force for us all, and that modern associations with romance and adoration are limiting. By redefining love, she helps us to recognize our desire for happiness and enhance our connections with each other.     </p>
<p>                    Real Love is a creative toolkit of mindfulness exercises and meditation techniques that can help you to truly engage with your present experience and create deeper love relationships &#8211; with yourself, your partner, friends and family, and with life itself. The book encourages us to strip away layers of negative habits and obstacles and to improve deeper connections, helping us to experience authentic love based on direct experience, rather than preconceptions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/real-love-the-art-of-mindful-connection-sharon-salzberg-abridged/">Real Love : The Art of Mindful Connection &#8211; Sharon Salzberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everyday Ubuntu : Living better together, the African way &#8211; Nompumelelo Mungi Ngomane (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everyday-ubuntu-living-better-together-the-african-way-nompumelelo-mungi-ngomane-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everyday-ubuntu-living-better-together-the-african-way-nompumelelo-mungi-ngomane-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book will open your eyes, mind and heart to a way of being in the world that will make our world a better and more caring one.&#8217; ARCHBISHOP DESMOND TUTU, author of The Book of Joy Ubuntu is an ancient Southern African philosophy about how to live life well, together. It is a belief [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everyday-ubuntu-living-better-together-the-african-way-nompumelelo-mungi-ngomane-abridged/">Everyday Ubuntu : Living better together, the African way &#8211; Nompumelelo Mungi Ngomane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book will open  your eyes, mind and heart to a way of being in the world that will make  our world a better and more caring one.&#8217; ARCHBISHOP DESMOND TUTU, author of The Book of Joy    </p>
<p>                    Ubuntu is an ancient Southern African philosophy about how to live life well, together. It is a belief in a universal human bond, which says: I am only because you are.     </p>
<p>                    It means that if you can see everyone as fully human, connected to  you by their humanity, you will never be able to treat others as  disposable or without worth. By embracing the philosophy of ubuntu  it&#8217;s possible to  overcome division and be stronger together in a world  where the wise build bridges and the foolish build walls.    </p>
<p>                    These  14 beautifully illustrated lessons from the Rainbow Nation are an  essential toolkit to helping us all to live better, together. In  stories, practical lessons and applications that recognise our common  humanity, our connectedness and interdependence, Everyday Ubuntu helps us to make sense of the world and our place in it.    </p>
<p>                    Exploring  ideas of kindness and forgiveness, tolerance and the power of  listening, this definitive guide offers practical tips on how we can all  benefit from embracing others and living a more fulfilling life as part  of the large family to which we all belong.<br />
                    __________    </p>
<p>                    What readers are saying about Everyday Ubuntu:    </p>
<p>                    ***** &#8216;A concept we should all live by.&#8217;<br />
                    ***** &#8216;Lots of little gems to help with everyday life.&#8217;<br />
                    ***** &#8216;Must read&#8230; Very inspiring and thought-provoking.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everyday-ubuntu-living-better-together-the-african-way-nompumelelo-mungi-ngomane-abridged/">Everyday Ubuntu : Living better together, the African way &#8211; Nompumelelo Mungi Ngomane (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Meditation for Fidgety Skeptics : A 10% Happier How-to Book &#8211; Dan Harris, Jeffrey Warren, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/meditation-for-fidgety-skeptics-a-10-happier-how-to-book-dan-harris-jeffrey-warren-carlye-adler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/meditation-for-fidgety-skeptics-a-10-happier-how-to-book-dan-harris-jeffrey-warren-carlye-adler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF 10% HAPPIER Too busy to meditate? Can&#8217;t turn off your brain? Curious about mindfulness but more comfortable in the gym? This book is for you. You&#8217;ll also get access to guided audio meditations on the 10% Happier app, to jumpstart your practice from day one. ABC [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/meditation-for-fidgety-skeptics-a-10-happier-how-to-book-dan-harris-jeffrey-warren-carlye-adler-abridged/">Meditation for Fidgety Skeptics : A 10% Happier How-to Book &#8211; Dan Harris, Jeffrey Warren, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF 10% HAPPIER Too busy to meditate? Can&#8217;t turn off your brain? Curious about mindfulness but more comfortable in the gym? This book is for you.  You&#8217;ll also get access to guided audio meditations on the 10% Happier app, to jumpstart your practice from day one. ABC News anchor Dan Harris used to think that meditation was for people who collect crystals, play Ultimate Frisbee, and use the word &#8220;namaste&#8221; without irony. After he had a panic attack on live television, he went on a strange and circuitous journey that ultimately led him to become one of meditation&#8217;s most vocal public proponents. Harris found that meditation made him more focused and less yanked around by his emotions. According to his wife, it also made him less annoying. Science suggests that the practice can lower your blood pressure, mitigate depression and anxiety, and literally rewire key parts of the brain. So what&#8217;s holding you back? In Meditation for Fidgety Skeptics,  Harris and Jeff Warren, a masterful teacher and &#8220;Meditation MacGyver,&#8221; embark on a gonzo cross-country quest to tackle the myths, misconceptions, and self-deceptions that keep people from meditating. It is filled with game-changing and deeply practical meditation instructions&#8211;all of which are also available (for free) on the 10% Happier app. This book is a trip worth taking. Praise for Meditation for Fidgety Skeptics  &#8220;If you&#8217;re intrigued by meditation but don&#8217;t know how to begin&#8211;or you&#8217;ve benefited from meditation in the past but need help to get started again&#8211;Dan Harris has written the book for you. Well researched, practical, and crammed with expert advice, it&#8217;s also an irreverent, hilarious page-turner.&#8221;&#8211;Gretchen Rubin, author of The Happiness Project &#8220;The ABC News anchor, a &#8216;defender of worrying&#8217; who once had an anxiety attack on air, offers a hilarious and stirring account of his two-steps-forward-one-step-back campaign to sort &#8216;useless rumination&#8217; from &#8216;constructive anguish&#8217; via mindfulness, along with invaluable suggestions for following in his footsteps.&#8221;&#8211;O: The Oprah Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/meditation-for-fidgety-skeptics-a-10-happier-how-to-book-dan-harris-jeffrey-warren-carlye-adler-abridged/">Meditation for Fidgety Skeptics : A 10% Happier How-to Book &#8211; Dan Harris, Jeffrey Warren, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Make Your Bed : Feel grounded and think positive in 10 simple steps &#8211; Admiral William H. McRaven (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Make a new start in 2022 with positive daily habits for a healthy mind, from the incredible No. 1 New York Times bestseller THE INCREDIBLE NO. 1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;SUPERB, SMART, AND SUCCINCT&#8217; FORBES ______ Struggling to find structure? Finding yourself lacking motivation? Start by making your bed. Maintaining routine and structure is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/">Make Your Bed : Feel grounded and think positive in 10 simple steps &#8211; Admiral William H. McRaven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Make a new start in 2022 with positive daily habits for a healthy mind, from the incredible No. 1 New York Times bestseller    </p>
<p>                    THE INCREDIBLE NO. 1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;SUPERB, SMART, AND SUCCINCT&#8217; FORBES<br />
                    ______    </p>
<p>                    Struggling to find structure? Finding yourself lacking motivation?    </p>
<p>                    Start by making your bed.    </p>
<p>                    Maintaining routine and structure is more important than ever in the age of home working, flexi-time and the general chaos of life.    </p>
<p>                    In Make Your Bed, Admiral William H. McRaven shares 10 life lessons he learned during his Navy Seal training that helped him overcome challenges not only in his long Naval career, but also throughout his life.    </p>
<p>                    He will teach you how to . . .<br />
                    * Master the essential daily habits for staying grounded<br />
                    * Learn how to keep your mind calm and ready for the day ahead<br />
                    * Find solace and companionship in the people around you<br />
                    * Cope with setbacks and keep moving forward<br />
                    * Stray beyond your comfort zone and take risks    </p>
<p>                    Written with great humility and optimism, this timeless book provides simple and universal wisdom, practical advice, and words of encouragement that will inspire every reader.<br />
                    ______    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book to inspire your children and grandchildren to become everything that they can&#8217; The Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/">Make Your Bed : Feel grounded and think positive in 10 simple steps &#8211; Admiral William H. McRaven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Better Sex Through Mindfulness : How Women Can Cultivate Desire &#8211; Lori A. Brotto, Foreword by Emily Nagoski (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/better-sex-through-mindfulness-how-women-can-cultivate-desire-lori-a-brotto-foreword-by-emily-nagoski-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/better-sex-through-mindfulness-how-women-can-cultivate-desire-lori-a-brotto-foreword-by-emily-nagoski-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As Seen/Heard in Bustle * Dan Savage&#8217;s Savage Lovecast * Jezebel * Women&#8217;s Health * Prevention * The New York Times * VICE * Pleasure Mechanics A groundbreaking method for improving desire, arousal, and sexual satisfaction through mindfulness. Studies show that approximately half of all women experience some kind of sexual difficulty at one point [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/better-sex-through-mindfulness-how-women-can-cultivate-desire-lori-a-brotto-foreword-by-emily-nagoski-abridged/">Better Sex Through Mindfulness : How Women Can Cultivate Desire &#8211; Lori A. Brotto, Foreword by Emily Nagoski (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As Seen/Heard in Bustle * Dan Savage&#8217;s Savage Lovecast * Jezebel * Women&#8217;s Health * Prevention * The New York Times * VICE * Pleasure Mechanics    </p>
<p>                    A groundbreaking method for improving desire, arousal, and sexual satisfaction through mindfulness.     </p>
<p>                    Studies show that approximately half of all women experience some kind of sexual difficulty at one point in their lives, with lack of interest in sex being by far the most common and the most distressing. And when sex suffers, so do all other areas of life.    </p>
<p>                    But it doesn&#8217;t have to be that way. In Better Sex through Mindfulness, acclaimed psychologist and sex researcher Lori A. Brotto offers a revolutionary approach to improving desire, arousal, and satisfaction inside and outside of the bedroom. A pioneer in the use of mindfulness for treating sexual difficulties, Brotto has helped hundreds of women cultivate more exciting, fulfilling sexual experiences.    </p>
<p>                    In this accessible, relatable book, she explores the various reasons for sexual problems, such as stress and incessant multitasking, and tells the stories of many of the women she has treated over the years. She also provides easy, effective exercises that readers can do on their own to increase desire and sexual enjoyment, whether their goal is to overcome a sexual difficulty or simply give their love life a boost.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/better-sex-through-mindfulness-how-women-can-cultivate-desire-lori-a-brotto-foreword-by-emily-nagoski-abridged/">Better Sex Through Mindfulness : How Women Can Cultivate Desire &#8211; Lori A. Brotto, Foreword by Emily Nagoski (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Welcoming the Unwelcome : Wholehearted Living in a Brokenhearted World &#8211; Pema Chodron (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/welcoming-the-unwelcome-wholehearted-living-in-a-brokenhearted-world-pema-chodron-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tibetan Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/welcoming-the-unwelcome-wholehearted-living-in-a-brokenhearted-world-pema-chodron-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the bestselling author of When Things Fall Apart, an open-hearted call for human connection, compassion, and learning to love the world just as it is during these most challenging times. In her first new book of spiritual teachings in over seven years, Pema Chödrön offers a combination of wisdom, heartfelt reflections, and the signature [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/welcoming-the-unwelcome-wholehearted-living-in-a-brokenhearted-world-pema-chodron-abridged/">Welcoming the Unwelcome : Wholehearted Living in a Brokenhearted World &#8211; Pema Chodron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the bestselling author of When Things Fall Apart, an open-hearted call for human connection, compassion, and learning to love the world just as it is during these most challenging times.      </p>
<p>                     In her first new book of spiritual teachings in over seven years, Pema Chödrön offers a combination of wisdom, heartfelt reflections, and the signature mix of humor and insight that have made her a beloved figure to turn to during times of change. In an increasingly polarized world, Pema shows us how to strengthen our abilities to find common ground, even when we disagree, and influence our environment in positive ways. Sharing never-before told personal stories from her remarkable life, simple and powerful everyday practices, and directly relatable advice, Pema encourages us all to become triumphant bodhisattvas&#8211;compassionate beings&#8211;in times of hardship.     </p>
<p>                     Welcoming the Unwelcome includes teachings on the true meaning of karma, recognizing the basic goodness in ourselves and the people we share our lives with&#8211;even the most challenging ones, transforming adversity into opportunities for growth, and freeing ourselves from the empty and illusory labels that separate us. Pema also provides step-by-step guides to a basic sitting meditation and a compassion meditation that anyone can use to bring light to the darkness we face, wherever and whatever it may be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/welcoming-the-unwelcome-wholehearted-living-in-a-brokenhearted-world-pema-chodron-abridged/">Welcoming the Unwelcome : Wholehearted Living in a Brokenhearted World &#8211; Pema Chodron (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE LIFE-CHANGING BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD &#8216;A deeply compassionate guide to self-care &#8211; simple and profound&#8217; Sir Kenneth Branagh &#8216;If you want to free yourself from anxiety and stress, and feel truly at ease with yourself, then read this book&#8217; Ruby Wax Authoritative, beautifully written and much-loved by its readers, Mindfulness: A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/">Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE LIFE-CHANGING BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 1.5 MILLION COPIES SOLD    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A deeply compassionate guide to self-care &#8211; simple and profound&#8217; Sir Kenneth Branagh    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you want to free yourself from anxiety and stress, and feel truly at ease with yourself, then read this book&#8217; Ruby Wax    </p>
<p>                    Authoritative, beautifully written and much-loved by its readers, Mindfulness: A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world has become a word-of-mouth bestseller and global phenomenon. It reveals a set of simple yet powerful practices that you can incorporate into daily life to break the cycle of anxiety, stress unhappiness and exhaustion. It promotes the kind of happiness that gets into your bones and allows you to meet the worst that life throws at you with new courage.     </p>
<p>                    Mindfulness is based on mindfulness-based cognitive therapy (MBCT). Co-developed by Professor Mark Williams of Oxford University, MBCT is recommended by the UK&#8217;s National Institute for Health and Care Excellence and is as effective as drugs for preventing depression. But, equally, it works for the rest of us who aren&#8217;t depressed but who are struggling to keep up with the relentless demands of the modern world.     </p>
<p>                    By investing just a few minutes each day, this classic guide to mindfulness will put you back in control of your life once again.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mindfulness-a-practical-guide-to-finding-peace-in-a-frantic-world-professor-mark-williams-dr-danny-penman-abridged/">Mindfulness : A practical guide to finding peace in a frantic world &#8211; Professor Mark Williams, Dr Danny Penman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Daily Stoic : 366 Meditations on Wisdom, Perseverance, and the Art of Living: Featuring new translations of Seneca, Epictetus, and Marcus Aurelius &#8211; Ryan Holiday, Stephen Hanselman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-daily-stoic-366-meditations-on-wisdom-perseverance-and-the-art-of-living-featuring-new-translations-of-seneca-epictetus-and-marcus-aurelius-ryan-holiday-stephen-hanselman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-daily-stoic-366-meditations-on-wisdom-perseverance-and-the-art-of-living-featuring-new-translations-of-seneca-epictetus-and-marcus-aurelius-ryan-holiday-stephen-hanselman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;A generous gift of guidance on modern living culled from a canon of wisdom hatched long ago.&#8217; &#8211; Maria Popova, editor of Brain Pickings &#8216;A richly rewarding spring of practical wisdom to help you focus on what&#8217;s in your control, eliminate false and limiting beliefs, and take more effective action.&#8217; &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-daily-stoic-366-meditations-on-wisdom-perseverance-and-the-art-of-living-featuring-new-translations-of-seneca-epictetus-and-marcus-aurelius-ryan-holiday-stephen-hanselman-abridged/">The Daily Stoic : 366 Meditations on Wisdom, Perseverance, and the Art of Living: Featuring new translations of Seneca, Epictetus, and Marcus Aurelius &#8211; Ryan Holiday, Stephen Hanselman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A generous gift of guidance on modern living culled from a canon of wisdom hatched long ago.&#8217; &#8211; Maria Popova, editor of Brain Pickings    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A richly rewarding spring of practical wisdom to help you focus on what&#8217;s in your control, eliminate false and limiting beliefs, and take more effective action.&#8217; &#8211; Jack Canfield, co-author of The Success PrinciplesT and the Chicken Soup for the Soul (R) series    </p>
<p>                    Daily doses of practical, uplifting philosophy from the bestselling author of The Obstacle is the Way    </p>
<p>                    Where can you find joy? What&#8217;s the true measure of success? How should we manage anger? Find meaning? Conquer grief? The answers to these questions and more lie at the heart of Stoic philosophy.    </p>
<p>                    The Daily Stoic is a wise, calming, page-a-day guide to living a good life, offering inspirational daily doses of classic wisdom. Each page features a powerful quotation from the likes of Emperor Marcus Aurelius, the playwright Seneca, or philosopher Epictetus, as well as historical anecdotes and thought-provoking commentary to help you tackle any problem, approach any goal and find the serenity, self-knowledge and resilience you need to live well.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-daily-stoic-366-meditations-on-wisdom-perseverance-and-the-art-of-living-featuring-new-translations-of-seneca-epictetus-and-marcus-aurelius-ryan-holiday-stephen-hanselman-abridged/">The Daily Stoic : 366 Meditations on Wisdom, Perseverance, and the Art of Living: Featuring new translations of Seneca, Epictetus, and Marcus Aurelius &#8211; Ryan Holiday, Stephen Hanselman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Body Keeps the Score : Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma &#8211; Bessel van der Kolk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trauma & Shock]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;An astonishing and important book. The trauma Bible. I cannot recommend it enough for anyone struggling with&#8230;well&#8230;anything&#8217; Tara Westover The effects of trauma can be devastating for sufferers, their families and future generations. Here one of the world&#8217;s experts on traumatic stress offers a bold new paradigm for treatment, moving [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/">The Body Keeps the Score : Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma &#8211; Bessel van der Kolk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An astonishing and important book. The trauma Bible. I  cannot recommend it enough for anyone struggling with&#8230;well&#8230;anything&#8217; Tara Westover    </p>
<p>                    The effects of trauma can be devastating for sufferers, their families and future generations. Here one of the world&#8217;s experts on traumatic stress offers a bold new paradigm for treatment, moving away from standard talking and drug therapies and towards an alternative approach that heals mind, brain and body.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Dr. van der Kolk&#8217;s masterpiece combines the boundless curiosity of the scientist, the erudition of the scholar, and the passion of the truth teller&#8217; Judith Herman, author of Trauma and Recovery</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-body-keeps-the-score-mind-brain-and-body-in-the-transformation-of-trauma-bessel-van-der-kolk-abridged/">The Body Keeps the Score : Mind, Brain and Body in the Transformation of Trauma &#8211; Bessel van der Kolk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Things You Can See Only When You Slow Down : How to be Calm in a Busy World &#8211; Haemin Sunim, Translated by Chi-Young Kim (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-things-you-can-see-only-when-you-slow-down-how-to-be-calm-in-a-busy-world-haemin-sunim-translated-by-chi-young-kim-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zen Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-things-you-can-see-only-when-you-slow-down-how-to-be-calm-in-a-busy-world-haemin-sunim-translated-by-chi-young-kim-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER, WITH OVER THREE MILLION COPIES SOLD AROUND THE WORLD &#8216;Is it the world that&#8217;s busy, or my mind?&#8217; The world moves fast, but that doesn&#8217;t mean we have to. In this timely guide to mindfulness, Haemin Sunim, a Buddhist monk born in Korea and educated in the United States, offers advice on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-things-you-can-see-only-when-you-slow-down-how-to-be-calm-in-a-busy-world-haemin-sunim-translated-by-chi-young-kim-abridged/">The Things You Can See Only When You Slow Down : How to be Calm in a Busy World &#8211; Haemin Sunim, Translated by Chi-Young Kim (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER, WITH OVER THREE MILLION COPIES SOLD AROUND THE WORLD    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Is it the world that&#8217;s busy, or my mind?&#8217;<br />
                    The world moves fast, but that doesn&#8217;t mean we have to. In this timely guide to mindfulness, Haemin Sunim, a Buddhist monk born in Korea and educated in the United States, offers advice on everything from handling setbacks to dealing with rest and relationships, in a beautiful book combining his teachings with calming full-colour illustrations. Haemin Sunim&#8217;s simple messages speak directly to the anxieties that have become part of modern life and remind us of the strength and joy that come from slowing down.    </p>
<p>                    Hugely popular in Korea, Haemin Sunim is a Zen meditation teacher whose teachings transcend religion, borders and ages. With insight and compassion drawn from a life full of change, the bestselling monk succeeds at encouraging all of us to notice that when you slow down, the world slows down with you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-things-you-can-see-only-when-you-slow-down-how-to-be-calm-in-a-busy-world-haemin-sunim-translated-by-chi-young-kim-abridged/">The Things You Can See Only When You Slow Down : How to be Calm in a Busy World &#8211; Haemin Sunim, Translated by Chi-Young Kim (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wherever You Go There You are &#8211; Jon Kabat-Zinn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-jon-kabat-zinn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Worship, Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-jon-kabat-zinn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>No matter how busy you are, find quiet reflective moments in your life&#8211;and reduce your stress levels drastically&#8211;with this classic bestselling guide from a mindfulness expert. When Wherever You Go, There You Are was first published in 1994, no one could have predicted that the book would launch itself onto bestseller lists nationwide and sell [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-jon-kabat-zinn-abridged/">Wherever You Go There You are &#8211; Jon Kabat-Zinn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No matter how busy you are, find quiet reflective moments in your life&#8211;and reduce your stress levels drastically&#8211;with this classic bestselling guide from a mindfulness expert. When Wherever You Go, There You Are was first published in 1994, no one could have predicted that the book would launch itself onto bestseller lists nationwide and sell over 750,000 copies to date. Ten years later, the book continues to change lives. In honor of the book&#8217;s 10th anniversary, Hyperion is proud to be releasing the book with a new afterword by the author, and to share this wonderful book with an even larger audience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-jon-kabat-zinn-abridged/">Wherever You Go There You are &#8211; Jon Kabat-Zinn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Woo-Woo Works : The Surprising Science Behind Meditation, Reiki, Crystals, and Other Alternative Practices &#8211; Dr David R. Hamilton, PhD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-woo-woo-works-the-surprising-science-behind-meditation-reiki-crystals-and-other-alternative-practices-dr-david-r-hamilton-phd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-woo-woo-works-the-surprising-science-behind-meditation-reiki-crystals-and-other-alternative-practices-dr-david-r-hamilton-phd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why should we meditate? How can crystals heal the mind and body? Why is visualization so powerful &#8211; and so effective? Alternative therapies, healing modalities, and spiritual practices are often referred to as &#8216;woo-woo,&#8217; &#8211; but many of these approaches are actually supported by compelling scientific evidence. In this dynamic and thought-provoking book, David R. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-woo-woo-works-the-surprising-science-behind-meditation-reiki-crystals-and-other-alternative-practices-dr-david-r-hamilton-phd-abridged/">Why Woo-Woo Works : The Surprising Science Behind Meditation, Reiki, Crystals, and Other Alternative Practices &#8211; Dr David R. Hamilton, PhD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why should we meditate? How can crystals heal the mind and body? Why is visualization so powerful &#8211; and so effective?     </p>
<p>                    Alternative therapies, healing modalities, and spiritual practices are often referred to as &#8216;woo-woo,&#8217; &#8211; but many of these approaches are actually supported by compelling scientific evidence.    </p>
<p>                    In this dynamic and thought-provoking book, David R. Hamilton PhD dives deeper into the true nature of consciousness and presents the cutting-edge research behind energy healing, crystals, meditation, and more.    </p>
<p>                    You&#8217;ll discover:<br />
                    *      The science behind some of today&#8217;s most popular alternative practices<br />
                    *      How your thoughts, emotions, and beliefs have healing power<br />
                    *      The benefits of nature and a holistic approach to healing<br />
                    *      A fascinating link between consciousness and human connection<br />
                    *      The relationship between suppressed emotions and disease    </p>
<p>                    The ideas behind some of these holistic therapies have been around for millennia &#8211; but now we have scientific evidence demonstrating how they can contribute to physical, emotional, and energetic healing too.     </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s time to embrace the truth: That woo-woo really does work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-woo-woo-works-the-surprising-science-behind-meditation-reiki-crystals-and-other-alternative-practices-dr-david-r-hamilton-phd-abridged/">Why Woo-Woo Works : The Surprising Science Behind Meditation, Reiki, Crystals, and Other Alternative Practices &#8211; Dr David R. Hamilton, PhD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Monk&#8217;s Guide to Happiness : Meditation in the 21st century &#8211; Gelong Thubten (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-monks-guide-to-happiness-meditation-in-the-21st-century-gelong-thubten-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Worship, Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zen Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-monks-guide-to-happiness-meditation-in-the-21st-century-gelong-thubten-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller FEATURED ON THE DELICIOUSLY ELLA PODCAST We&#8217;re all on a search for happiness, but we&#8217;re looking in the wrong places. Everyone looks externally to find contentment, we think material possessions will unlock our happiness. A Monk&#8217;s Guide to Happiness explains how and why we need to look within, and connect to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-monks-guide-to-happiness-meditation-in-the-21st-century-gelong-thubten-abridged/">A Monk&#8217;s Guide to Happiness : Meditation in the 21st century &#8211; Gelong Thubten (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller    </p>
<p>                    FEATURED ON THE DELICIOUSLY ELLA PODCAST    </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;re all on a search for happiness, but we&#8217;re looking in the wrong places.    </p>
<p>                    Everyone looks externally to find contentment, we think material possessions will unlock our happiness. A Monk&#8217;s Guide to Happiness explains how and why we need to look within, and connect to our true essence, in order to find peace. Everyone has the potential to be happy, after all, we&#8217;re all &#8216;hardwired&#8217; for happiness.    </p>
<p>                    But how do we get there? By meditating. Not just in the morning, but throughout the day by introducing micro moments so we never drop the mindfulness ball, even when we&#8217;re busy. Meditation is more than just a stress-reduction tool or a relaxation therapy, it is the key to finding long-lasting happiness.    </p>
<p>                    Gelong Thubten, a Buddhist monk who has worked with everyone from Silicon Valley entrepreneurs to Ruby Wax and Benedict Cumberbatch, explores the theme of happiness in his debut book and explains how to bring meditation into our busy 21st century lives with simple exercises.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thubten is a very generous and kind monk who writes with the lived honesty and humour of someone who has experienced the wisdom he shares. His writing is full of inspiration but also the pragmatism needed to form a sustainable practice. His book clearly illustrates why we all need meditation and mindfulness in our lives.&#8217; &#8211; Benedict Cumberbatch</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-monks-guide-to-happiness-meditation-in-the-21st-century-gelong-thubten-abridged/">A Monk&#8217;s Guide to Happiness : Meditation in the 21st century &#8211; Gelong Thubten (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Joy on Demand : The Art of Discovering the Happiness Within &#8211; Chade-Meng Tan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/joy-on-demand-the-art-of-discovering-the-happiness-within-chade-meng-tan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/joy-on-demand-the-art-of-discovering-the-happiness-within-chade-meng-tan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A long-awaited follow-up to the New York Times bestselling Search Inside Yourself shows us how to cultivate joy within the context of our fast-paced lives and explains why it is critical to creativity, innovation, confidence, and ultimately success in every arena. In Joy on Demand, Chade-Meng Tan shows that you don&#8217;t need to meditate for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/joy-on-demand-the-art-of-discovering-the-happiness-within-chade-meng-tan-abridged/">Joy on Demand : The Art of Discovering the Happiness Within &#8211; Chade-Meng Tan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A long-awaited follow-up to the New York Times bestselling Search Inside Yourself shows us how to cultivate joy within the context of our fast-paced lives and explains why it is critical to creativity, innovation, confidence, and ultimately success in every arena.  In Joy on Demand, Chade-Meng Tan shows that you don&#8217;t need to meditate for hours, days, months or years to achieve lasting joy-you can actually get consistent access to it in as little as fifteen seconds. Explaining joy and meditation as complementary things that naturally reinforce each other, Meng explains how these two skills form a virtuous cycle, and once put into motion, become a solid practice that can be sustained in daily life.  For many years, meditation has been taught and practiced in cultures where almost all meditators practice full-time for years, resulting in training programs optimized for practitioners with lots of free time and not much else to do but develop profound mastery over the mind.<br />
                    Seeing a disconnect between the traditional practice and the modern world, the bestselling author and Google&#8217;s &#8220;Jolly Good Fellow&#8221; has developed a program, through &#8220;wise laziness,&#8221; to help readers meditate more efficiently and effectively. Meng shares the three pillars of joy (inner peace, insight, and happiness), why joy is the secret is to success, and demonstrates the practical tools anyone can use to cultivate it on demand.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/joy-on-demand-the-art-of-discovering-the-happiness-within-chade-meng-tan-abridged/">Joy on Demand : The Art of Discovering the Happiness Within &#8211; Chade-Meng Tan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Altruism : The Science and Psychology of Kindness &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/altruism-the-science-and-psychology-of-kindness-matthieu-ricard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/altruism-the-science-and-psychology-of-kindness-matthieu-ricard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The concern for the well-being of others could be the saving grace of the 21st century. Matthieu Ricard&#8217;s Altruism, an erudite, brilliantly ranging synthesis of philosophy, psychology and ages old wisdom, is a radical call to kindness, which has the potential as a new global movement to answer the biggest problems of our time: the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/altruism-the-science-and-psychology-of-kindness-matthieu-ricard-abridged/">Altruism : The Science and Psychology of Kindness &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The concern for the well-being of others could be the saving grace of the 21st century. Matthieu Ricard&#8217;s Altruism, an erudite, brilliantly ranging synthesis of philosophy, psychology and ages old wisdom, is a radical call to kindness, which has the potential as a new global movement to answer the biggest problems of our time: the economy in the short term, life satisfaction in the mid-term, and the environment in the long term. As the faultlines of inequality and nationalism leave us ever more divided, Ricard challenges us to be better people &#8211; and in the process, make the world a better place.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/altruism-the-science-and-psychology-of-kindness-matthieu-ricard-abridged/">Altruism : The Science and Psychology of Kindness &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
