<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Philosophy: Logic Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/philosophy-logic/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/philosophy-logic/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Philosophy: Logic Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/philosophy-logic/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Art of Logic : How to Make Sense in a World that Doesn&#8217;t &#8211; Eugenia Cheng (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-logic-how-to-make-sense-in-a-world-that-doesnt-eugenia-cheng-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematical Logic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Logic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-logic-how-to-make-sense-in-a-world-that-doesnt-eugenia-cheng-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For thousands of years, mathematicians have used the timeless art of logic to see the world more clearly. In The Art of Logic, Royal Society Science Book Prize nominee Eugenia Cheng shows how anyone can think like a mathematician &#8211; and see, argue and think better. Learn how to simplify complex decisions without over-simplifying them. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-logic-how-to-make-sense-in-a-world-that-doesnt-eugenia-cheng-abridged/">The Art of Logic : How to Make Sense in a World that Doesn&#8217;t &#8211; Eugenia Cheng (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For thousands of years, mathematicians have used the timeless art of logic to see the world more clearly. In The Art of Logic, Royal Society Science Book Prize nominee Eugenia Cheng shows how anyone can think like a mathematician &#8211; and see, argue and think better.    </p>
<p>                    Learn how to simplify complex decisions without over-simplifying them. Discover the power of analogies and the dangers of false equivalences. Find out how people construct misleading arguments, and how we can argue back.    </p>
<p>                    Eugenia Cheng teaches us how to find clarity without losing nuance, taking a careful scalpel to the complexities of politics, privilege, sexism and dozens of other real-world situations. Her Art of Logic is a practical and inspiring guide to decoding the modern world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-logic-how-to-make-sense-in-a-world-that-doesnt-eugenia-cheng-abridged/">The Art of Logic : How to Make Sense in a World that Doesn&#8217;t &#8211; Eugenia Cheng (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Logic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why do Internet, financial service, and beer commercials dominate Super Bowl advertising? How do political ceremonies establish authority? Why does repetition characterize anthems and ritual speech? Why were circular forms favored for public festivals during the French Revolution? This book answers these questions using a single concept: common knowledge. Game theory shows that in order [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/">Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why do Internet, financial service, and beer commercials dominate Super Bowl advertising? How do political ceremonies establish authority? Why does repetition characterize anthems and ritual speech? Why were circular forms favored for public festivals during the French Revolution? This book answers these questions using a single concept: common knowledge. Game theory shows that in order to coordinate its actions, a group of people must form &#8220;common knowledge.&#8221; Each person wants to participate only if others also participate. Members must have knowledge of each other, knowledge of that knowledge, knowledge of the knowledge of that knowledge, and so on. Michael Chwe applies this insight, with striking erudition, to analyze a range of rituals across history and cultures. He shows that public ceremonies are powerful not simply because they transmit meaning from a central source to each audience member but because they let audience members know what other members know. For instance, people watching the Super Bowl know that many others are seeing precisely what they see and that those people know in turn that many others are also watching.<br />
                    This creates common knowledge, and advertisers selling products that depend on consensus are willing to pay large sums to gain access to it. Remarkably, a great variety of rituals and ceremonies, such as formal inaugurations, work in much the same way. By using a rational-choice argument to explain diverse cultural practices, Chwe argues for a close reciprocal relationship between the perspectives of rationality and culture. He illustrates how game theory can be applied to an unexpectedly broad spectrum of problems, while showing in an admirably clear way what game theory might hold for scholars in the social sciences and humanities who are not yet acquainted with it. In a new afterword, Chwe delves into new applications of common knowledge, both in the real world and in experiments, and considers how generating common knowledge has become easier in the digital age.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/">Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
