<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>E-commerce: Business Aspects Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/e-commerce-business-aspects/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/e-commerce-business-aspects/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>E-commerce: Business Aspects Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/e-commerce-business-aspects/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Chaos Monkeys : Inside the Silicon Valley Money Machine &#8211; Antonio Garcia Martinez</title>
		<link>/chaos-monkeys-inside-the-silicon-valley-money-machine-antonio-garcia-martinez/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chaos-monkeys-inside-the-silicon-valley-money-machine-antonio-garcia-martinez/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER An adrenaline-fuelled expose of life inside the tech bubble, Chaos Monkeys lays bare the secrets, power plays and lifestyle excesses of the visionaries, grunts, sociopaths, opportunists and money cowboys who are revolutionising our world. Written by startup CEO and industry provocateur Antonio Garcia Martinez, this is Liar&#8217;s Poker meets The Social [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chaos-monkeys-inside-the-silicon-valley-money-machine-antonio-garcia-martinez/">Chaos Monkeys : Inside the Silicon Valley Money Machine &#8211; Antonio Garcia Martinez</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    An adrenaline-fuelled expose of life inside the tech bubble, Chaos Monkeys lays bare the secrets, power plays and lifestyle excesses of the visionaries, grunts, sociopaths, opportunists and money cowboys who are revolutionising our world. Written by startup CEO and industry provocateur Antonio Garcia Martinez, this is Liar&#8217;s Poker meets The Social Network. </p>
<p>                    Computer engineers use &#8216;chaos monkey&#8217; software to wreak havoc and test system robustness. Similarly, tech entrepreneurs like Antonio Garcia Martinez are society&#8217;s chaos monkeys &#8211; their innovations disrupt every aspect of our lives, from transportation (Uber) and holidays (Airbnb) to television (Netflix) and dating (Tinder) &#8211; all in search of the perfect business miracle.  </p>
<p>                    Describing himself as &#8216;high-strung, fast-talking, and wired on a combination of caffeine, fear, and greed at all times&#8217;, Garcia Martinez left Wall Street to make his fortune in Silicon Valley, becoming CEO of his own startup, before bailing and being poached by Facebook&#8217;s nascent advertising team. Here he turned users&#8217; data into profit for COO Sheryl Sandberg and chairman and CEO Mark &#8216;Zuck&#8217; Zuckerberg. Forced out of Facebook in the wake of a bitter internal product war, Garcia Martinez  took his unique brand of entrepreneurial hyperactivity to rivals Twitter. Along the way, he got into a lot of trouble with a lot of people, brewed illegal beer on the Facebook campus (accidentally flooding Zuckerberg&#8217;s desk), lived on a yacht, raced sport cars on the highway, and enthusiastically pursued the lifestyle of an overpaid Silicon Valley mercenary.</p>
<p>                    In Chaos Monkeys he tells you HOW &#8211; and HOW NOT &#8211; to make a fortune through startups and digital marketing.  Highly entertaining and always offering genuine insight, Garcia Martinez  unravels the chaotic evolution of social media and online marketing. From startups and credit derivatives to Big Brother and data tracking, social media monetisation and digital &#8216;privacy&#8217;, he shares both his scathing observations and outrageous antics, taking us on a subversive and very funny tour of the fascinatingly insular and unbelievably wealthy tech industry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chaos-monkeys-inside-the-silicon-valley-money-machine-antonio-garcia-martinez/">Chaos Monkeys : Inside the Silicon Valley Money Machine &#8211; Antonio Garcia Martinez</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Thank You Economy &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</title>
		<link>/the-thank-you-economy-gary-vaynerchuk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-thank-you-economy-gary-vaynerchuk/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Thank You Economy isn&#8217;t some abstract concept or wacky business strategy. It&#8217;s the way we buy and sell, the way we&#8217;re interacting as consumers, as employees, as entrepreneurs on all levels, right now. The way our marketplace functions has been evolving right before our eyes. Top-down, one-way exchanges are gone, replaced by relationships based [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-thank-you-economy-gary-vaynerchuk/">The Thank You Economy &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Thank You Economy isn&#8217;t some abstract concept or wacky business strategy. It&#8217;s the way we buy and sell, the way we&#8217;re interacting as consumers, as employees, as entrepreneurs on all levels, right now. The way our marketplace functions has been evolving right before our eyes. Top-down, one-way exchanges are gone, replaced by relationships based on open, honest, and constant communication between customers and business. Today, individuals and brands that out-care and out-love their competition &#8211; those emphasising quality, value, responsiveness, and attention to detail, among other essentials &#8211; see the biggest returns. Gary Vaynerchuk contends that the people and companies harnessing the word-of-mouth power provided by multiplatform media &#8211; those that can shift their outlook and operations to be more customer-aware and fan-friendly &#8211; will pull away from the pack and profit in today&#8217;s markets. In &#8220;The Thank You Economy&#8221;, he dissects the companies on the leading edge, showing how they are succeeding &#8211; and sometimes failing.<br />
                    Laying out the ideas and insight that support this enormous change, Vaynerchuk explores these emerging connections &#8211; from consumer to consumer and business to business and everything in between. Passionate and persuasive, he reminds us that, surviving and thriving today it takes more than just hard work-it takes a heartfelt thanks to those who make it possible.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-thank-you-economy-gary-vaynerchuk/">The Thank You Economy &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crush It! : Why NOW Is the Time to Cash In on Your Passion &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</title>
		<link>/crush-it-why-now-is-the-time-to-cash-in-on-your-passion-gary-vaynerchuk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crush-it-why-now-is-the-time-to-cash-in-on-your-passion-gary-vaynerchuk/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you have a hobby you wish you could do all day? An obsession that keeps you up at night? Now is the perfect time to take those passions and make a living doing what you love. In Crush It! Why Now Is The Time To Cash In On Your Passion, Gary Vaynerchuk shows you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crush-it-why-now-is-the-time-to-cash-in-on-your-passion-gary-vaynerchuk/">Crush It! : Why NOW Is the Time to Cash In on Your Passion &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you have a hobby you wish you could do all day? An obsession that keeps you up at night? Now is the perfect time to take those passions and make a living doing what you love. In Crush It! Why Now Is The Time To Cash In On Your Passion, Gary Vaynerchuk shows you how to use the power of the Internet to turn your real interests into real businesses. Gary spent years building his family business from a local wine shop into a national industry leader. Then one day he turned on a video camera, and by using the secrets revealed in this book, transformed his entire life and earning potential by building his personal brand. By the end of this book, any reader will have learned how to harness the power of the Internet to make their entrepreneurial dreams come true. Step by step, Crush It! is the ultimate driver&#8217;s manual for modern business. Gary Vaynerchuk has captured attention with his pioneering, multi-faceted approach to personal branding and business.<br />
                    After primarily utilizing traditional advertising techniques to build his family&#8217;s local retail wine business into a national industry leader, Gary rapidly leveraged social media tools such as Twitter and Facebook to promote Wine Library TV. Gary has always had an early-to-market approach, launching Wine Library&#8217;s retail website in 1997 and Wine Library TV in February of 2006. His lessons on social media, passion, transparency, and reactionary business are not to be missed!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crush-it-why-now-is-the-time-to-cash-in-on-your-passion-gary-vaynerchuk/">Crush It! : Why NOW Is the Time to Cash In on Your Passion &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising. For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                     A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising.     </p>
<p>                     For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup founder, a small business owner, or part of a large corporation.     </p>
<p>                     No matter what your product or service, this book will help you reframe how it&#8217;s presented to the world, in order to meaningfully connect with people who want it. Seth employs his signature blend of insight, observation, and memorable examples to teach you:    </p>
<p>                     * How to build trust and permission with your target market.<br />
                     * The art of positioning&#8211;deciding not only who it&#8217;s for, but who it&#8217;s not for.<br />
                     * Why the best way to achieve your goals is to help others become who they want to be.<br />
                     * Why the old approaches to advertising and branding no longer work.<br />
                     * The surprising role of tension in any decision to buy (or not).<br />
                     * How marketing is at its core about the stories we tell ourselves about our social status.    </p>
<p>                     You can do work that matters for people who care. This book shows you the way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This Is Marketing is a very accessible way into Godin&#8217;s thinking&#8230;. Godin writes in pacy, jargon-free prose and this book is interesting and useful for anyone who wants an insight into how, and why, we buy things or change our habits in any way.&#8221; &#8211; The Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed reading this, check out Seth Godin&#8217;s Purple Cow, a true business classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Life After Google : The Fall of Big Data and the Rise of the Blockchain Economy &#8211; George Gilder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE MONTH FROM THE WALL STREET JOURNAL: &#8220;Nothing Mr. Gilder says or writes is ever delivered at anything less than the fullest philosophical decibel&#8230; Mr. Gilder sounds less like a tech guru than a poet, and his words tumble out in a romantic cascade.&#8221; &#8220;Google&#8217;s algorithms assume the world&#8217;s future [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/">Life After Google : The Fall of Big Data and the Rise of the Blockchain Economy &#8211; George Gilder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE MONTH      </p>
<p>                     FROM THE WALL STREET JOURNAL: &#8220;Nothing Mr. Gilder says or writes is ever delivered at anything less than the fullest philosophical decibel&#8230; Mr. Gilder sounds less like a tech guru than a poet, and his words tumble out in a romantic cascade.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Google&#8217;s algorithms assume the world&#8217;s future is nothing more than the next moment in a random process. George Gilder shows how deep this assumption goes, what motivates people to make it, and why it&#8217;s wrong: the future depends on human action.&#8221; &#8212; Peter Thiel, founder of PayPal and Palantir Technologies and author of Zero to One: Notes on Startups, or How to Build the Future     </p>
<p>                     The Age of Google, built on big data and machine intelligence, has been an awesome era. But it&#8217;s coming to an end. In Life after Google, George Gilder&#8211;the peerless visionary of technology and culture&#8211;explains why Silicon Valley is suffering a nervous breakdown and what to expect as the post-Google age dawns.     </p>
<p>                     Google&#8217;s astonishing ability to &#8220;search and sort&#8221; attracts the entire world to its search engine and countless other goodies&#8211;videos, maps, email, calendars&#8230;.And everything it offers is free, or so it seems. Instead of paying directly, users submit to advertising. The system of &#8220;aggregate and advertise&#8221; works&#8211;for a while&#8211;if you control an empire of data centers, but a market without prices strangles entrepreneurship and turns the Internet into a wasteland of ads.     </p>
<p>                     The crisis is not just economic. Even as advances in artificial intelligence induce delusions of omnipotence and transcendence, Silicon Valley has pretty much given up on security. The Internet firewalls supposedly protecting all those passwords and personal information have proved hopelessly permeable.     </p>
<p>                     The crisis cannot be solved within the current computer and network architecture. The future lies with the &#8220;cryptocosm&#8221;&#8211;the new architecture of the blockchain and its derivatives. Enabling cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin and ether, NEO and Hashgraph, it will provide the Internet a secure global payments system, ending the aggregate-and-advertise Age of Google.     </p>
<p>                     Silicon Valley, long dominated by a few giants, faces a &#8220;great unbundling,&#8221; which will disperse computer power and commerce and transform the economy and the Internet.     </p>
<p>                     Life after Google is almost here.     </p>
<p>                     For fans of &#8220;Wealth and Poverty,&#8221; &#8220;Knowledge and Power,&#8221; and &#8220;The Scandal of Money.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/">Life After Google : The Fall of Big Data and the Rise of the Blockchain Economy &#8211; George Gilder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s Not the Size of the Data &#8212; It&#8217;s How You Use It : Smarter Marketing with Analytics and Dashboards &#8211; Koen Pauwels (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/its-not-the-size-of-the-data-its-how-you-use-it-smarter-marketing-with-analytics-and-dashboards-koen-pauwels-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Enterprise Software]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/its-not-the-size-of-the-data-its-how-you-use-it-smarter-marketing-with-analytics-and-dashboards-koen-pauwels-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Did you know that your business already has the world&#8217;s greatest information-tracking team working tirelessly for you 24/7 to gather all the info you could possibly need to find your next customers? Between brand tracking, CRM programs, and online behavior tracking, as well as the always-dependable trade shows and satisfaction studies, mounds of marketing metrics [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-not-the-size-of-the-data-its-how-you-use-it-smarter-marketing-with-analytics-and-dashboards-koen-pauwels-abridged/">It&#8217;s Not the Size of the Data &#8212; It&#8217;s How You Use It : Smarter Marketing with Analytics and Dashboards &#8211; Koen Pauwels (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Did you know that your business already has the world&#8217;s greatest information-tracking team working tirelessly for you 24/7 to gather all the info you could possibly need to find your next customers? Between brand tracking, CRM programs, and online behavior tracking, as well as the always-dependable trade shows and satisfaction studies, mounds of marketing metrics are being generated for you across various touchpoints and channels. The numbers available to you are mind-blowing&#8211;but the amount itself can be mind-numbing. Where can one begin to filter through it all to find what is most beneficial for their company? Locked in the vast quantity of information are accurate, data-driven answers to every marketing question&#8211;and analytic dashboards are the key to finding it all. In It&#8217;s Not the Size of the Data&#8211;It&#8217;s How You Use It, marketing expert Koen Pauwels introduces readers to these transformative web-based tools that gather, synthesize, and visually display essential data in real time, directly connecting marketing with performance. He then supplies a simple yet rigorous methodology that explains step by step how to: &#8211; Gain crucial IT support &#8211; Build a rock-solid database &#8211; Select key leading performance indicators &#8211; Design the optimal dashboard layout &#8211; Use marketing analytics to improve decisions and reap rewards There is simply too much customer-produced information out there today for marketing teams to go with gut decisions or the same old standbys. Dashboard analytics will bring scientific precision and insight to the marketing efforts of any size organization, in any industry, and turn this eye-popping data into a specific plan of attack.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-not-the-size-of-the-data-its-how-you-use-it-smarter-marketing-with-analytics-and-dashboards-koen-pauwels-abridged/">It&#8217;s Not the Size of the Data &#8212; It&#8217;s How You Use It : Smarter Marketing with Analytics and Dashboards &#8211; Koen Pauwels (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You Should Test That : Conversion Optimization for More Leads, Sales and Profit or The Art and Science of Optimized Marketing &#8211; Chris Goward (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to convert website visitors into customers Part science and part art, conversion optimization is designed to turn visitors into customers. Carefully developed testing procedures are necessary to help you fine-tune images, headlines, navigation, colors, buttons, and every other element, creating a website that encourages visitors to take the action you seek. This book [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/">You Should Test That : Conversion Optimization for More Leads, Sales and Profit or The Art and Science of Optimized Marketing &#8211; Chris Goward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to convert website visitors into customers Part science and part art, conversion optimization is designed to turn visitors into customers. Carefully developed testing procedures are necessary to help you fine-tune images, headlines, navigation, colors, buttons, and every other element, creating a website that encourages visitors to take the action you seek. This book guides you through creating an optimization strategy that supports your business goals, using appropriate analytics tools, generating quality testing ideas, running online experiments, and making the adjustments that work.<br />
                    * Conversion optimization is part science and part art; this guide provides step-by-step guidance to help you optimize your website for maximum conversion rates * Explains how to analyze data, prioritize experiment opportunities, and choose the right testing methods * Helps you learn what to adjust, how to do it, and how to analyze the results * Features hands-on exercises, case studies, and a full-color insert reinforcing key tactics * Author has used these techniques to assist Fortune 500 clients You Should Test That explains both the &#8220;why&#8221; and the &#8220;how&#8221; of conversion optimization, helping you maximize the value of your website.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/">You Should Test That : Conversion Optimization for More Leads, Sales and Profit or The Art and Science of Optimized Marketing &#8211; Chris Goward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dragonfly Effect : Quick, Effective, and Powerful Ways To Use Social Media to Drive Social Change &#8211; Jennifer Aaker, Andy Smith, Carlye Adler, Dan Ariely, Foreword by Chip Heath (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-dragonfly-effect-quick-effective-and-powerful-ways-to-use-social-media-to-drive-social-change-jennifer-aaker-andy-smith-carlye-adler-dan-ariely-foreword-by-chip-heath-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dragonfly-effect-quick-effective-and-powerful-ways-to-use-social-media-to-drive-social-change-jennifer-aaker-andy-smith-carlye-adler-dan-ariely-foreword-by-chip-heath-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for harnessing the power of social media to drive social change Many books teach the mechanics of using Facebook, Twitter, and YouTube to compete in business. But no book addresses how to harness the incredible power of social media to make a difference. The Dragonfly Effect shows you how to tap social media [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dragonfly-effect-quick-effective-and-powerful-ways-to-use-social-media-to-drive-social-change-jennifer-aaker-andy-smith-carlye-adler-dan-ariely-foreword-by-chip-heath-abridged/">The Dragonfly Effect : Quick, Effective, and Powerful Ways To Use Social Media to Drive Social Change &#8211; Jennifer Aaker, Andy Smith, Carlye Adler, Dan Ariely, Foreword by Chip Heath (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for harnessing the power of social media to drive social change Many books teach the mechanics of using Facebook, Twitter, and YouTube to compete in business. But no book addresses how to harness the incredible power of social media to make a difference. The Dragonfly Effect shows you how to tap social media and consumer psychological insights to achieve a single, concrete goal.<br />
                    Named for the only insect that is able to move in any direction when its four wings are working in concert, this book * Reveals the four &#8220;wings&#8221; of the Dragonfly Effect-and how they work together to produce colossal results * Features original case studies of global organizations like the Gap, Starbucks, Kiva, Nike, eBay, Facebook; and start-ups like Groupon and COOKPAD, showing how they achieve social good and customer loyalty * Leverage the power of design thinking and psychological research with practical strategies * Reveals how everyday people achieve unprecedented results-whether finding an almost impossible bone marrow match for a friend, raising millions for cancer research, or electing the current president of the United States The Dragonfly Effect shows that you don&#8217;t need money or power to inspire seismic change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dragonfly-effect-quick-effective-and-powerful-ways-to-use-social-media-to-drive-social-change-jennifer-aaker-andy-smith-carlye-adler-dan-ariely-foreword-by-chip-heath-abridged/">The Dragonfly Effect : Quick, Effective, and Powerful Ways To Use Social Media to Drive Social Change &#8211; Jennifer Aaker, Andy Smith, Carlye Adler, Dan Ariely, Foreword by Chip Heath (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge    </p>
<p>                    With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. This clear, concise, and accessible guide from two industry insiders shows you how to navigate this brave new blockchain world-and how to invest in these emerging assets to secure your financial future.    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets gives you all the tools you need:    </p>
<p>                    * An actionable framework for investigating and valuing cryptoassets     </p>
<p>                    * Portfolio management techniques to maximize returns while managing risk    </p>
<p>                    * Historical context and tips to navigate inevitable bubbles and manias    </p>
<p>                    * Practical guides to exchanges, wallets, capital market vehicles, and ICOs    </p>
<p>                    * Predictions on how blockchain technology may disrupt current portfolios    </p>
<p>                    In addition to offering smart investment strategies, this authoritative resource will help you understand how these assets were created, how they work, and how they are evolving amid the blockchain revolution. The authors define a clear and original cryptoasset taxonomy, composed of cryptocurrencies, cryptocommodities, and cryptotokens, with insights into how each subset is blending technology and markets. You&#8217;ll find a variety of methods to invest in these assets, whether through global exchanges that trade 24/7 or initial cryptoasset offerings (ICOs). By sequentially building on the concepts of each prior chapter, the book will provide you with a full understanding of the cryptoasset economy and the opportunities that await the innovative investor .    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets represent the future of money and markets. This book is your guide to that future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crushing It! : How Great Entrepreneurs Build Business and Influence &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crushing-it-how-great-entrepreneurs-build-business-and-influence-and-how-you-can-too-gary-vaynerchuk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crushing-it-how-great-entrepreneurs-build-business-and-influence-and-how-you-can-too-gary-vaynerchuk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Four-time New York Times bestselling author Gary Vaynerchuk offers new lessons and inspiration drawn from the experiences of dozens of influencers and entrepreneurs who rejected the predictable corporate path in favor of pursuing their dreams by building thriving businesses and extraordinary personal brands. In his 2009 international bestseller Crush It, Gary insisted that a vibrant [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crushing-it-how-great-entrepreneurs-build-business-and-influence-and-how-you-can-too-gary-vaynerchuk-abridged/">Crushing It! : How Great Entrepreneurs Build Business and Influence &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Four-time New York Times bestselling author Gary Vaynerchuk offers new lessons and inspiration drawn from the experiences of dozens of influencers and entrepreneurs who rejected the predictable corporate path in favor of pursuing their dreams by building thriving businesses and extraordinary personal brands.    </p>
<p>                    In his 2009 international bestseller Crush It, Gary insisted that a vibrant personal brand was crucial to entrepreneurial success, In Crushing It!, Gary explains why that’s even more true today, offering his unique perspective on what has changed and what principles remain timeless. He also shares stories from other entrepreneurs who have grown wealthier—and not just financially—than they ever imagined possible by following Crush It principles. The secret to their success (and Gary’s) has everything to do with their understanding of the social media platforms, and their willingness to do whatever it took to make these tools work to their utmost potential. That’s what Crushing It! teaches readers to do.    </p>
<p>                    In this lively, practical, and inspiring book, Gary dissects every current major social media platform so that anyone, from a plumber to a professional ice skater, will know exactly how to amplify his or her personal brand on each. He offers both theoretical and tactical advice on how to become the biggest thing on old standbys like Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, Pinterest, and Snapchat; podcast platforms like Spotify, Soundcloud, iHeartRadio, and iTunes; and other emerging platforms such as Musical.ly. For those with more experience, Crushing It! illuminates some little-known nuances and provides innovative tips and clever tweaks proven to enhance more common tried-and-true strategies.    </p>
<p>                    Crushing It! is a state-of-the-art guide to building your own path to professional and financial success, but it’s not about getting rich. It’s a blueprint to living life on your own terms.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crushing-it-how-great-entrepreneurs-build-business-and-influence-and-how-you-can-too-gary-vaynerchuk-abridged/">Crushing It! : How Great Entrepreneurs Build Business and Influence &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>User experience (UX) strategy lies at the intersection of UX design and business strategy, but until now, there hasn&#8217;t been an easy-to-apply framework for executing it. This hands-on guide introduces lightweight product strategy tools and techniques to help you and your team devise innovative digital solutions that people want. Author Jaime Levy shows UX/UI designers, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/">UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>User experience (UX) strategy lies at the intersection of UX design and business strategy, but until now, there hasn&#8217;t been an easy-to-apply framework for executing it. This hands-on guide introduces lightweight product strategy tools and techniques to help you and your team devise innovative digital solutions that people want.    </p>
<p>                    Author Jaime Levy shows UX/UI designers, product managers, entrepreneurs, and aspiring strategists simple to advanced methods that can be applied right away. You&#8217;ll gain valuable perspective through business cases and historical context. This second edition includes new real-world examples, updated techniques, and a chapter on conducting qualitative online user research.    </p>
<p>                    Define value propositions and validate target users through provisional personas and customer discovery techniques<br />
                    Explore marketplace opportunities by conducting competitive research and analysis<br />
                    Design experiments using rapid prototypes that are focused on the business model<br />
                    Conduct online user research to gain valuable insights quickly on any budget<br />
                    Test business ideas and validate marketing channels by running online advertising and landing page campaigns</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/">UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Visual Storytelling: How to Use Visuals, Videos, and Social Media to Market Your Brand &#8211; Ekaterina Walter, Jessica Gioglio (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Attention is the new commodity. Visual Storytelling is the new currency. Human brain processes visuals 60,000x faster than text.Web posts with visuals drive up to 180% more engagement than those without.Viewers spend 100% more time on web pages with videos. Filled with full-color images and thought-provoking examples from leading companies, The Power of Visual Storytelling [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/">The Power of Visual Storytelling: How to Use Visuals, Videos, and Social Media to Market Your Brand &#8211; Ekaterina Walter, Jessica Gioglio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Attention is the new commodity. Visual Storytelling is the new currency.    </p>
<p>                    Human brain processes visuals 60,000x faster than text.Web posts with visuals drive up to 180% more engagement than those without.Viewers spend 100% more time on web pages with videos.<br />
                    Filled with full-color images and thought-provoking examples from leading companies, The Power of Visual Storytelling explains how to grow your business and strengthen your brand by leveraging photos, videos, infographics, presentations, and other rich media. The book delivers a powerful road map for getting started, while inspiring new levels of creativity within organizations of all types and sizes.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book is not only a complete overview of [visual storytelling] but, most importantly, the key to doing it right, a total Right Hook!&#8221;<br />
                    -Gary Vaynerchuk, New York Times bestselling author of Crush It! and Jab, Jab, Jab, Right Hook    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A valuable guide to understanding how to develop powerful marketing programs using the art of visual storytelling.&#8221;<br />
                    -Guy Kawasaki, author of APE: Author, Publisher, Entrepreneur and former chief evangelist of Apple    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The Power of Visual Storytelling is the new marketing bible!&#8221;<br />
                    -Nancy Bhagat, Vice President, Global Marketing Strategy and Campaigns, Intel    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If a picture is worth a thousand words, The Power of Visual Storytelling is worth a million.&#8221;<br />
                    -Scott Monty, Global Digital &#038; Multimedia Communications for Ford Motor Company</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-visual-storytelling-how-to-use-visuals-videos-and-social-media-to-market-your-brand-ekaterina-walter-jessica-gioglio-abridged/">The Power of Visual Storytelling: How to Use Visuals, Videos, and Social Media to Market Your Brand &#8211; Ekaterina Walter, Jessica Gioglio (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Epic Content Marketing: How to Tell a Different Story, Break through the Clutter, and Win More Customers by Marketing Less &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of FORTUNE Magazine&#8217;s Top 5 Business Book Must-Reads How do you cut through the noise, commotion, and bad information that is right now cluttering up your customers&#8217; digital space? EPIC CONTENT MARKETINGOne of the world&#8217;s leading experts on content marketing, Joe Pulizzi explains how to attract prospects and customers by creating information and content [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Epic Content Marketing: How to Tell a Different Story, Break through the Clutter, and Win More Customers by Marketing Less &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of FORTUNE Magazine&#8217;s Top 5 Business Book Must-Reads How do you cut through the noise, commotion, and bad information that is right now cluttering up your customers&#8217; digital space?    </p>
<p>                    EPIC CONTENT MARKETINGOne of the world&#8217;s leading experts on content marketing, Joe Pulizzi explains how to attract prospects and customers by creating information and content they actually want to engage with. No longer can we interrupt our customers with mediocre content and sales messages they don&#8217;t care about.    </p>
<p>                    Epic Content Marketing takes you step-by-stepthrough the process of developing stories that inform and entertain and compel customers to act&#8211;without actually telling them to. Epic content, distributed to the right person at the right time, is the way to truly capture the hearts and minds of customers. It&#8217;s how to position your business as a trusted expert in its industry. It&#8217;s what customers share and talk about.    </p>
<p>                    Once we hook customers with epic content, they reward us by sending our sales through the roof.    </p>
<p>                    Epic Content Marketing provides everything youneed to:    </p>
<p>                    Determine what your content niche should be to attract and retain customersDiscover and develop your content marketing mission statementSet up a process for creating and curating epic contentLearn how to leverage social and e-mail channels to create&#8211;and grow&#8211;your audienceMeasure the performance of your content&#8211;and increase your content marketing budget    </p>
<p>                    With in-depth case studies of how John Deere, LEGO, Coca-Cola, and other leading corporations are using content to drive epic sales, this groundbreaking guide gives you all the tools to start creating and disseminating content that leads directly to greater profits and growth.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re the CMO of a Fortune 500, a digital marketer, or an entrepreneur, Epic Content Marketing gives you the tools you need to vanquish the competition. Start your epic journey now!    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR EPIC CONTENT MARKETING&#8221;From the man who invented content marketing. Listen to this guy. He really understands the new world of marketing. The concepts in Epic Content Marketing are usable all over the world&#8211;instantly usable and useful for any business.&#8221; &#8212; Don Schultz, the &#8220;father of integrated marketing,&#8221; Professor Emeritus at Northwestern University&#8217;s Medill School of Journalism, and author of 13 books    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Joe Pulizzi&#8217;s ideas are so consistently . . . well, epic (!) that they really don&#8217;t need any endorsement by anyone. But here&#8217;s mine anyway: You don&#8217;t need MORE content. You need the right kind of content,strategically applied. For those organizations struggling to create a content marketing program that drives results, Joe delivers. Again.&#8221; &#8212; Ann Handley, coauthor of Content Rules and Chief Content Officer, MarketingProfs    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;As Joe shows us in his wonderful Epic Content Marketing, you must unlearn interrupting people with your nonsense. Instead, publish the valuable content they want to consume and are eager to share.&#8221; &#8212; David Meerman Scott, marketing strategist and bestselling author ofThe New Rules of Marketing and PR    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This is a brilliant canter through the rapid and ever-changing world of content marketing. Joe has managed to capture the right blend of art and science as he plots the major trends impacting all marketers right now.&#8221; &#8212; Jonathan Mildenhall, VP, Global Advertising Strategy and Creative Excellence, Coca-Cola Company    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You could say that Joe Pulizzi wrote the book on content marketing, but now it&#8217;s more than just a saying.It&#8217;s what you&#8217;re holding in your hands. If you truly want to be successful at content marketing, Pulizzi is one of the few who can show you the way.&#8221; &#8212; Mitch Joel, President, Twist Image, and author of Six Pixels of Separation and CTRL ALT Delete    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Joe Pulizzi may know more about content marketing than any person alive. He proves it in these pages.&#8221; &#8212; Jay Baer, New York Times bestselling author of Youtility: Why Smart Marketing is About Help Not Hype    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The future of successful brand building, and especially the art of solidifying the emotional connection between people and brands, will require expertise in Content Marketing. Epic Content Marketing gives all the details practitioners need without overcomplicating.&#8221; &#8212; Professor JoAnn Sciarrino, Knight Chair, Digital Advertising and Marketing, UNC Chapel Hill    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Joe Pulizzi is the godfather of our burgeoning profession of Content Marketing. He lays out the objectives, principles, and core strategies of our field in a way that&#8217;s easy-to-understand, inspiring, and entertaining. If your company doesn&#8217;t yet realize that it&#8217;s a media company, with all the challenges and advantages that implies, you&#8217;re missing the most powerful way to connect with your customers.&#8221; &#8212; Julie Fleischer, Director, Media &#038; Consumer Engagement, Kraft Foods</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-content-marketing-how-to-tell-a-different-story-break-through-the-clutter-and-win-more-customers-by-marketing-less-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Epic Content Marketing: How to Tell a Different Story, Break through the Clutter, and Win More Customers by Marketing Less &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated for the post-COVID economy! The proven low-risk, cost-effective way to launch a successful business Today&#8217;s markets are getting more and more dynamic, and customers are increasingly fickle. Meanwhile the COVID-driven economic crash has made mitigating financial risk more important than ever. From one of today&#8217;s leading experts in content marketing, Content Inc. is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated for the post-COVID economy! The proven low-risk, cost-effective way to launch a successful business     </p>
<p>                    Today&#8217;s markets are getting more and more dynamic, and customers are increasingly fickle. Meanwhile the COVID-driven economic crash has made mitigating financial risk more important than ever.    </p>
<p>                    From one of today&#8217;s leading experts in content marketing, Content Inc. is the go-to guide to building a solid small-business by establishing a loyal audience before you sell any products or services. In these pages, Joe Pulizzi provides a lower-risk, better way to build a successful business by re-engineering the process that so often leads to failure: You&#8217;ll learn how to develop valuable content, build an audience around that content-and then create a product for that audience. Content Inc. walks you through the entire process, showing how to    </p>
<p>                    Identify the intersection of your expertise and your future customer&#8217;s needs<br />
                    Determine how to &#8220;tilt&#8221; your sweet spot to find a place where little or no competition exists<br />
                    Establish your number-one channel for disseminating content (blog, podcast, YouTube, etc.)<br />
                    Use social-media and SEO to convert one-time visitors into long-term subscribers<br />
                    Grow your business by expanding into multiple delivery channels<br />
                    Monetize your product or service for ultimate business success<br />
                    Understand how to sell your content asset for millions or build the business into a large enterprise    </p>
<p>                    This fully updated edition includes new and enhanced coverage of platforms like TikTok, SnapChat, and Instagram, a new section about the exit strategy for the model, more practical how-tos, and current examples of companies that have successfully implemented these strategies.      </p>
<p>                    Apply the methods laid out for you in Content Inc., and before you know it, you&#8217;ll be running your own profitable, scalable business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global Content Marketing: How to Create Great Content, Reach More Customers, and Build a Worldwide Marketing Strategy that Works &#8211; Pam Didner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/global-content-marketing-how-to-create-great-content-reach-more-customers-and-build-a-worldwide-marketing-strategy-that-works-pam-didner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/global-content-marketing-how-to-create-great-content-reach-more-customers-and-build-a-worldwide-marketing-strategy-that-works-pam-didner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Engage Customers Around the World with Cross-Regional Content MarketingTechnology has virtually erased national borders, forever transforming the way we reach and engage customers, as well as the way we search for and consumecontent. Global Content Marketing takes you step-by-step through the process of creating and refining your strategies to meet this new reality. LEARN HOW [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/global-content-marketing-how-to-create-great-content-reach-more-customers-and-build-a-worldwide-marketing-strategy-that-works-pam-didner-abridged/">Global Content Marketing: How to Create Great Content, Reach More Customers, and Build a Worldwide Marketing Strategy that Works &#8211; Pam Didner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Engage Customers Around the World with Cross-Regional Content MarketingTechnology has virtually erased national borders, forever transforming the way we reach and engage customers, as well as the way we search for and consumecontent. Global Content Marketing takes you step-by-step through the process of creating and refining your strategies to meet this new reality.    </p>
<p>                    LEARN HOW TO:    </p>
<p>                    Create content that engages people&#8211;regardless of their country and cultureIdentify key actions and strategies to apply to your projectsConnect &#8220;dots&#8221; that others don&#8217;t see and connect them in ways you never thought of before    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Content marketing across geographies is a diff erent animal. In this smart, practical, and authoritative book, Pam Didner has tamed this animal for all of us.&#8221; &#8212; DOUG KESSLER, Creative Director, Velocity    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A valuable guide to developing and distributing your global content effectively.&#8221; &#8212; NANCY BHAGAT, former VP, Global Marketing Strategy, Intel, and current Divisional CMO, TE Connectivity    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book is the blueprint for engineering a modern scalable content marketing operation.&#8221; &#8212; PAWAN DESHPANDE, CEO, Curata    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Finally the book that explores all critical aspects of global content marketing! Whether you are a small business or a Fortune 500 company, it is essential to understand the 4P&#8217;s developed by Pam Didner. Read it and take your content strategy to the whole new level.&#8221;  &#8212; EKATERINA WALTER, author of Think Like Zuck and coauthor of The Power of Visual Storytelling</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/global-content-marketing-how-to-create-great-content-reach-more-customers-and-build-a-worldwide-marketing-strategy-that-works-pam-didner-abridged/">Global Content Marketing: How to Create Great Content, Reach More Customers, and Build a Worldwide Marketing Strategy that Works &#8211; Pam Didner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Programming / Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Skills & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Starting a new venture is like jumping off a cliff and sewing a parachute on the way down. This book is the parachute.&#8221; Joe Gebbia, cofounder and chief product officer, Airbnb How do you make your start-up a genuine success in the long term? While most books and press focus on the more sensational moments [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/">The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Starting a new venture is like jumping off a cliff and sewing a parachute on the way down. This book is the parachute.&#8221;<br />
                     Joe Gebbia, cofounder and chief product officer, Airbnb    </p>
<p>                    How do you make your start-up a genuine success in the long term?  While most books and press focus on the more sensational moments of creation and conclusion, The Messy Middle argues that the real key to success is how you navigate the ups-and-downs after initial investment is secured. It will give you all the insights you need to build and optimize your team, improve your product and develop your own capacity to lead covering:<br />
                    *         Coping with uncertainty and conflict<br />
                    *         Playing the long game<br />
                    *         Optimising your team<br />
                    *         Problem solving through the ups and downs<br />
                    *         Adapting your strategy<br />
                    *         When to quit<br />
                    Building on seven years&#8217; of meticulous research with entrepreneurs, small agencies, start-ups and billion-dollar companies, Scott Belsky offers indispensable lessons on how to endure and thrive in the long term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-messy-middle-finding-your-way-through-the-hardest-and-most-crucial-part-of-any-bold-venture-scott-belsky-abridged/">The Messy Middle : Finding Your Way Through the Hardest and Most Crucial Part of Any Bold Venture &#8211; Scott Belsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ultimate Guide to Local Business Marketing &#8211; Perry Marshall, Talor Zamir (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ultimate-guide-to-local-business-marketing-perry-marshall-talor-zamir-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ultimate-guide-to-local-business-marketing-perry-marshall-talor-zamir-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>MASTER LOCAL SEO AND REACH THE RIGHT CUSTOMERS EVERY TIME With Google, Yahoo!, and Bing returning local businesses as results on more than a billion daily searches, Google Adwords expert Perry Marshall and lead generation expert Talor Zamir introduce you to the basic framework behind a successful local SEO campaign. From defining local search&#8211;often confused [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultimate-guide-to-local-business-marketing-perry-marshall-talor-zamir-abridged/">Ultimate Guide to Local Business Marketing &#8211; Perry Marshall, Talor Zamir (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MASTER LOCAL SEO AND REACH THE RIGHT CUSTOMERS EVERY TIME  With Google, Yahoo!, and Bing returning local businesses as results on more than a billion daily searches, Google Adwords expert Perry Marshall and lead generation expert Talor Zamir introduce you to the basic framework behind a successful local SEO campaign.  From defining local search&#8211;often confused with paid search and search engine marketing&#8211;to local listing and reviews to social outreach and effective content development, this guide delivers the tools to build an entire local marketing campaign. You&#8217;ll learn how to: Capture high-quality leads from Google AdWords and Bing in 48 hours Master the components of a high-converting campaign and get the most bang for your buck Harness mobile search advertising and Facebook ads for maximum results</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultimate-guide-to-local-business-marketing-perry-marshall-talor-zamir-abridged/">Ultimate Guide to Local Business Marketing &#8211; Perry Marshall, Talor Zamir (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Facebook, PayPal, Alibaba, Uber-these companies have upended entire industries by harnessing a single phenomenon: the platform business model. Platform Revolution delivers the first comprehensive analysis of how platforms match producers and consumers in a multi-sided marketplace, unlocking hidden resources and creating new forms of value. Platform Revolution explores the what, how and why of this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/">Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Facebook, PayPal, Alibaba, Uber-these companies have upended entire industries by harnessing a single phenomenon: the platform business model. Platform Revolution delivers the first comprehensive analysis of how platforms match producers and consumers in a multi-sided marketplace, unlocking hidden resources and creating new forms of value.    </p>
<p>                     Platform Revolution explores the what, how and why of this revolution and provides the first &#8220;owner&#8217;s manual&#8221; for creating a platform marketplace. It provides the essential guide to unlocking the potential of an economic landscape transformed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/">Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that philosophy and illustrates how successful businesses have redefined themselves in the new customer universe.    </p>
<p>                    Personality Not Included is a powerhouse resource packed with bold new insights that show you how to shed the lifeless armor of your business and rediscover the soul of your brand. Sharing stories from the ethos of the world&#8217;s weirdest city, to how Manga has taken the comic book industry by storm, to showcasing brands like Intel, Boeing, ING, and Dyson, Bhargava shows you why personality matters from the inside out.    </p>
<p>                    In Part One, you&#8217;ll be introduced to the key components to building a personality and learn how to:    </p>
<p>                    Recognize the greatest myth that most marketers blindly follow, and how to get past itUse the &#8220;UAT Filter&#8221; to understand the personality of your organization and products in order to develop a communication strategy that drives your marketingCreate your company&#8217;s &#8220;marketing backstory&#8221; using techniques pioneered by Hollywood screenwritersHarness the influence of &#8220;accidental spokespeople&#8221; and use it to your advantageNavigate the roadblocks of using personality that come from bosses, peers, investors, and lawyers, without getting fired or flamedPinpoint and capitalize on the moments where personality can make a difference<br />
                    Part Two is packed with guides, tools, and techniques to help you flawlessly implement your plan. It features practical, step-by-step lessons that help you effectively move from theory to action, and includes a valuable collection of guides, checklists, question forms, printable resources, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Don&#8217;t be another faceless company-learn the new rules for succeeding in the social media era with Personality Not Included.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award A New York Times technology and business reporter charts the dramatic rise of Bitcoin and the fascinating personalities who are striving to create a new global money for the Internet age. Digital Gold is New York Times reporter Nathaniel Popper&#8217;s brilliant and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/">Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award    </p>
<p>                    A New York Times technology and business reporter charts the dramatic rise of Bitcoin and the fascinating personalities who are striving to create a new global money for the Internet age.    </p>
<p>                    Digital Gold is New York Times reporter Nathaniel Popper&#8217;s brilliant and engrossing history of Bitcoin, the landmark digital money and financial technology that has spawned a global social movement.    </p>
<p>                    The notion of a new currency, maintained by the computers of users around the world, has been the butt of many jokes, but that has not stopped it from growing into a technology worth billions of dollars, supported by the hordes of followers who have come to view it as the most important new idea since the creation of the Internet. Believers from Beijing to Buenos Aires see the potential for a financial system free from banks and governments. More than just a tech industry fad, Bitcoin has threatened to decentralize some of society&#8217;s most basic institutions.    </p>
<p>                    An unusual tale of group invention, Digital Gold charts the rise of the Bitcoin technology through the eyes of the movement&#8217;s colorful central characters, including an Argentinian millionaire, a Chinese entrepreneur, Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss, and Bitcoin&#8217;s elusive creator, Satoshi Nakamoto. Already, Bitcoin has led to untold riches for some, and prison terms for others.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/">Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jab, Jab, Jab, Right Hook : How to Tell Your Story in a Noisy, Social World &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/jab-jab-jab-right-hook-how-to-tell-your-story-in-a-noisy-social-world-gary-vaynerchuk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/jab-jab-jab-right-hook-how-to-tell-your-story-in-a-noisy-social-world-gary-vaynerchuk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling author and social media expert Gary Vaynerchuk shares hard-won advice on how to connect with customers and beat the competition.When managers, marketers, and small business owners outline their social media strategies, they plan for the `right hook`&#8211;their next campaign that will produce profits. Even companies committed to `jabbing`&#8211;creating content for consumers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jab-jab-jab-right-hook-how-to-tell-your-story-in-a-noisy-social-world-gary-vaynerchuk-abridged/">Jab, Jab, Jab, Right Hook : How to Tell Your Story in a Noisy, Social World &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times bestselling author and social media expert Gary Vaynerchuk shares hard-won advice on how to connect with customers and beat the competition.When managers, marketers, and small business owners outline their social media strategies, they plan for the `right hook`&#8211;their next campaign that will produce profits. Even companies committed to `jabbing`&#8211;creating content for consumers and engaging with customers to build relationships&#8211;still desperately want to land the powerful, bruising swing that will knock out their opponents or their customers&#8217; resistance in one tooth-shattering, killer blow. Right hooks, after all, convert traffic to sales. They easily show results and return on investment. Except when they don&#8217;t.In the same passionate, streetwise style his readers have come to expect, Vaynerchuk is on a mission to strengthen marketers&#8217; right hooks by changing the way they fight to make their consumers happy, and ultimately to compete. Thanks to the massive change in and proliferation of social media platforms in the last four years, the winning combination of jabs and right hooks is different now. Communication is still key, but context matters more than ever. It&#8217;s not just about developing high-quality content; it&#8217;s also about developing high-quality content that&#8217;s perfectly adapted to specific social media platforms and mobile devices. It&#8217;s about truly engaging with customers, not by shouting at them over social media but by using new narrative forms particular to each different media platform&#8211;especially, though not exclusively, Facebook, Instagram, Pinterest, Twitter, and Tumblr. Jab, Jab, Jab, Right Hook is a blueprint to social media marketing strategies that really work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jab-jab-jab-right-hook-how-to-tell-your-story-in-a-noisy-social-world-gary-vaynerchuk-abridged/">Jab, Jab, Jab, Right Hook : How to Tell Your Story in a Noisy, Social World &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD. This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career. An MBA at a top business school is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>10th Anniversary edition * Completely revised and updated * over 800,000 copies sold     </p>
<p>                    ARE YOU TEMPTED TO GO TO BUSINESS SCHOOL? SAVE YOUR MONEY AND READ THE PERSONAL MBA INSTEAD.    </p>
<p>                    This bestselling business classic gives you everything you need to transform your business and your career.    </p>
<p>                    An MBA at a top business school is an enormous investment in time and cash. And if you don&#8217;t want to work for a consulting firm or an investment bank, the chances are it simply isn&#8217;t worth it.    </p>
<p>                    The Personal MBA gives you simple mental models for every subject that&#8217;s key to commercial success. From the basics of products and marketing to the nuances of teamwork and systems, this book distils everything you need to know to take on the MBA graduates and win.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;File this book under: NO EXCUSES&#8217; Seth Godin    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;No matter what they tell you, an MBA is not essential. If you combine reading this book with actually trying stuff, you&#8217;ll be far ahead in the business game&#8217; Kevin Kelly, founder of Wired</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-personal-mba-a-world-class-business-education-in-a-single-volume-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The Personal MBA : A World-Class Business Education in a Single Volume &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lost and Founder : A Painfully Honest Field Guide to the Startup World &#8211; Rand Fishkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Systems Analysis & Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You won&#8217;t find a more honest, raw and helpful look into the trenches of founding a tech startup than this book&#8217; Nir Eyal, author of Hooked &#8216;Rand Fishkin is the real deal&#8217; Seth Godin, entrepreneur and author &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; Everyone knows how a startup story is supposed to go: a young, brilliant entrepreneur has an cool [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/">Lost and Founder : A Painfully Honest Field Guide to the Startup World &#8211; Rand Fishkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You won&#8217;t find a more honest, raw and helpful look into the trenches of founding a tech startup than this book&#8217; Nir Eyal, author of Hooked    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Rand Fishkin is the real deal&#8217; Seth Godin, entrepreneur and author     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    Everyone knows how a startup story is supposed to go: a young, brilliant entrepreneur has an cool idea, drops out of college, defies the doubters, overcomes all odds, makes billions and becomes the envy of the technology world.     </p>
<p>                    This is not that story.    </p>
<p>                    Rand Fishkin, the founder and former CEO of Moz, is one of the world&#8217;s leading experts on SEO. Moz is now a $45 million a year business, but Fishkin&#8217;s business and reputation took 15 years to grow, and his startup began not in a Harvard dorm room but as a mother-and-son family business that fell deeply into debt.     </p>
<p>                    Now Fishkin pulls back the curtain on tech startup mythology, exposing the ups and downs of startup life that most CEOs would rather keep secret. For instance: a minimally viable product can be destructive if you launch at the wrong moment. Growth hacking may be the buzzword du jour, but initiatives to your business can fizzle quickly. Revenue and profitability won&#8217;t protect you from layoffs. And venture capital always comes with strings attached.     </p>
<p>                    In Lost and Founder Fishkin reveals the mostly awful, sometimes awesome truth about startup culture with the transparency and humour that his hundreds of thousands of blog readers have come to love. Fishkin&#8217;s hard-won lessons are applicable to any kind of business environment and this book can help solve your problems, and make you feel less alone for having them.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is a truly courageous book. It&#8217;s one part business-building guide and two parts Indiana Jones-style adventure memoir&#8217; Chris Guillebeau, author of Side Hustle and The $100 Startup    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Rand Fishkin is like the industry friend we all wish we had &#8211; funny, warm, and refreshingly honest about the rollercoaster ride that is founding your own company&#8217; Julie Zhou, VP of Product Design at Facebook</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-and-founder-a-painfully-honest-field-guide-to-the-startup-world-rand-fishkin-abridged/">Lost and Founder : A Painfully Honest Field Guide to the Startup World &#8211; Rand Fishkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Managing Online Reputation is a comprehensive look at online reputation management. Drawing on recent examples of organizations managing their online reputations effectively and ineffectively, it provides a practical and visual tool-kit of processes and techniques to help limit and respond effectively to negative situations on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/">Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Managing Online Reputation is a comprehensive look at online reputation management. Drawing on recent examples of organizations managing their online reputations effectively and ineffectively, it provides a practical and visual tool-kit of processes and techniques to help limit and respond effectively to negative situations on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/">Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Third Wave : An Entrepreneur&#8217;s Vision of the Future &#8211; Steve Case (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-third-wave-an-entrepreneurs-vision-of-the-future-steve-case-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Project Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-third-wave-an-entrepreneurs-vision-of-the-future-steve-case-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steve Case&#8217;s career began when he cofounded America Online (AOL) in 1985. At the time, only three percent of Americans were online. It took a decade for AOL to achieve mainstream success. AOL became the top performing company of the 1990s, and at its peak more than half of all consumer Internet traffic in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-wave-an-entrepreneurs-vision-of-the-future-steve-case-abridged/">The Third Wave : An Entrepreneur&#8217;s Vision of the Future &#8211; Steve Case (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steve Case&#8217;s career began when he cofounded America Online (AOL) in 1985. At the time, only three percent of Americans were online. It took a decade for AOL to achieve mainstream success. AOL became the top performing company of the 1990s, and at its peak more than half of all consumer Internet traffic in the United States ran through the service. After Case engineered AOL&#8217;s merger with Time Warner and he became Chairman of the combined business, Case oversaw the biggest media and communications empire in the world.<br />
                         In The Third Wave, which pays homage to the work of the futurist Alvin Toffler, Case takes us behind the scenes of some of the most consequential and riveting business decisions of our time while offering illuminating insights from decades of working as an entrepreneur, an investor, a philanthropist, and an advocate for sensible bipartisan policies.<br />
                         We are entering, as Case explains, a new paradigm called the &#8220;Third Wave&#8221; of the Internet. The first wave saw AOL and other companies lay the foundation for consumers to connect to the Internet. The second wave saw companies like Google and Facebook build on top of the Internet to create search and social networking capabilities, while apps like Snapchat and Instagram leverage the smartphone revolution. Now, Case argues, we&#8217;re entering the Third Wave: a period in which entrepreneurs will vastly transform major &#8220;real world&#8221; sectors like health, education, transportation, energy, and food-and in the process change the way we live our daily lives.<br />
                         The Third Wave is part memoir, part manifesto, and part playbook for the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-wave-an-entrepreneurs-vision-of-the-future-steve-case-abridged/">The Third Wave : An Entrepreneur&#8217;s Vision of the Future &#8211; Steve Case (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Paid Attention : Innovative Advertising for a Digital World &#8211; Faris Yakob (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/paid-attention-innovative-advertising-for-a-digital-world-faris-yakob-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/paid-attention-innovative-advertising-for-a-digital-world-faris-yakob-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The advertising attention marketplace is a confusing and vast playing field where the rules have changed drastically over the last decade. Make yourself heard and win the attention of your target audience with the new edition of this ultimate guide. Paid Attention delivers new and innovative insights into advertising ideas: what they are, why they [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/paid-attention-innovative-advertising-for-a-digital-world-faris-yakob-abridged/">Paid Attention : Innovative Advertising for a Digital World &#8211; Faris Yakob (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The advertising attention marketplace is a confusing and vast playing field where the rules have changed drastically over the last decade. Make yourself heard and win the attention of your target audience with the new edition of this ultimate guide.    </p>
<p>                    Paid Attention delivers new and innovative insights into advertising ideas: what they are, why they are evolving and how to use them in day to day strategy to ensure commercial stability within a changing digital landscape. Packed with real-world examples of advertising campaigns such as Google, Sony and Old Spice, it provides a robust model for influencing human behaviour and toolkits that offer best practice on brand behaviour and effective communication.    </p>
<p>                    This second edition includes two new chapters exploring the latest evidence about attention spans and trends in online advertising, as well as new case studies on compelling brand ideas. In a world where being a consumer is confusing, learn to take control of the situation and make yourself heard in today&#8217;s crowded attention marketplace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/paid-attention-innovative-advertising-for-a-digital-world-faris-yakob-abridged/">Paid Attention : Innovative Advertising for a Digital World &#8211; Faris Yakob (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for staying top of mind with your audience-from Inc.com&#8217;s #1 content marketing company What do all successful businesses have in common? They&#8217;re the first name that comes to mind when people think about their particular market. How do companies achieve this? By developing habits and strategies that focus on building meaningful relationships and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/">Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Proven strategies for staying top of mind with your audience-from Inc.com&#8217;s #1 content marketing company     </p>
<p>                    What do all successful businesses have in common? They&#8217;re the first name that comes to mind when people think about their particular market. How do companies achieve this? By developing habits and strategies that focus on building meaningful relationships and delivering value consistently, day in and day out.    </p>
<p>                    In Top of Mind, the cofounder of a leading content marketing company shows you how to create business opportunities by occupying the space at the top of your audience&#8217;s minds-and keeping it there. This groundbreaking book explains how consumer needs and expectations have changed and what this shift means for readers interested in building a brand-whether you&#8217;re a leader in marketing engaging potential customers, a VP of sales bringing in new business, or a director of HR who&#8217;s recruiting the best talent in the industry. It provides effective ways to establish trust and foster connections; maintain transparency and consistency; identify and clearly communicate the &#8220;why&#8221; behind the message; and create processes to make that message part of a brand&#8217;s DNA.     </p>
<p>                    Maintaining a prominent spot in your audience&#8217;s minds will increase the likelihood that the moment they need to make a choice, you&#8217;ll be the first one they call.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-of-mind-use-content-to-unleash-your-influence-and-engage-those-who-matter-to-you-john-hall-abridged/">Top of Mind: Use Content to Unleash Your Influence and Engage Those Who Matter To You &#8211; John Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba&#8217;s World : How One Remarkable Chinese Company Is Changing the Face of Global Business &#8211; Porter Erisman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In September 2014, a Chinese company that most Westerners had never heard of held the largest IPO in history &#8211; bigger than Google, Facebook and Twitter combined. Alibaba, now the world&#8217;s largest e-commerce company, mostly escaped Western notice for over ten years, while building a customer base larger than Amazon&#8217;s, and handling the bulk of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/">Alibaba&#8217;s World : How One Remarkable Chinese Company Is Changing the Face of Global Business &#8211; Porter Erisman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In September 2014, a Chinese company that most Westerners had never heard of held the largest IPO in history &#8211; bigger than Google, Facebook and Twitter combined. Alibaba, now the world&#8217;s largest e-commerce company, mostly escaped Western notice for over ten years, while building a customer base larger than Amazon&#8217;s, and handling the bulk of e-commerce transactions in China. How did it happen? And what was it like to be along for such a revolutionary ride?    </p>
<p>                    In Alibaba&#8217;s World, author Porter Erisman, one of Alibaba&#8217;s first Western employees, who helped spearhead its international expansion, shows how Jack Ma, a Chinese schoolteacher who twice failed his college entrance exams, rose from obscurity to found Alibaba and lead it from struggling startup to the world&#8217;s most dominant e-commerce player.     </p>
<p>                    Now, in the first English language account of Alibaba&#8217;s extraordinary success, Erisman shares stories of weathering the dotcom crash, facing down eBay and Google, negotiating with the unpredictable Chinese government, and enduring the misguided advice of foreign experts, all to build the behemoth that&#8217;s poised to sweep the ecommerce world today. And he analyzes Alibaba&#8217;s role as a harbinger of the new global business landscape &#8211; with its focus on the East rather than the West, emerging markets over developed ones, and the nimble entrepreneur over the industry titan. As we face this near future, the story of Alibaba &#8211; and its inevitable descendants &#8211; is both essential and instructive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibabas-world-how-one-remarkable-chinese-company-is-changing-the-face-of-global-business-porter-erisman-abridged/">Alibaba&#8217;s World : How One Remarkable Chinese Company Is Changing the Face of Global Business &#8211; Porter Erisman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba : The House That Jack Ma Built &#8211; Duncan Clark (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An engrossing, insider&#8217;s account of how a teacher built one of the world&#8217;s most valuable companies-rivaling Walmart and Amazon-and forever reshaped the global economy In just a decade and a half, Jack Ma, a man from modest beginnings who started out as an English teacher, founded Alibaba and built it into one of the world&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/">Alibaba : The House That Jack Ma Built &#8211; Duncan Clark (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An engrossing, insider&#8217;s account of how a teacher built one of the world&#8217;s most valuable companies-rivaling Walmart and Amazon-and forever reshaped the global economy  In just a decade and a half, Jack Ma, a man from modest beginnings who started out as an English teacher, founded Alibaba and built it into one of the world&#8217;s largest companies, an e-commerce empire on which hundreds of millions of Chinese consumers depend. In 2014, Alibaba&#8217;s $25 billion IPO was the largest global IPO in history. A Rockefeller of his time, who is courted by CEOs and presidents around the world, Jack is an icon for China&#8217;s booming private sector and the gatekeeper to hundreds of millions of middle-class consumers. Duncan Clark first met Jack in 1999 in the small apartment where Jack founded Alibaba. Granted unprecedented access to a wealth of new material, including exclusive interviews, Clark draws on his own experience as an early adviser to Alibaba as well as his two decades in China chronicling the Internet&#8217;s impact on the country to create an authoritative, compelling narrative account of Alibaba&#8217;s rise.<br />
                    How did Jack overcome his humble origins and early failures to achieve massive success with Alibaba? How did he outsmart rival entrepreneurs from both China and Silicon Valley? Can Alibaba maintain its 80 percent market share? As it forges ahead into finance and entertainment, are there limits to Alibaba&#8217;s ambitions? How does the Chinese government view its rise? Will Alibaba expand farther overseas, including into the United States?  Clark tells Alibaba&#8217;s tale in the context of China&#8217;s momentous economic and social changes, illuminating an unlikely corporate titan as never before.  Advance Praise For Alibaba  &#8220;Anybody who thinks the Chinese just copy or steal technology from the West should read this book and think again. Jack Ma is part Bill Gates, part Steve Jobs, part Larry Page, part Sergey Brin, and part Mark Zuckerberg, all rolled into one.&#8221;-Sir Martin Sorrell, CEO of WPP &#8220;Duncan Clark gets into the heart and soul of Alibaba and its founder, Jack Ma, who deftly maneuvered through the discontinuities and barriers in China to create one of the greatest companies in the world. China has thrived under the leadership of Jack Ma.<br />
                    This book is a must-read for anyone who wants to understand the present China and the heartbeat of a great entrepreneur.&#8221;-Tim Draper, founder of Draper Associates, DFJ, and Draper University  &#8220;This book provides excellent insight into the world of Jack Ma, perhaps the most famous of the leaders of the new economy in China. Duncan Clark is a real China &#8216;Old Hand,&#8217; unique in his knowledge of the Jack Ma generation. This book is definitely on the short list for those who wish to understand the Chinese economy today.&#8221;-Ken Wilcox, Chairman Emeritus, Silicon Valley Bank</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/">Alibaba : The House That Jack Ma Built &#8211; Duncan Clark (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Free Prize Inside : How to Make a Purple Cow &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/free-prize-inside-how-to-make-a-purple-cow-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Programming & Scripting Languages: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/free-prize-inside-how-to-make-a-purple-cow-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to find the soft innovation that will make your product, service, school, church, or career worth talking about. We live in an era of too much noise, too much clutter, too many choices, and too much spam. And as Seth Godin&#8217;s 200,000-copy bestseller Purple Cow taught the business world, the old ways of marketing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/free-prize-inside-how-to-make-a-purple-cow-seth-godin-abridged/">Free Prize Inside : How to Make a Purple Cow &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to find the soft innovation that will make your product, service, school, church, or career worth talking about.  We live in an era of too much noise, too much clutter, too many choices, and too much spam. And as Seth Godin&#8217;s 200,000-copy bestseller Purple Cow taught the business world, the old ways of marketing simply don&#8217;t work anymore. The best way to sell anything these days is through word of mouth and the only real way to get word of mouth is to create something remarkable.  Free Prize Inside, the sequel to Purple Cow, explains how to do just that. It&#8217;s jammed with practical ideas you can use right now to make your product or service remarkable, so that it will virtually sell itself.  Remember when cereal came with a free prize inside? Even if you already liked the cereal, it was the little plastic toy that made it irresistible. Godin explains how you can think of a bonus that will make your customers feel just as excited, no matter what business you&#8217;re in. Consider these free prizes: &#8211; The Tupperware party, which turned buying plastic bowls into a social event<br />
                    &#8211; Flintstones vitamins, which turned a serious product into something fun<br />
                    &#8211; The free change-counting machine at every Commerce Bank branch<br />
                    &#8211; The little blue box from Tiffany, which makes people happy before they even open it  This book offers a way to create free prizes quickly, cheaply, and reliably and persuade others in your organization to help you bring them to life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/free-prize-inside-how-to-make-a-purple-cow-seth-godin-abridged/">Free Prize Inside : How to Make a Purple Cow &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bitcoin Standard : The Decentralized Alternative to Central Banking &#8211; Saifedean Ammous (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When a pseudonymous programmer introduced &#8220;a new electronic cash system that&#8217;s fully peer-to-peer, with no trusted third party&#8221; to a small online mailing list in 2008, very few paid attention. Ten years later, and against all odds, this upstart autonomous decentralized software offers an unstoppable and globally-accessible hard money alternative to modern central banks. The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/">The Bitcoin Standard : The Decentralized Alternative to Central Banking &#8211; Saifedean Ammous (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When a pseudonymous programmer introduced &#8220;a new electronic cash system that&#8217;s fully peer-to-peer, with no trusted third party&#8221; to a small online mailing list in 2008, very few paid attention. Ten years later, and against all odds, this upstart autonomous decentralized software offers an unstoppable and globally-accessible hard money alternative to modern central banks. The Bitcoin Standard analyzes the historical context to the rise of Bitcoin, the economic properties that have allowed it to grow quickly, and its likely economic, political, and social implications.    </p>
<p>                     While Bitcoin is a new invention of the digital age, the problem it purports to solve is as old as human society itself: transferring value across time and space. Ammous takes the reader on an engaging journey through the history of technologies performing the functions of money, from primitive systems of trading limestones and seashells, to metals, coins, the gold standard, and modern government debt. Exploring what gave these technologies their monetary role, and how most lost it, provides the reader with a good idea of what makes for sound money, and sets the stage for an economic discussion of its consequences for individual and societal future-orientation, capital accumulation, trade, peace, culture, and art. Compellingly, Ammous shows that it is no coincidence that the loftiest achievements of humanity have come in societies enjoying the benefits of sound monetary regimes, nor is it coincidental that monetary collapse has usually accompanied civilizational collapse.    </p>
<p>                     With this background in place, the book moves on to explain the operation of Bitcoin in a functional and intuitive way. Bitcoin is a decentralized, distributed piece of software that converts electricity and processing power into indisputably accurate records, thus allowing its users to utilize the Internet to perform the traditional functions of money without having to rely on, or trust, any authorities or infrastructure in the physical world. Bitcoin is thus best understood as the first successfully implemented form of digital cash and digital hard money. With an automated and perfectly predictable monetary policy, and the ability to perform final settlement of large sums across the world in a matter of minutes, Bitcoin&#8217;s real competitive edge might just be as a store of value and network for final settlement of large payments-a digital form of gold with a built-in settlement infrastructure.    </p>
<p>                     Ammous&#8217; firm grasp of the technological possibilities as well as the historical realities of monetary evolution provides for a fascinating exploration of the ramifications of voluntary free market money. As it challenges the most sacred of government monopolies, Bitcoin shifts the pendulum of sovereignty away from governments in favor of individuals, offering us the tantalizing possibility of a world where money is fully extricated from politics and unrestrained by borders.    </p>
<p>                     The final chapter of the book explores some of the most common questions surrounding Bitcoin: Is Bitcoin mining a waste of energy? Is Bitcoin for criminals? Who controls Bitcoin, and can they change it if they please? How can Bitcoin be killed? And what to make of all the thousands of Bitcoin knock-offs, and the many supposed applications of Bitcoin&#8217;s &#8216;blockchain technology&#8217;? The Bitcoin Standard is the essential resource for a clear understanding of the rise of the Internet&#8217;s decentralized, apolitical, free-market alternative to national central banks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bitcoin-standard-the-decentralized-alternative-to-central-banking-saifedean-ammous-abridged/">The Bitcoin Standard : The Decentralized Alternative to Central Banking &#8211; Saifedean Ammous (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chaos Monkeys : Inside the Silicon Valley Money Machine &#8211; Antonio Garcia Martinez (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chaos-monkeys-inside-the-silicon-valley-money-machine-antonio-garcia-martinez-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chaos-monkeys-inside-the-silicon-valley-money-machine-antonio-garcia-martinez-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER An adrenaline-fuelled expose of life inside the tech bubble, Chaos Monkeys lays bare the secrets, power plays and lifestyle excesses of the visionaries, grunts, sociopaths, opportunists and money cowboys who are revolutionising our world. Written by startup CEO and industry provocateur Antonio Garcia Martinez, this is Liar&#8217;s Poker meets The Social [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chaos-monkeys-inside-the-silicon-valley-money-machine-antonio-garcia-martinez-abridged/">Chaos Monkeys : Inside the Silicon Valley Money Machine &#8211; Antonio Garcia Martinez (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    An adrenaline-fuelled expose of life inside the tech bubble, Chaos Monkeys lays bare the secrets, power plays and lifestyle excesses of the visionaries, grunts, sociopaths, opportunists and money cowboys who are revolutionising our world. Written by startup CEO and industry provocateur Antonio Garcia Martinez, this is Liar&#8217;s Poker meets The Social Network.     </p>
<p>                    Computer engineers use &#8216;chaos monkey&#8217; software to wreak havoc and test system robustness. Similarly, tech entrepreneurs like Antonio Garcia Martinez are society&#8217;s chaos monkeys &#8211; their innovations disrupt every aspect of our lives, from transportation (Uber) and holidays (Airbnb) to television (Netflix) and dating (Tinder) &#8211; all in search of the perfect business miracle.      </p>
<p>                    Describing himself as &#8216;high-strung, fast-talking, and wired on a combination of caffeine, fear, and greed at all times&#8217;, Garcia Martinez left Wall Street to make his fortune in Silicon Valley, becoming CEO of his own startup, before bailing and being poached by Facebook&#8217;s nascent advertising team. Here he turned users&#8217; data into profit for COO Sheryl Sandberg and chairman and CEO Mark &#8216;Zuck&#8217; Zuckerberg. Forced out of Facebook in the wake of a bitter internal product war, Garcia Martinez  took his unique brand of entrepreneurial hyperactivity to rivals Twitter. Along the way, he got into a lot of trouble with a lot of people, brewed illegal beer on the Facebook campus (accidentally flooding Zuckerberg&#8217;s desk), lived on a yacht, raced sport cars on the highway, and enthusiastically pursued the lifestyle of an overpaid Silicon Valley mercenary.    </p>
<p>                    In Chaos Monkeys he tells you HOW &#8211; and HOW NOT &#8211; to make a fortune through startups and digital marketing.  Highly entertaining and always offering genuine insight, Garcia Martinez  unravels the chaotic evolution of social media and online marketing. From startups and credit derivatives to Big Brother and data tracking, social media monetisation and digital &#8216;privacy&#8217;, he shares both his scathing observations and outrageous antics, taking us on a subversive and very funny tour of the fascinatingly insular and unbelievably wealthy tech industry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chaos-monkeys-inside-the-silicon-valley-money-machine-antonio-garcia-martinez-abridged/">Chaos Monkeys : Inside the Silicon Valley Money Machine &#8211; Antonio Garcia Martinez (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trust Agents : Using the Web to Build Influence, Improve Reputation, and Earn Trust &#8211; Chris Brogan, Julien Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trust-agents-using-the-web-to-build-influence-improve-reputation-and-earn-trust-chris-brogan-julien-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trust-agents-using-the-web-to-build-influence-improve-reputation-and-earn-trust-chris-brogan-julien-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times and Wall Street Journal bestseller-now in a new, updated paperback edition Today&#8217;s online influencers are Web natives who trade in trust, reputation, and relationships, using social media to accrue the influence that builds up or brings down businesses online. In Trust Agents, two social media veterans show you how to tap [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trust-agents-using-the-web-to-build-influence-improve-reputation-and-earn-trust-chris-brogan-julien-smith-abridged/">Trust Agents : Using the Web to Build Influence, Improve Reputation, and Earn Trust &#8211; Chris Brogan, Julien Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times and Wall Street Journal bestseller-now in a new, updated paperback edition  Today&#8217;s online influencers are Web natives who trade in trust, reputation, and relationships, using social media to accrue the influence that builds up or brings down businesses online. In Trust Agents, two social media veterans show you how to tap into the power of social networks to build your brand&#8217;s influence, reputation, and, of course, profits.  In this revised paperback version, learn how businesses are using the latest online social tools to build networks of influence and how you can use those networks to positively impact your business. Combining high-level theory and practical actions, this guide delivers actionable steps and case studies that show how social media can positively impact your business.<br />
                    * New edition features specific first moves for entering social media for small businesses, educators, travel and hospitality enterprises, nonprofit organizations, and corporations * Authors both have a major presence on the social Web as well as years of online marketing and new media experience If you want your business to succeed, don&#8217;t sit on the sidelines while new markets and channels grow. Instead, use the Web to build trust with your consumers using  Trust Agents.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trust-agents-using-the-web-to-build-influence-improve-reputation-and-earn-trust-chris-brogan-julien-smith-abridged/">Trust Agents : Using the Web to Build Influence, Improve Reputation, and Earn Trust &#8211; Chris Brogan, Julien Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Psychology of Selling : Increase Your Sales Faster and Easier Than You Ever Thought Possible &#8211; Brian Tracy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Top professional speaker and sales trainer Brian Tracy found that his most important breakthrough was the discovery that it is the &#8220;psychology of selling&#8221; that is more important than the techniques and methods of selling. Learn how to double and triple your sales in any market. It&#8217;s a promise of prosperity that sales guru Brian [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/">The Psychology of Selling : Increase Your Sales Faster and Easier Than You Ever Thought Possible &#8211; Brian Tracy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Top professional speaker and sales trainer Brian Tracy found that his most important breakthrough was the discovery that it is the &#8220;psychology of selling&#8221; that is more important than the techniques and methods of selling.    </p>
<p>                    Learn how to double and triple your sales in any market. It&#8217;s a promise of prosperity that sales guru Brian Tracy has seen fulfilled again and again.    </p>
<p>                    More salespeople have become millionaires by listening to and applying his ideas than from any other sales training process ever developed.    </p>
<p>                    In Psychology of Selling, Tracy teaches you:    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The inner game of sales and selling&#8221;<br />
                    How to eliminate the fear of rejection<br />
                    How to build unshakeable confidence    </p>
<p>                    Tracy shows how salespeople must learn to control their thoughts, feelings and actions to make themselves more effective.    </p>
<p>                    Psychology of Selling gives you a series of ideas, methods, strategies, and techniques that you can use immediately to make more sales, faster and easier than ever before.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/">The Psychology of Selling : Increase Your Sales Faster and Easier Than You Ever Thought Possible &#8211; Brian Tracy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Startupland : How Three Guys Risked Everything to Turn an Idea into a Global Business &#8211; Mikkel Svane, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/startupland-how-three-guys-risked-everything-to-turn-an-idea-into-a-global-business-mikkel-svane-carlye-adler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Programming / Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/startupland-how-three-guys-risked-everything-to-turn-an-idea-into-a-global-business-mikkel-svane-carlye-adler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The real story of what it takes to risk it all and go for broke. Conventional wisdom says most startups need to be in Silicon Valley, started by young engineers around a sexy new idea, and backed by VC funding. But as Mikkel Svane reveals in Startupland, the story of founding Zendesk was anything but [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startupland-how-three-guys-risked-everything-to-turn-an-idea-into-a-global-business-mikkel-svane-carlye-adler-abridged/">Startupland : How Three Guys Risked Everything to Turn an Idea into a Global Business &#8211; Mikkel Svane, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The real story of what it takes to risk it all and go for broke. Conventional wisdom says most startups need to be in Silicon Valley, started by young engineers around a sexy new idea, and backed by VC funding. But as Mikkel Svane reveals in Startupland, the story of founding Zendesk was anything but conventional. Founded in a Copenhagen loft by three thirty-something friends looking to break free from corporate doldrums, Zendesk Inc. is now one of the hottest enterprise software companies, still rapidly growing with customers in 150 countries. But its success was anything but predestined. With revealing stories both funny and frank, Mikkel shares how he and his friends bravely left secure jobs to start something on their own, how he almost went broke several times, how they picked up themselves and their families to travel across the world to California and the unknown, and how the three friends were miraculously still together for Zendesk&#8217;s IPO and (still growing) success.<br />
                    Much like Zendesk&#8217;s mission itself to remove friction, barriers, and mystery in order to make customer service easier and more approachable Startupland removes some of the myths about startups and startup founders. Mikkel&#8217;s advice, hard-won through experience, often bucks conventional wisdom and entrepreneurial tropes. He shares why failure (whether fast or slow) is awful, why a seemingly boring product or idea can be the most exciting, why giving back to the community is as important as the bottom line. From how to hire right (look for people who are not offended by swearing) to which personas generate the highest response rates, Mikkel answers the most pressing questions from the perspective of someone still in the trenches and willing to share the hard truth, warts and all. While there are books by consultants who tell you how to build businesses, or by entrepreneurs now running billion-dollar businesses, there are few books from people still in the trenches who acutely remember the difficult daily decisions, the thrill (and fears) of the early days, the problems that scale with growing a business, and the reason why they all went on the adventure in the first place.<br />
                    Startupland is indispensable reading for all entrepreneurs who want to make their ideas the next big thing. The book will inspire and empower you to follow your own dream and create your own story.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startupland-how-three-guys-risked-everything-to-turn-an-idea-into-a-global-business-mikkel-svane-carlye-adler-abridged/">Startupland : How Three Guys Risked Everything to Turn an Idea into a Global Business &#8211; Mikkel Svane, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you know how to find out what people really want to buy? (Not what you think they want, not what they say they want, but what they really want?) The secret is asking the right questions&#8230; and the right questions are not what you might expect. Introducing Ask: the most powerful way to discover [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/">Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you know how to find out what people really want to buy? (Not what you think they want, not what they say they want, but what they really want?)    </p>
<p>                    The secret is asking the right questions&#8230; and the right questions are not what you might expect.    </p>
<p>                    Introducing Ask: the most powerful way to discover exactly what people want to buy, and how to give it to them &#8211; and in a way that makes people fall in love with you and your company.     </p>
<p>                    The proven, repeatable (yet slightly counterintuitive) Ask Method has quietly generated over $100 million in online sales across 23 different industries, and counting. In this tell-all book, Ryan Levesque reveals this exact method step-by-step, as well as the unusual story behind its discovery.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re an aspiring Internet entrepreneur, advanced online marketer, or established business owner, this book will both inspire you and show you how to skyrocket your online income-while creating a mass of raving fans in the process-simply by asking the right questions in a surprisingly different way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ryan has uncovered some enormous misunderstandings about human buying behavior and then utilized his neuroscience background to create this game-changing marketing and survey strategy. Before you finish the first third of the book, you&#8217;ll be eager to jump ahead and implement his process immediately &#8211; it&#8217;s that powerful!&#8217; &#8211; Annie Hyman Pratt, former CEO of The Coffee Bean and Tea Leaf and CEO of IMPAQ Entrepreneur Business Execution Systems    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ask may be the most important book written for anyone who sells products or services directly to consumers since Breakthrough Advertising was published in 1966. Like that masterpiece, Ask gives us a new paradigm for understanding human behavior at the deepest level, which gives rise to a more intelligent and profitable way to sell almost anything. Ryan Levsque will go down in history as the marketer who used his background to change the way products and services are sold online.&#8217; &#8211; Brian Kurtz, business builder of Boardroom Inc. and serial direct marketer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/">Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Think Like Zuck: The Five Business Secrets of Facebook&#8217;s Improbably Brilliant CEO Mark Zuckerberg &#8211; Ekaterina Walter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/think-like-zuck-the-five-business-secrets-of-facebooks-improbably-brilliant-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-ekaterina-walter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/think-like-zuck-the-five-business-secrets-of-facebooks-improbably-brilliant-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-ekaterina-walter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal BestsellerMake Your Mark in the World with the Five Success Principles of the World-Changing Social Media Site If Facebook were a country, it would be the third largest in the world. Facebook accounts for one of every seven minutes spent online. More than one billion pieces of content are shared on Facebook. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/think-like-zuck-the-five-business-secrets-of-facebooks-improbably-brilliant-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-ekaterina-walter-abridged/">Think Like Zuck: The Five Business Secrets of Facebook&#8217;s Improbably Brilliant CEO Mark Zuckerberg &#8211; Ekaterina Walter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal BestsellerMake Your Mark in the World with the Five Success Principles of the World-Changing Social Media Site    </p>
<p>                    If Facebook were a country, it would be the third largest in the world.<br />
                    Facebook accounts for one of every seven minutes spent online.<br />
                    More than one billion pieces of content are shared on Facebook.    </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s no doubt about it. Mark Zuckerberg&#8217;s creation has changed the world. Literally. Facebook has singlehandedly revolutionized the way more than one-seventh of the world&#8217;s population communicates, engages, and consumes information.    </p>
<p>                    If you run a business or plan to start one, you&#8217;re probably asking yourself the same question organizational leaders worldwide are asking: What did Mark Zuckerberg do right?At long last, the answer is here. Think Like Zuck examines the five principles behind Facebook&#8217;s meteoric rise, presented in actionable lessons anyone can apply-in any organization, in any industry. Written by social business trailblazer Ekaterina Walter, this groundbreaking book reveals the five &#8220;P&#8221;s of Facebook&#8217;s success:    </p>
<p>                    PASSION-Keep your energy and commitment fully charged at all times by pursuing something you believe in<br />
                    PURPOSE-Don&#8217;t just create a great product; drive a meaningful movement<br />
                    PEOPLE-Build powerful teams that can execute your vision<br />
                    PRODUCT-Create a product that is innovative, that breaks all the rules, that changes everything<br />
                    PARTNERSHIPS-Build powerful partnerships with people who fuel imagination and energize execution    </p>
<p>                    Packed with examples of Facebook&#8217;s success principles in action-as well as those of Zappos, TOMS, Threadless, Dyson, and other companies-Think Like Zuck gives you the inspiration, knowledge, and insight to make your own mark in the world, to build a business that makes a difference, and to lead your organization to long-term profitability and growth.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Think Like Zuck is a fascinating look at how entrepreneurial vision drives success. If you want more out of work than just a job, if you have the burning desire to build something of lasting value, then this is your guide.&#8221;<br />
                    -DAVID MEERMAN SCOTT, bestselling author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Whether you&#8217;re a seasoned business executive or the next Mark Zuckerberg in your dorm room right now, this book is a must-read! Two likeable thumbs up!&#8221;<br />
                    -DAVE KERPEN, New York Times bestselling author of Likeable Social Media and Likeable Business    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;True success lies at the place where passion and purpose collide-this book will help you uncover yours.&#8221;<br />
                    -JOHN JANTSCH, bestselling author of Duct Tape Marketing and The Commitment Engine    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Think Like Zuck is a must-read for any innovator, social entrepreneur, or business owner looking to capitalize on the success of Facebook to propel and realize their own vision.&#8221;<br />
                    -SIMON MAINWARING, New York Times bestselling author of We First    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book takes you on the ride of a lifetime and shows you how YOU can be successful! The question is: What does it take? Ekaterina gives us the answers!&#8221;<br />
                     -JEFFREY HAYZLETT, bestselling author of Running the Gauntlet and global business celebrity    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;In Think Like Zuck, you will find important principles to infuse meaning into your business strategies and inspire change. Don&#8217;t just read this book; use it.&#8221;<br />
                    -SHAWN ACHOR, author of the international bestseller The Happiness Advantage</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/think-like-zuck-the-five-business-secrets-of-facebooks-improbably-brilliant-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-ekaterina-walter-abridged/">Think Like Zuck: The Five Business Secrets of Facebook&#8217;s Improbably Brilliant CEO Mark Zuckerberg &#8211; Ekaterina Walter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world where all the news you see is defined by your salary, where you live, and who your friends are. Imagine a world where you never discover new ideas. And where you can&#8217;t have secrets. Welcome to 2011. Google and Facebook are already feeding you what they think you want to see. Advertisers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/">The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world where all the news you see is defined by your salary, where you live, and who your friends are. Imagine a world where you never discover new ideas. And where you can&#8217;t have secrets.    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to 2011.    </p>
<p>                    Google and Facebook are already feeding you what they think you want to see. Advertisers are following your every click. Your computer monitor is becoming a one-way mirror, reflecting your interests and reinforcing your prejudices.    </p>
<p>                    The internet is no longer a free, independent space. It is commercially controlled and ever more personalised. The Filter Bubble reveals how this hidden web is starting to control our lives &#8211; and shows what we can do about it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/">The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>WTF?: What&#8217;s the Future and Why It&#8217;s Up to Us &#8211; Tim O&#8217;Reilly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An indispensable guide.&#8217; Reid Hoffman, co-founder of LinkedIn &#8216;Tech&#8217;s most valuable teacher.&#8217; Forbes Silicon Valley&#8217;s leading intellectual and the founder of O&#8217;Reilly Media explores the upside and the potential downsides of our future &#8211; what he calls the &#8216;next economy&#8217;. Tim O&#8217;Reilly&#8217;s genius is to identify and explain emerging technologies with world shaking potential &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/">WTF?: What&#8217;s the Future and Why It&#8217;s Up to Us &#8211; Tim O&#8217;Reilly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An indispensable guide.&#8217; Reid Hoffman, co-founder of LinkedIn    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Tech&#8217;s most valuable teacher.&#8217; Forbes    </p>
<p>                    Silicon Valley&#8217;s leading intellectual and the founder of O&#8217;Reilly Media explores the upside and the potential downsides of our future &#8211; what he calls the &#8216;next economy&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    Tim O&#8217;Reilly&#8217;s genius is to identify and explain emerging technologies with world shaking potential &#8211; the World Wide Web, Open Source Software, Web 2.0, Open Government data, the Maker Movement, Big Data. &#8216;The man who can really can make a whole industry happen,&#8217; according to Executive Chairman of Google Eric Schmidt, O&#8217;Reilly has most recently focused on the future of work &#8211; AI, algorithms, and new approaches to business organisation that will shape our lives. He has brought together an unlikely coalition of technologists, business leaders, labour advocates, and policy makers to wrestle with these issues. In WTF? he shares the evolution of his intellectual development, applying his approach to a number of challenging issues we will face as citizens, employees, business leaders, and a nation.    </p>
<p>                    What is the future when an increasing number of jobs can be performed by intelligent machines instead of people, or only done by people in partnership with those machines? What happens to our consumer based societies &#8211; to workers and to the companies that depend on their purchasing power? Is income inequality and unemployment an inevitable consequence of technological advancement, or are there paths to a better future? What will happen to business when technology-enabled networks and marketplaces are better at deploying talent than traditional companies? What&#8217;s the future of education when on-demand learning outperforms traditional institutions? Will the fundamental social safety nets of the developed world survive the transition, and if not, what will replace them?    </p>
<p>                    The digital revolution has transformed the world of media, upending centuries-old companies and business models. Now, it is restructuring every business, every job, and every sector of society. Yet the biggest changes are still ahead. To survive, every industry and organisation will have to transform itself in multiple ways. O&#8217;Reilly explores what the next economy will mean for the world and every aspect of our lives &#8211; and what we can do to shape it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wtf-whats-the-future-and-why-its-up-to-us-tim-oreilly-abridged/">WTF?: What&#8217;s the Future and Why It&#8217;s Up to Us &#8211; Tim O&#8217;Reilly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A refreshing approach to entrepreneurship centered on staying small and avoiding growth &#8211; maximizing happiness, sustainability and profitability. Paul Jarvis left the corporate world when he realized that working in a high-pressure, high-profile world was not his idea of success. Instead, he now works for himself out of his home, and lives a much more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/">Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A refreshing approach to entrepreneurship centered on staying small and avoiding growth &#8211; maximizing happiness, sustainability and profitability.    </p>
<p>                    Paul Jarvis left the corporate world when he realized that working in a high-pressure, high-profile world was not his idea of success. Instead, he now works for himself out of his home, and lives a much more rewarding and productive life. He no longer has to contend with an environment that constantly demands more productivity, more output and more growth.    </p>
<p>                    In Company of One, Jarvis explains how you can do the same, including:    </p>
<p>                    *         Planning to set up<br />
                    *         Determining desired revenues<br />
                    *         Keeping clients happy<br />
                    *         And, of course, doing all this on your own.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Jarvis makes a compelling case for making your business better instead of bigger. A must-read for any entrepreneur who prioritizes a rich life over riches.&#8221;<br />
                     -CAL NEWPORT, bestselling author of DEEP WORK and DIGITAL MINIMALISM    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You&#8217;re not a machine, so why would you run your business like one? Company of One shows you another way. If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how to have a business that works for you-instead of the other way around-you need this book.&#8221;<br />
                    -CHRIS GUILLEBEAU, bestselling author of SIDE HUSTLE and THE $100 STARTUP</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/">Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WHAT IF YOU HAD AN ANGEL ON YOUR SIDE?&#8221;Terrific advice from a master of the angel investing game. Brian Cohen reveals the art and craft of raising angel money. An investment in this book will payoff a thousandfold.&#8221; &#8212; DR. HOWARD MORGAN, founder andpartner at First Round Capital When you connect with the right angel [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/">What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WHAT IF YOU HAD AN ANGEL ON YOUR SIDE?&#8221;Terrific advice from a master of the angel investing game. Brian Cohen reveals the art and craft of raising angel money. An investment in this book will payoff a thousandfold.&#8221; &#8212; DR. HOWARD MORGAN, founder andpartner at First Round Capital    </p>
<p>                    When you connect with the right angel investor, it&#8217;s like finding a new best friend&#8211;you just have to know what makes him or her happy.    </p>
<p>                    Smart funding is waiting for smart founders. Raising funds is all about connecting with the investor who&#8217;s right for you&#8211;and What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know shows you exactly how to succeed.    </p>
<p>                    Veteran early-stage investor Brian Cohen knows how to spot a great company destined for success, and in this groundbreaking book he offers soup-to-nuts guidance for anyentrepreneur seeking to launch an invention, a product, or a great new idea into a receptive marketplace.    </p>
<p>                    As chairman of the board of directors of the New York Angels, Cohen is one of the most engaged angel investors out there today. The first investor in Pinterest, he describes exactly what angels want to see, hear, and feelbefore they take out their checkbooks:    </p>
<p>                    A clear exit strategy before the startup even launchesFacts that turn &#8220;due&#8221; diligence into &#8220;do&#8221; diligenceAuthenticity&#8211;&#8220;save your spinning for the fitness center&#8221;Proof that you &#8220;live inside the customer&#8217;s head&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Cohen gives invaluable insight into how the most successful angels view due diligence, friends and family money, crowdfunding, team building, scalability, iteration, exit strategies&#8211;and much more.    </p>
<p>                    This one-of-a-kind book provides a rare look inside the minds of people who are in the business of funding businesses just like yours.    </p>
<p>                    Read What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know to get your best shot at funding for your product after your very first pitch.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR WHAT EVERY ANGEL INVESTOR WANTS YOU TO KNOW:&#8221;Brian Cohen is truly the entrepreneur&#8217;s best friend. Cohen and Kador haven distilled their first-hand experiences into an intensely personal, highly readablejourney into the mind of angels that should be kept at the bedside of every startup CEO.&#8221; &#8212; DAVID S. ROSE, founder, New York Angels, and CEO, Gust    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Meet one of the fundamental building blocks of the entrepreneurial scene. In one easy-to-read package, readers now have the wisdom of Brian Cohen, perhaps themost well-connected investor/entrepreneur in New York.&#8221; &#8212; MURAT AKTIHANOGLU, founder and managing director, Entrepreneurs Roundtable Accelerator    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know gives you an actionable checklist for success in fund-raising and entrepreneurship. Cohen and Kador provide anexhilarating ride for those who want to pilot their own business.&#8221; &#8212; REED HOLDEN, serial entrepreneur and author of Negotiating with Backbone    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Personal insights from a seasoned angel investor. An important addition to the reading list for today&#8217;s entrepreneurs.&#8221; &#8212; SCOTT CASE, CEO, Startup America Partnership    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know is a must-read for entrepreneurs and investors who want to fi nance startup dreams&#8211;an accessible, jargon-free,practical primer.&#8221; &#8212; WHITNEY JOHNSON, author of Dare, Dream, Do: Remarkable Things Happen When You Dare to Dream and cofounder, Rose Park Advisors    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;While [this] book is anecdotal, [the authors] discuss in depth how angels view a potential investment as well as how they evaluate its prospects. This is the book&#8217;s strength. Recommended. All levels of students, entrepreneurs, practitioners.&#8221; &#8212; CHOICE</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/">What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UnMarketing : Everything Has Changed and Nothing is Different &#8211; Scott Stratten, Alison Stratten (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unmarketing-everything-has-changed-and-nothing-is-different-scott-stratten-alison-stratten-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unmarketing-everything-has-changed-and-nothing-is-different-scott-stratten-alison-stratten-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>UnMarket to build trust and make lifelong customers! In 2009, Scott Stratten and Alison Stratten wrote the bestselling UnMarketing: Stop Marketing, Start Engaging and began a journey that would take them around the world sharing their message of engagement with corporations, entrepreneurs, and students.They are now back with this second edition, because Everything has Changed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unmarketing-everything-has-changed-and-nothing-is-different-scott-stratten-alison-stratten-abridged/">UnMarketing : Everything Has Changed and Nothing is Different &#8211; Scott Stratten, Alison Stratten (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>UnMarket to build trust and make lifelong customers! In 2009, Scott Stratten and Alison Stratten wrote the bestselling UnMarketing: Stop Marketing, Start Engaging and began a journey that would take them around the world sharing their message of engagement with corporations, entrepreneurs, and students.They are now back with this second edition, because Everything has Changed and Nothing is Different, with all the brilliance of the first edition, plus new content and commentary to reflect the rapidly changing landscape we all live, buy, and work in today. For generations, marketing has been hypocritical. We&#8217;ve been taught to market to others in ways we hate being marketed to (cold-calling, flyers, ads, etc.). So why do we still keep trying the same stale marketing moves? UnMarketing shows you how to unlearn the old ways and consistently attract and engage the right customers. You&#8217;ll stop just pushing out your message and praying that it sticks somewhere. Potential and current customers want to be listened to, validated, and have a platform to be heard-especially online.<br />
                    With UnMarketing, you&#8217;ll create a relationship with your customers, and make yourself the logical choice for their needs. We know you&#8217;ve been told to act like other people, talk like other people, and market like all the people, but it is time for you to unlearn everything and start to UnMarket yourself. UnMarketing includes the latest information on: Idea Creation, Viral Marketing and Video, Marketing to Millennials, Authenticity, Transparency and Immediacy, Ethics and Affiliates, Social Media Platforming, UnPodcasting, Word of Mouth, Customer Service, Consumer Advocacy and Leadership. With examples of what to do, and what not to do, from small business right up to worldwide corporations in areas such as real estate, travel, service, retail, and B2B.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unmarketing-everything-has-changed-and-nothing-is-different-scott-stratten-alison-stratten-abridged/">UnMarketing : Everything Has Changed and Nothing is Different &#8211; Scott Stratten, Alison Stratten (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smarter Screen : What Your Business Can Learn from the Way Consumers Think Online &#8211; Shlomo Benartzi, Jonah Lehrer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The typical office worker now spends the majority of their waking hours staring at a screen. In the 21st century, every business is a digital business, which is why it&#8217;s so critical to understand how we think and behave online. Acclaimed behavioural economist Shlomo Benartzi has teamed up with science writer Jonah Lehrer to reveal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/">The Smarter Screen : What Your Business Can Learn from the Way Consumers Think Online &#8211; Shlomo Benartzi, Jonah Lehrer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The typical office worker now spends the majority of their waking hours staring at a screen. In the 21st century, every business is a digital business, which is why it&#8217;s so critical to understand how we think and behave online.    </p>
<p>                    Acclaimed behavioural economist Shlomo Benartzi has teamed up with science writer Jonah Lehrer to reveal a toolkit of cues and nudges for the digital age. Using provocative case-studies and engaging reader exercises, Benartzi shows how businesses can update their nudges to help consumers make better decisions on screens. Up-to-the-minute research will help optimise your business&#8217;s online presence, from designing a webshop that helps your customers find what they are looking for, to laying out your website so that it both attracts and holds attention.    </p>
<p>                    This book will help you transform the challenges of the digital world into powerful new opportunities that will drive your success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/">The Smarter Screen : What Your Business Can Learn from the Way Consumers Think Online &#8211; Shlomo Benartzi, Jonah Lehrer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Content Rules : How to Create Killer Blogs, Podcasts, Videos, Ebooks, Webinars (and More) That Engage Customers and Ignite Your Business &#8211; Ann Handley, C. C. Chapman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/content-rules-how-to-create-killer-blogs-podcasts-videos-ebooks-webinars-and-more-that-engage-customers-and-ignite-your-business-ann-handley-c-c-chapman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/content-rules-how-to-create-killer-blogs-podcasts-videos-ebooks-webinars-and-more-that-engage-customers-and-ignite-your-business-ann-handley-c-c-chapman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The guide to creating engaging web content and building a loyal following, revised and updated Blogs, YouTube, Facebook, Twitter, Google+, and other platforms are giving everyone a &#8220;voice,&#8221; including organizations and their customers. So how do you create the stories, videos, and blog posts that cultivate fans, arouse passion for your products or services, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-rules-how-to-create-killer-blogs-podcasts-videos-ebooks-webinars-and-more-that-engage-customers-and-ignite-your-business-ann-handley-c-c-chapman-abridged/">Content Rules : How to Create Killer Blogs, Podcasts, Videos, Ebooks, Webinars (and More) That Engage Customers and Ignite Your Business &#8211; Ann Handley, C. C. Chapman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The guide to creating engaging web content and building a loyal following, revised and updated Blogs, YouTube, Facebook, Twitter, Google+, and other platforms are giving everyone a &#8220;voice,&#8221; including organizations and their customers. So how do you create the stories, videos, and blog posts that cultivate fans, arouse passion for your products or services, and ignite your business? Content Rules equips you for online success as a one-stop source on the art and science of developing content that people care about. This coverage is interwoven with case studies of companies successfully spreading their ideas online and using them to establish credibility and build a loyal customer base.<br />
                    * Find an authentic &#8220;voice&#8221; and craft bold content that will resonate with prospects and buyers and encourage them to share it with others * Leverage social media and social tools to get your content and ideas distributed as widely as possible * Understand why you are generating content getting to the meat of your message in practical, commonsense language, and defining the goals of your content strategy * Write in a way that powerfully communicates your service, product, or message across various Web mediums * Boost your online presence and engage with customers and prospects like never before with Content Rules.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-rules-how-to-create-killer-blogs-podcasts-videos-ebooks-webinars-and-more-that-engage-customers-and-ignite-your-business-ann-handley-c-c-chapman-abridged/">Content Rules : How to Create Killer Blogs, Podcasts, Videos, Ebooks, Webinars (and More) That Engage Customers and Ignite Your Business &#8211; Ann Handley, C. C. Chapman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Reputation Economy : How to Optimise Your Digital Footprint in a World Where Your Reputation Is Your Most Valuable Asset &#8211; Michael Fertik, David Thompson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-reputation-economy-how-to-optimise-your-digital-footprint-in-a-world-where-your-reputation-is-your-most-valuable-asset-michael-fertik-david-thompson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-reputation-economy-how-to-optimise-your-digital-footprint-in-a-world-where-your-reputation-is-your-most-valuable-asset-michael-fertik-david-thompson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a world where technology allows companies to gather, aggregate and analyse data about us that includes our buying habits, our financial behavior, our professional and personal networks, and even our physical whereabouts &#8211; our digital reputations are becoming our most valuable currency. Whether you like it or not, everywhere you go, other people will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-reputation-economy-how-to-optimise-your-digital-footprint-in-a-world-where-your-reputation-is-your-most-valuable-asset-michael-fertik-david-thompson-abridged/">The Reputation Economy : How to Optimise Your Digital Footprint in a World Where Your Reputation Is Your Most Valuable Asset &#8211; Michael Fertik, David Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a world where technology allows companies to gather, aggregate and analyse data about us that includes our buying habits, our financial behavior, our professional and personal networks, and even our physical whereabouts &#8211; our digital reputations are becoming our most valuable currency. Whether you like it or not, everywhere you go, other people will be able to instantly access information about your reputation &#8211; with or without your knowledge or consent.    </p>
<p>                    In The Reputation Economy, Michael Fertik reveals the secrets used to optimise the digital reputations and improve the lives of millions of users of Reputation.com.     </p>
<p>                    Discover:<br />
                    *Which keywords to include in your CV, performance review, and LinkedIn profile to ensure you come up at the top of recruiters and potential employers&#8217; search results<br />
                    *How to curate your on and offline activity in way that will reduce the risk profile (and therefore your premiums) calculated by insurers<br />
                    *How to lure venture capital for your business idea or start-up, court low interest rates from investors, and garner the attention of tech giants like Google and Microsoft<br />
                    *How to hide the negative information (or information that doesn&#8217;t match how you want to be perceived) that&#8217;s out in the ether. There&#8217;s nothing you can do to erase that digital footprint, but there are tricks you can use to keep it from being discovered.     </p>
<p>                    It will also show how you can use all this technology evaluate others&#8217; reputations so you always know who you&#8217;re dealing with, whether it&#8217;s a potential employee, investor or romantic partner.     </p>
<p>                    In short, The Reputation Economy will show you how to become &#8216;reputation rich&#8217; in a world where your digital reputation is as valuable as the cash in your wallet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-reputation-economy-how-to-optimise-your-digital-footprint-in-a-world-where-your-reputation-is-your-most-valuable-asset-michael-fertik-david-thompson-abridged/">The Reputation Economy : How to Optimise Your Digital Footprint in a World Where Your Reputation Is Your Most Valuable Asset &#8211; Michael Fertik, David Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Podcasting Marketing Strategy : A Complete Guide to Creating, Publishing and Monetizing a Successful Podcast &#8211; Daniel Rowles, Ciaran Rogers (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/podcasting-marketing-strategy-a-complete-guide-to-creating-publishing-and-monetizing-a-successful-podcast-daniel-rowles-ciaran-rogers-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Music: Consumer/user Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Music: Professional]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/podcasting-marketing-strategy-a-complete-guide-to-creating-publishing-and-monetizing-a-successful-podcast-daniel-rowles-ciaran-rogers-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Take advantage of the skyrocketing popularity of podcasts and learn how your business can use the unique opportunity to stand out and drive loyal engagement with target audiences, using this complete guide to podcast marketing &#8211; written by the hosts of the global top ten iTunes podcast, The Digital Marketing Podcast. Podcasting is a hugely [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/podcasting-marketing-strategy-a-complete-guide-to-creating-publishing-and-monetizing-a-successful-podcast-daniel-rowles-ciaran-rogers-abridged/">Podcasting Marketing Strategy : A Complete Guide to Creating, Publishing and Monetizing a Successful Podcast &#8211; Daniel Rowles, Ciaran Rogers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Take advantage of the skyrocketing popularity of podcasts and learn how your business can use the unique opportunity to stand out and drive loyal engagement with target audiences, using this complete guide to podcast marketing &#8211; written by the hosts of the global top ten iTunes podcast, The Digital Marketing Podcast.    </p>
<p>                    Podcasting is a hugely persuasive, yet under-utilized channel accessed by an affluent and influential demographic. In a crowded and noisy digital environment, it gives organizations, brand builders and marketers the unique opportunity to stand out and drive engagement with target audiences, with accurate and measurable levels of allegiance that can only be dreamed of on other digital channels.    </p>
<p>                    This book is the complete guide to the podcast environment. It describes the importance of podcasting for businesses and explains why, uniquely, it has the highest level of consumer commitment than any other social media.     </p>
<p>                    Written by award-winning author Daniel Rowles, and his co-host of the global top ten iTunes podcast, The Digital Marketing Podcast, this book:    </p>
<p>                    -Explains how podcasting can drive business results<br />
                    -Advises on how to record, edit, and advertise your content<br />
                    -Provides a unique digital marketing toolkit<br />
                    -Is supported by case studies from influential organizations around the globe    </p>
<p>                    Quite simply, Podcasting Marketing Strategy is the definitive authority to making and publishing podcasts that deliver quantifiable results.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/podcasting-marketing-strategy-a-complete-guide-to-creating-publishing-and-monetizing-a-successful-podcast-daniel-rowles-ciaran-rogers-abridged/">Podcasting Marketing Strategy : A Complete Guide to Creating, Publishing and Monetizing a Successful Podcast &#8211; Daniel Rowles, Ciaran Rogers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are you an entrepreneur about to create a new web application? If you want to maximize your chances of building something customers want, this book demonstrates ways to apply and test techniques for customer development, Lean Startup, and bootstrapping. Learn how to identify and engage customers throughout the development cycle so you can focus on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/">Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are you an entrepreneur about to create a new web application? If you want to maximize your chances of building something customers want, this book demonstrates ways to apply and test techniques for customer development, Lean Startup, and bootstrapping. Learn how to identify and engage customers throughout the development cycle so you can focus on building a product that people will actually buy and use. By rigorously following the techniques described in Running Lean, you can eliminate waste &#8211; whether it&#8217;s time, money, effort, or all of the above &#8211; and get your product to market quickly. Refined through the real-world experiences of dozens of startup companies, these techniques are part of Eric Ries&#8217; Lean Startup methodology. Principles covered in this book include: * Find a problem worth solving, then define a solution * Demo before building * Pricing is part of the product * Maximize for speed, learning, and focus * Build a continuous feedback loop with customers throughout the product development cycle * Right Action, Right Time * Build a path to customers from day one</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/running-lean-ash-maurya-abridged/">Running Lean &#8211; Ash Maurya (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutionary Groups & Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. To manage the risks and spread the benefits, we have to act now, and in the interest of stakeholders everywhere&#8217; Andrew McAfee, Co-Founder, MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy, MIT, USA    </p>
<p>                    We are on the brink of the Fourth Industrial Revolution. And this one will be unlike any other in human history.    </p>
<p>                    Characterized by new technologies fusing the physical, digital and biological worlds, the Fourth Industrial Revolution will impact all disciplines, economies and industries &#8211; and it will do so at an unprecedented rate. World Economic Forum data predicts that by 2025 we will see: commercial use of nanomaterials 200 times stronger than steel and a million times thinner than human hair; the first transplant of a 3D-printed liver; 10% of all cars on US roads being driverless; and much more besides.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Industrial Revolution, Schwab outlines the key technologies driving this revolution, discusses the major impacts on governments, businesses, civil society and individuals, and offers bold ideas for what can be done to shape a better future for all.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The technologies of the Fourth Industrial Revolution are extraordinary. Leadership has to be equally extraordinary to manage the complexities of systemic change&#8217; Eric Schmidt, Technical Advisor, Alphabet, USA</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behind the Cloud : The Untold Story of How Salesforce.com Went from Idea to Billion-Dollar Company-and Revolutionized an Industry &#8211; Marc Benioff, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/behind-the-cloud-the-untold-story-of-how-salesforce-com-went-from-idea-to-billion-dollar-company-and-revolutionized-an-industry-marc-benioff-carlye-adler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/behind-the-cloud-the-untold-story-of-how-salesforce-com-went-from-idea-to-billion-dollar-company-and-revolutionized-an-industry-marc-benioff-carlye-adler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How did salesforce.com grow from a start up in a rented apartment into the world&#8217;s fastest growing software company in less than a decade? For the first time, Marc Benioff, the visionary founder, chairman and CEO of salesforce.com, tells how he and his team created and used new business, technology, and philanthropic models tailored to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behind-the-cloud-the-untold-story-of-how-salesforce-com-went-from-idea-to-billion-dollar-company-and-revolutionized-an-industry-marc-benioff-carlye-adler-abridged/">Behind the Cloud : The Untold Story of How Salesforce.com Went from Idea to Billion-Dollar Company-and Revolutionized an Industry &#8211; Marc Benioff, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How did salesforce.com grow from a start up in a rented apartment into the world&#8217;s fastest growing software company in less than a decade? For the first time, Marc Benioff, the visionary founder, chairman and CEO of salesforce.com, tells how he and his team created and used new business, technology, and philanthropic models tailored to this time of extraordinary change. Showing how salesforce.com not only survived the dotcom implosion of 2001, but went on to define itself as the leader of the cloud computing revolution and spark a $46-billion dollar industry, Benioff&#8217;s story will help business leaders and entrepreneurs stand out, innovate better, and grow faster in any economic climate. In Behind the Cloud, Benioff shares the strategies that have inspired employees, turned customers into evangelists, leveraged an ecosystem of partners, and allowed innovation to flourish.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behind-the-cloud-the-untold-story-of-how-salesforce-com-went-from-idea-to-billion-dollar-company-and-revolutionized-an-industry-marc-benioff-carlye-adler-abridged/">Behind the Cloud : The Untold Story of How Salesforce.com Went from Idea to Billion-Dollar Company-and Revolutionized an Industry &#8211; Marc Benioff, Carlye Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New Rules of Marketing and PR : How to Use Content Marketing, Podcasting, Social Media, AI, Live Video, and Newsjacking to Reach Buyers Directly &#8211; David Meerman Scott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-new-rules-of-marketing-and-pr-how-to-use-content-marketing-podcasting-social-media-ai-live-video-and-newsjacking-to-reach-buyers-directly-david-meerman-scott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-rules-of-marketing-and-pr-how-to-use-content-marketing-podcasting-social-media-ai-live-video-and-newsjacking-to-reach-buyers-directly-david-meerman-scott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The seventh edition of the pioneering guide to generating attention for your idea or business, packed with new and updated information In the Digital Age, marketing tactics seem to change on a day-to-day basis. As the ways we communicate continue to evolve, keeping pace with the latest trends in social media, the newest online videos, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-rules-of-marketing-and-pr-how-to-use-content-marketing-podcasting-social-media-ai-live-video-and-newsjacking-to-reach-buyers-directly-david-meerman-scott-abridged/">The New Rules of Marketing and PR : How to Use Content Marketing, Podcasting, Social Media, AI, Live Video, and Newsjacking to Reach Buyers Directly &#8211; David Meerman Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The seventh edition of the pioneering guide to generating attention for your idea or business, packed with new and updated information    </p>
<p>                     In the Digital Age, marketing tactics seem to change on a day-to-day basis. As the ways we communicate continue to evolve, keeping pace with the latest trends in social media, the newest online videos, the latest mobile apps, and all the other high-tech influences can seem an almost impossible task. How can you keep your product or service from getting lost in the digital clutter? The seventh edition of The New Rules of Marketing and PR provides everything you need to speak directly to your audience, make a strong personal connection, and generate the best kind of attention for your business.    </p>
<p>                     An international bestseller with more than 400,000 copies sold in twenty-nine languages, this revolutionary guide gives you a proven, step-by-step plan for leveraging the power of technology to get your message seen and heard by the right people at the right time. You will learn the latest approaches for highly effective public relations, marketing, and customer communications-all at a fraction of the cost of traditional advertising!    </p>
<p>                     The latest edition of The New Rules of Marketing &#038; PR has been completely revised and updated to present more innovative methods and cutting-edge strategies than ever. The new content shows you how to harness AI and machine learning to automate routine tasks so you can focus on marketing and PR strategy. Your life is already AI-assisted. Your marketing should be too! Still the definitive guide on the future of marketing, this must-have resource will help you:    </p>
<p>                    Incorporate the new rules that will keep you ahead of the digital marketing curve<br />
                    Make your marketing and public relations real-time by incorporating techniques like newsjacking to generate instant attention when your audience is eager to hear from you<br />
                    Use web-based communication technologies to their fullest potential<br />
                    Gain valuable insights through compelling case studies and real-world examples<br />
                    Take advantage of marketing opportunities on platforms like Facebook Live and Snapchat    </p>
<p>                     The seventh edition of The New Rules of Marketing and PR: How to Use Content Marketing, Podcasting, Social Media, AI, Live Video, and Newsjacking to Reach Buyers Directly is the ideal resource for entrepreneurs, business owners, marketers, PR professionals, and managers in organizations of all types and sizes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-rules-of-marketing-and-pr-how-to-use-content-marketing-podcasting-social-media-ai-live-video-and-newsjacking-to-reach-buyers-directly-david-meerman-scott-abridged/">The New Rules of Marketing and PR : How to Use Content Marketing, Podcasting, Social Media, AI, Live Video, and Newsjacking to Reach Buyers Directly &#8211; David Meerman Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Make Your Mark : The Creative&#8217;s Guide to Building a Business with Impact &#8211; Jocelyn K. Glei (Editor) (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/make-your-mark-the-creatives-guide-to-building-a-business-with-impact-jocelyn-k-glei-editor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/make-your-mark-the-creatives-guide-to-building-a-business-with-impact-jocelyn-k-glei-editor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Finally, a business book for makers, not managers. Are you ready to &#8220;make a dent in the universe&#8221;? As a creative, you no longer have to take a backseat. In fact, stepping up and embracing entrepreneurship is the fastest route to impact. But where do you start? And what sets the businesses that succeed apart? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-your-mark-the-creatives-guide-to-building-a-business-with-impact-jocelyn-k-glei-editor-abridged/">Make Your Mark : The Creative&#8217;s Guide to Building a Business with Impact &#8211; Jocelyn K. Glei (Editor) (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Finally, a business book for makers, not managers.     </p>
<p>                    Are you ready to &#8220;make a dent in the universe&#8221;? As a creative, you no longer have to take a backseat. In fact, stepping up and embracing entrepreneurship is the fastest route to impact. But where do you start? And what sets the businesses that succeed apart?     </p>
<p>                    To find out, we asked the bright minds behind companies like Google X, Warby Parker, Facebook, O&#8217;Reilly Media, and more to share their startup wisdom. Featuring hard-won wisdom from 20 leading entrepreneurs and designers, 99U&#8217;s Make Your Mark will arm you with practical insights for launching a purpose-driven business, refining your product, delighting your customers, inspiring your team&#8211;and ultimately&#8211;making something that matters.     </p>
<p>                    Make Your Mark features contributions from: Will Allen, Rich Armstrong, Warren Berger, Sean Blanda, Neil Blumenthal, Craig Dalton, Jane ni Dhulchaointigh, Aaron Dignan, Andy Dunn, Joel Gascoigne, Seth Godin, Chris Guillebeau, Emily Heyward, John Maeda, David Marquet, Tim O&#8217;Reilly, Shane Snow, Sebastian Thrun, Keith Yamashita, and Julie Zhuo. Plus, a foreword from Behance founder Scott Belsky</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-your-mark-the-creatives-guide-to-building-a-business-with-impact-jocelyn-k-glei-editor-abridged/">Make Your Mark : The Creative&#8217;s Guide to Building a Business with Impact &#8211; Jocelyn K. Glei (Editor) (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Success Secrets of Social Media Marketing Superstars &#8211; Entrepreneur Press, Mitch Meyerson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/success-secrets-of-social-media-marketing-superstars-entrepreneur-press-mitch-meyerson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/success-secrets-of-social-media-marketing-superstars-entrepreneur-press-mitch-meyerson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;An amazing book &#8211; top social media professionals provide the &#8216;inside&#8217; tips on how they stay on top and stay organized. Filled with specific tricks, tips and strategies to cut the clutter and build your business, you really want to read this one.&#8221; &#8211;Dave Evans, Author of Social Media Marketing: An Hour a DayRevelations from [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/success-secrets-of-social-media-marketing-superstars-entrepreneur-press-mitch-meyerson-abridged/">Success Secrets of Social Media Marketing Superstars &#8211; Entrepreneur Press, Mitch Meyerson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;An amazing book &#8211; top social media professionals provide the &#8216;inside&#8217; tips on how they stay on top and stay organized.  Filled with specific tricks, tips and strategies to cut the clutter and build your business, you really want to read this one.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Dave Evans, Author of Social Media Marketing: An Hour a DayRevelations from Top Social Media Revolution Leaders<br />
                    Online marketing expert Mitch Meyerson presents you with an unmatched advantage into the world of social media &#8211; the priceless secrets, strategies, tactics and insights of more than 20 of today&#8217;s social media elite. Handpicked to cover almost every aspect of social media marketing, Meyerson and this distinguished team of experts open their playbooks and teach you how to create effective social media campaigns to cut through the clutter, reach out to millions and grow your business.Features:    </p>
<p>                    Proven tips and tactics from 20+ top social media marketersThe biggest mistakes businesses make with social media and how to fix themActionable plans for all areas including social networks, blogs, web TV and mobile marketingReal-world case studies, best practices and proven techniques from the expertsDetailed list of resources<br />
                    Contributions from World-Class Social Media Experts:    </p>
<p>                    Keith Ferrazi &#038; Tahl Raz: Relationship StrategyBrian Clark: Psychology of Social MediaMitch Meyerson: Online MarketingAnn Handley: Creating ContentGary Vaynerchuk: Building Mega-FollowingsAndy Willbes: PersonalityChris Brogan: Building CommunitiesJoel Comm: Success QualitiesCraig Valentine: Communicate with ImpactStarr Hall: Building ProfitsDan Janal: PR StrategiesMichael Stelzner: Go ViralDenise Wakeman: Business BlogsMari Smith: FacebookDeborah Cole Micek: TwitterBarbara Rozgonyi: LinkedInJulie Perry: YouTubePaul Colligan: PodcastingChris Garrett: Social BookmarkingKim Dushinski: Mobile MarketingShama Kabani: Online VideoDave Evans: One Hour a Day</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/success-secrets-of-social-media-marketing-superstars-entrepreneur-press-mitch-meyerson-abridged/">Success Secrets of Social Media Marketing Superstars &#8211; Entrepreneur Press, Mitch Meyerson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Airbnb Story : How Three Guys Disrupted an Industry, Made Billions of Dollars &#8230; and Plenty of Enemies &#8211; Leigh Gallagher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-airbnb-story-how-three-guys-disrupted-an-industry-made-billions-of-dollars-and-plenty-of-enemies-leigh-gallagher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hospitality Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-airbnb-story-how-three-guys-disrupted-an-industry-made-billions-of-dollars-and-plenty-of-enemies-leigh-gallagher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An engrossing story of audacious entrepreneurism&#8217; &#8212; Charles Duhigg &#8216;Captures the remarkable journey of Airbnb exceedingly well&#8217; &#8212; Reid Hoffman &#8216;fast paced, fun dive into one of the seminal firms of our time&#8217; &#8212; Rana Foroohar In 2008, two broke art school graduates and their coder-whiz friend set up a platform that &#8211; in less [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-airbnb-story-how-three-guys-disrupted-an-industry-made-billions-of-dollars-and-plenty-of-enemies-leigh-gallagher-abridged/">The Airbnb Story : How Three Guys Disrupted an Industry, Made Billions of Dollars &#8230; and Plenty of Enemies &#8211; Leigh Gallagher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An engrossing story of audacious entrepreneurism&#8217; &#8212; Charles Duhigg    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Captures the remarkable journey of Airbnb exceedingly well&#8217; &#8212; Reid Hoffman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;fast paced, fun dive into one of the seminal firms of our time&#8217; &#8212; Rana Foroohar     </p>
<p>                    In 2008, two broke art school graduates and their coder-whiz friend set up a platform that &#8211; in less than a decade &#8211; became one of the largest provider of accommodations in the world.  Now valued at $31 billion, Airbnb is in the very top tier of Silicon Valley&#8217;s &#8216;unicorn&#8217; startups.    </p>
<p>                    Yet the company has not been without controversy &#8211; disrupting a $500 billion hotel industry makes you a few enemies.  This is also a story of regulators who want to shut it down, hotel industry leaders who want it to disappear and neighbourhoods that struggle with private homes open for public rental.  But beyond the headlines and the horror stories, Airbnb has changed the terms of travel for a whole generation &#8211; where a sense of belonging has built trust between hosts and guests seeking a more original travel experience that hotels have struggled to replicate.    </p>
<p>                    This is the first, definitive book to tell the remarkable story behind Airbnb in all its forms &#8211; cultural zeitgeist, hotel disruptor, enemy to regulators &#8211; and the first in-depth character study of its leader Brian Chesky, the company&#8217;s curious co-founder and CEO.  It reveals what got Airbnb where it is today, why they are nothing like Uber, and where they are going next.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-airbnb-story-how-three-guys-disrupted-an-industry-made-billions-of-dollars-and-plenty-of-enemies-leigh-gallagher-abridged/">The Airbnb Story : How Three Guys Disrupted an Industry, Made Billions of Dollars &#8230; and Plenty of Enemies &#8211; Leigh Gallagher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Throwing Rocks at the Google Bus : How Growth Became the Enemy of Prosperity &#8211; Douglas Rushkoff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/throwing-rocks-at-the-google-bus-how-growth-became-the-enemy-of-prosperity-douglas-rushkoff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/throwing-rocks-at-the-google-bus-how-growth-became-the-enemy-of-prosperity-douglas-rushkoff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why doesn&#8217;t the explosive growth of companies like Facebook and Uber deliver more prosperity for everyone? What is the systemic problem that sets the rich against the poor and the technologists against everybody else? When protesters shattered the windows of a bus carrying Google employees to work, their anger may have been justifiable, but it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/throwing-rocks-at-the-google-bus-how-growth-became-the-enemy-of-prosperity-douglas-rushkoff-abridged/">Throwing Rocks at the Google Bus : How Growth Became the Enemy of Prosperity &#8211; Douglas Rushkoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why doesn&#8217;t the explosive growth of companies like Facebook and Uber deliver more prosperity for everyone?     </p>
<p>                    What is the systemic problem that sets the rich against the poor and the technologists against everybody else?     </p>
<p>                    When protesters shattered the windows of a bus carrying Google employees to work, their anger may have been justifiable, but it was misdirected. The true conflict of our age isn&#8217;t between the unem­ployed and the digital elite, or even the 99 percent and the 1 percent. Rather, a tornado of technological improvements has spun our economic program out of control, and humanity as a whole&#8211;the protesters and the Google employees as well as the shareholders and the executives&#8211;are all trapped by the consequences. It&#8217;s time to optimize our economy for the human beings it&#8217;s supposed to be serving.     </p>
<p>                    In this groundbreaking book, acclaimed media scholar and author Douglas Rushkoff tells us how to combine the best of human nature with the best of modern technology. Tying together disparate threads&#8211;big data, the rise of robots and AI, the increasing participation of algorithms in stock market trading, the gig economy, the collapse of the eurozone&#8211;Rushkoff provides a critical vocabulary for our economic moment and a nuanced portrait of humans and commerce at a critical crossroads.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/throwing-rocks-at-the-google-bus-how-growth-became-the-enemy-of-prosperity-douglas-rushkoff-abridged/">Throwing Rocks at the Google Bus : How Growth Became the Enemy of Prosperity &#8211; Douglas Rushkoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amazon : How the World&#8217;s Most Relentless Retailer will Continue to Revolutionize Commerce &#8211; Natalie Berg, Miya Knights (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/amazon-how-the-worlds-most-relentless-retailer-will-continue-to-revolutionize-commerce-natalie-berg-miya-knights-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/amazon-how-the-worlds-most-relentless-retailer-will-continue-to-revolutionize-commerce-natalie-berg-miya-knights-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is the secret to Amazon&#8217;s success? What does the ecommerce giant have in store for the future? Explore the disruptive new retail strategies of the world&#8217;s most relentless retailer and gain valuable lessons that can be applied to any business in the ecommerce sector, with original insight from the company as it continues to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/amazon-how-the-worlds-most-relentless-retailer-will-continue-to-revolutionize-commerce-natalie-berg-miya-knights-abridged/">Amazon : How the World&#8217;s Most Relentless Retailer will Continue to Revolutionize Commerce &#8211; Natalie Berg, Miya Knights (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What is the secret to Amazon&#8217;s success? What does the ecommerce giant have in store for the future? Explore the disruptive new retail strategies of the world&#8217;s most relentless retailer and gain valuable lessons that can be applied to any business in the ecommerce sector, with original insight from the company as it continues to revolutionize itself even further.    </p>
<p>                    The retail industry is facing unprecedented challenges. Across all sectors and markets, retailers are shifting their business models and customer engagement strategies to ensure they survive. The rise of online shopping, and its primary player, Amazon, is at the heart of these changes and opportunities.    </p>
<p>                    Amazon&#8217;s relentless dissatisfaction with the status quo is what makes it such an extraordinary retailer. This book explores whether Amazon has what it takes to become a credible grocery retailer, and as it transitions to bricks and mortar retailing, investigates whether Amazon&#8217;s stores can be as compelling as its online offering.    </p>
<p>                    Exploring the ecommerce giant&#8217;s strategies, Amazon offers unique insight into how innovations such voice technology, checkout-free stores and its Prime ecosystem, will fundamentally change the way consumers shop.    </p>
<p>                    Written by industry leading retail analysts who have spent decades providing research-based analysis and opinion on retail strategy and enterprise technology use in retail, Amazon analyzes the impact these initiatives will have on the wider retail sector and the lessons that can be learned from its unprecedented rise to dominance &#8211; as stores of the future become less about transactions and more about experiences.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/amazon-how-the-worlds-most-relentless-retailer-will-continue-to-revolutionize-commerce-natalie-berg-miya-knights-abridged/">Amazon : How the World&#8217;s Most Relentless Retailer will Continue to Revolutionize Commerce &#8211; Natalie Berg, Miya Knights (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
