<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Age Groups: Children Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/age-groups-children/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/age-groups-children/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Age Groups: Children Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/age-groups-children/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Raising Cain : Protecting the Emotional Life of Boys &#8211; Dan Kindlon, Michael Thompson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/raising-cain-protecting-the-emotional-life-of-boys-dan-kindlon-michael-thompson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/raising-cain-protecting-the-emotional-life-of-boys-dan-kindlon-michael-thompson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Raising Cain, Dan Kindlon, Ph.D., and Michael Thompson, Ph.D., two of the country&#8217;s leading child psychologists, share what they have learned in more than thirty-five years of combined experience working with boys and their families. They reveal a nation of boys who are hurting&#8211;sad, afraid, angry, and silent. Kindlon and Thompson set out to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raising-cain-protecting-the-emotional-life-of-boys-dan-kindlon-michael-thompson-abridged/">Raising Cain : Protecting the Emotional Life of Boys &#8211; Dan Kindlon, Michael Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Raising Cain, Dan Kindlon, Ph.D., and Michael Thompson, Ph.D., two of the country&#8217;s leading child psychologists, share what they have learned in more than thirty-five years of combined experience working with boys and their families. They reveal a nation of boys who are hurting&#8211;sad, afraid, angry, and silent. Kindlon and Thompson set out to answer this basic, crucial question: What do boys need that they&#8217;re not getting? They illuminate the forces that threaten our boys, teaching them to believe that &#8220;cool&#8221; equals macho strength and stoicism. Cutting through outdated theories of &#8220;mother blame,&#8221; &#8220;boy biology,&#8221; and &#8220;testosterone,&#8221; the authors shed light on the destructive emotional training our boys receive&#8211;the emotional miseducation of boys. Kindlon and Thompson make a compelling case that emotional literacy is the most valuable gift we can offer our sons, urging parents to recognize the price boys pay when we hold them to an impossible standard of manhood. They identify the social and emotional challenges that boys encounter in school and show how parents can help boys cultivate emotional awareness and empathy&#8211;giving them the vital connections and support they need to navigate the social pressures of youth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/raising-cain-protecting-the-emotional-life-of-boys-dan-kindlon-michael-thompson-abridged/">Raising Cain : Protecting the Emotional Life of Boys &#8211; Dan Kindlon, Michael Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Nonfiction Pick; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly Best Book of the Year Clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair takes an in-depth look at how the Internet and the digital revolution are profoundly changing childhood and family dynamics, and offers solutions parents can use to successfully shepherd their children through the technological wilderness. As the focus of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/">The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Nonfiction Pick; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly Best Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair takes an in-depth look at how the Internet and the digital revolution are profoundly changing childhood and family dynamics, and offers solutions parents can use to successfully shepherd their children through the technological wilderness.    </p>
<p>                    As the focus of the family has turned to the glow of the screen&#8211;children constantly texting their friends or going online to do homework; parents working online around the clock&#8211;everyday life is undergoing a massive transformation. Easy access to the Internet and social media has erased the boundaries that protect children from damaging exposure to excessive marketing and the unsavory aspects of adult culture. Parents often feel they are losing a meaningful connection with their children. Children are feeling lonely and alienated. The digital world is here to stay, but what are families losing with technology&#8217;s gain?    </p>
<p>                    As renowned clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair explains, families are in crisis as they face this issue, and even more so than they realize. Not only do chronic tech distractions have deep and lasting effects but children also desperately need parents to provide what tech cannot: close, significant interactions with the adults in their lives. Drawing on real-life stories from her clinical work with children and parents and her consulting work with educators and experts across the country, Steiner-Adair offers insights and advice that can help parents achieve greater understanding, authority, and confidence as they engage with the tech revolution unfolding in their living rooms.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/">The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Strength Switch : how the new science of strength-based parenting helps your child and your teen flourish &#8211; Lea Waters (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-strength-switch-how-the-new-science-of-strength-based-parenting-helps-your-child-and-your-teen-flourish-lea-waters-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-strength-switch-how-the-new-science-of-strength-based-parenting-helps-your-child-and-your-teen-flourish-lea-waters-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your child&#8217;s potential by helping them build their strengths. As a strengths-based scientist for more than 20 years, Dr Lea Waters has witnessed first-hand how focusing on our children&#8217;s strengths, rather than correcting their weaknesses, can help build resilience and optimism, and offer protection from depression and anxiety. In this game-changing book, she argues [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-strength-switch-how-the-new-science-of-strength-based-parenting-helps-your-child-and-your-teen-flourish-lea-waters-abridged/">The Strength Switch : how the new science of strength-based parenting helps your child and your teen flourish &#8211; Lea Waters (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unlock your child&#8217;s potential by helping them build their strengths.    </p>
<p>                    As a strengths-based scientist for more than 20 years, Dr Lea Waters has witnessed first-hand how focusing on our children&#8217;s strengths, rather than correcting their weaknesses, can help build resilience and optimism, and offer protection from depression and anxiety.     </p>
<p>                    In this game-changing book, she argues that by throwing the &#8216;strength switch&#8217; parents can encourage creativity, develop their children&#8217;s self-esteem and energy, and enhance achievement &#8211; and she offers easy-to-follow steps to teach parents how.    </p>
<p>                    With specific tips for interacting with your kids and your teens, The Strength Switch offers all the tools parents need to discover talents in their children, use positive emotions as a resource, build strong brains, and deal with problem behaviours and difficult emotions. This essential book will show parents how a small shift can yield enormous results.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-strength-switch-how-the-new-science-of-strength-based-parenting-helps-your-child-and-your-teen-flourish-lea-waters-abridged/">The Strength Switch : how the new science of strength-based parenting helps your child and your teen flourish &#8211; Lea Waters (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thirty Million Words : Building a Child&#8217;s Brain &#8211; Dana Suskind (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The founder and director of the Thirty Million Words Initiative, Professor Dana Suskind, explains why the most important&#8211;and astoundingly simple&#8211;thing you can do for your child&#8217;s future success in life is to to talk to them. What nurtures the brain to optimum intelligence and stability? It is a secret hiding in plain sight: the most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/">Thirty Million Words : Building a Child&#8217;s Brain &#8211; Dana Suskind (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The founder and director of the Thirty Million Words Initiative, Professor Dana Suskind, explains why the most important&#8211;and astoundingly simple&#8211;thing you can do for your child&#8217;s future success in life is to to talk to them.     </p>
<p>                    What nurtures the brain to optimum intelligence and stability?     </p>
<p>                    It is a secret hiding in plain sight: the most important thing we can do for our children is to have conversations with them. The way you talk with your growing child literally builds his or her brain. Parent talk can drastically improve school readiness and lifelong learning in everything from math to art. Indeed, parent-child talk is a fundamental, critical factor in building grit, self-control, leadership skills, and generosity. It is crucial to making the most in life of the luck you have with your genes.     </p>
<p>                    This landmark account of a new scientific perspective describes what works and what doesn&#8217;t (baby talk is fine; relentless correction isn&#8217;t). Discover how to create the best language environments for children by following the simple structure of the Three Ts: Tune In; Talk More; Take Turns. Dr. Suskind and her colleagues around the country have worked with thousands of families; now their insights and successful, measured approaches are available to all.     </p>
<p>                    This is the first book to reveal how and why the first step in nurturing successful lives is talking to children in ways that build their brains. Your family&#8211;and our nation&#8211;need to know.     </p>
<p>                    *Nominated for the Books for a Better Life Award*</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirty-million-words-building-a-childs-brain-dana-suskind-abridged/">Thirty Million Words : Building a Child&#8217;s Brain &#8211; Dana Suskind (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First They Killed My Father : A Daughter of Cambodia Remembers &#8211; Loung Ung (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/first-they-killed-my-father-a-daughter-of-cambodia-remembers-loung-ung-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Postwar 20th Century History, From C 1945 To C 2000]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/first-they-killed-my-father-a-daughter-of-cambodia-remembers-loung-ung-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Soon to be a major film, co-written and directed by Angelina Jolie Pitt Until the age of five, Loung Ung lived in Phnom Penh, one of seven children of a high-ranking government official. She was a precocious child who loved the open city markets, fried crickets, chicken fights and being cheeky to her parents. When [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-they-killed-my-father-a-daughter-of-cambodia-remembers-loung-ung-abridged/">First They Killed My Father : A Daughter of Cambodia Remembers &#8211; Loung Ung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Soon to be a major film, co-written and directed by Angelina Jolie Pitt    </p>
<p>                    Until the age of five, Loung Ung lived in Phnom Penh, one of seven children of a high-ranking government official. She was a precocious child who loved the open city markets, fried crickets, chicken fights and being cheeky to her parents.    </p>
<p>                    When Pol Pot&#8217;s Khmer Rouge army stormed into Phnom Penh in April 1975, Loung&#8217;s family fled their home and were eventually forced to disperse to survive. Loung was trained as a child soldier while her brothers and sisters were sent to labour camps. The surviving siblings were only finally reunited after the Vietnamese penetrated Cambodia and started to destroy the Khmer Rouge.    </p>
<p>                    Bolstered by the bravery of one brother, the vision of the others and the gentle kindness of her sister, Loung forged on to create for herself a courageous new life.    </p>
<p>                    First They Killed My Father is an unforgettable book told through the voice of the young and fearless Loung. It is a shocking and tragic tale of a girl who was determined to survive despite the odds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-they-killed-my-father-a-daughter-of-cambodia-remembers-loung-ung-abridged/">First They Killed My Father : A Daughter of Cambodia Remembers &#8211; Loung Ung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happy Kids Handbook : How to Raise Joyful Children in a Stressful World &#8211; Katie Hurley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happy-kids-handbook-how-to-raise-joyful-children-in-a-stressful-world-katie-hurley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happy-kids-handbook-how-to-raise-joyful-children-in-a-stressful-world-katie-hurley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With all the parenting information out there and the constant pressure to be the &#8220;perfect&#8221; parent, it seems as if many parents have lost track of one very important piece of the parenting puzzle: raising happy kids. Parenting today has gotten far too complicated. It&#8217;s never been the easiest job in the world, but with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happy-kids-handbook-how-to-raise-joyful-children-in-a-stressful-world-katie-hurley-abridged/">The Happy Kids Handbook : How to Raise Joyful Children in a Stressful World &#8211; Katie Hurley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With all the parenting information out there and the constant pressure to be the &#8220;perfect&#8221; parent, it seems as if many parents have lost track of one very important piece of the parenting puzzle: raising happy kids.     </p>
<p>                     Parenting today has gotten far too complicated. It&#8217;s never been the easiest job in the world, but with all the &#8220;parenting advice&#8221; parents are met with at every corner, it&#8217;s hard not to become bewildered. It seems that in the past it was a good deal simpler. You made sure there was dinner on the table and the kids got to school on time and no one set anything on fire, and you called it a success. But today everybody has a different method for dealing with the madness&#8211;attachment parenting, free-range parenting, mindful parenting. And who is to say one is more right or better than another? How do you choose?     </p>
<p>                     The truth is that whatever drumbeat you march to, all parents would agree that we just want our kids to be happy. It seems like a no-brainer, right? But in the face of all the many parenting theories out there, happiness feels like it has become incidental. That&#8217;s where The Happy Kid Handbook by child and adolescent psychotherapist and parenting expert Katie Hurley comes in. She shows parents how happiness is the key to raising confident, capable children. It&#8217;s not about giving in every time your child wants something so they won&#8217;t feel bad when you say no, or making sure that they&#8217;re taking that art class, and the ballet class, and the soccer class (to help with their creativity and their coordination and all that excess energy). Happiness is about parenting the individual, because not every child is the same, and not every child will respond to parenting the same way. By exploring the differences among introverts, extroverts, and everything in between, this definitive guide to parenting offers parents the specific strategies they need to meet their child exactly where he or she needs to be met from a social-emotional perspective. A back-to-basics guide to parenting, The Happy Kid Handbook is a must-have for any parent hoping to be the best parent they can be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happy-kids-handbook-how-to-raise-joyful-children-in-a-stressful-world-katie-hurley-abridged/">The Happy Kids Handbook : How to Raise Joyful Children in a Stressful World &#8211; Katie Hurley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
