<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Management Of Land &amp; Natural Resources Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/management-of-land-natural-resources/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/management-of-land-natural-resources/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Management Of Land &amp; Natural Resources Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/management-of-land-natural-resources/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Let There Be Water : Israel&#8217;s Solution for a Water-Starved World &#8211; Siegel, Seth M. (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/let-there-be-water-israels-solution-for-a-water-starved-world-siegel-seth-m-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drought & Water Supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hydrology & The Hydrosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Irrigation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Supply & Treatment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/let-there-be-water-israels-solution-for-a-water-starved-world-siegel-seth-m-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With hardly a day without a water-crisis story somewhere, Let There Be Water offers prescriptions on how countries, cities, and businesses can avoid the worst of it. With sixty percent of the country in a desert and despite a rapidly growing population, Israel has been jumping ahead of the water-innovation curve for decades. Beyond securing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-there-be-water-israels-solution-for-a-water-starved-world-siegel-seth-m-abridged/">Let There Be Water : Israel&#8217;s Solution for a Water-Starved World &#8211; Siegel, Seth M. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With hardly a day without a water-crisis story somewhere, Let There Be Water offers prescriptions on how countries, cities, and businesses can avoid the worst of it. With sixty percent of the country in a desert and despite a rapidly growing population, Israel has been jumping ahead of the water-innovation curve for decades. Beyond securing its own water supply, Israel has also created a high-export industry in water technology, a timely example of how countries can build their economies while making the world better. Built on meticulous research and hundreds of interviews with both world leaders and experts in the field, Let There Be Water tells the inspiring story of how this all came to be. The author is now widely considered to be one of the nation&#8217;s go-to authorities on water and has in the last year alone, spoken to more than 160 different organisations, civic groups, and universities all across the country.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-there-be-water-israels-solution-for-a-water-starved-world-siegel-seth-m-abridged/">Let There Be Water : Israel&#8217;s Solution for a Water-Starved World &#8211; Siegel, Seth M. (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moral Case For Fossil Fuels &#8211; Afterword by Alex Epstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/moral-case-for-fossil-fuels-afterword-by-alex-epstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy Industries & Utilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fossil Fuel Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/moral-case-for-fossil-fuels-afterword-by-alex-epstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Could everything we know about fossil fuels be wrong? For decades, environmentalists have told us that using fossil fuels is a self-destructive addiction that will destroy our planet. Yet at the same time, by every measure of human well-being, from life expectancy to clean water to climate safety, life has been getting better and better. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moral-case-for-fossil-fuels-afterword-by-alex-epstein-abridged/">Moral Case For Fossil Fuels &#8211; Afterword by Alex Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Could everything we know about fossil fuels be wrong?     </p>
<p>                    For decades, environmentalists have told us that using fossil fuels is a self-destructive addiction that will destroy our planet. Yet at the same time, by every measure of human well-being, from life expectancy to clean water to climate safety, life has been getting better and better.     </p>
<p>                    How can this be?     </p>
<p>                    The explanation, energy expert Alex Epstein argues in The Moral Case for Fossil Fuels, is that we usually hear only one side of the story. We&#8217;re taught to think only of the negatives of fossil fuels, their risks and side effects, but not their positives&#8211;their unique ability to provide cheap, reliable energy for a world of seven billion people. And the moral significance of cheap, reliable energy, Epstein argues, is woefully underrated. Energy is our ability to improve every single aspect of life, whether economic or environmental.     </p>
<p>                    If we look at the big picture of fossil fuels compared with the alternatives, the overall impact of using fossil fuels is to make the world a far better place. We are morally obligated to use more fossil fuels for the sake of our economy and our environment.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on original insights and cutting-edge research, Epstein argues that most of what we hear about fossil fuels is a myth. For instance . . .     </p>
<p>                    Myth Fossil fuels are dirty.<br />
                    Truth The environmental benefits of using fossil fuels far outweigh the risks. Fossil fuels don&#8217;t take a naturally clean environment and make it dirty; they take a naturally dirty environment and make it clean. They don&#8217;t take a naturally safe climate and make it dangerous; they take a naturally dangerous climate and make it ever safer.     </p>
<p>                    Myth Fossil fuels are unsustainable, so we should strive to use &#8220;renewable&#8221; solar and wind.<br />
                    Truth The sun and wind are intermittent, unreliable fuels that always need backup from a reliable source of energy&#8211;usually fossil fuels. There are huge amounts of fossil fuels left, and we have plenty of time to find something cheaper.     </p>
<p>                    Myth Fossil fuels are hurting the developing world.<br />
                    Truth Fossil fuels are the key to improving the quality of life for billions of people in the developing world. If we withhold them, access to clean water plummets, critical medical machines like incubators become impossible to operate, and life expectancy drops significantly. Calls to &#8220;get off fossil fuels&#8221; are calls to degrade the lives of innocent people who merely want the same opportunities we enjoy in the West.     </p>
<p>                    Taking everything into account, including the facts about climate change, Epstein argues that &#8220;fossil fuels are easy to misunderstand and demonize, but they are absolutely good to use. And they absolutely need to be championed. . . . Mankind&#8217;s use of fossil fuels is supremely virtuous&#8211;because human life is the standard of value and because using fossil fuels transforms our environment to make it wonderful for human life.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/moral-case-for-fossil-fuels-afterword-by-alex-epstein-abridged/">Moral Case For Fossil Fuels &#8211; Afterword by Alex Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Salt &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rocks, Minerals & Fossils]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Homer called it a divine substance. Plato described it as especially dear to the gods. As Mark Kurlansky so brilliantly relates here, salt has shaped civilisation from the beginning, and its story is a glittering, often surprising part of the history of mankind. Wars have been fought over salt and, while salt taxes secured empires [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/">Salt &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Homer called it a divine substance. Plato described it as especially dear to the gods. As Mark Kurlansky so brilliantly relates here, salt has shaped civilisation from the beginning, and its story is a glittering, often surprising part of the history of mankind. Wars have been fought over salt and, while salt taxes secured empires across Europe and Asia, they have also inspired revolution &#8211; Gandhi&#8217;s salt march in 1930 began the overthrow of British rule in India.     </p>
<p>                    From the rural Sichuan province where the last home-made soya sauce is produced to the Cheshire brine springs that supplied salt around the globe, Mark Kurlansky has produced a kaleidoscope of world history, a multi-layered masterpiece that blends political, commercial, scientific, religious and culinary records into a rich and memorable tale.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/">Salt &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agricultural Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Beverage Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainable Agriculture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is the future of food looking bleak &#8211; or better than ever? At a time when every day brings news of drought and famine, Amanda Little investigates what it will take to feed a hotter, hungrier, more crowded world. She explores the past along with the present and discovers startling innovations: remote-control crops, vertical farms, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/">The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is the future of food looking bleak &#8211; or better than ever?    </p>
<p>                    At a time when every day brings news of drought and famine, Amanda Little investigates what it will take to feed a hotter, hungrier, more crowded world.    </p>
<p>                    She explores the past along with the present and discovers startling innovations: remote-control crops, vertical farms, robot weedkillers, lab-grown meat, 3D-printed meals, water networks run by supercomputers, cloud seeding and sensors that monitor the microclimate of individual plants. She meets the creative and controversial minds changing the face of modern food production, and tackles fears over genetic modification with hard facts.    </p>
<p>                    The Fate of Food is a fascinating look at the threats and opportunities that lie ahead as we struggle for food security.    </p>
<p>                    Faced with a perilous future, it gives us reason to hope.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/">The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Triumph of Seeds : How Grains, Nuts, Kernels, Pulses, and Pips Conquered the Plant Kingdom and Shaped Human History &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-triumph-of-seeds-how-grains-nuts-kernels-pulses-and-pips-conquered-the-plant-kingdom-and-shaped-human-history-thor-hanson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gardening Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trees, Wildflowers & Plants]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-triumph-of-seeds-how-grains-nuts-kernels-pulses-and-pips-conquered-the-plant-kingdom-and-shaped-human-history-thor-hanson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We live in a world of seeds. From our morning toast to the cotton in our clothes, they are quite literally the stuff and staff of life: supporting diets, economies, and civilizations around the globe. Just as the search for nutmeg and pepper drove the Age of Discovery, coffee beans fueled the Enlightenment and cottonseed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-triumph-of-seeds-how-grains-nuts-kernels-pulses-and-pips-conquered-the-plant-kingdom-and-shaped-human-history-thor-hanson-abridged/">The Triumph of Seeds : How Grains, Nuts, Kernels, Pulses, and Pips Conquered the Plant Kingdom and Shaped Human History &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We live in a world of seeds. From our morning toast to the cotton in our clothes, they are quite literally the stuff and staff of life: supporting diets, economies, and civilizations around the globe. Just as the search for nutmeg and pepper drove the Age of Discovery, coffee beans fueled the Enlightenment and cottonseed sparked the Industrial Revolution. Seeds are fundamental objects of beauty, evolutionary wonders, and simple fascinations. Yet, despite their importance, seeds are often seen as commonplace, their extraordinary natural and human histories overlooked. Thanks to this stunning new book, they can be overlooked no more. This is a book of knowledge, adventure, and wonder, spun by an award-winning writer with both the charm of a fireside story-teller and the hard-won expertise of a field biologist. A fascinating scientific adventure, it is essential reading for anyone who loves to see a plant grow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-triumph-of-seeds-how-grains-nuts-kernels-pulses-and-pips-conquered-the-plant-kingdom-and-shaped-human-history-thor-hanson-abridged/">The Triumph of Seeds : How Grains, Nuts, Kernels, Pulses, and Pips Conquered the Plant Kingdom and Shaped Human History &#8211; Thor Hanson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rare : The High-Stakes Race to Satisfy Our Need for the Scarcest Metals on Earth &#8211; Keith Veronese (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rare-the-high-stakes-race-to-satisfy-our-need-for-the-scarcest-metals-on-earth-keith-veronese-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inorganic Chemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Materials Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metals Technology / Metallurgy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rare-the-high-stakes-race-to-satisfy-our-need-for-the-scarcest-metals-on-earth-keith-veronese-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How will your life change when the supply of tantalum dries up? You may have never heard of this unusual metal, but without it smartphones would be instantly less omniscient, video game systems would falter, and laptops fail. Tantalum is not alone. Rhodium. Osmium. Niobium. Such refugees from the bottom of the periodic table are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rare-the-high-stakes-race-to-satisfy-our-need-for-the-scarcest-metals-on-earth-keith-veronese-abridged/">Rare : The High-Stakes Race to Satisfy Our Need for the Scarcest Metals on Earth &#8211; Keith Veronese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How will your life change when the supply of tantalum dries up? You may have never heard of this unusual metal, but without it smartphones would be instantly less omniscient, video game systems would falter, and laptops fail. Tantalum is not alone. Rhodium. Osmium. Niobium. Such refugees from the bottom of the periodic table are key components of many consumer products like cell phones, hybrid car batteries, and flat screen televisions, as well as sophisticated medical devices and even weapon systems. Their versatile properties have led manufacturers to seek these elements out to maximize longevity, value, and efficiency, but not without a human price.     </p>
<p>                    In addition to explaining the chemistry behind rare earth metals, Rare delves into the economic and geopolitical issues surrounding these &#8220;conflict minerals,&#8221; blending tales of financial and political struggles with glimpses into the human lives that are shattered by the race to secure them. In the past decade, the Congo has been ravaged by tribal wars fought to obtain control of tantalum, tungsten, and tin supplies in the region, with over five million people dying at the crossroads of supply and demand. A burgeoning black market in China, Africa, and India is propped up by school-age children retrieving and purifying these metals while risking their lives and health in the process. Fears of future political struggles inside China, the world&#8217;s largest supplier of these metals, have already sent the United States, Great Britain, and Japan racing to find alternative sources.    </p>
<p>                    Will scientists be able to create lab substitutes for some or all of these metals? Will Afghanistan be the next big supplier of rare metals? What happens when the limited supply runs out? Whatever the answers, it is clear that our modern lifestyle, dependent on technology, is far from stable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rare-the-high-stakes-race-to-satisfy-our-need-for-the-scarcest-metals-on-earth-keith-veronese-abridged/">Rare : The High-Stakes Race to Satisfy Our Need for the Scarcest Metals on Earth &#8211; Keith Veronese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
