<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Legal History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/legal-history/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/legal-history/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Legal History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/legal-history/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Innocent Man : Murder and Injustice in a Small Town &#8211; John Grisham</title>
		<link>/the-innocent-man-murder-and-injustice-in-a-small-town-john-grisham/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Law & Procedure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Penology & Punishment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Police & Security Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-innocent-man-murder-and-injustice-in-a-small-town-john-grisham/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the town of Ada, Oklahoma, Ron Williamson was going to be the next Mickey Mantle. But on his way to the Big Leagues, Ron stumbled, his dreams broken by drinking, drugs, and women. Then, on a winter night in 1982, not far from Ron&#8217;s home, a young cocktail waitress named Debra Sue Carter was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innocent-man-murder-and-injustice-in-a-small-town-john-grisham/">The Innocent Man : Murder and Injustice in a Small Town &#8211; John Grisham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the town of Ada, Oklahoma, Ron Williamson was going to be the next Mickey Mantle. But on his way to the Big Leagues, Ron stumbled, his dreams broken by drinking, drugs, and women. Then, on a winter night in 1982, not far from Ron&#8217;s home, a young cocktail waitress named Debra Sue Carter was savagely murdered. The investigation led nowhere. Until, on the flimsiest evidence, it led to Ron Williamson. The washed-up small-town hero was charged, tried, and sentenced to death&#8211;in a trial littered with lying witnesses and tainted evidence that would shatter a man&#8217;s already broken life&#8230;and let a true killer go free. Impeccably researched, grippingly told, filled with eleventh-hour drama, John Grisham&#8217;s first work of nonfiction reads like a page-turning legal thriller. It is a book that will terrify anyone who believes in the presumption of innocence&#8211;a book no American can afford to miss.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innocent-man-murder-and-injustice-in-a-small-town-john-grisham/">The Innocent Man : Murder and Injustice in a Small Town &#8211; John Grisham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Boundaries Of Desire : A Century of Good Sex, Bad Laws, and Changing Identities &#8211; Eric Berkowitz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-boundaries-of-desire-a-century-of-good-sex-bad-laws-and-changing-identities-eric-berkowitz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Sexual Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-boundaries-of-desire-a-century-of-good-sex-bad-laws-and-changing-identities-eric-berkowitz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The act of reproduction, and its variants, never change much, but our ideas about the meaning of sex are in constant flux. Switch a decade, cross a border, or traverse class lines and the harmless pleasures of one group become the gravest crimes in another. Combining meticulous research and lively storytelling, The Boundaries of Desire [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-boundaries-of-desire-a-century-of-good-sex-bad-laws-and-changing-identities-eric-berkowitz-abridged/">The Boundaries Of Desire : A Century of Good Sex, Bad Laws, and Changing Identities &#8211; Eric Berkowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The act of reproduction, and its variants, never change much, but our ideas about the meaning of sex are in constant flux. Switch a decade, cross a border, or traverse class lines and the harmless pleasures of one group become the gravest crimes in another.     </p>
<p>                    Combining meticulous research and lively storytelling, The Boundaries of Desire traces the fast-moving bloodsport of sex law over the past century, and challenges our most cherished notions about family, power, gender, and identity.     </p>
<p>                    Starting when courts censored birth control information as pornography and let men rape their wives, and continuing through the &#8220;sexual revolution&#8221; and into the present day (when rape, gay rights, sex trafficking, and sex on the internet saturate the news), Berkowitz shows how the law has remained out of synch with the convulsive changes in sexual morality.     </p>
<p>                    By focusing on the stories of real people, Berkowitz adds a compelling human element to what might otherwise be faceless legal battles. The law is made by people, after all, and nothing sparks intolerance &#8211; on the left and right &#8212; more than sex. Ultimately, Berkowitz shows the emptiness of sanctimonious condemnation, and argues that sexual questions are too subtle and volatile for simple, catch-all solutions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-boundaries-of-desire-a-century-of-good-sex-bad-laws-and-changing-identities-eric-berkowitz-abridged/">The Boundaries Of Desire : A Century of Good Sex, Bad Laws, and Changing Identities &#8211; Eric Berkowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Run of His Life : The People v. O. J. Simpson &#8211; Jeffrey Toobin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-run-of-his-life-the-people-v-o-j-simpson-jeffrey-toobin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Law & Procedure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-run-of-his-life-the-people-v-o-j-simpson-jeffrey-toobin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The inspiration for American Crime Story: The People v. O. J. Simpson on FX, starring Cuba Gooding, Jr., John Travolta, David Schwimmer, and Connie Britton The definitive account of the O. J. Simpson trial, The Run of His Life is a prodigious feat of reporting that could have been written [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-run-of-his-life-the-people-v-o-j-simpson-jeffrey-toobin-abridged/">The Run of His Life : The People v. O. J. Simpson &#8211; Jeffrey Toobin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The inspiration for American Crime Story: The People v. O. J. Simpson on FX, starring Cuba Gooding, Jr., John Travolta, David Schwimmer, and Connie Britton     </p>
<p>                     The definitive account of the O. J. Simpson trial, The Run of His Life is a prodigious feat of reporting that could have been written only by the foremost legal journalist of our time. First published less than a year after the infamous verdict, Jeffrey Toobin&#8217;s nonfiction masterpiece tells the whole story, from the murders of Nicole Brown Simpson and Ronald Goldman to the ruthless gamesmanship behind the scenes of &#8220;the trial of the century.&#8221; Rich in character, as propulsive as a legal thriller, this enduring narrative continues to shock and fascinate with its candid depiction of the human drama that upended American life.    </p>
<p>                     Praise for The Run of His Life    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This is the book to read.&#8221;&#8211;Michiko Kakutani, The New York Times      </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This book stands out as a gripping and colorful account of the crime and trial that captured the world&#8217;s attention.&#8221;&#8211;Boston Sunday Globe    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A real page-turner . . . strips away the months of circuslike televised proceedings and the sordid tell-all books and lays out a simple, but devastating, synopsis of the case.&#8221;&#8211;Entertainment Weekly    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A well-written, profoundly rational analysis of the trial and, more specifically, the lawyers who conducted it.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Engrossing . . . Toobin&#8217;s insight into the motives and mind-set of key players sets this Simpson book apart from the pack.&#8221;&#8211;People (one of the top ten books of the year)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-run-of-his-life-the-people-v-o-j-simpson-jeffrey-toobin-abridged/">The Run of His Life : The People v. O. J. Simpson &#8211; Jeffrey Toobin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
