<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Literary Studies: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/literary-studies-general/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/literary-studies-general/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Literary Studies: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/literary-studies-general/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve &#8211; Stephen Greenblatt</title>
		<link>/the-rise-and-fall-of-adam-and-eve-stephen-greenblatt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewish Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rise-and-fall-of-adam-and-eve-stephen-greenblatt/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bolder, even, than the ambitious books for which Stephen Greenblatt is already renowned, The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve explores the enduring story of humanity&#8217;s first parents. Comprising only a few ancient verses, the story of Adam and Eve has served as a mirror in which we seem to glimpse the whole, long [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-adam-and-eve-stephen-greenblatt/">The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve &#8211; Stephen Greenblatt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bolder, even, than the ambitious books for which Stephen Greenblatt is already renowned, The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve explores the enduring story of humanity&#8217;s first parents. Comprising only a few ancient verses, the story of Adam and Eve has served as a mirror in which we seem to glimpse the whole, long history of our fears and desires, as both a hymn to human responsibility and a dark fable about human wretchedness.    </p>
<p>                     Tracking the tale into the deep past, Greenblatt uncovers the tremendous theological, artistic, and cultural investment over centuries that made these fictional figures so profoundly resonant in the Jewish, Christian, and Muslim worlds and, finally, so very &#8220;real&#8221; to millions of people even in the present. With the uncanny brilliance he previously brought to his depictions of William Shakespeare and Poggio Bracciolini (the humanist monk who is the protagonist of The Swerve), Greenblatt explores the intensely personal engagement of Augustine, Durer, and Milton in this mammoth project of collective creation, while he also limns the diversity of the story&#8217;s offspring: rich allegory, vicious misogyny, deep moral insight, and some of the greatest triumphs of art and literature.    </p>
<p>                     The biblical origin story, Greenblatt argues, is a model for what the humanities still have to offer: not the scientific nature of things, but rather a deep encounter with problems that have gripped our species for as long as we can recall and that continue to fascinate and trouble us today.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-adam-and-eve-stephen-greenblatt/">The Rise and Fall of Adam and Eve &#8211; Stephen Greenblatt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me by David Goggins : Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds &#8211; Get The Key Ideas From Can&#8217;t Hurt Me In Minutes &#8211; Quick Reads</title>
		<link>/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are You Ready To Get The Most Out Of Yourself And Out Of Life?When it comes to getting fit, a lot of us find excuses. We&#8217;re too busy; we sleep in, we don&#8217;t feel like it. But what happens when we stop making excuses? David Goggins stopped making excuses and started giving life 100%. If [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads/">Summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me by David Goggins : Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds &#8211; Get The Key Ideas From Can&#8217;t Hurt Me In Minutes &#8211; Quick Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are You Ready To Get The Most Out Of Yourself And Out Of Life?When it comes to getting fit, a lot of us find excuses. We&#8217;re too busy; we sleep in, we don&#8217;t feel like it. But what happens when we stop making excuses? </p>
<p>                    David Goggins stopped making excuses and started giving life 100%. If you&#8217;ve heard his name, it&#8217;s probably because this former Air Force serviceman and Navy SEAL is also an ultra-endurance athlete and once held a world record for the most pull-ups in 24 hours. He is one of the toughest people alive. </p>
<p>                    His success wasn&#8217;t handed to him, though. Goggins had a terribly hard life. After surviving an abusive and traumatic childhood, he faced poverty and became overweight in his twenties. As a result of the trauma from his childhood, he was nearly illiterate as a teen. None of this stopped him, though. </p>
<p>                    Now he&#8217;s here to help you stop backing away from challenges, too. In his book &#8220;Can&#8217;t Hurt Me: Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds,&#8221; he teaches that the difficult things in life make you the strongest. </p>
<p>                    If you are ready to get the most out of yourself and out of life, then you need this summary by Quick Reads. After reading this summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me, you&#8217;ll discover: What it takes to master your mind from someone who has overcome huge obstacles and become one of the toughest people on earth.How to break your mental roadblocks and take control of your success.How you can always come out stronger from any condition no matter how much trauma you&#8217;ve experiencedHow to work hard and push yourself to be your best self instead of believing in overnight successHow to be ready to dump your excuses and do and become better than ever before. And most importantly, how to become the master of your mind and achieve more than you thought possible using the 40% rule and much more&#8230; See the Table of Contents to find out by clicking on &#8220;Look inside.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    So, if you want a concise yet very informative summary book on Can&#8217;t Hurt Me that can help you grasp the insights, key ideas, and main points within minutes, simply scroll up and click the &#8220;BUY NOW&#8221; button for instant access! </p>
<p>                    DISCLAIMER:  </p>
<p>                    This is not the official book, but an unofficial summary and analysis of the book &#8220;Can&#8217;t Hurt Me: Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds by David Goggins bringing you the main points, concise and easy to consume. It is a way to get you the key ideas from great books and bestsellers in minutes, not hours. More knowledge in less time! </p>
<p>                    QUICK READS = Learn Faster &#038; Get Smarter!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads/">Summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me by David Goggins : Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds &#8211; Get The Key Ideas From Can&#8217;t Hurt Me In Minutes &#8211; Quick Reads</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stephen King, American Master : A Creepy Corpus of Facts About Stephen King &#038; His Work &#8211; Stephen Spignesi</title>
		<link>/stephen-king-american-master-a-creepy-corpus-of-facts-about-stephen-king-his-work-stephen-spignesi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction Companions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Horror]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Novelists & Prose Writers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stephen-king-american-master-a-creepy-corpus-of-facts-about-stephen-king-his-work-stephen-spignesi/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fun and informative compendium for Stephen King fans-interviews, essays, and loads of facts and details about all of his work. Fascinating facts, trivia, and little-known details about the Master of the Macabre&#8217;s life and work, plus interviews, essays, and insights for King fans, from the casual to the fanatical! Did you know&#8230;? In his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stephen-king-american-master-a-creepy-corpus-of-facts-about-stephen-king-his-work-stephen-spignesi/">Stephen King, American Master : A Creepy Corpus of Facts About Stephen King &#038; His Work &#8211; Stephen Spignesi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fun and informative compendium for Stephen King fans-interviews, essays, and loads of facts and details about all of his work.</p>
<p>                    Fascinating facts, trivia, and little-known details about the Master of the Macabre&#8217;s life and work, plus interviews, essays, and insights for King fans, from the casual to the fanatical!</p>
<p>                    Did you know&#8230;?</p>
<p>                    In his early teens, Stephen King sold typed copies of his short stories at school.<br />
                    King originally thought his novel Pet Sematary was too frightening to publish.<br />
                    King&#8217;s legendary Dark Tower series took him more than 30 years to write.<br />
                    Thinner was the novel that revealed his &#8220;Richard Bachman&#8221; pseudonym to the world.<br />
                    King wrote The Eyes of the Dragon for his daughter Naomi.<br />
                    He has never liked Stanley Kubrick&#8217;s film version of his novel The Shining.<br />
                    It took him four years to write what some consider his magnum opus, IT.<br />
                    The 2017 film version of IT has grossed more than $700 million worldwide.<br />
                    In addition to novels, King has written essays, plays, screenplays, and even poetry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stephen-king-american-master-a-creepy-corpus-of-facts-about-stephen-king-his-work-stephen-spignesi/">Stephen King, American Master : A Creepy Corpus of Facts About Stephen King &#038; His Work &#8211; Stephen Spignesi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Licence to Kill : The Science of 007 &#8211; Kathryn Harkup</title>
		<link>/licence-to-kill-the-science-of-007-kathryn-harkup/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Theory & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/licence-to-kill-the-science-of-007-kathryn-harkup/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ian Fleming&#8217;s series of novels based on the adventures of the secret service agent James Bond have thrilled and delighted readers since Casino Royale first published in 1953. And when the film of Dr No was released in 1962, Bond quickly became one of the world&#8217;s favourite secret agents. The character has been through some [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/licence-to-kill-the-science-of-007-kathryn-harkup/">Licence to Kill : The Science of 007 &#8211; Kathryn Harkup</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ian Fleming&#8217;s series of novels based on the adventures of the secret service agent James Bond have thrilled and delighted readers since Casino Royale first published in 1953. And when the film of Dr No was released in 1962, Bond quickly became one of the world&#8217;s favourite secret agents. The character has been through some changes and had a few ups and downs but his popularity endures, and the film franchise is currently the fifth-highest-grossing series in history. </p>
<p>                    Science and technology have always been central to the thrilling plots than make up the world of Bond, and in this book Kathryn Harkup explores this; as in some of her previous books, she takes the angle of death as a starting point to explore the science behind the story. </p>
<p>                    Naturally, there are 007 chapters, covering the full range of Bond&#8217;s exploits, and the arms, technologies, tactics and downfalls of his various foes. </p>
<p>                    In Licence to Kill, Kathryn turns her expert eye on the world&#8217;s favourite secret agent, using the hook of Bond&#8217;s enduring popularity to discuss the realities behind the silver screen. Could our favourite Bond villains actually achieve world domination? Were the huge variety of weapons and technology in Bond&#8217;s arsenal ever actually developed? And would 007 actually escape all those close shaves with his life intact? Readers will see the Bond films through new eyes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/licence-to-kill-the-science-of-007-kathryn-harkup/">Licence to Kill : The Science of 007 &#8211; Kathryn Harkup</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World Is Not Enough : A Biography of Ian Fleming &#8211; Oliver Buckton</title>
		<link>/the-world-is-not-enough-a-biography-of-ian-fleming-oliver-buckton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Novelists & Prose Writers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-world-is-not-enough-a-biography-of-ian-fleming-oliver-buckton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The definitive history of the flamboyant life of Ian Fleming and his most famous creation, James Bond. This new biography of Ian Fleming presents a fresh and illuminating portrayal of the iconic creator of James Bond. Oliver Buckton provides the first in-depth exploration of the entire process of Ian Fleming&#8217;s writing-from initial conception, through composition, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-world-is-not-enough-a-biography-of-ian-fleming-oliver-buckton/">The World Is Not Enough : A Biography of Ian Fleming &#8211; Oliver Buckton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The definitive history of the flamboyant life of Ian Fleming and his most famous creation, James Bond.    </p>
<p>                    This new biography of Ian Fleming presents a fresh and illuminating portrayal of the iconic creator of James Bond. Oliver Buckton provides the first in-depth exploration of the entire process of Ian Fleming&#8217;s writing-from initial conception, through composition, to his involvement in the innovative publication methods of his books. He also investigates the vital impact of Fleming&#8217;s work in naval intelligence during World War Two on his later writings, especially the wartime operations he planned and executed and how they drove the plots of the James Bond novels. Buckton considers the vital role of wartime deception, disinformation, and propaganda in shaping Fleming&#8217;s later techniques and imaginative creations. Offering a radically new view of Fleming&#8217;s relationships with women, Buckton traces the role of strong, independent, and intelligent women such as Maud Russell, Phyllis Bottome, and his wife, Ann, on Fleming&#8217;s portrayal of female characters. The book concludes with a thorough analysis of the James Bond films from Eon productions, and their influence in promoting, while also distorting, the public&#8217;s recognition of Fleming&#8217;s writing.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-world-is-not-enough-a-biography-of-ian-fleming-oliver-buckton/">The World Is Not Enough : A Biography of Ian Fleming &#8211; Oliver Buckton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sexual Personae : Art &#038; Decadence from Nefertiti to Emily Dickinson &#8211; Camille Paglia</title>
		<link>/sexual-personae-art-decadence-from-nefertiti-to-emily-dickinson-camille-paglia/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sexual-personae-art-decadence-from-nefertiti-to-emily-dickinson-camille-paglia/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is the fiery, provocative, and unparalleled work of feminist art criticism that launched Camille Paglia&#8217;s exceptional career as one of our most important public intellectuals. Is Emily Dickinson &#8220;the female Sade&#8221;? Is Donatello&#8217;s David a bit of pedophile pornography? What is the secret kinship between Byron and Elvis Presley, between Medusa and Madonna? How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sexual-personae-art-decadence-from-nefertiti-to-emily-dickinson-camille-paglia/">Sexual Personae : Art &#038; Decadence from Nefertiti to Emily Dickinson &#8211; Camille Paglia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here is the fiery, provocative, and unparalleled work of feminist art criticism that launched Camille Paglia&#8217;s exceptional career as one of our most important public intellectuals. Is Emily Dickinson &#8220;the female Sade&#8221;? Is Donatello&#8217;s David a bit of pedophile pornography? What is the secret kinship between Byron and Elvis Presley, between Medusa and Madonna? How do liberals and feminists&#8211;as well as conservatives&#8211;fatally misread human nature? This audacious and omnivorously learned work of guerrilla scholarship offers nothing less than a unified-field theory of Western culture, high and low, since Egyptians invented beauty&#8211;making a persuasive case for all art as a pagan battleground between male and female, form and chaos, civilization and daemonic nature.     </p>
<p>                     47 photographs.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sexual-personae-art-decadence-from-nefertiti-to-emily-dickinson-camille-paglia/">Sexual Personae : Art &#038; Decadence from Nefertiti to Emily Dickinson &#8211; Camille Paglia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>There and Back Again : J R R Tolkien and the Origins of The Hobbit &#8211; Mark Atherton</title>
		<link>/there-and-back-again-j-r-r-tolkien-and-the-origins-of-the-hobbit-mark-atherton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Novelists & Prose Writers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/there-and-back-again-j-r-r-tolkien-and-the-origins-of-the-hobbit-mark-atherton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Even the smallest person can change the course of the future.&#8217; The prophetic words of Galadriel, addressed to Frodo as he prepared to travel from Lothlorien to Mordor to destroy the One Ring, are just as pertinent to J R R Tolkien&#8217;s own fiction. For decades, hobbits and the other fantastical creatures of Middle-earth have [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/there-and-back-again-j-r-r-tolkien-and-the-origins-of-the-hobbit-mark-atherton/">There and Back Again : J R R Tolkien and the Origins of The Hobbit &#8211; Mark Atherton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Even the smallest person can change the course of the future.&#8217; The prophetic words of Galadriel, addressed to Frodo as he prepared to travel from Lothlorien to Mordor to destroy the One Ring, are just as pertinent to J R R Tolkien&#8217;s own fiction. For decades, hobbits and the other fantastical creatures of Middle-earth have captured the imaginations of a fiercely loyal tribe of readers, all enhanced by the immense success of Peter Jackson&#8217;s films: first &#8220;The Lord of the Rings&#8221;, and now his new &#8220;The Hobbit&#8221;. But for all Tolkien&#8217;s global fame and the familiarity of modern culture with Gandalf, Bilbo, Frodo and Sam, the sources of the great mythmaker&#8217;s own myth-making have been neglected. Mark Atherton here explores the chief influences on Tolkien&#8217;s work: his boyhood in the West Midlands; the landscapes and seascapes which shaped his mythologies; his experiences in World War I; his interest in Scandinavian myth; his friendships, especially with the other Oxford-based Inklings; and the relevance of his themes, especially ecological themes, to the present-day.<br />
                    &#8220;There and Back Again&#8221; offers a unique guide to the varied inspirations behind Tolkien&#8217;s life and work, and sheds new light on how a legend is born.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/there-and-back-again-j-r-r-tolkien-and-the-origins-of-the-hobbit-mark-atherton/">There and Back Again : J R R Tolkien and the Origins of The Hobbit &#8211; Mark Atherton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>the princess saves herself in this one &#8211; Amanda Lovelace, ladybookmad</title>
		<link>/the-princess-saves-herself-in-this-one-amanda-lovelace-ladybookmad/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Foreign Language Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erotic Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Poetry & Poets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry By Individual Poets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-princess-saves-herself-in-this-one-amanda-lovelace-ladybookmad/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the 2016 Goodreads Choice Award, the princess saves herself in this one is a collection of poetry about resilience. It is about writing your own ending. From Amanda Lovelace, a poetry collection in four parts: the princess, the damsel, the queen, and you. The first three sections piece together the life of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-princess-saves-herself-in-this-one-amanda-lovelace-ladybookmad/">the princess saves herself in this one &#8211; Amanda Lovelace, ladybookmad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the 2016 Goodreads Choice Award, the princess saves herself in this one is a collection of poetry about resilience. It is about writing your own ending.    </p>
<p>                     From Amanda Lovelace, a poetry collection in four parts: the princess, the damsel, the queen, and you. The first three sections piece together the life of the author while the final section serves as a note to the reader. This moving book explores love, loss, grief, healing, empowerment, and inspiration.    </p>
<p>                    the princess saves herself in this one is the first book in the &#8220;women are some kind of magic&#8221; series.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-princess-saves-herself-in-this-one-amanda-lovelace-ladybookmad/">the princess saves herself in this one &#8211; Amanda Lovelace, ladybookmad</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Times book of the year A Guardian book of the year &#8216;Magnificent&#8217;The Times &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; New Statesman &#8216;It filled me with hope&#8217; Zadie Smith What happens to our behaviour when we live most of our lives online? What does it mean to &#8216;always be optimising&#8217;? And what is it about scams and the millennial generation? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/">Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Times book of the year<br />
                              A Guardian book of the year<br />
                              &#8216;Magnificent&#8217;The Times<br />
                              &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; New Statesman<br />
                              &#8216;It filled me with hope&#8217; Zadie Smith<br />
                              What happens to our behaviour when we live most of our lives online? What does it mean to &#8216;always be optimising&#8217;? And what is it about scams and the millennial generation?    </p>
<p>                              Offering nuanced and witty reflections on feminism, reality TV, the internet, drugs, identity and more, Trick Mirror is a multifaceted, thought-provoking and entertaining response to our zeitgeist &#8211; a must-read for anyone interested in the way we live and think today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/">Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Storytelling Animal : How Stories Make Us Human &#8211; Instructor Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-storytelling-animal-how-stories-make-us-human-instructor-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-storytelling-animal-how-stories-make-us-human-instructor-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this delightful and original book, Jonathan Gottschall offers the first unified theory of storytelling. Drawing on neuroscience and evolutionary biology, The Storytelling Animal explores what stories reveal about human nature, how we process information, and think about the world. Humans live in landscapes of make-believe. We spin fantasies. We devour novels, films, and plays. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-storytelling-animal-how-stories-make-us-human-instructor-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/">The Storytelling Animal : How Stories Make Us Human &#8211; Instructor Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this delightful and original book, Jonathan Gottschall offers the first unified theory of storytelling. Drawing on neuroscience and evolutionary biology, The Storytelling Animal explores what stories reveal about human nature, how we process information, and think about the world.<br />
                    Humans live in landscapes of make-believe. We spin fantasies. We devour novels, films, and plays. Even sporting events and criminal trials unfold as narratives. Gottschall argues that stories help us navigate life&#8217;s complex social problems &#8212; just as flight simulators prepare pilots for difficult situations. Storytelling has evolved, like other behaviors, to ensure our survival. Gottschall tells us what it means to be a storytelling animal and explains how stories can change the world for the better.<br />
                    We know we are master shapers of story. The Storytelling Animal finally reveals how stories shape us.<br />
                    A NYTimes.com Editor&#8217;s Choice<br />
                    A Los Angeles Times Book Prizes Finalist<br />
                    &#8220;A jaunty, insightful new book . . . [that] draws from disparate corners of history and science to celebrate our compulsion to storify everything around us.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-storytelling-animal-how-stories-make-us-human-instructor-jonathan-gottschall-abridged/">The Storytelling Animal : How Stories Make Us Human &#8211; Instructor Jonathan Gottschall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Read and Why &#8211; Harold Bloom (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-read-and-why-harold-bloom-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Poetry & Poets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-read-and-why-harold-bloom-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new book by America&#8217;s leading literary critic on the uses of deep reading. Practical, inspirational and learned, How to Read and Why is Bloom&#8217;s manifesto for the preponderance of written culture. In the vastly influential The Western Canon, Harold Bloom outlined what we should read to understand a greater depth of the individual self. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-read-and-why-harold-bloom-abridged/">How to Read and Why &#8211; Harold Bloom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new book by America&#8217;s leading literary critic on the uses of deep reading. Practical, inspirational and learned, How to Read and Why is Bloom&#8217;s manifesto for the preponderance of written culture.    </p>
<p>                              In the vastly influential The Western Canon, Harold Bloom outlined what we should read to understand a greater depth of the individual self. How to Read and Why continues the argument and focusses on how we use literature in order to gain deeper self-awareness. Poems, stories, novels, plays and parables are all analysed as forms of writing as immersion, the language of individuality and inwardness: Shakespeare&#8217;s sonnets, the short stories of Hemingway and de Cervantes, the novels of Proust and Calvino, Sophocles&#8217;s Oedipus Rex and Mark&#8217;s Gospel. Harold Bloom also addresses the idea of why we read: increased individuality, respite from visual bombardment, a return to &#8216;deep feeling&#8217; and &#8216;deep thinking&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                              How to Read and Why is an essential book for any reader, an introduction to the world of written culture, an inspirational self-help book for students and teachers alike.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-read-and-why-harold-bloom-abridged/">How to Read and Why &#8211; Harold Bloom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Summary Analysis Of Inner Engineering : A Yogi&#8217;s Guide to Joy By Sadhguru Jaggi Vasudev &#8211; Printright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/summary-analysis-of-inner-engineering-a-yogis-guide-to-joy-by-sadhguru-jaggi-vasudev-printright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/summary-analysis-of-inner-engineering-a-yogis-guide-to-joy-by-sadhguru-jaggi-vasudev-printright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SYNOPSIS: Inner Engіnееrіng (2016) еxрlаіnѕ hоw hарріnеѕѕ саn оnlу be found wіthіn yourself. Thеѕе summaries introduce ѕріrіtuаl wisdom thаt wіll mаkе уоu hарріеr, more fulfіllеd аnd at реасе wіth thе life уоu аrе lіvіng. ABOUT THЕ AUTHОR: Sаdhguru Jаggі Vаѕudеv is аn Indіаn mуѕtіс. Rаthеr thаn practicing asceticism, he believes in leading a full and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summary-analysis-of-inner-engineering-a-yogis-guide-to-joy-by-sadhguru-jaggi-vasudev-printright-abridged/">Summary Analysis Of Inner Engineering : A Yogi&#8217;s Guide to Joy By Sadhguru Jaggi Vasudev &#8211; Printright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SYNOPSIS: Inner Engіnееrіng (2016) еxрlаіnѕ hоw hарріnеѕѕ саn оnlу be found wіthіn yourself. Thеѕе summaries introduce ѕріrіtuаl wisdom thаt wіll mаkе уоu hарріеr, more fulfіllеd аnd at реасе wіth thе life уоu аrе lіvіng. ABOUT THЕ AUTHОR: Sаdhguru Jаggі Vаѕudеv is аn Indіаn mуѕtіс. Rаthеr thаn practicing asceticism, he believes in leading a full and joyful lіfе. In addition to hіѕ ѕріrіtuаl mіѕѕіоn, hе is thе founder оf a charitable оrgаnіzаtіоn thаt wоrkѕ tо аllеvіаtе роvеrtу in India.DISCLAIMER: This book is a SUMMARY. It is meant to be a companion, not a replacement, to the original book. Please note that this summary is not authorized, licensed, approved, or endorsed by the author or publisher of the main book. The author of this summary is wholly responsible for the content of this summary and is not associated with the original author or publisher of the main book. If you&#8217;d like to purchase the original book, kindly search for the title in the search box.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summary-analysis-of-inner-engineering-a-yogis-guide-to-joy-by-sadhguru-jaggi-vasudev-printright-abridged/">Summary Analysis Of Inner Engineering : A Yogi&#8217;s Guide to Joy By Sadhguru Jaggi Vasudev &#8211; Printright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Because Internet : Understanding the New Rules of Language &#8211; Gretchen McCulloch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/because-internet-understanding-the-new-rules-of-language-gretchen-mcculloch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/because-internet-understanding-the-new-rules-of-language-gretchen-mcculloch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER!! Named a Best Book of 2019 by TIME, Amazon, and The Washington Post A Wired Must-Read Book of Summer   “Gretchen McCulloch is the internet’s favorite linguist, and this book is essential reading. Reading her work is like suddenly being able to see the matrix.” —Jonny Sun, author of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/because-internet-understanding-the-new-rules-of-language-gretchen-mcculloch-abridged/">Because Internet : Understanding the New Rules of Language &#8211; Gretchen McCulloch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER!!    </p>
<p>                    Named a Best Book of 2019 by TIME, Amazon, and The Washington Post    </p>
<p>                    A Wired Must-Read Book of Summer       </p>
<p>                    “Gretchen McCulloch is the internet’s favorite linguist, and this book is essential reading. Reading her work is like suddenly being able to see the matrix.” —Jonny Sun, author of everyone&#8217;s a aliebn when ur a aliebn too       </p>
<p>                    Because Internet is for anyone who&#8217;s ever puzzled over how to punctuate a text message or wondered where memes come from. It&#8217;s the perfect book for understanding how the internet is changing the English language, why that&#8217;s a good thing, and what our online interactions reveal about who we are.      </p>
<p>                    Language is humanity&#8217;s most spectacular open-source project, and the internet is making our language change faster and in more interesting ways than ever before. Internet conversations are structured by the shape of our apps and platforms, from the grammar of status updates to the protocols of comments and @replies. Linguistically inventive online communities spread new slang and jargon with dizzying speed. What&#8217;s more, social media is a vast laboratory of unedited, unfiltered words where we can watch language evolve in real time.     </p>
<p>                    Even the most absurd-looking slang has genuine patterns behind it. Internet linguist Gretchen McCulloch explores the deep forces that shape human language and influence the way we communicate with one another. She explains how your first social internet experience influences whether you prefer &#8220;LOL&#8221; or &#8220;lol,&#8221; why ~sparkly tildes~ succeeded where centuries of proposals for irony punctuation had failed, what emoji have in common with physical gestures, and how the artfully disarrayed language of animal memes like lolcats and doggo made them more likely to spread.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/because-internet-understanding-the-new-rules-of-language-gretchen-mcculloch-abridged/">Because Internet : Understanding the New Rules of Language &#8211; Gretchen McCulloch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Works Well with Others : Shaking Hands, Shutting Up, and Other Crucial Skills in Business That No One Ever Teaches You &#8211; Ross McCammon (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/works-well-with-others-shaking-hands-shutting-up-and-other-crucial-skills-in-business-that-no-one-ever-teaches-you-ross-mccammon-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/works-well-with-others-shaking-hands-shutting-up-and-other-crucial-skills-in-business-that-no-one-ever-teaches-you-ross-mccammon-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A hilarious and indispensable guide to the weirdness of the workplace from Esquire editor and Entrepreneur etiquette columnist Ross McCammon Ten years ago, Ross McCammon made an incredible and unexpected transition from working at an in-flight magazine in suburban Dallas to landing his dream job at Esquire in New York. What followed was a period [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/works-well-with-others-shaking-hands-shutting-up-and-other-crucial-skills-in-business-that-no-one-ever-teaches-you-ross-mccammon-abridged/">Works Well with Others : Shaking Hands, Shutting Up, and Other Crucial Skills in Business That No One Ever Teaches You &#8211; Ross McCammon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A hilarious and indispensable guide to the weirdness of the workplace from Esquire editor and Entrepreneur etiquette columnist Ross McCammon    </p>
<p>                     Ten years ago, Ross McCammon made an incredible and unexpected transition from working at an in-flight magazine in suburban Dallas to landing his dream job at Esquire in New York. What followed was a period of almost debilitating anxiety and awkwardness&#8211;interspersed with minor instances of professional glory&#8211;as McCammon learned how to navigate the workplace while feeling entirely ill-equipped for achieving success in his new career.  Works Well with Others is McCammon&#8217;s &#8220;relentlessly funny and soberingly insightful&#8221;* journey from impostor to authority, a story that reveals the workplace for what it is: an often absurd landscape of ego and fear guided by social rules that no one ever talks about. By mining his own experiences at the magazine, McCammon provides advice on everything from firm handshakes to small talk in elevators to dealing with jerks and underminers. Here is an inspirational new way of looking at your job, your career, and success itself; an accessible guide for those of us who are smart, talented, and ambitious but who aren&#8217;t well-&#8220;leveraged&#8221; and don&#8217;t quite feel prepared for success . . . or know what to do once we&#8217;ve made it.  *Entertainment Weekly</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/works-well-with-others-shaking-hands-shutting-up-and-other-crucial-skills-in-business-that-no-one-ever-teaches-you-ross-mccammon-abridged/">Works Well with Others : Shaking Hands, Shutting Up, and Other Crucial Skills in Business That No One Ever Teaches You &#8211; Ross McCammon (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Death of Truth &#8211; Michiko Kakutani (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-death-of-truth-michiko-kakutani-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-death-of-truth-michiko-kakutani-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a Pulitzer Prize-winning critic comes an impassioned critique of the West&#8217;s retreat from reason. &#8216;The Death of Truth is destined to become the defining treatise of our age&#8217; David Grann &#8216;The first great book of the Trump administration &#8230; essential reading&#8217; Rolling Stone We live in a time when the very idea of objective [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-death-of-truth-michiko-kakutani-abridged/">The Death of Truth &#8211; Michiko Kakutani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a Pulitzer Prize-winning critic comes an impassioned critique of the West&#8217;s retreat from reason.    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;The Death of Truth is destined to become the defining treatise of our age&#8217; David Grann    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;The first great book of the Trump administration &#8230; essential reading&#8217; Rolling Stone    </p>
<p>                              We live in a time when the very idea of objective truth is mocked and discounted by the US President. Discredited conspiracy theories and ideologies have resurfaced, proven science is once more up for debate, and Russian propaganda floods our screens. The wisdom of the crowd has usurped research and expertise, and we are each left clinging to the beliefs that best confirm our biases.    </p>
<p>                              How did truth become an endangered species? This decline began decades ago, and in The Death of Truth, former New York Times critic Michiko Kakutani takes a penetrating look at the cultural forces that contributed to this gathering storm. In social media and literature, television, academia, and political campaigns, Kakutani identifies the trends &#8211; originating on both the right and the left &#8211; that have combined to elevate subjectivity over factuality, science, and common values. And she returns us to the words of the great critics of authoritarianism, writers like George Orwell and Hannah Arendt, whose work is newly and eerily relevant.    </p>
<p>                              With remarkable erudition and insight, Kakutani offers a provocative diagnosis of our current condition and presents a path forward for our truth-challenged times.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-death-of-truth-michiko-kakutani-abridged/">The Death of Truth &#8211; Michiko Kakutani (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I&#8217;m Judging You : The Do-Better Manual &#8211; Luvvie Ajayi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/im-judging-you-the-do-better-manual-luvvie-ajayi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Fiction, Novelists & Prose Writers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/im-judging-you-the-do-better-manual-luvvie-ajayi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With over 500,000 readers a month at her enormously popular blog, AwesomelyLuvvie.com, Luvvie Ajayi has become a go-to source for smart takes on pop culture. I&#8217;m Judging You is her debut book of humorous essays that dissects our cultural obsessions and calls out bad behavior in our increasingly digital, connected lives-from the cultural importance of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/im-judging-you-the-do-better-manual-luvvie-ajayi-abridged/">I&#8217;m Judging You : The Do-Better Manual &#8211; Luvvie Ajayi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With over 500,000 readers a month at her enormously popular blog, AwesomelyLuvvie.com, Luvvie Ajayi has become a go-to source for smart takes on pop culture. I&#8217;m Judging You is her debut book of humorous essays that dissects our cultural obsessions and calls out bad behavior in our increasingly digital, connected lives-from the cultural importance of the newest Shonda Rhimes television drama to serious discussions of race and media representation to what to do about your fool cousin sharing casket pictures from Grandma&#8217;s wake on Facebook. With a lighthearted, rapier wit and a unique perspective, I&#8217;m Judging You is the handbook the world needs, doling out the hard truths and a road map for bringing some &#8220;act right&#8221; into our lives, social media, and popular culture.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/im-judging-you-the-do-better-manual-luvvie-ajayi-abridged/">I&#8217;m Judging You : The Do-Better Manual &#8211; Luvvie Ajayi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unfinished Business : Women Men Work Family &#8211; Anne-Marie Slaughter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unfinished-business-women-men-work-family-anne-marie-slaughter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unfinished-business-women-men-work-family-anne-marie-slaughter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the Orwell Prize for Books 2016 Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award 2015 When Anne-Marie Slaughter&#8217;s Atlantic article, &#8220;Why Women Still Can&#8217;t Have it All&#8221; first appeared, it immediately went viral, sparking a firestorm of debate across countries and continents. Within four days, it had become [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfinished-business-women-men-work-family-anne-marie-slaughter-abridged/">Unfinished Business : Women Men Work Family &#8211; Anne-Marie Slaughter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the Orwell Prize for Books 2016    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award 2015    </p>
<p>                    When Anne-Marie Slaughter&#8217;s Atlantic article, &#8220;Why Women Still Can&#8217;t Have it All&#8221; first appeared, it immediately went viral, sparking a firestorm of debate across countries and continents. Within four days, it had become the most-read article in the history of the magazine. In the following months, Slaughter became a leading voice in the discussion on work-life balance and on women&#8217;s changing role in the workplace.    </p>
<p>                    Now, Slaughter is here with her eagerly anticipated take on the problems we still face, and how we can finally get past them. In her pragmatic, down-to-earth style, Slaughter bursts the bubble on all the &#8220;half-truths&#8221; we tell young women about &#8220;having it all&#8221;, and explains what is really necessary to get true gender equality, both in the workplace and at home. Deeply researched, and filled with all the warm, wise and funny anecdotes that first made her the most trusted and admired voice on the issue, Anne-Marie Slaughter&#8217;s book is sure to change minds, ignite debate and be the topic of conversation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfinished-business-women-men-work-family-anne-marie-slaughter-abridged/">Unfinished Business : Women Men Work Family &#8211; Anne-Marie Slaughter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me by David Goggins : Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds &#8211; Get The Key Ideas From Can&#8217;t Hurt Me In Minutes &#8211; Quick Reads (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are You Ready To Get The Most Out Of Yourself And Out Of Life?When it comes to getting fit, a lot of us find excuses. We&#8217;re too busy; we sleep in, we don&#8217;t feel like it. But what happens when we stop making excuses? David Goggins stopped making excuses and started giving life 100%. If [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads-abridged/">Summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me by David Goggins : Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds &#8211; Get The Key Ideas From Can&#8217;t Hurt Me In Minutes &#8211; Quick Reads (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are You Ready To Get The Most Out Of Yourself And Out Of Life?When it comes to getting fit, a lot of us find excuses. We&#8217;re too busy; we sleep in, we don&#8217;t feel like it. But what happens when we stop making excuses?     </p>
<p>                    David Goggins stopped making excuses and started giving life 100%. If you&#8217;ve heard his name, it&#8217;s probably because this former Air Force serviceman and Navy SEAL is also an ultra-endurance athlete and once held a world record for the most pull-ups in 24 hours. He is one of the toughest people alive.     </p>
<p>                    His success wasn&#8217;t handed to him, though. Goggins had a terribly hard life. After surviving an abusive and traumatic childhood, he faced poverty and became overweight in his twenties. As a result of the trauma from his childhood, he was nearly illiterate as a teen. None of this stopped him, though.     </p>
<p>                    Now he&#8217;s here to help you stop backing away from challenges, too. In his book &#8220;Can&#8217;t Hurt Me: Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds,&#8221; he teaches that the difficult things in life make you the strongest.     </p>
<p>                    If you are ready to get the most out of yourself and out of life, then you need this summary by Quick Reads. After reading this summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me, you&#8217;ll discover: What it takes to master your mind from someone who has overcome huge obstacles and become one of the toughest people on earth.How to break your mental roadblocks and take control of your success.How you can always come out stronger from any condition no matter how much trauma you&#8217;ve experiencedHow to work hard and push yourself to be your best self instead of believing in overnight successHow to be ready to dump your excuses and do and become better than ever before. And most importantly, how to become the master of your mind and achieve more than you thought possible using the 40% rule and much more&#8230; See the Table of Contents to find out by clicking on &#8220;Look inside.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    So, if you want a concise yet very informative summary book on Can&#8217;t Hurt Me that can help you grasp the insights, key ideas, and main points within minutes, simply scroll up and click the &#8220;BUY NOW&#8221; button for instant access!     </p>
<p>                    DISCLAIMER:      </p>
<p>                    This is not the official book, but an unofficial summary and analysis of the book &#8220;Can&#8217;t Hurt Me: Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds by David Goggins bringing you the main points, concise and easy to consume. It is a way to get you the key ideas from great books and bestsellers in minutes, not hours. More knowledge in less time!     </p>
<p>                    QUICK READS = Learn Faster &#038; Get Smarter!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summary-of-cant-hurt-me-by-david-goggins-master-your-mind-and-defy-the-odds-get-the-key-ideas-from-cant-hurt-me-in-minutes-quick-reads-abridged/">Summary of Can&#8217;t Hurt Me by David Goggins : Master Your Mind and Defy the Odds &#8211; Get The Key Ideas From Can&#8217;t Hurt Me In Minutes &#8211; Quick Reads (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Read a Book &#8211; Mortimer J. Adler, Charles Van Doren (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-read-a-book-mortimer-j-adler-charles-van-doren-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult Literacy Guides & Handbooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language: Reference & General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Companions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-read-a-book-mortimer-j-adler-charles-van-doren-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With half a million copies in print, How to Read a Book is the best and most successful guide to reading comprehension for the general reader, completely rewritten and updated with new material. Originally published in 1940, this book is a rare phenomenon, a living classic that introduces and elucidates the various levels of reading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-read-a-book-mortimer-j-adler-charles-van-doren-abridged/">How to Read a Book &#8211; Mortimer J. Adler, Charles Van Doren (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With half a million copies in print, How to Read a Book is the best and most successful guide to reading comprehension for the general reader, completely rewritten and updated with new material.<br />
                         Originally published in 1940, this book is a rare phenomenon, a living classic that introduces and elucidates the various levels of reading and how to achieve them-from elementary reading, through systematic skimming and inspectional reading, to speed reading. Readers will learn when and how to &#8220;judge a book by its cover,&#8221; and also how to X-ray it, read critically, and extract the author&#8217;s message from the text.<br />
                         Also included is instruction in the different techniques that work best for reading particular genres, such as practical books, imaginative literature, plays, poetry, history, science and mathematics, philosophy and social science works.<br />
                         Finally, the authors offer a recommended reading list and supply reading tests you can use measure your own progress in reading skills, comprehension, and speed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-read-a-book-mortimer-j-adler-charles-van-doren-abridged/">How to Read a Book &#8211; Mortimer J. Adler, Charles Van Doren (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lost Connections : Why You&#8217;re Depressed and How to Find Hope &#8211; Johann Hari (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lost-connections-why-youre-depressed-and-how-to-find-hope-johann-hari-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Care Of The Mentally Ill]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lost-connections-why-youre-depressed-and-how-to-find-hope-johann-hari-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* Pre-order Johann Hari&#8217;s new book Stolen Focus now! * THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8216;A book that could actually make us happy&#8217; SIMON AMSTELL &#8216;This amazing book will change your life&#8217; ELTON JOHN &#8216;One of the most important texts of recent years&#8217; BRITISH JOURNAL OF GENERAL PRACTICE &#8216;Brilliant, stimulating, radical&#8217; MATT HAIG &#8216;The more people read [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-connections-why-youre-depressed-and-how-to-find-hope-johann-hari-abridged/">Lost Connections : Why You&#8217;re Depressed and How to Find Hope &#8211; Johann Hari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* Pre-order Johann Hari&#8217;s new book Stolen Focus now! *    </p>
<p>                    THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book that could actually make us happy&#8217; SIMON AMSTELL<br />
                    &#8216;This amazing book will change your life&#8217; ELTON JOHN<br />
                    &#8216;One of the most important texts of recent years&#8217; BRITISH JOURNAL OF GENERAL PRACTICE<br />
                     &#8216;Brilliant, stimulating, radical&#8217; MATT HAIG<br />
                    &#8216;The more people read this book, the better off the world will be&#8217; NAOMI KLEIN<br />
                     &#8216;Wonderful&#8217; HILLARY CLINTON<br />
                    &#8216;Eye-opening&#8217; GUARDIAN<br />
                    &#8216;Brilliant for anyone wanting a better understanding of mental health&#8217; ZOE BALL<br />
                     &#8216;A game-changer&#8217; DAVINA MCCALL<br />
                     &#8216;Extraordinary&#8217; DR MAX PEMBERTON<br />
                    &#8216;Beautiful&#8217; RUSSELL BRAND    </p>
<p>                    Depression and anxiety are now at epidemic levels. Why? Across the world, scientists have uncovered evidence for nine different causes. Some are in our biology, but most are in the way we are living today.    </p>
<p>                     Lost Connections offers a radical new way of thinking about this crisis. It shows that once we understand the real causes, we can begin to turn to pioneering new solutions &#8211; ones that offer real hope.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lost-connections-why-youre-depressed-and-how-to-find-hope-johann-hari-abridged/">Lost Connections : Why You&#8217;re Depressed and How to Find Hope &#8211; Johann Hari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Better Living Through Criticism: How to Think about Art, Pleasure, Beauty and Truth &#8211; A. O. Scott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/better-living-through-criticism-how-to-think-about-art-pleasure-beauty-and-truth-a-o-scott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Theory & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy, From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/better-living-through-criticism-how-to-think-about-art-pleasure-beauty-and-truth-a-o-scott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Few could explain, let alone seek out, a career in criticism. Yet what A. O. Scott shows in Better Living Through Criticism is that we are, in fact, all critics: because critical thinking informs almost every aspect of artistic creation, of civil action, of interpersonal life. With penetrating insight and humour, Scott shows that while [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/better-living-through-criticism-how-to-think-about-art-pleasure-beauty-and-truth-a-o-scott-abridged/">Better Living Through Criticism: How to Think about Art, Pleasure, Beauty and Truth &#8211; A. O. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Few could explain, let alone seek out, a career in criticism. Yet what A. O. Scott shows in Better Living Through Criticism is that we are, in fact, all critics: because critical thinking informs almost every aspect of artistic creation, of civil action, of interpersonal life. With penetrating insight and humour, Scott shows that while individual critics &#8211; himself included &#8211; can make mistakes and find flaws where they shouldn&#8217;t, criticism as a discipline is one of the noblest, most creative and urgent activities.    </p>
<p>                    Using his own film criticism as a starting point &#8211; everything from an infamous dismissal of the international blockbuster The Avengers to his intense affection for Pixar&#8217;s animated Ratatouille &#8211; Scott expands outwards, easily guiding readers through the complexities of Rilke and Shelley, the origins of Chuck Berry and the Rolling Stones, the power of Marina Abramovic and &#8216;Ode on a Grecian Urn&#8217; Scott shows that real criticism was and always will be the breath of fresh air that allows true creativity to thrive. As he puts it: &#8216;The time for criticism is always now, because the imperative to think clearly, never goes away.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/better-living-through-criticism-how-to-think-about-art-pleasure-beauty-and-truth-a-o-scott-abridged/">Better Living Through Criticism: How to Think about Art, Pleasure, Beauty and Truth &#8211; A. O. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orwell&#8217;s Revenge : The 1984 Palimpsest &#8211; Senior Fellow Peter Huber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/orwells-revenge-the-1984-palimpsest-senior-fellow-peter-huber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orwells-revenge-the-1984-palimpsest-senior-fellow-peter-huber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mark Zuckerberg&#8217;s &#8216;A Year of Books&#8217; Selection George Orwell&#8217;s bleak visions of the future, one in which citizens are monitored through telescreens by an insidious Big Brother, has haunted our imagination long after the publication of 1984. Orwell&#8217;s dystopian image of the telescreen as a repressive instrument of state power has profoundly affected our view [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orwells-revenge-the-1984-palimpsest-senior-fellow-peter-huber-abridged/">Orwell&#8217;s Revenge : The 1984 Palimpsest &#8211; Senior Fellow Peter Huber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mark Zuckerberg&#8217;s &#8216;A Year of Books&#8217; Selection     </p>
<p>                    George Orwell&#8217;s bleak visions of the future, one in which citizens are monitored through telescreens by an insidious Big Brother, has haunted our imagination long after the publication of 1984. Orwell&#8217;s dystopian image of the telescreen as a repressive instrument of state power has profoundly affected our view of technology, posing a stark confrontational question: Who will be master, human or machine? Experience has shown, however, that Orwell&#8217;s vision of the future was profoundly and significantly wrong: The conjunction of the new communications technologies has not produced a master-slave relation between person and computer, but rather exciting possibilities for partnership.     </p>
<p>                    In an extraordinary demonstration of the emerging supermedium&#8217;s potential to engender new forms of creativity, Huber&#8217;s book boldly reimagines 1984 from the computer&#8217;s point of view. After first scanning all of Orwell&#8217;s writings into his personal computer, Huber used the machine to rewrite the book completely, for the most part using Orwell&#8217;s own language. Alternating fiction and non-fiction chapters, Huber advances Orwell&#8217;s plot to a surprising new conclusion while seamlessly interpolating his own explanations and arguments. The result is a fascinating utopian work which envisions a world at our fingertips of ever-increasing information, equal opportunity, and freedom of choice.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orwells-revenge-the-1984-palimpsest-senior-fellow-peter-huber-abridged/">Orwell&#8217;s Revenge : The 1984 Palimpsest &#8211; Senior Fellow Peter Huber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Summary and Analysis of Keto Answers : Simplifying Everything You Need to Know about the World&#8217;s Most Confusing Diet By Anthony Gustin, Chris Irvin &#8211; Acesprint (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/summary-and-analysis-of-keto-answers-simplifying-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-worlds-most-confusing-diet-by-anthony-gustin-chris-irvin-acesprint-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/summary-and-analysis-of-keto-answers-simplifying-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-worlds-most-confusing-diet-by-anthony-gustin-chris-irvin-acesprint-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kеtо Anѕwеrѕ (2019), bу Anthоnу Gustin аnd Chrіѕ Irvіn, clears uр all уоur ԛuеѕtіоnѕ аbоut thе ketogenic diet. As ketogenic eating hаѕ grown in рорulаrіtу, ѕо-саllеd &#8220;expert advice&#8221; and mіѕіnfоrmаtіоn аbоut thе kеtо dіеt hаѕ grоwn, too. Kеtо Anѕwеrѕ сutѕ thrоugh thе соnfuѕіоn, еxрlаіnіng the ѕсіеnсе bеhіnd kеtо and laying out the ѕtrаtеgіеѕ you nееd [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summary-and-analysis-of-keto-answers-simplifying-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-worlds-most-confusing-diet-by-anthony-gustin-chris-irvin-acesprint-abridged/">Summary and Analysis of Keto Answers : Simplifying Everything You Need to Know about the World&#8217;s Most Confusing Diet By Anthony Gustin, Chris Irvin &#8211; Acesprint (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kеtо Anѕwеrѕ (2019), bу Anthоnу Gustin аnd Chrіѕ Irvіn, clears uр all уоur ԛuеѕtіоnѕ аbоut thе ketogenic diet. As ketogenic eating hаѕ grown in рорulаrіtу, ѕо-саllеd &#8220;expert advice&#8221; and mіѕіnfоrmаtіоn аbоut thе kеtо dіеt hаѕ grоwn, too. Kеtо Anѕwеrѕ сutѕ thrоugh thе соnfuѕіоn, еxрlаіnіng the ѕсіеnсе bеhіnd kеtо and laying out the ѕtrаtеgіеѕ you nееd tо іmрlеmеnt уоur оwn kеtоgеnіс eating plan ѕuссеѕѕfullу.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/summary-and-analysis-of-keto-answers-simplifying-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-worlds-most-confusing-diet-by-anthony-gustin-chris-irvin-acesprint-abridged/">Summary and Analysis of Keto Answers : Simplifying Everything You Need to Know about the World&#8217;s Most Confusing Diet By Anthony Gustin, Chris Irvin &#8211; Acesprint (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I&#8217;d Rather Be Reading : The Delights and Dilemmas of the Reading Life &#8211; Anne Bogel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/id-rather-be-reading-the-delights-and-dilemmas-of-the-reading-life-anne-bogel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/id-rather-be-reading-the-delights-and-dilemmas-of-the-reading-life-anne-bogel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For so many people, reading isn&#8217;t just a hobby or a way to pass the time&#8211;it&#8217;s a lifestyle. Our books shape us, define us, enchant us, and even sometimes infuriate us. Our books are a part of who we are as people, and we can&#8217;t imagine life without them. I&#8217;d Rather Be Reading is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/id-rather-be-reading-the-delights-and-dilemmas-of-the-reading-life-anne-bogel-abridged/">I&#8217;d Rather Be Reading : The Delights and Dilemmas of the Reading Life &#8211; Anne Bogel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For so many people, reading isn&#8217;t just a hobby or a way to pass the time&#8211;it&#8217;s a lifestyle. Our books shape us, define us, enchant us, and even sometimes infuriate us. Our books are a part of who we are as people, and we can&#8217;t imagine life without them.    </p>
<p>                    I&#8217;d Rather Be Reading is the perfect literary companion for everyone who feels that way. In this collection of charming and relatable reflections on the reading life, beloved blogger and author Anne Bogel leads readers to remember the book that first hooked them, the place where they first fell in love with reading, and all of the moments afterward that helped make them the reader they are today. Known as a reading tastemaker through her popular podcast What Should I Read Next?, Bogel invites book lovers into a community of like-minded people to discover new ways to approach literature, learn fascinating new things about books and publishing, and reflect on the role reading plays in their lives.    </p>
<p>                    The perfect gift for the bibliophile in everyone&#8217;s life, I&#8217;d Rather Be Reading will command an honored place on the overstuffed bookshelves of any book lover.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/id-rather-be-reading-the-delights-and-dilemmas-of-the-reading-life-anne-bogel-abridged/">I&#8217;d Rather Be Reading : The Delights and Dilemmas of the Reading Life &#8211; Anne Bogel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time (chronology), Time Systems & Standards]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR From the acclaimed author of The Information and Chaos, a mind-bending exploration of time travel: its subversive origins, its evolution in literature and science, and its influence on our understanding of time itself. Gleick&#8217;s story begins at the turn of the twentieth century with the young H. G. Wells [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/">Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                              From the acclaimed author of The Information and Chaos, a mind-bending exploration of time travel: its subversive origins, its evolution in literature and science, and its influence on our understanding of time itself.    </p>
<p>                              Gleick&#8217;s story begins at the turn of the twentieth century with the young H. G. Wells writing and rewriting the fantastic tale that became his first book, an international sensation, The Time Machine. A host of forces were converging to transmute the human understanding of time, some philosophical and some technological &#8211; the electric telegraph, the steam railroad, the discovery of buried civilisations, and the perfection of clocks. Gleick tracks the evolution of time travel as an idea in the culture &#8211; from Marcel Proust to Doctor Who, from Woody Allen to Jorge Luis Borges. He explores the inevitable looping paradoxes and examines the porous boundary between pulp fiction and modern physics. Finally, he delves into a temporal shift that is unsettling our own moment: the instantaneous wired world, with its all-consuming present and vanishing future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/">Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Investigation & Detection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING * &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING *     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly written haymaker&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on nearly three years of reporting, hundreds of hours of interviews and more than two hundred sources, including some of the most senior members of the administration, friends and first-hand witnesses who have never spoken before, Philip Rucker and Carol Leonnig take us inside some of the most controversial moments of Trump&#8217;s presidency. They peer deeply into Trump&#8217;s White House &#8211; at the aides pressured to lie to the public, the lawyers scrambling to clear up norm-breaking disasters, and the staffers whose careers have been reduced to ashes &#8211; to paint an unparalleled group portrait of an administration driven by self-preservation and paranoia.     </p>
<p>                    Rucker and Leonnig reveal Trump at his most unvarnished, showing the unhinged decision-making and incompetence that has floored officials and stunned foreign leaders. They portray unscripted calls with Vladimir Putin, steak dinners with Kim Jong-un, and calls with Theresa May so hostile that they left her aides shaken. They also take a hard look at Robert Mueller, Trump&#8217;s greatest antagonist to date, and how his investigation slowly unravelled an administration whose universal value is loyalty &#8211; not to country, but to the president himself.    </p>
<p>                    Grippingly told, A Very Stable Genius is a behind-the-scenes account of Trump&#8217;s vainglorious pursuit of power in his first term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Read Literature Like a Professor Revised Edition : A Lively and Entertaining Guide to Reading Between the Lines &#8211; Thomas C Foster (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-read-literature-like-a-professor-revised-edition-a-lively-and-entertaining-guide-to-reading-between-the-lines-thomas-c-foster-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poetry & Drama]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-read-literature-like-a-professor-revised-edition-a-lively-and-entertaining-guide-to-reading-between-the-lines-thomas-c-foster-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A thoroughly revised and updated edition of Thomas C. Foster&#8217;s classic guide-a lively and entertaining introduction to literature and literary basics, including symbols, themes and contexts, that shows you how to make your everyday reading experience more rewarding and enjoyable. While many books can be enjoyed for their basic stories, there are often deeper literary [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-read-literature-like-a-professor-revised-edition-a-lively-and-entertaining-guide-to-reading-between-the-lines-thomas-c-foster-abridged/">How to Read Literature Like a Professor Revised Edition : A Lively and Entertaining Guide to Reading Between the Lines &#8211; Thomas C Foster (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A thoroughly revised and updated edition of Thomas C. Foster&#8217;s classic guide-a lively and entertaining introduction to literature and literary basics, including symbols, themes and contexts, that shows you how to make your everyday reading experience more rewarding and enjoyable.  While many books can be enjoyed for their basic stories, there are often deeper literary meanings interwoven in these texts. How to Read Literature Like a Professor helps us to discover those hidden truths by looking at literature with the eyes-and the literary codes-of the ultimate professional reader, the college professor.  What does it mean when a literary hero is traveling along a dusty road? When he hands a drink to his companion? When he&#8217;s drenched in a sudden rain shower?  Ranging from major themes to literary models, narrative devices and form, Thomas C. Foster provides us with a broad overview of literature-a world where a road leads to a quest, a shared meal may signify a communion, and rain, whether cleansing or destructive, is never just a shower-and shows us how to make our reading experience more enriching, satisfying, and fun.<br />
                    This revised edition includes new chapters, a new preface and epilogue, and incorporates updated teaching points that Foster has developed over the past decade.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-read-literature-like-a-professor-revised-edition-a-lively-and-entertaining-guide-to-reading-between-the-lines-thomas-c-foster-abridged/">How to Read Literature Like a Professor Revised Edition : A Lively and Entertaining Guide to Reading Between the Lines &#8211; Thomas C Foster (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reading Like a Writer : A Guide for People Who Loves Books and for Those Who Want to Write Them &#8211; Francine Prose (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reading-like-a-writer-a-guide-for-people-who-loves-books-and-for-those-who-want-to-write-them-francine-prose-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reading-like-a-writer-a-guide-for-people-who-loves-books-and-for-those-who-want-to-write-them-francine-prose-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A distinguished novelist and critic inspires readers and writers with this inside look at how the professionals read&#8211;and write Long before there were creative writing workshops and degrees, how did aspiring writers learn to write? By reading the work of their predecessors and contemporaries, says Francine Prose. As she takes us on a guided tour [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reading-like-a-writer-a-guide-for-people-who-loves-books-and-for-those-who-want-to-write-them-francine-prose-abridged/">Reading Like a Writer : A Guide for People Who Loves Books and for Those Who Want to Write Them &#8211; Francine Prose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A distinguished novelist and critic inspires readers and writers with this inside look at how the professionals read&#8211;and write     </p>
<p>                    Long before there were creative writing workshops and degrees, how did aspiring writers learn to write? By reading the work of their predecessors and contemporaries, says Francine Prose.     </p>
<p>                     As she takes us on a guided tour of the tools and the tricks of the masters&#8211;Dostoyevsky, Flaubert, Kafka, Austen, Dickens, Woolf, Chekhov&#8211;Prose discovers why these writers endure. She takes pleasure in the signature elements of such outsatanding writers as Philip Roth, Isaac Babel, John Le Carré, James Joyce, and Katherine Mansfield. Throughout, she cautions readers to slow down and pay attention to words, the raw material out of which literature is crafted. Written with passion, humor, and wisdom, Reading Like a Writer will inspire readers to return to literature with a fresh eye and an eager heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reading-like-a-writer-a-guide-for-people-who-loves-books-and-for-those-who-want-to-write-them-francine-prose-abridged/">Reading Like a Writer : A Guide for People Who Loves Books and for Those Who Want to Write Them &#8211; Francine Prose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
