<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sociology: Death &amp; Dying Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/sociology-death-dying/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/sociology-death-dying/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Sociology: Death &amp; Dying Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/sociology-death-dying/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Mortality &#8211; Christopher Hitchens (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mortality-christopher-hitchens-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Death & Dying]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mortality-christopher-hitchens-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On June 8, 2010, while on a book tour for his bestselling memoir, Hitch-22, Christopher Hitchens was stricken in his New York hotel room with excruciating pain in his chest and thorax. As he would later write in the first of a series of award-winning columns for Vanity Fair, he suddenly found himself being deported [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mortality-christopher-hitchens-abridged/">Mortality &#8211; Christopher Hitchens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On June 8, 2010, while on a book tour for his bestselling memoir, Hitch-22, Christopher Hitchens was stricken in his New York hotel room with excruciating pain in his chest and thorax. As he would later write in the first of a series of award-winning columns for Vanity Fair, he suddenly found himself being deported from the country of the well across the stark frontier that marks off the land of malady. Over the next eighteen months, until his death in Houston on December 15, 2011, he wrote constantly and brilliantly on politics and culture, astonishing readers with his capacity for superior work even in extremis.     </p>
<p>                     Throughout the course of his ordeal battling esophageal cancer, Hitchens adamantly and bravely refused the solace of religion, preferring to confront death with both eyes open. In this riveting account of his affliction, Hitchens poignantly describes the torments of illness, discusses its taboos, and explores how disease transforms experience and changes our relationship to the world around us. By turns personal and philosophical, Hitchens embraces the full panoply of human emotions as cancer invades his body and compels him to grapple with the enigma of death.     </p>
<p>                    Mortality is the exemplary story of one man&#8217;s refusal to cower in the face of the unknown, as well as a searching look at the human predicament. Crisp and vivid, veined throughout with penetrating intelligence, Hitchens&#8217;s testament is a courageous and lucid work of literature, an affirmation of the dignity and worth of man.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mortality-christopher-hitchens-abridged/">Mortality &#8211; Christopher Hitchens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Death&#8217;s Summer Coat : What the History of Death and Dying Can Tell Us About Life and Living &#8211; Brandy Schillace (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/deaths-summer-coat-what-the-history-of-death-and-dying-can-tell-us-about-life-and-living-brandy-schillace-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Death & Dying]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deaths-summer-coat-what-the-history-of-death-and-dying-can-tell-us-about-life-and-living-brandy-schillace-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new conversation is starting on this most universal of topics. But to know where we are heading, we need to know where we have come from&#8230;Death is the one subject we will all confront; it touches our families, our homes, our hearts. And yet we have grown used to denying its existence, treating it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deaths-summer-coat-what-the-history-of-death-and-dying-can-tell-us-about-life-and-living-brandy-schillace-abridged/">Death&#8217;s Summer Coat : What the History of Death and Dying Can Tell Us About Life and Living &#8211; Brandy Schillace (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new conversation is starting on this most universal of topics. But to know where we are heading, we need to know where we have come from&#8230;Death is the one subject we will all confront; it touches our families, our homes, our hearts. And yet we have grown used to denying its existence, treating it as an enemy to be beaten back with medical advances. What led us to this point &#8211; what drove us to sanitize death and make it foreign and unfamiliar? In Death&#8217;s Summer Coat Brandy Schillace explores our past to examine what it might mean for our future. From Victorian Britain to contemporary Cambodia, forgotten customs and modern-day rituals, we learn about the incredibly diverse &#8211; and sometimes just incredible &#8211; ways in which humans have dealt with mortality in different times and places. Today, as we begin to talk about mortality, there are difficult questions to face. What does it mean to have a &#8216;good death&#8217;? What should a funeral do? As Schillace shows, talking about death and the rituals associated with it can help to provide answers. It also brings us closer together. And conversation and community are just as important for living as for dying.Some of the stories are strikingly unfamiliar; others are far more familiar than you might suppose.<br />
                    But all reveal a lot about the present &#8211; and about ourselves. It&#8217;s time to meet the new (old) death. As seen reviewed in The Guardian in the article Smoke Gets in Your Eyes by Caitlin Doughty review &#8211; startling stories from the crematorium. If you are keen to learn more, you can listen to the interview with Brandy Schillace on Radio Gorgeous or the interview on BBC Radio 4 Thinking Allowed, both to be aired in May 2015.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deaths-summer-coat-what-the-history-of-death-and-dying-can-tell-us-about-life-and-living-brandy-schillace-abridged/">Death&#8217;s Summer Coat : What the History of Death and Dying Can Tell Us About Life and Living &#8211; Brandy Schillace (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
