<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Study &amp; Learning Skills: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/study-learning-skills-general/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/study-learning-skills-general/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Study &amp; Learning Skills: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/study-learning-skills-general/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The First 20 Hours : How to Learn Anything &#8230; Fast &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-first-20-hours-how-to-learn-anything-fast-josh-kaufman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult Education, Continuous Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-first-20-hours-how-to-learn-anything-fast-josh-kaufman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lots of books promise to change your life. This one actually will&#8217; Seth Godin, bestselling author of Purple Cow Have you always wanted to learn a new language? Play an instrument? Launch a business? What&#8217;s holding you back from getting started? Are you worried about the time it takes to acquire new skills &#8211; time [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-first-20-hours-how-to-learn-anything-fast-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The First 20 Hours : How to Learn Anything &#8230; Fast &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lots of books promise to change your life. This one actually will&#8217; Seth Godin, bestselling author of Purple Cow    </p>
<p>                    Have you always wanted to learn a new language? Play an instrument? Launch a business? What&#8217;s holding you back from getting started? Are you worried about the time it takes to acquire new skills &#8211; time you can&#8217;t spare?    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;    </p>
<p>                    Pick up this book and set aside twenty hours to go from knowing nothing to performing like a pro. That&#8217;s it.    </p>
<p>                    Josh Kaufman, author of international bestseller The Personal MBA, has developed a unique approach to mastering anything. Fast.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;After reading this book, you&#8217;ll be ready to take on any number of skills and make progress on that big project you&#8217;ve been putting off for years&#8217; Chris Guillebeau, bestselling author of Un-F*ck Yourself     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;All that&#8217;s standing between you and playing the ukulele is your TV time for the next two weeks&#8217; Laura Vanderkam, author of What the Most Successful People Do Before Breakfast</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-first-20-hours-how-to-learn-anything-fast-josh-kaufman-abridged/">The First 20 Hours : How to Learn Anything &#8230; Fast &#8211; Josh Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Mind for Numbers : How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra) &#8211; Barbara Oakley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The companion book to COURSERA(R)&#8217;s wildly popular massive open online course Learning How to Learn Whether you are a student struggling to fulfill a math or science requirement, or you are embarking on a career change that requires a new skill set, A Mind for Numbers offers the tools you need to get a better [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/">A Mind for Numbers : How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra) &#8211; Barbara Oakley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The companion book to COURSERA(R)&#8217;s wildly popular massive open online course Learning How to Learn     </p>
<p>                    Whether you are a student struggling to fulfill a math or science requirement, or you are embarking on a career change that requires a new skill set, A Mind for Numbers offers the tools you need to get a better grasp of that intimidating material. Engineering professor Barbara Oakley knows firsthand how it feels to struggle with math. She flunked her way through high school math and science courses, before enlisting in the army immediately after graduation. When she saw how her lack of mathematical and technical savvy severely limited her options&#8211;both to rise in the military and to explore other careers&#8211;she returned to school with a newfound determination to re-tool her brain to master the very subjects that had given her so much trouble throughout her entire life.     </p>
<p>                     In A Mind for Numbers, Dr. Oakley lets us in on the secrets to learning effectively&#8211;secrets that even dedicated and successful students wish they&#8217;d known earlier. Contrary to popular belief, math requires creative, as well as analytical, thinking. Most people think that there&#8217;s only one way to do a problem, when in actuality, there are often a number of different solutions&#8211;you just need the creativity to see them. For example, there are more than three hundred different known proofs of the Pythagorean Theorem. In short, studying a problem in a laser-focused way until you reach a solution is not an effective way to learn. Rather, it involves taking the time to step away from a problem and allow the more relaxed and creative part of the brain to take over. The learning strategies in this book apply not only to math and science, but to any subject in which we struggle. We all have what it takes to excel in areas that don&#8217;t seem to come naturally to us at first, and learning them does not have to be as painful as we might think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/">A Mind for Numbers : How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra) &#8211; Barbara Oakley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Become a Straight-A Student : The Unconventional Strategies Real College Students Use to Score High While Studying Less &#8211; Cal Newport (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-become-a-straight-a-student-the-unconventional-strategies-real-college-students-use-to-score-high-while-studying-less-cal-newport-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-become-a-straight-a-student-the-unconventional-strategies-real-college-students-use-to-score-high-while-studying-less-cal-newport-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking to jumpstart your GPA? Most college students believe that straight A&#8217;s can be achieved only through cramming and painful all-nighters at the library. But Cal Newport knows that real straight-A students don&#8217;t study harder&#8211;they study smarter. A breakthrough approach to acing academic assignments, from quizzes and exams to essays and papers, How to Become [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-become-a-straight-a-student-the-unconventional-strategies-real-college-students-use-to-score-high-while-studying-less-cal-newport-abridged/">How to Become a Straight-A Student : The Unconventional Strategies Real College Students Use to Score High While Studying Less &#8211; Cal Newport (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Looking to jumpstart your GPA?      </p>
<p>                    Most college students believe that straight A&#8217;s can be achieved only through cramming and painful all-nighters at the library. But Cal Newport knows that real straight-A students don&#8217;t study harder&#8211;they study smarter. A breakthrough approach to acing academic assignments, from quizzes and exams to essays and papers, How to Become a Straight-A Student reveals for the first time the proven study secrets of real straight-A students across the country and weaves them into a simple, practical system that anyone can master.     </p>
<p>                    You will learn how to:      </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Streamline and maximize your study time<br />
                     &#8211; Conquer procrastination<br />
                     &#8211; Absorb the material quickly and effectively<br />
                     &#8211; Know which reading assignments are critical&#8211;and which are not<br />
                     &#8211; Target the paper topics that wow professors<br />
                     &#8211; Provide A+ answers on exams<br />
                     &#8211; Write stellar prose without the agony     </p>
<p>                    A strategic blueprint for success that promises more free time, more fun, and top-tier results, How to Become a Straight-A Student is the only study guide written by students for students&#8211;with the insider knowledge and real-world methods to help you master the college system and rise to the top of the class.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-become-a-straight-a-student-the-unconventional-strategies-real-college-students-use-to-score-high-while-studying-less-cal-newport-abridged/">How to Become a Straight-A Student : The Unconventional Strategies Real College Students Use to Score High While Studying Less &#8211; Cal Newport (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Importance Of Being Little : What Preschoolers Really Need from Grownups &#8211; Erika Christakis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-importance-of-being-little-what-preschoolers-really-need-from-grownups-erika-christakis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pre-school & Kindergarten]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-importance-of-being-little-what-preschoolers-really-need-from-grownups-erika-christakis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Christakis . . . expertly weaves academic research, personal experience and anecdotal evidence into her book . . . a bracing and convincing case that early education has reached a point of crisis . . . her book is a rare thing: a serious work of research that also happens to be well-written and personal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-importance-of-being-little-what-preschoolers-really-need-from-grownups-erika-christakis-abridged/">The Importance Of Being Little : What Preschoolers Really Need from Grownups &#8211; Erika Christakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Christakis . . . expertly weaves academic research, personal experience and anecdotal evidence into her book . . . a bracing and convincing case that early education has reached a point of crisis . . . her book is a rare thing: a serious work of research that also happens to be well-written and personal . . . engaging and important.&#8221;<br />
                     &#8211;Washington Post     </p>
<p>                    What kids need from grown-ups (but aren&#8217;t getting)&#8230;an impassioned plea for educators and parents to put down the worksheets and flash cards, ditch the tired craft projects (yes, you, Thanksgiving Handprint Turkey) and exotic vocabulary lessons, and double-down on one, simple word: play.<br />
                    &#8211;NPR     </p>
<p>                    The New York Times bestseller that provides a bold challenge to the conventional wisdom about early childhood, with a pragmatic program to encourage parents and teachers to rethink how and where young children learn best by taking the child&#8217;s eye view of the learning environment     </p>
<p>                     To a four-year-old watching bulldozers at a construction site or chasing butterflies in flight, the world is awash with promise. Little children come into the world hardwired to learn in virtually any setting and about any matter. Yet in today&#8217;s preschool and kindergarten classrooms, learning has been reduced to scripted lessons and suspect metrics that too often undervalue a child&#8217;s intelligence while overtaxing the child&#8217;s growing brain. These mismatched expectations wreak havoc on the family: parents fear that if they choose the &#8220;wrong&#8221; program, their child won&#8217;t get into the &#8220;right&#8221; college. But Yale early childhood expert Erika Christakis says our fears are wildly misplaced. Our anxiety about preparing and safeguarding our children&#8217;s future seems to have reached a fever pitch at a time when, ironically, science gives us more certainty than ever before that young children are exceptionally strong thinkers.<br />
                     In her pathbreaking book, Christakis explains what it&#8217;s like to be a young child in America today, in a world designed by and for adults, where we have confused schooling with learning. She offers real-life solutions to real-life issues, with nuance and direction that takes us far beyond the usual prescriptions for fewer tests, more play. She looks at children&#8217;s use of language, their artistic expressions, the way their imaginations grow, and how they build deep emotional bonds to stretch the boundaries of their small worlds. Rather than clutter their worlds with more and more stuff, sometimes the wisest course for us is to learn how to get out of their way.<br />
                     Christakis&#8217;s message is energizing and reassuring: young children are inherently powerful, and they (and their parents) will flourish when we learn new ways of restoring the vital early learning environment to one that is best suited to the littlest learners. This bold and pragmatic challenge to the conventional wisdom peels back the mystery of childhood, revealing a place that&#8217;s rich with possibility.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-importance-of-being-little-what-preschoolers-really-need-from-grownups-erika-christakis-abridged/">The Importance Of Being Little : What Preschoolers Really Need from Grownups &#8211; Erika Christakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Learn Better : Mastering the Skills for Success in Life, Business, and School, or How to Become an Expert in Just About Anything &#8211; Ulrich Boser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For centuries, experts have argued that learning was about memorizing information: You&#8217;re supposed to study facts, dates, and details; burn them into your memory; and then apply that knowledge at opportune times. But this approach to learning isn&#8217;t nearly enough for the world that we live in today, and in Learn Better journalist and education [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/">Learn Better : Mastering the Skills for Success in Life, Business, and School, or How to Become an Expert in Just About Anything &#8211; Ulrich Boser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For centuries, experts have argued that learning was about memorizing information: You&#8217;re supposed to study facts, dates, and details; burn them into your memory; and then apply that knowledge at opportune times. But this approach to learning isn&#8217;t nearly enough for the world that we live in today, and in Learn Better journalist and education researcher Ulrich Boser demonstrates that how we learn can matter just as much as what we learn.     </p>
<p>                    In this brilliantly researched book, Boser maps out the new science of learning, showing how simple techniques like comprehension check-ins and making material personally relatable can help people gain expertise in dramatically better ways. He covers six key steps to help you &#8220;learn how to learn,&#8221; all illuminated with fascinating stories like how Jackson Pollock developed his unique painting style and why an ancient Japanese counting device allows kids to do math at superhuman speeds. Boser&#8217;s witty, engaging writing makes this book feel like a guilty pleasure, not homework.    </p>
<p>                    Learn Better will revolutionize the way students and society alike approach learning and makes the case that being smart is not an innate ability&#8211;learning is a skill everyone can master. With Boser as your guide, you will be able to fully capitalize on your brain&#8217;s remarkable ability to gain new skills and open up a whole new world of possibilities.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/learn-better-mastering-the-skills-for-success-in-life-business-and-school-or-how-to-become-an-expert-in-just-about-anything-ulrich-boser-abridged/">Learn Better : Mastering the Skills for Success in Life, Business, and School, or How to Become an Expert in Just About Anything &#8211; Ulrich Boser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Listening Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BRILLIANT&#8217; Chris Evans, Virgin Radio Breakfast Show When was the last time you listened to someone, or someone really listened to you? This life-changing book will transform your conversations forever. At work, we&#8217;re taught to lead the conversation. On social media, we shape our personal narratives. At parties, we talk over one another. So do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/">You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BRILLIANT&#8217; Chris Evans, Virgin Radio Breakfast Show    </p>
<p>                    When was the last time you listened to someone, or someone really listened to you?     </p>
<p>                    This life-changing book will transform your conversations forever.    </p>
<p>                     At work, we&#8217;re taught to lead the conversation.    </p>
<p>                     On social media, we shape our personal narratives.    </p>
<p>                     At parties, we talk over one another. So do our politicians.    </p>
<p>                     We&#8217;re not listening.    </p>
<p>                     And no one is listening to us.    </p>
<p>                    Now more than ever, we need to listen to those around us. New York Times contributor Kate Murphy draws on countless conversations she has had with everyone from priests to CIA interrogators, focus group moderators to bartenders, her great-great aunt to her friend&#8217;s toddler, to show how only by listening well can we truly connect with others.    </p>
<p>                     Listening has the potential to transform our relationships and our working lives, improve our self-knowledge, and increase our creativity and happiness. While it may take some effort, it&#8217;s a skill that can be learnt and perfected.    </p>
<p>                     When all we crave is to understand and be understood, You&#8217;re Not Listening shows us how.    </p>
<p>                    * With a new afterword by the author *    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book couldn&#8217;t be more timely. Inspiringly profound&#8230;smart and playful&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;ll be adopting Murphy&#8217;s advice&#8217; Sunday Times, Style</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/">You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Decision Theory: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking presents practical, lively, and inspiring ways for you to become more successful through better thinking. The idea is simple: You can learn how to think far better by adopting specific strategies. Brilliant people aren&#8217;t a special breed&#8211;they just use their minds differently. By using the straightforward and thought-provoking techniques [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/">The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking presents practical, lively, and inspiring ways for you to become more successful through better thinking. The idea is simple: You can learn how to think far better by adopting specific strategies. Brilliant people aren&#8217;t a special breed&#8211;they just use their minds differently. By using the straightforward and thought-provoking techniques in The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking, you will regularly find imaginative solutions to difficult challenges, and you will discover new ways of looking at your world and yourself&#8211;revealing previously hidden opportunities. The book offers real-life stories, explicit action items, and concrete methods that allow you to attain a deeper understanding of any issue, exploit the power of failure as a step toward success, develop a habit of creating probing questions, see the world of ideas as an ever-flowing stream of thought, and embrace the uplifting reality that we are all capable of change. No matter who you are, the practical mind-sets introduced in the book will empower you to realize any goal in a more creative, intelligent, and effective manner.<br />
                    Filled with engaging examples that unlock truths about thinking in every walk of life, The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking is written for all who want to reach their fullest potential&#8211;including students, parents, teachers, businesspeople, professionals, athletes, artists, leaders, and lifelong learners. Whenever you are stuck, need a new idea, or want to learn and grow, The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking will inspire and guide you on your way. To share thinking stories, go to: http://5elementsofthinking.wordpress.com/</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-elements-of-effective-thinking-edward-b-burger-michael-starbird-abridged/">The 5 Elements of Effective Thinking &#8211; Edward B. Burger, Michael Starbird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fluent Forever : How to Learn Any Language Fast and Never Forget It &#8211; Gabriel Wyner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Children's Foreign Language Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language Teaching & Learning (other Than ELT)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Language Teaching & Learning Material & Coursework]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; For anyone who wants to learn a foreign language, this is the method that will finally make the words stick. &#8220;A brilliant and thoroughly modern guide to learning new languages.&#8221;&#8211;Gary Marcus, cognitive psychologist and author of the New York Times bestseller Guitar Zero At thirty years old, Gabriel Wyner speaks six languages [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/">Fluent Forever : How to Learn Any Language Fast and Never Forget It &#8211; Gabriel Wyner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; For anyone who wants to learn a foreign language, this is the method that will finally make the words stick.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A brilliant and thoroughly modern guide to learning new languages.&#8221;&#8211;Gary Marcus, cognitive psychologist and author of the New York Times bestseller Guitar Zero     </p>
<p>                    At thirty years old, Gabriel Wyner speaks six languages fluently. He didn&#8217;t learn them in school&#8211;who does? Rather, he learned them in the past few years, working on his own and practicing on the subway, using simple techniques and free online resources&#8211;and here he wants to show others what he&#8217;s discovered.     </p>
<p>                    Starting with pronunciation, you&#8217;ll learn how to rewire your ears and turn foreign sounds into familiar sounds. You&#8217;ll retrain your tongue to produce those sounds accurately, using tricks from opera singers and actors. Next, you&#8217;ll begin to tackle words, and connect sounds and spellings to imagery rather than translations, which will enable you to think in a foreign language. And with the help of sophisticated spaced-repetition techniques, you&#8217;ll be able to memorize hundreds of words a month in minutes every day.     </p>
<p>                    This is brain hacking at its most exciting, taking what we know about neuroscience and linguistics and using it to create the most efficient and enjoyable way to learn a foreign language in the spare minutes of your day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fluent-forever-how-to-learn-any-language-fast-and-never-forget-it-gabriel-wyner-abridged/">Fluent Forever : How to Learn Any Language Fast and Never Forget It &#8211; Gabriel Wyner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ungifted : Intelligence Redefined &#8211; Scott Kaufman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ungifted-intelligence-redefined-scott-kaufman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ungifted-intelligence-redefined-scott-kaufman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Ungifted , cognitive psychologist Scott Barry Kaufman,who was relegated to special education as a child,offers a new way of looking at intelligence. He explores the latest research in genetics, neuroscience, and psychology to challenge the conventional wisdom about the childhood predictors of adult success, arguing for a more holistic approach to intelligence that takes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ungifted-intelligence-redefined-scott-kaufman-abridged/">Ungifted : Intelligence Redefined &#8211; Scott Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In  Ungifted , cognitive psychologist Scott Barry Kaufman,who was relegated to special education as a child,offers a new way of looking at intelligence. He explores the latest research in genetics, neuroscience, and psychology to challenge the conventional wisdom about the childhood predictors of adult success, arguing for a more holistic approach to intelligence that takes into account each individual&#8217;s abilities, engagement, and personal goals. Combining original research and a singular compassion,  Ungifted  increases our appreciation for all different kinds of minds and ways of achieving both personally meaningful and publicly recognized forms of success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ungifted-intelligence-redefined-scott-kaufman-abridged/">Ungifted : Intelligence Redefined &#8211; Scott Kaufman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
