<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Computer Hardware Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/computer-hardware/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/computer-hardware/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Computer Hardware Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/computer-hardware/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fabricated : The New World of 3D Printing &#8211; Hod Lipson, Melba Kurman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3D Graphics & Modelling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fabricated tells the story of 3D printers, humble manufacturing machines that are bursting out of the factory and into schools, kitchens, hospitals, even onto the fashion catwalk. Fabricated describes our emerging world of printable products, where people design and 3D print their own creations as easily as they edit an online document. A 3D printer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/">Fabricated : The New World of 3D Printing &#8211; Hod Lipson, Melba Kurman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fabricated tells the story of 3D printers, humble manufacturing machines that are bursting out of the factory and into schools, kitchens, hospitals, even onto the fashion catwalk. Fabricated describes our emerging world of printable products, where people design and 3D print their own creations as easily as they edit an online document. A 3D printer transforms digital information into a physical object by carrying out instructions from an electronic design file, or &#8216;blueprint.&#8217; Guided by a design file, a 3D printer lays down layer after layer of a raw material to &#8216;print&#8217; out an object. That&#8217;s not the whole story, however. The magic happens when you plug a 3D printer into today s mind-boggling digital technologies. Add to that the Internet, tiny, low cost electronic circuitry, radical advances in materials science and biotech and voila! The result is an explosion of technological and social innovation. Fabricated takes the reader onto a rich and fulfilling journey that explores how 3D printing is poised to impact nearly every part of our lives.<br />
                    Aimed at people who enjoy books on business strategy, popular science and novel technology, Fabricated will provide readers with practical and imaginative insights to the question &#8216;how will this technology change my life?&#8217; Based on hundreds of hours of research and dozens of interviews with experts from a broad range of industries, Fabricated offers readers an informative, engaging and fast-paced introduction to 3D printing now and in the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/">Fabricated : The New World of 3D Printing &#8211; Hod Lipson, Melba Kurman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brand Gap, The : Revised Edition &#8211; Marty Neumeier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brand-gap-the-revised-edition-marty-neumeier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brand-gap-the-revised-edition-marty-neumeier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE BRAND GAP is the first book to present a unified theory of brand-building. Whereas most books on branding are weighted toward either a strategic or creative approach, this book shows how both ways of thinking can unite to produce a &#8220;charismatic brand&#8221;-a brand that customers feel is essential to their lives. In an entertaining [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brand-gap-the-revised-edition-marty-neumeier-abridged/">Brand Gap, The : Revised Edition &#8211; Marty Neumeier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE BRAND GAP is the first book to present a unified theory of brand-building.  Whereas most books on branding are weighted toward either a strategic or creative approach, this book shows how both ways of thinking can unite to produce a &#8220;charismatic brand&#8221;-a brand that customers feel is essential to their lives. In an entertaining two-hour read you&#8217;ll learn:     </p>
<p>                    * the new definition of brand<br />
                    * the five essential disciplines of brand-building<br />
                    * how branding is changing the dynamics of competition<br />
                    * the three most powerful questions to ask about any brand<br />
                    * why collaboration is the key to brand-building<br />
                    * how design determines a customer&#8217;s experience<br />
                    * how to test brand concepts quickly and cheaply<br />
                    * the importance of managing brands from the inside<br />
                    * 220-word brand glossary     </p>
<p>                    From the back cover:<br />
                    Not since McLuhan&#8217;s THE MEDIUM IS THE MESSAGE has a book compressed so many ideas into so few pages. Using the visual language of the boardroom, Neumeier presents the first unified theory of branding-a set of five disciplines to help companies bridge the gap between brand strategy and customer experience. Those with a grasp of branding will be inspired by the new perspectives they find here, and those who would like to understand it better will suddenly &#8220;get it.&#8221; This deceptively simple book offers everyone in the company access to &#8220;the most powerful business tool since the spreadsheet.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brand-gap-the-revised-edition-marty-neumeier-abridged/">Brand Gap, The : Revised Edition &#8211; Marty Neumeier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics & Communications Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phones: Consumer/user Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is your phone the first thing you reach for when you wake up? And the last thing you see before you sleep? Do you find the hours slip away as you idly scroll through your social media timeline? In short, are you addicted to your phone? If so, How to Break Up with Your Phone [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/">How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is your phone the first thing you reach for when you wake up? And the  last thing you see before you sleep? Do you find the hours slip away as  you idly scroll through your social media timeline?     </p>
<p>                     In short, are you addicted to your phone? If so, How to Break Up with Your Phone is here to help.     </p>
<p>                     How to Break Up With Your Phone  is a smart, practical and useful plan to help you conquer your mobile  phone addiction in just 30 days &#8211; and take back your life in the  process.     </p>
<p>                    Recent studies have shown that spending extended time  on our phones affects our ability to form new memories, think deeply,  focus and absorb information, and the hormones triggered every time we  hear our phones buzz both add to our stress levels and are the hallmark  signs of addiction. In How to Break Up with Your Phone,  award-winning science journalist Catherine Price explores the effects  that our constant connectivity is having on our brains, bodies,  relationships, and society at large and asks, how much time do you really want to spend on your phone?     </p>
<p>                    Over  the course of 30 days, Catherine will guide you through an  easy-to-follow plan that enables you to identify your goals, priorities  and bad habits, tidy your apps, prune your email, and take time away.  Lastly, you will create a new, healthier relationship with your phone  and establish habits and routines to ensure this new relationship  sticks.     </p>
<p>                    You don&#8217;t have to give up your phone forever; instead  you will be more mindful not only of how you use your phone, but also  about how you choose to spend the precious moments of your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/">How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
