<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Investment &amp; Securities Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/investment-securities/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/investment-securities/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Investment &amp; Securities Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/investment-securities/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Intelligent Investor : The Classic Text on Value Investing &#8211; Benjamin Graham</title>
		<link>/intelligent-investor-the-classic-text-on-value-investing-benjamin-graham/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/intelligent-investor-the-classic-text-on-value-investing-benjamin-graham/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The greatest investment advisor of the twentieth century, Benjamin Graham taught and inspired people worldwide. Graham&#8217;s philosophy of `value investing`-which shields investors from substantial error and teaches them to develop long-term strategies-has made The Intelligent Investor the stock market bible ever since its original publication in 1949. Vital and indispensable, The Intelligent Investor is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/intelligent-investor-the-classic-text-on-value-investing-benjamin-graham/">Intelligent Investor : The Classic Text on Value Investing &#8211; Benjamin Graham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The greatest investment advisor of the twentieth century, Benjamin Graham taught and inspired people worldwide. Graham&#8217;s philosophy of `value investing`-which shields investors from substantial error and teaches them to develop long-term strategies-has made The Intelligent Investor the stock market bible ever since its original publication in 1949.    </p>
<p>                    Vital and indispensable, The Intelligent Investor is the most important book you will ever read on how to reach your financial goals.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/intelligent-investor-the-classic-text-on-value-investing-benjamin-graham/">Intelligent Investor : The Classic Text on Value Investing &#8211; Benjamin Graham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New Market Wizards : Conversations with America&#8217;s Top Traders &#8211; Jack D. Schwager</title>
		<link>/the-new-market-wizards-conversations-with-americas-top-traders-jack-d-schwager/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-market-wizards-conversations-with-americas-top-traders-jack-d-schwager/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The New Market Wizards, successful traders relate the financial strategies that have rocketed them to success. Asking questions that readers with an interest or involvement in the financial markets would love to pose to the financial superstars, Jack D. Schwager encourages these financial wizards to share their insights. Entertaining, informative, and invaluable, The New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-market-wizards-conversations-with-americas-top-traders-jack-d-schwager/">The New Market Wizards : Conversations with America&#8217;s Top Traders &#8211; Jack D. Schwager</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The New Market Wizards, successful traders relate the financial strategies that have rocketed them to success. Asking questions that readers with an interest or involvement in the financial markets would love to pose to the financial superstars, Jack D. Schwager encourages these financial wizards to share their insights. Entertaining, informative, and invaluable, The New Market Wizards is destined to become another Schwager classic.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-market-wizards-conversations-with-americas-top-traders-jack-d-schwager/">The New Market Wizards : Conversations with America&#8217;s Top Traders &#8211; Jack D. Schwager</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crush It! : Why NOW Is the Time to Cash In on Your Passion &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</title>
		<link>/crush-it-why-now-is-the-time-to-cash-in-on-your-passion-gary-vaynerchuk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crush-it-why-now-is-the-time-to-cash-in-on-your-passion-gary-vaynerchuk/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you have a hobby you wish you could do all day? An obsession that keeps you up at night? Now is the perfect time to take those passions and make a living doing what you love. In Crush It! Why Now Is The Time To Cash In On Your Passion, Gary Vaynerchuk shows you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crush-it-why-now-is-the-time-to-cash-in-on-your-passion-gary-vaynerchuk/">Crush It! : Why NOW Is the Time to Cash In on Your Passion &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you have a hobby you wish you could do all day? An obsession that keeps you up at night? Now is the perfect time to take those passions and make a living doing what you love. In Crush It! Why Now Is The Time To Cash In On Your Passion, Gary Vaynerchuk shows you how to use the power of the Internet to turn your real interests into real businesses. Gary spent years building his family business from a local wine shop into a national industry leader. Then one day he turned on a video camera, and by using the secrets revealed in this book, transformed his entire life and earning potential by building his personal brand. By the end of this book, any reader will have learned how to harness the power of the Internet to make their entrepreneurial dreams come true. Step by step, Crush It! is the ultimate driver&#8217;s manual for modern business. Gary Vaynerchuk has captured attention with his pioneering, multi-faceted approach to personal branding and business.<br />
                    After primarily utilizing traditional advertising techniques to build his family&#8217;s local retail wine business into a national industry leader, Gary rapidly leveraged social media tools such as Twitter and Facebook to promote Wine Library TV. Gary has always had an early-to-market approach, launching Wine Library&#8217;s retail website in 1997 and Wine Library TV in February of 2006. His lessons on social media, passion, transparency, and reactionary business are not to be missed!    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crush-it-why-now-is-the-time-to-cash-in-on-your-passion-gary-vaynerchuk/">Crush It! : Why NOW Is the Time to Cash In on Your Passion &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bogleheads&#8217; Guide to Investing &#8211; Mel Lindauer</title>
		<link>/the-bogleheads-guide-to-investing-mel-lindauer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bogleheads-guide-to-investing-mel-lindauer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The irreverent guide to investing, Boglehead style The Boglehead&#8217;s Guide to Investing is a DIY handbook that espouses the sage investment wisdom of John C. Bogle. This witty and wonderful book offers contrarian advice that provides the first step on the road to investment success, illustrating how relying on typical &#8220;common sense&#8221; promoted by Wall [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bogleheads-guide-to-investing-mel-lindauer/">The Bogleheads&#8217; Guide to Investing &#8211; Mel Lindauer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The irreverent guide to investing, Boglehead style The Boglehead&#8217;s Guide to Investing is a DIY handbook that espouses the sage investment wisdom of John C. Bogle. This witty and wonderful book offers contrarian advice that provides the first step on the road to investment success, illustrating how relying on typical &#8220;common sense&#8221; promoted by Wall Street is destined to leave you poorer. This updated edition includes new information on backdoor Roth IRAs and ETFs as mainstream buy and hold investments, estate taxes and gifting, plus changes to the laws regarding Traditional and Roth IRAs, and 401k and 403b retirement plans. With warnings and principles both precisely accurate and grandly counterintuitive, the Boglehead authors show how beating the market is a zero-sum game. Investing can be simple, but it&#8217;s certainly not simplistic. Over the course of twenty years, the followers of John C. Bogle have evolved from a loose association of investors to a major force with the largest and most active non-commercial financial forum on the Internet.<br />
                    The Boglehead&#8217;s Guide to Investing brings that communication to you with comprehensive guidance to the investment prowess on display at Bogleheads.org. You&#8217;ll learn how to craft your own investment strategy using the Bogle-proven methods that have worked for thousands of investors, and how to: * Choose a sound financial lifestyle and diversify your portfolio * Start early, invest regularly, and know what you&#8217;re buying * Preserve your buying power, keeping costs and taxes low * Throw out the &#8220;good&#8221; advice promoted by Wall Street that leads to investment failure Financial markets are essentially closed systems in which one&#8217;s gain garners another&#8217;s loss. Investors looking for a roadmap to successfully navigating these choppy waters long-term will find expert guidance, sound advice, and a little irreverent humor in The Boglehead&#8217;s Guide to Investing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bogleheads-guide-to-investing-mel-lindauer/">The Bogleheads&#8217; Guide to Investing &#8211; Mel Lindauer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unshakeable : Your Guide to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins</title>
		<link>/unshakeable-your-guide-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unshakeable-your-guide-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER* Tony Robbins, arguably the most recognizable life and business strategist and guru, is back with a timely, unique follow-up to his smash New York Times bestseller Money: Master the Game. Market corrections are as constant as seasons are in nature. There have been 30 such corrections in the past 30 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unshakeable-your-guide-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins/">Unshakeable : Your Guide to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER*</p>
<p>                     Tony Robbins, arguably the most recognizable life and business strategist and guru, is back with a timely, unique follow-up to his smash New York Times bestseller Money: Master the Game.<br />
                       Market corrections are as constant as seasons are in nature. There have been 30 such corrections in the past 30 years, yet there&#8217;s never been an action plan for how not only to survive, but thrive through each change in the stock market.<br />
                       Building upon the principles in Money: Master the Game, Robbins offers the reader specific steps they can implement to protect their investments while maximizing their wealth. It&#8217;s a detailed guide designed for investors, articulated in the common-sense, practical manner that the millions of loyal Robbins fans and students have come to expect and rely upon.<br />
                       Few have navigated the turbulence of the stock market as adeptly and successfully as Tony Robbins. His proven, consistent success over decades makes him singularly qualified to help investors (both seasoned and first-timers alike) preserve and add to their investments.</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Tony&#8217;s power is super-human&#8217; Oprah Winfrey<br />
                     &#8216;He has a great gift. He has the gift to inspire&#8217; Bill Clinton<br />
                     &#8216;Tony Robbins needs no introduction. He is committed to helping make life better for every investor&#8217; Carl Icahn<br />
                     &#8216;The high priest of human potential. The world can&#8217;t get enough of Anthony Robbins&#8217; The New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unshakeable-your-guide-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins/">Unshakeable : Your Guide to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review</p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.</p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.</p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.</p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Index Card &#8211; Helaine Olen, Harold Pollack (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-index-card-helaine-olen-harold-pollack-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-index-card-helaine-olen-harold-pollack-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The newbie investor will not find a better guide to personal finance.&#8221; &#8211;Burton Malkiel, author of A RANDOM WALK DOWN WALL STREET TV analysts and money managers would have you believe your finances are enormously complicated, and if you don&#8217;t follow their guidance, you&#8217;ll end up in the poorhouse. They&#8217;re wrong. When University of Chicago [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-index-card-helaine-olen-harold-pollack-abridged/">The Index Card &#8211; Helaine Olen, Harold Pollack (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The newbie investor will not find a better guide to personal finance.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Burton Malkiel, author of A RANDOM WALK DOWN WALL STREET       </p>
<p>                    TV analysts and money managers would have you believe your finances are enormously complicated, and if you don&#8217;t follow their guidance, you&#8217;ll end up in the poorhouse.     </p>
<p>                    They&#8217;re wrong.     </p>
<p>                    When University of Chicago professor Harold Pollack interviewed Helaine Olen, an award-winning financial journalist and the author of the bestselling Pound Foolish, he made an off­hand suggestion: everything you need to know about managing your money could fit on an index card. To prove his point, he grabbed a 4 x 6 card, scribbled down a list of rules, and posted a picture of the card online. The post went viral.     </p>
<p>                    Now, Pollack teams up with Olen to explain why the ten simple rules of the index card outperform more complicated financial strategies. Inside is an easy-to-follow action plan that works in good times and bad, giving you the tools, knowledge, and confidence to seize control of your financial life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-index-card-helaine-olen-harold-pollack-abridged/">The Index Card &#8211; Helaine Olen, Harold Pollack (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: The Elderly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pensions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface* Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time? Many of us have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface*    </p>
<p>                    Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time?     </p>
<p>                    Many of us have been raised on the traditional notion of a three-stage approach to our working lives: education, followed by work and then retirement.  But this well-established pathway is already beginning to collapse &#8211; life expectancy is rising, final-salary pensions are vanishing, and increasing numbers of people are juggling multiple careers. Whether you are 18, 45 or 60, you will need to do things very differently from previous generations and learn to structure your life in completely new ways.    </p>
<p>                    The 100-Year Life is here to help.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the unique pairing of their experience in psychology and economics, Lynda Gratton and Andrew J. Scott offer a broad-ranging analysis as well as a raft of solutions, showing how to rethink your finances, your education, your career and your relationships and create a fulfilling 100-year life.     </p>
<p>                    * How can you fashion a career and life path that defines you and your values and creates a shifting balance between work and leisure?    </p>
<p>                    * What are the most effective ways of boosting your physical and mental health over a longer and more dynamic lifespan?    </p>
<p>                    * How can you make the most of your intangible assets &#8211; such as family and friends &#8211; as you build a productive, longer life?    </p>
<p>                    * In a multiple-stage life how can you learn to make the transitions that will be so crucial and experiment with new ways of living, working and learning?    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award and featuring a new preface, The 100-Year Life is a wake-up call that describes what to expect and considers the choices and options that you will face. It is also fundamentally a call to action for individuals, politicians, firms and governments and offers the clearest demonstration that a 100-year life can be a wonderful and inspiring one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Barefoot Investor : The Only Money Guide You&#8217;ll Ever Need &#8211; Scott Pape (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-barefoot-investor-the-only-money-guide-youll-ever-need-scott-pape-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-barefoot-investor-the-only-money-guide-youll-ever-need-scott-pape-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** Reviewed and updated for the 2020-2021 financial year** This is the only money guide you&#8217;ll ever need That&#8217;s a bold claim, given there are already thousands of finance books on the shelves. So what makes this one different? Well, you won&#8217;t be overwhelmed with a bunch of &#8216;tips&#8217; &#8230; or a strict budget (that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-barefoot-investor-the-only-money-guide-youll-ever-need-scott-pape-abridged/">The Barefoot Investor : The Only Money Guide You&#8217;ll Ever Need &#8211; Scott Pape (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** Reviewed and updated for the 2020-2021 financial year**    </p>
<p>                     This is the only money guide you&#8217;ll ever need    </p>
<p>                     That&#8217;s a bold claim, given there are already thousands of finance books on the shelves.    </p>
<p>                     So what makes this one different?    </p>
<p>                     Well, you won&#8217;t be overwhelmed with a bunch of &#8216;tips&#8217; &#8230; or a strict budget (that you won&#8217;t follow).    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll get a step-by-step formula: open this account, then do this; call this person, and say this; invest money here, and not there. All with a glass of wine in your hand.    </p>
<p>                     This book will show you how to create an entire financial plan that is so simple you can sketch it on the back of a serviette &#8230; and you&#8217;ll be able to manage your money in 10 minutes a week.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll also get the skinny on:    </p>
<p>                     Saving up a six-figure house deposit in 20 months    </p>
<p>                     Doubling your income using the &#8216;Trapeze Strategy&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     Saving $78,173 on your mortgage and wiping out 7 years of payments    </p>
<p>                     Finding a financial advisor who won&#8217;t rip you off    </p>
<p>                     Handing your kids (or grandkids) a $140,000 cheque on their 21st birthday    </p>
<p>                     Why you don&#8217;t need $1 million to retire &#8230; with the &#8216;Donald Bradman Retirement Strategy&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     Sound too good to be true? It&#8217;s not.    </p>
<p>                     This book is full of stories from everyday Aussies &#8211; single people, young families, empty nesters, retirees &#8211; who have applied the simple steps in this book and achieved amazing, life-changing results.    </p>
<p>                     And you&#8217;re next.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-barefoot-investor-the-only-money-guide-youll-ever-need-scott-pape-abridged/">The Barefoot Investor : The Only Money Guide You&#8217;ll Ever Need &#8211; Scott Pape (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Mistakes : The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments &#8211; Michael Batnick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/big-mistakes-the-best-investors-and-their-worst-investments-michael-batnick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/big-mistakes-the-best-investors-and-their-worst-investments-michael-batnick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Must-Read for Any Investor Looking to Maximize Their Chances of Success Big Mistakes: The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments explores the ways in which the biggest names have failed, and reveals the lessons learned that shaped more successful strategies going forward. Investing can be a rollercoaster of highs and lows, and the investors [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-mistakes-the-best-investors-and-their-worst-investments-michael-batnick-abridged/">Big Mistakes : The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments &#8211; Michael Batnick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Must-Read for Any Investor Looking to Maximize Their Chances of Success Big Mistakes: The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments explores the ways in which the biggest names have failed, and reveals the lessons learned that shaped more successful strategies going forward. Investing can be a rollercoaster of highs and lows, and the investors detailed here show just how low it can go; stories from Warren Buffet, Bill Ackman, Chris Sacca, Jack Bogle, Mark Twain, John Maynard Keynes, and many more illustrate the simple but overlooked concept that investing is really hard, whether you&#8217;re managing a few thousand dollars or a few billion, failures and losses are part of the game. Much more than just anecdotal diversion, these stories set the basis for the book&#8217;s critical focus: learning from mistakes. These investors all recovered from their missteps, and moved forward armed with a wealth of knowledge than can only come from experience. Lessons learned through failure carry a weight that no textbook can convey, and in the case of these legendary investors, informed a set of skills and strategy that propelled them to the top.<br />
                    Research-heavy and grounded in realism, this book is a must-read for any investor looking to maximize their chances of success. * Learn the most common ways even successful investors fail * Learn from the mistakes of the greats to avoid losing ground * Anticipate challenges and obstacles, and develop an advance plan * Exercise caution when warranted, and only take the smart risks While learning from your mistakes is always a valuable experience, learning from the mistakes of others gives you the benefit of wisdom without the consequences of experience. Big Mistakes: The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments provides an incomparable, invaluable resource for investors of all stripes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-mistakes-the-best-investors-and-their-worst-investments-michael-batnick-abridged/">Big Mistakes : The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments &#8211; Michael Batnick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The FALCON Method : A Proven System for Building Passive Income and Wealth Through Stock Investing &#8211; David Solyomi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-falcon-method-a-proven-system-for-building-passive-income-and-wealth-through-stock-investing-david-solyomi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-falcon-method-a-proven-system-for-building-passive-income-and-wealth-through-stock-investing-david-solyomi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Beat the Market and Grow Your Cash Flow Without Becoming a Full-time Investor Most investment strategies are just too complicated, too risky, or too subjective. Most investors fail because they don&#8217;t manage risk. But the biggest risks in investing are emotional and psychological. That&#8217;s why you The Falcon Method is designed to force you to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-falcon-method-a-proven-system-for-building-passive-income-and-wealth-through-stock-investing-david-solyomi-abridged/">The FALCON Method : A Proven System for Building Passive Income and Wealth Through Stock Investing &#8211; David Solyomi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Beat the Market and Grow Your Cash Flow Without Becoming a Full-time Investor    </p>
<p>                     Most investment strategies are just too complicated, too risky, or too subjective.    </p>
<p>                     Most investors fail because they don&#8217;t manage risk. But the biggest risks in investing are emotional and psychological. That&#8217;s why you The Falcon Method is designed to force you to make good investment decisions even when you get emotional.    </p>
<p>                     One bad investment decision could ruin your entire financial future. With The Falcon Method, you&#8217;ll learn how to protect yourself from market risk (and from your own emotions) so you never again have to face financial ruin.    </p>
<p>                     Risky trading strategies advertised with get-rich-quick hype may create big wins for a lucky few, but most people just end up with big losses and nothing to show for all their hard work and the emotional rollercoaster they endured.    </p>
<p>                     Creating and maintaining real wealth through stock investing requires a long-term investment strategy that properly manages risk and prevents emotional decision-making so that you never suffer major losses.    </p>
<p>                     The FALCON Method is completely different than typical stock investing strategies. The reason it beats the market, again and again, is because it uses an evidence-based stock selection process that anyone can follow. You don&#8217;t need to get lucky, take big risks, or fly by the seat of your pants in order to retire wealthy from stock investing.    </p>
<p>                     Successful investing requires structured decision-making based on a proven process, and that&#8217;s exactly how The FALCON Method was created.    </p>
<p>                     If you&#8217;re looking for a proven, step-by-step guide to getting higher returns in the stock market with less risk, this book is for you.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll love this book if you are a fan of How to Day Trade for a Living by Andrew Aziz, The Total Money Makeover by Dave Ramsey, The Intelligent Investor by Benjamin Graham, and How to Make Money in Stocks by William J. O&#8217;Neil.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-falcon-method-a-proven-system-for-building-passive-income-and-wealth-through-stock-investing-david-solyomi-abridged/">The FALCON Method : A Proven System for Building Passive Income and Wealth Through Stock Investing &#8211; David Solyomi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Quit Like a Millionaire : No Gimmicks, Luck, or Trust Fund Required &#8211; Kristy Shen, Bryce Leung (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/quit-like-a-millionaire-no-gimmicks-luck-or-trust-fund-required-kristy-shen-bryce-leung-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Accounting & Bookkeeping]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tips & Advice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/quit-like-a-millionaire-no-gimmicks-luck-or-trust-fund-required-kristy-shen-bryce-leung-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From two leaders of the FIRE (Financial Independence, Retire Early) movement, a bold, contrarian guide to retiring at any age, with a reproducible formula to financial independence A bull***t-free guide to growing your wealth, retiring early, and living life on your own terms Kristy Shen retired with a million dollars at the age of thirty-one, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/quit-like-a-millionaire-no-gimmicks-luck-or-trust-fund-required-kristy-shen-bryce-leung-abridged/">Quit Like a Millionaire : No Gimmicks, Luck, or Trust Fund Required &#8211; Kristy Shen, Bryce Leung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From two leaders of the FIRE (Financial Independence, Retire Early) movement, a bold, contrarian guide to retiring at any age, with a reproducible formula to financial independence     </p>
<p>                    A bull***t-free guide to growing your wealth, retiring early, and living life on your own terms     </p>
<p>                    Kristy Shen retired with a million dollars at the age of thirty-one, and she did it without hitting a home run on the stock market, starting the next Snapchat in her garage, or investing in hot real estate. Learn how to cut down on spending without decreasing your quality of life, build a million-dollar portfolio, fortify your investments to survive bear markets and black-swan events, and use the 4 percent rule and the Yield Shield&#8211;so you can quit the rat race forever. Not everyone can become an entrepreneur or a real estate baron; the rest of us need Shen&#8217;s mathematically proven approach to retire decades before sixty-five.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/quit-like-a-millionaire-no-gimmicks-luck-or-trust-fund-required-kristy-shen-bryce-leung-abridged/">Quit Like a Millionaire : No Gimmicks, Luck, or Trust Fund Required &#8211; Kristy Shen, Bryce Leung (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Edge : Inside Information, Dirty Money, and the Quest to Bring Down the Most Wanted Man on Wall Street &#8211; Sheelah Kolhatkar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nominated for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Nominated for the Carnegie Medal for Excellence in Nonfiction Amazon Top 5 Business Books of 2017 &#8216;A prodigious feat of reporting&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell &#8216;Black Edge has the grip of a thriller &#8230; Everyone should read this book&#8217; &#8211; David Grann, New York Times bestselling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/">Black Edge : Inside Information, Dirty Money, and the Quest to Bring Down the Most Wanted Man on Wall Street &#8211; Sheelah Kolhatkar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nominated for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year<br />
                    Nominated for the Carnegie Medal for Excellence in Nonfiction<br />
                    Amazon Top 5 Business Books of 2017    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A prodigious feat of reporting&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Black Edge has the grip of a thriller &#8230; Everyone should read this book&#8217; &#8211; David Grann, New York Times bestselling author of THE LOST CITY OF Z     </p>
<p>                    How do super-rich bankers get away with it?    </p>
<p>                    There is a powerful new class of billionaire financiers in the world, who use their phenomenal wealth to write their own rules and laws.  Chief among them is Steven Cohen, a Wall Street legend, and the basis for Damian Lewis&#8217;s character in BILLIONS, who built his hedge fund into a $15 billion empire on the basis of wizard-like stock trading, and who flies to work by helicopter and owns one of the largest private art collections in the world.  But his iconic status was shattered when his fund became the target of a sprawling FBI investigation into insider trading, charged with using illegal inside information &#8211; or &#8216;black edge&#8217; &#8211; to beat the market.  His firm, SAC Capital, was ultimately indicted and pled guilty to charges of securities and wire fraud, and paid record criminal and civil fines of nearly $2 billion.  But even as the company bearing his name pled guilty, Cohen himself was never charged, and is free to start trading publicly again from January 2018.    </p>
<p>                    Black Edge offers a revelatory look at the grey zone in which so much of Wall Street functions, and a window into the transformation of the worldwide economy. With meticulous reporting and powerful storytelling, this is a riveting, true-life legal thriller that takes readers inside the US government&#8217;s pursuit of Cohen and his employees, and raises urgent questions about the power and wealth of those who sit at the pinnacle of the financial world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/">Black Edge : Inside Information, Dirty Money, and the Quest to Bring Down the Most Wanted Man on Wall Street &#8211; Sheelah Kolhatkar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>STARTUP WEALTH delivers engaging interviews with early- stage investors in Google, Invisalign, ZipCar, Uber, Twilio, Localytics, and other successful and not so successful companies. Find out how an amazing IPO can result in early investors getting pennies on the dollar&#8211;or a 10x+ return. Josh Maher profiles 23 of the country&#8217;s best investors over the last [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/">Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>STARTUP WEALTH delivers engaging interviews with early- stage investors in Google, Invisalign, ZipCar, Uber, Twilio, Localytics, and other successful and not so successful companies. Find out how an amazing IPO can result in early investors getting pennies on the dollar&#8211;or a 10x+ return.    </p>
<p>                    Josh Maher profiles 23 of the country&#8217;s best investors over the last two decades by way of real-world case studies. Through revealing interviews, readers are introduced to Mark Suster, Catherine Mott, Christopher Mirabile, Brad Feld, Allan May, Joanne Wilson, and many other accomplished angel investors and venture capitalists. In these interviews you&#8217;ll learn:<br />
                     &#8211; How the best investors think about identifying companies, negotiating terms, and partnering with founders and other investors<br />
                     &#8211; How angel investing can involve many different successful approaches<br />
                     &#8211; What the best investors have learned from their largest successes and failures<br />
                     &#8211; How investors design their portfolios and work with companies to achieve the most successful results.    </p>
<p>                    STARTUP WEALTH is an insightful and useful tool for anyone seeking to make better investments, select great investors, or raise early-stage capital for their business.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;There is nothing better when it comes to learning &#8216;best practices&#8217; than hearing from successful people in the trenches. Josh&#8217;s book captures the best of the best, as they reveal both what worked and what didn&#8217;t for them as angel investors and entrepreneurs. Required reading whatever side of the investing fence you&#8217;re on!&#8221;&#8211;Gerry Langeler, Managing Director at OVP Venture Partners. Co-founder of Mentor Graphics (NASDAQ: MENT). Author of The Success Matrix and Take the Money and Run! An Insider&#8217;s Guide to Venture Capital.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/">Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The innovative investor&#8217;s guide to an entirely new asset class-from two experts on the cutting edge    </p>
<p>                    With the rise of bitcoin and blockchain technology, investors can capitalize on the greatest investment opportunity since the Internet. Bitcoin was the first cryptoasset, but today there are over 800 and counting, including ether, ripple, litecoin, monero, and more. This clear, concise, and accessible guide from two industry insiders shows you how to navigate this brave new blockchain world-and how to invest in these emerging assets to secure your financial future.    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets gives you all the tools you need:    </p>
<p>                    * An actionable framework for investigating and valuing cryptoassets     </p>
<p>                    * Portfolio management techniques to maximize returns while managing risk    </p>
<p>                    * Historical context and tips to navigate inevitable bubbles and manias    </p>
<p>                    * Practical guides to exchanges, wallets, capital market vehicles, and ICOs    </p>
<p>                    * Predictions on how blockchain technology may disrupt current portfolios    </p>
<p>                    In addition to offering smart investment strategies, this authoritative resource will help you understand how these assets were created, how they work, and how they are evolving amid the blockchain revolution. The authors define a clear and original cryptoasset taxonomy, composed of cryptocurrencies, cryptocommodities, and cryptotokens, with insights into how each subset is blending technology and markets. You&#8217;ll find a variety of methods to invest in these assets, whether through global exchanges that trade 24/7 or initial cryptoasset offerings (ICOs). By sequentially building on the concepts of each prior chapter, the book will provide you with a full understanding of the cryptoasset economy and the opportunities that await the innovative investor .    </p>
<p>                    Cryptoassets represent the future of money and markets. This book is your guide to that future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cryptoassets-the-innovative-investors-guide-to-bitcoin-and-beyond-chris-burniske-jack-tatar-abridged/">Cryptoassets: The Innovative Investor&#8217;s Guide to Bitcoin and Beyond &#8211; Chris Burniske, Jack Tatar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Laws of Wealth : Psychology and the Secret to Investing Success &#8211; Daniel Crosby (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-laws-of-wealth-psychology-and-the-secret-to-investing-success-daniel-crosby-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Theory (Behaviourism)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-laws-of-wealth-psychology-and-the-secret-to-investing-success-daniel-crosby-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times and USA Today bestselling author, Dr Daniel Crosby, comes the behavioral finance book all investors have been waiting for. In The Laws of Wealth, psychologist and behavioral finance expert Daniel Crosby offers an accessible and applied take on a discipline that has long tended toward theory at the expense of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-laws-of-wealth-psychology-and-the-secret-to-investing-success-daniel-crosby-abridged/">The Laws of Wealth : Psychology and the Secret to Investing Success &#8211; Daniel Crosby (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times and USA Today bestselling author, Dr Daniel Crosby, comes the behavioral finance book all investors have been waiting for. In The Laws of Wealth, psychologist and behavioral finance expert Daniel Crosby offers an accessible and applied take on a discipline that has long tended toward theory at the expense of the practical. Readers are treated to real, actionable guidance as the promise of behavioral finance is realised and practical applications for everyday investors are delivered. Crosby presents a framework of timeless principles for managing your behavior and your investing process. He begins by outlining ten rules that are the hallmarks of good investor behavior, including &#8216;Forecasting is for Weathermen&#8217; and &#8216;If You&#8217;re Excited, It&#8217;s Probably a Bad Idea&#8217;. He then goes on to introduce a unique new taxonomy of behavioral investment risk that will enable investors and academics alike to understand behavioral risk in a newly coherent and complete way.From here, attention turns to the four ways in which behavioral risk can be combatted and the five equity selection methods investors should harness to take advantage of behaviorally-induced opportunities in the stock market.<br />
                    Throughout, readers are treated to anecdotes, research and graphics that illustrate the lessons in memorable ways. And in highly valuable &#8216;What now?&#8217; summaries at the end of each chapter, Crosby provides clear, concise direction on what investors should think, ask and do to benefit from the behavioral research. Dr. Crosby&#8217;s training as a clinical psychologist and work as an asset manager provide a unique vantage and result in a book that breaks new ground in behavioral finance. You need to follow the laws of wealth to manage your behavior and improve your investing process!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-laws-of-wealth-psychology-and-the-secret-to-investing-success-daniel-crosby-abridged/">The Laws of Wealth : Psychology and the Secret to Investing Success &#8211; Daniel Crosby (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adaptive Markets : Financial Evolution at the Speed of Thought &#8211; Andrew W. Lo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new, evolutionary explanation of markets and investor behavior Half of all Americans have money in the stock market, yet economists can&#8217;t agree on whether investors and markets are rational and efficient, as modern financial theory assumes, or irrational and inefficient, as behavioral economists believe&#8211;and as financial bubbles, crashes, and crises suggest. This is one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/">Adaptive Markets : Financial Evolution at the Speed of Thought &#8211; Andrew W. Lo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new, evolutionary explanation of markets and investor behavior  Half of all Americans have money in the stock market, yet economists can&#8217;t agree on whether investors and markets are rational and efficient, as modern financial theory assumes, or irrational and inefficient, as behavioral economists believe&#8211;and as financial bubbles, crashes, and crises suggest. This is one of the biggest debates in economics and the value or futility of investment management and financial regulation hang on the outcome. In this groundbreaking book, Andrew Lo cuts through this debate with a new framework, the Adaptive Markets Hypothesis, in which rationality and irrationality coexist. Drawing on psychology, evolutionary biology, neuroscience, artificial intelligence, and other fields, Adaptive Markets shows that the theory of market efficiency isn&#8217;t wrong but merely incomplete. When markets are unstable, investors react instinctively, creating inefficiencies for others to exploit. Lo&#8217;s new paradigm explains how financial evolution shapes behavior and markets at the speed of thought&#8211;a fact revealed by swings between stability and crisis, profit and loss, and innovation and regulation.<br />
                    A fascinating intellectual journey filled with compelling stories, Adaptive Markets starts with the origins of market efficiency and its failures, turns to the foundations of investor behavior, and concludes with practical implications&#8211;including how hedge funds have become the Galapagos Islands of finance, what really happened in the 2008 meltdown, and how we might avoid future crises. An ambitious new answer to fundamental questions in economics, Adaptive Markets is essential reading for anyone who wants to know how markets really work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adaptive-markets-financial-evolution-at-the-speed-of-thought-andrew-w-lo-abridged/">Adaptive Markets : Financial Evolution at the Speed of Thought &#8211; Andrew W. Lo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Hour Between Dog and Wolf : Risk-Taking, Gut Feelings and the Biology of Boom and Bust &#8211; John Coates (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-hour-between-dog-and-wolf-risk-taking-gut-feelings-and-the-biology-of-boom-and-bust-john-coates-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-hour-between-dog-and-wolf-risk-taking-gut-feelings-and-the-biology-of-boom-and-bust-john-coates-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now shortlisted for the 2012 Financial Times Business Book of the Year Award and the Wellcome Trust Book Prize, The Hour Between Dog and Wolf is a resonant exploration of economic behaviour and its consequences. Shortlisted for the 2012 Financial Times and Goldman Sachs Business Book of the Year Award and the Wellcome Trust Book [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hour-between-dog-and-wolf-risk-taking-gut-feelings-and-the-biology-of-boom-and-bust-john-coates-abridged/">The Hour Between Dog and Wolf : Risk-Taking, Gut Feelings and the Biology of Boom and Bust &#8211; John Coates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now shortlisted for the 2012 Financial Times Business Book of the Year Award and the Wellcome Trust Book Prize, The Hour Between Dog and Wolf is a resonant exploration of economic behaviour and its consequences.    </p>
<p>                              Shortlisted for the 2012 Financial Times and Goldman Sachs Business Book of the Year Award and the Wellcome Trust Book Prize, this startling and unconventional book from neuroscientist and former Wall Street trader John Coates shows us the bankers in their natural environment, revealing how their biochemistry has a lasting and significant impact on our economy.    </p>
<p>                              We learn how risk stimulates the most primitive part of the banker&#8217;s brain and how making the deals our bank balances depend on provokes an overwhelming fight-or-flight response. Constant swinging between aggression and apprehension impairs their judgment, causing economic upheaval in the wider world. The transformation between each split-second decision is what Coates calls the hour between dog and wolf, and understanding the biology behind bubbles and crashes may be the key to stabilising the markets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-hour-between-dog-and-wolf-risk-taking-gut-feelings-and-the-biology-of-boom-and-bust-john-coates-abridged/">The Hour Between Dog and Wolf : Risk-Taking, Gut Feelings and the Biology of Boom and Bust &#8211; John Coates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smartest Guys in the Room : The Amazing Rise and Scandalous Fall of Enron &#8211; Peter Elkind, Bethany McLean (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Company Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy Industries & Utilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What went wrong with American business at the end of the 20th century? Until the spring of 2001, Enron epitomized the triumph of the New Economy. Feared by rivals, worshipped by investors, Enron seemingly could do no wrong. Its profits rose every year; its stock price surged ever upward; its leaders were hailed as visionaries. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/">The Smartest Guys in the Room : The Amazing Rise and Scandalous Fall of Enron &#8211; Peter Elkind, Bethany McLean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What went wrong with American business at the end of the 20th century?    </p>
<p>                    Until the spring of 2001, Enron epitomized the triumph of the New Economy. Feared by rivals, worshipped by investors, Enron seemingly could do no wrong. Its profits rose every year; its stock price surged ever upward; its leaders were hailed as visionaries.      </p>
<p>                    Then a young Fortune writer, Bethany McLean, wrote an article posing a simple question &#8211;  how, exactly, does Enron make its money?    </p>
<p>                    Within a year Enron was facing humiliation and bankruptcy, the largest in US history, which caused Americans to lose faith in a system that rewarded top insiders with millions of dollars, while small investors lost everything. It was revealed that Enron was a company whose business was an illusion, an illusion that Wall Street was willing to accept even though they knew what the real truth was.  This book &#8211; fully updated for the paperback &#8211; tells the extraordinary story of Enron&#8217;s fall.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/">The Smartest Guys in the Room : The Amazing Rise and Scandalous Fall of Enron &#8211; Peter Elkind, Bethany McLean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Picking up where Liar&#8217;s Poker left off (literally, in the bond dealer&#8217;s desks of Salomon Brothers) the story of Long-Term Capital Management is of a group of elite investors who believed they could beat the market and, like alchemists, create limitless wealth for themselves and their partners. Founded by John Meriweather, a notoriously confident bond [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Picking up where Liar&#8217;s Poker left off (literally, in the bond dealer&#8217;s desks of Salomon Brothers) the story of Long-Term Capital Management is of a group of elite investors who believed they could beat the market and, like alchemists, create limitless wealth for themselves and their partners.    </p>
<p>                              Founded by John Meriweather, a notoriously confident bond dealer, along with two Nobel prize winners and a floor of Wall Street&#8217;s brightest and best, Long-Term Captial Management was from the beginning hailed as a new gold standard in investing. It was to be the hedge fund to end all other hedge funds: a discreet private investment club limited to those rich enough to pony up millions.    </p>
<p>                              It became the banks&#8217; own favourite fund and from its inception achieved a run of dizzyingly spectacular returns. New investors barged each other aside to get their investment money into LTCM&#8217;s hands. But as competitors began to mimic Meriweather&#8217;s fund, he altered strategy to maintain the fund&#8217;s performance, leveraging capital with credit on a scale not fully understood and never seen before.    </p>
<p>                              When the markets in Indonesia, South America and Russia crashed in 1998 LCTM&#8217;s investments crashed with them and mountainous debts accumulated. The fund was in melt-down, and threatening to bring down into its trillion-dollar black hole a host of financial instiutions from New York to Switzerland. It&#8217;s a tale of vivid characters, overwheening ambition, and perilous drama told, in Roger Lowenstein&#8217;s hands, with brilliant style and panache.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Millennial Money &#8211; Patrick O&#8217;Shaughnessy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/millennial-money-patrick-oshaughnessy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/millennial-money-patrick-oshaughnessy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We have witnessed one of the worst stock market beatings ever. As a result, abysmal returns are the new normal, financial experts are ringing the death knell of buy-and-hold, and investorsâ faith in equities has hit an all-time low. You have choices, you can abandon the stock market, or invest for tomorrow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millennial-money-patrick-oshaughnessy-abridged/">Millennial Money &#8211; Patrick O&#8217;Shaughnessy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We have witnessed one of the worst stock market beatings ever. As a result, abysmal returns are the new normal, financial experts are ringing the death knell of buy-and-hold, and investorsâ faith in equities has hit an all-time low. You have choices, you can abandon the stock market, or invest for tomorrow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millennial-money-patrick-oshaughnessy-abridged/">Millennial Money &#8211; Patrick O&#8217;Shaughnessy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Most Important Thing Illuminated : Uncommon Sense for the Thoughtful Investor &#8211; Howard Marks, Foreword by Bruce Greenwald (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Howard Marks&#8217;s The Most Important Thing distilled the investing insight of his celebrated client memos into a single volume and, for the first time, made his time-tested philosophy available to general readers. In this edition, Marks&#8217;s wisdom is joined by the comments, insights, and counterpoints of four renowned investors and investment educators: Christopher C. Davis [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/">The Most Important Thing Illuminated : Uncommon Sense for the Thoughtful Investor &#8211; Howard Marks, Foreword by Bruce Greenwald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Howard Marks&#8217;s The Most Important Thing distilled the investing insight of his celebrated client memos into a single volume and, for the first time, made his time-tested philosophy available to general readers. In this edition, Marks&#8217;s wisdom is joined by the comments, insights, and counterpoints of four renowned investors and investment educators: Christopher C. Davis (Davis Funds), Joel Greenblatt (Gotham Capital), Paul Johnson (Nicusa Capital), and Seth A. Klarman (Baupost Group). These experts lend insight into such concepts as &#8220;second-level thinking,&#8221; the price/value relationship, patient opportunism, and defensive investing. Marks also adds his own annotations, expanding on his book&#8217;s original themes and issues. A new chapter addresses the importance of reasonable expectations, and a foreword by Bruce C. Greenwald, called &#8220;a guru to Wall Street&#8217;s gurus&#8221; by the New York Times, speaks on value investing, productivity, and the economics of information.  ***  Howard Marks, the chairman and cofounder of Oaktree Capital Management, is renowned for his insightful assessments of market opportunity and risk.<br />
                    After four decades spent ascending to the top of the investment management profession, he is today sought out by the world&#8217;s leading value investors, and his client memos brim with insightful commentary and a time-tested, fundamental philosophy. Now for the first time, all readers can benefit from Marks&#8217;s wisdom, concentrated into a single volume that speaks to both the amateur and seasoned investor.  Informed by a lifetime of experience and study, The Most Important Thing explains the keys to successful investment and the pitfalls that can destroy capital or ruin a career. Utilizing passages from his memos to illustrate his ideas, Marks teaches by example, detailing the development of an investment philosophy that fully acknowledges the complexities of investing and the perils of the financial world. Brilliantly applying insight to today&#8217;s volatile markets, Marks offers a volume that is part memoir, part creed, with a number of broad takeaways.  Marks expounds on such concepts as &#8220;second-level thinking,&#8221; the price/value relationship, patient opportunism, and defensive investing.<br />
                    Frankly and honestly assessing his own decisions&#8211;and occasional missteps&#8211;he provides valuable lessons for critical thinking, risk assessment, and investment strategy. Encouraging investors to be &#8220;contrarian,&#8221; Marks wisely judges market cycles and achieves returns through aggressive yet measured action. Which element is the most essential? Successful investing requires thoughtful attention to many separate aspects, and each of Marks&#8217;s subjects proves to be the most important thing.  &#8220;This is that rarity, a useful book.&#8221;&#8211;Warren Buffett</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-most-important-thing-illuminated-uncommon-sense-for-the-thoughtful-investor-howard-marks-foreword-by-bruce-greenwald-abridged/">The Most Important Thing Illuminated : Uncommon Sense for the Thoughtful Investor &#8211; Howard Marks, Foreword by Bruce Greenwald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Charlie Munger : The Complete Investor &#8211; Tren Griffin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/charlie-munger-the-complete-investor-tren-griffin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/charlie-munger-the-complete-investor-tren-griffin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Charlie Munger, Berkshire Hathaway&#8217;s visionary vice chairman and Warren Buffett&#8217;s indispensable financial partner, has outperformed market indexes again and again, and he believes any investor can do the same. His notion of &#8220;elementary, worldly wisdom&#8221;-a set of interdisciplinary mental models involving economics, business, psychology, ethics, and management-allows him to keep his emotions out of his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/charlie-munger-the-complete-investor-tren-griffin-abridged/">Charlie Munger : The Complete Investor &#8211; Tren Griffin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Charlie Munger, Berkshire Hathaway&#8217;s visionary vice chairman and Warren Buffett&#8217;s indispensable financial partner, has outperformed market indexes again and again, and he believes any investor can do the same. His notion of &#8220;elementary, worldly wisdom&#8221;-a set of interdisciplinary mental models involving economics, business, psychology, ethics, and management-allows him to keep his emotions out of his investments and avoid the common pitfalls of bad judgment.  Munger&#8217;s system has steered his investments for forty years and has guided generations of successful investors. This book presents the essential steps of Munger&#8217;s investing strategy, condensed here for the first time from interviews, speeches, writings, and shareholder letters, and paired with commentary from fund managers, value investors, and business-case historians. Derived from Ben Graham&#8217;s value-investing system, Munger&#8217;s approach is straightforward enough that ordinary investors can apply it to their portfolios. This book is not simply about investing. It is about cultivating mental models for your whole life, but especially for your investments.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/charlie-munger-the-complete-investor-tren-griffin-abridged/">Charlie Munger : The Complete Investor &#8211; Tren Griffin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Money Master the Game : 7 Simple Steps to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/money-master-the-game-7-simple-steps-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mysteries & The Supernatural (Children's/YA)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/money-master-the-game-7-simple-steps-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR TONY ROBBINS BRINGS YOU 7 SIMPLE STEPS TO FINANCIAL FREEDOM &#8216;Tony Robbins needs no introduction. He is committed to helping make life better for every investor. Every investor will find this book extremely interesting and illuminating&#8217; Carl Icahn, billionaire and investor &#8216;Tony Robbins is a catalyst for getting people to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-master-the-game-7-simple-steps-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins-abridged/">Money Master the Game : 7 Simple Steps to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR TONY ROBBINS BRINGS YOU 7 SIMPLE STEPS TO FINANCIAL FREEDOM    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Tony Robbins needs no introduction. He is committed to helping make life better for every investor. Every investor will find this book extremely interesting and illuminating&#8217; Carl Icahn, billionaire and investor     </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Tony Robbins is a catalyst for getting people to change&#8217; Oprah Winfrey     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Tony Robbins is a genius . . .  His ability to strategically guide people through any challege is unparalleled&#8217; Steve Wynn, CEO and Founder of Wynn Resorts     </p>
<p>                    Tony Robbins, the multimillion-copy bestselling author of Awaken the Giant Within and Unlimited Power has created a 7-step blueprint for securing financial freedom.    </p>
<p>                     Based on extensive research and one-on-one interviews with more than 50 of the most legendary financial experts in the world &#8211; from Carl Icahn, to Warren Buffett, to Jack Bogle and Steve Forbes.     </p>
<p>                     Robbins has a brilliant way of using metaphor and story to illustrate even the most complex financial concepts &#8211; making them simple and actionable. With expert advice on our most important financial decisions, Robbins dispels the myths that often rob people of their financial dreams.    </p>
<p>                    Money: Master the Game contains expert advice for readers of every income level, providing guidance through the steps to become financially free by creating a lifetime income plan. This book delivers invaluable information and essential practices for getting your financial house in order. It&#8217;s the book millions of people have been waiting for.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-master-the-game-7-simple-steps-to-financial-freedom-tony-robbins-abridged/">Money Master the Game : 7 Simple Steps to Financial Freedom &#8211; Tony Robbins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book That Still Beats the Market &#8211; Joel Greenblatt, Foreword by Andrew Tobias (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-that-still-beats-the-market-joel-greenblatt-foreword-by-andrew-tobias-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-that-still-beats-the-market-joel-greenblatt-foreword-by-andrew-tobias-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2005, Joel Greenblatt published a book that is already considered one of the classics of finance literature. In The Little Book that Beats the Market a New York Times bestseller with 300,000 copies in print Greenblatt explained how investors can outperform the popular market averages by simply and systematically applying a formula that seeks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-that-still-beats-the-market-joel-greenblatt-foreword-by-andrew-tobias-abridged/">The Little Book That Still Beats the Market &#8211; Joel Greenblatt, Foreword by Andrew Tobias (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2005, Joel Greenblatt published a book that is already considered one of the classics of finance literature. In  The Little Book that Beats the Market a  New York Times bestseller with 300,000 copies in print Greenblatt explained how investors can outperform the popular market averages by simply and systematically applying a formula that seeks out good businesses when they are available at bargain prices. Now, with a new Introduction and Afterword for 2010,  The Little Book that Still Beats the Market updates and expands upon the research findings from the original book. Included are data and analysis covering the recent financial crisis and model performance through the end of 2009. In a straightforward and accessible style, the book explores the basic principles of successful stock market investing and then reveals the author s time-tested formula that makes buying above average companies at below average prices automatic. Though the formula has been extensively tested and is a breakthrough in the academic and professional world, Greenblatt explains it using 6 th grade math, plain language and humor.<br />
                    He shows how to use his method to beat both the market and professional managers by a wide margin. You ll also learn why success eludes almost all individual and professional investors, and why the formula will continue to work even after everyone knows it.  While the formula may be simple, understanding why the formula works is the true key to success for investors. The book will take readers on a step-by-step journey so that they can learn the principles of value investing in a way that will provide them with a long term strategy that they can understand and stick with through both good and bad periods for the stock market.  As the Wall Street Journal stated about the original edition, Mr. Greenblatt says his goal was to provide advice that, while sophisticated, could be understood and followed by his five children, ages 6 to 15. They are in luck. His Little Book is one of the best, clearest guides to value investing out there.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-that-still-beats-the-market-joel-greenblatt-foreword-by-andrew-tobias-abridged/">The Little Book That Still Beats the Market &#8211; Joel Greenblatt, Foreword by Andrew Tobias (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Smell a Rat : The Five Signs of Financial Fraud &#8211; Kenneth L. Fisher, Lara W. Hoffmans (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-smell-a-rat-the-five-signs-of-financial-fraud-kenneth-l-fisher-lara-w-hoffmans-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-smell-a-rat-the-five-signs-of-financial-fraud-kenneth-l-fisher-lara-w-hoffmans-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A timely guide to uncovering financial fraud 2008 and 2009 will be remembered for bear markets, a global credit crunch, and some of the largest investment scams ever. But these scams are nothing new, they&#8217;ve been repeated throughout history, and there will certainly be more to come. But the good news is fraudsters often follow [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-smell-a-rat-the-five-signs-of-financial-fraud-kenneth-l-fisher-lara-w-hoffmans-abridged/">How to Smell a Rat : The Five Signs of Financial Fraud &#8211; Kenneth L. Fisher, Lara W. Hoffmans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A timely guide to uncovering financial fraud  2008 and 2009 will be remembered for bear markets, a global credit crunch, and some of the largest investment scams ever. But these scams are nothing new, they&#8217;ve been repeated throughout history, and there will certainly be more to come. But the good news is fraudsters often follow the same basic playbook. Learn the playbook, and know how to ask the right questions, and financial fraud can be easy to detect and simple to avoid.  In How to Smell a Rat, trusted financial expert Ken Fisher provides you with an inside&#8217;s view on how to spot financial disasters before you become a part of them. Filled with in-depth insights and practical advice, this reliable resource takes an engaging look at recent and historic examples of fraudsters, how they operated, and how they can be easily avoided. Fisher also shows you the quick, identifiable features of financial frauds and arms you with the questions to ask when assessing a money manager.<br />
                    * Prepares you to identify and avoid financials cams that could instantly destroy your wealth * Contains examples that highlight how financial frauds are committed * Provides questions everyone should ask before entering any investment endeavor With How to Smell a Rat as your guide, you&#8217;ll learn how to protect your interests and assets from unnecessary losses.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-smell-a-rat-the-five-signs-of-financial-fraud-kenneth-l-fisher-lara-w-hoffmans-abridged/">How to Smell a Rat : The Five Signs of Financial Fraud &#8211; Kenneth L. Fisher, Lara W. Hoffmans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Wealth of Common Sense : Why Simplicity Trumps Complexity in Any Investment Plan &#8211; Ben Carlson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A simple guide to a smarter strategy for the individual investor A Wealth of Common Sense sheds a refreshing light on investing, and shows you how a simplicity-based framework can lead to better investment decisions. The financial market is a complex system, but that doesn&#8217;t mean it requires a complex strategy; in fact, this false [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/">A Wealth of Common Sense : Why Simplicity Trumps Complexity in Any Investment Plan &#8211; Ben Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A simple guide to a smarter strategy for the individual investor A Wealth of Common Sense sheds a refreshing light on investing, and shows you how a simplicity-based framework can lead to better investment decisions. The financial market is a complex system, but that doesn&#8217;t mean it requires a complex strategy; in fact, this false premise is the driving force behind many investors&#8217; market &#8220;mistakes.&#8221; Information is important, but understanding and perspective are the keys to better decision-making. This book describes the proper way to view the markets and your portfolio, and show you the simple strategies that make investing more profitable, less confusing, and less time-consuming. Without the burden of short-term performance benchmarks, individual investors have the advantage of focusing on the long view, and the freedom to construct the kind of portfolio that will serve their investment goals best. This book proves how complex strategies essentially waste these advantages, and provides an alternative game plan for those ready to simplify.<br />
                    Complexity is often used as a mechanism for talking investors into unnecessary purchases, when all most need is a deeper understanding of conventional options. This book explains which issues you actually should pay attention to, and which ones are simply used for an illusion of intelligence and control. * Keep up with or beat professional money managers * Exploit stock market volatility to your utmost advantage * Learn where advisors and consultants fit into smart strategy * Build a portfolio that makes sense for your particular situation You don&#8217;t have to outsmart the market if you can simply outperform it. Cut through the confusion and noise and focus on what actually matters. A Wealth of Common Sense clears the air, and gives you the insight you need to become a smarter, more successful investor.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/">A Wealth of Common Sense : Why Simplicity Trumps Complexity in Any Investment Plan &#8211; Ben Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buffett : The Making of an American Capitalist &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since its hardcover publication in August of 1995, Buffett has appeared on the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, San Francisco Chronicle, Los Angeles Times, Seattle Times, Newsday and Business Week bestseller lists. Starting from scratch, simply by picking stocks and companies for investment, Warren Buffett amassed one of the epochal fortunes of the twentieth [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">Buffett : The Making of an American Capitalist &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since its hardcover publication in August of 1995, Buffett has appeared on the Wall Street Journal, New York Times, San Francisco Chronicle, Los Angeles Times, Seattle Times, Newsday and Business Week bestseller lists. Starting from scratch, simply by picking stocks and companies for investment, Warren Buffett amassed one of the epochal fortunes of the twentieth century&#8211;an astounding net worth of $10 billion, and counting. His awesome investment record has made him a cult figure popularly known for his seeming contradictions: a billionaire who has a modest lifestyle, a phenomenally successful investor who eschews the revolving-door trading of modern Wall Street, a brilliant dealmaker who cultivates a homespun aura. Journalist Roger Lowenstein draws on three years of unprecedented access to Buffett&#8217;s family, friends, and colleagues to provide the first definitive, inside account of the life and career of this American original. Buffett explains Buffett&#8217;s investment strategy&#8211;a long-term philosophy grounded in buying stock in companies that are undervalued on the market and hanging on until their worth invariably surfaces&#8211;and shows how it is a reflection of his inner self.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buffett-the-making-of-an-american-capitalist-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">Buffett : The Making of an American Capitalist &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Geometry of Wealth : How to shape a life of money and meaning &#8211; Brian Portnoy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-geometry-of-wealth-how-to-shape-a-life-of-money-and-meaning-brian-portnoy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-geometry-of-wealth-how-to-shape-a-life-of-money-and-meaning-brian-portnoy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How does money figure into a happy life? In The Geometry of Wealth, behavioral finance expert Brian Portnoy delivers an inspired answer, building on the critical distinction between being rich and being wealthy. While one is an unsatisfying treadmill, the other is the ability to underwrite a meaningful life, however one chooses to define that. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-geometry-of-wealth-how-to-shape-a-life-of-money-and-meaning-brian-portnoy-abridged/">The Geometry of Wealth : How to shape a life of money and meaning &#8211; Brian Portnoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How does money figure into a happy life?    </p>
<p>                    In The Geometry of Wealth, behavioral finance expert Brian Portnoy delivers an inspired answer, building on the critical distinction between being rich and being wealthy. While one is an unsatisfying treadmill, the other is the ability to underwrite a meaningful life, however one chooses to define that. Truly viewed, wealth is funded contentment.    </p>
<p>                    At the heart of this groundbreaking perspective, Portnoy takes readers on a journey toward wealth, informed by disciplines ranging from ancient history to modern neuroscience. He contends that tackling the big questions about a joyful life and tending to financial decisions are complementary, not separate, tasks.     </p>
<p>                    These big questions include:<br />
                    &#8211; How is the human brain wired for two distinct experiences of happiness? And why can money &#8220;buy&#8221; one but not the other?<br />
                    &#8211; What are the touchstones of a meaningful life, and are they affordable?<br />
                    &#8211; Why is market savvy among the least important sources of wealth but self-awareness is among the most?<br />
                    &#8211; How does one strike a balance between striving for more while being content with enough?    </p>
<p>                    This journey memorably contours along three basic shapes: A circle, triangle and square help us to visualize how we adapt to evolving circumstances, set clear priorities, and find empowerment in simplicity. In this accessible and entertaining book, Portnoy reveals that true wealth is achievable for many &#8211; including those who despair it is out of reach &#8211; but only in the context of a life in which purpose and practice are thoughtfully calibrated.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-geometry-of-wealth-how-to-shape-a-life-of-money-and-meaning-brian-portnoy-abridged/">The Geometry of Wealth : How to shape a life of money and meaning &#8211; Brian Portnoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trading for a Living : Psychology, Trading Tactics, Money Management &#8211; Alexander Elder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trading-for-a-living-psychology-trading-tactics-money-management-alexander-elder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trading-for-a-living-psychology-trading-tactics-money-management-alexander-elder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Trading for a Living Successful trading is based on three Ma s: Mind, Method, and Money. Trading for a Living helps you master all of those three areas: aeo How to become a cool, calm, and collected trader aeo How to profit from reading the behavior of the market crowd aeo How to use a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trading-for-a-living-psychology-trading-tactics-money-management-alexander-elder-abridged/">Trading for a Living : Psychology, Trading Tactics, Money Management &#8211; Alexander Elder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Trading for a Living Successful trading is based on three Ma s: Mind, Method, and Money. Trading for a Living helps you master all of those three areas: aeo How to become a cool, calm, and collected trader aeo How to profit from reading the behavior of the market crowd aeo How to use a computer to find good trades aeo How to develop a powerful trading system aeo How to find the trades with the best odds of success aeo How to find entry and exit points, set stops, and take profits Trading for a Living helps you discipline your Mind, shows you the Methods for trading the markets, and shows you how to manage Money in your trading accounts so that no string of losses can kick you out of the game. To help you profit even more from the ideas in Trading for a Living, look for the companion volume&#8212;-Study Guide for Trading for a Living. It asks over 200 multiple&#8211;choice questions, with answers and 11 rating scales for sharpening your trading skills.<br />
                    For example: Question Markets rise when aeo there are more buyers than sellers aeo buyers are more aggressive than sellers aeo sellers are afraid and demand a premium aeo more shares or contracts are bought than sold aeo I and II aeo II and III aeo II and IV aeo III and IV Answer B. II and III. Every change in price reflects what happens in the battle between bulls and bears. Markets rise when bulls feel more strongly than bears. They rally when buyers are confident and sellers demand a premium for participating in the game that is going against them. There is a buyer and a seller behind every transaction. The number of stocks or futures bought and sold is equal by definition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trading-for-a-living-psychology-trading-tactics-money-management-alexander-elder-abridged/">Trading for a Living : Psychology, Trading Tactics, Money Management &#8211; Alexander Elder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Your Retirement Salary : How to use your lifetime of pension savings to pay yourself an income in your retirement &#8211; Richard Dyson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/your-retirement-salary-how-to-use-your-lifetime-of-pension-savings-to-pay-yourself-an-income-in-your-retirement-richard-dyson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/your-retirement-salary-how-to-use-your-lifetime-of-pension-savings-to-pay-yourself-an-income-in-your-retirement-richard-dyson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You have spent a few decades working, earning a salary from your employers, and saving into company and personal pensions along the way. Now, retirement is approaching. How will you turn your savings into a salary to pay for essentials and leisure time in retirement? How will you make sure that you don&#8217;t run out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/your-retirement-salary-how-to-use-your-lifetime-of-pension-savings-to-pay-yourself-an-income-in-your-retirement-richard-dyson-abridged/">Your Retirement Salary : How to use your lifetime of pension savings to pay yourself an income in your retirement &#8211; Richard Dyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You have spent a few decades working, earning a salary from your employers, and saving into company and personal pensions along the way. Now, retirement is approaching.<br />
                     How will you turn your savings into a salary to pay for essentials and leisure time in retirement? How will you make sure that you don&#8217;t run out of money too soon? What do the UK pension freedoms mean for you?     </p>
<p>                    In this one-of-a-kind book, personal finance experts Richard Dyson and Richard Evans answer these questions and equip you with everything you need to know to turn your pension savings into an income that will last throughout your retirement.<br />
                     You will learn:<br />
                    &#8212; How to take control of your pension savings by tracking down all of your pension pots and combining them.<br />
                    &#8212; When you can afford to retire.<br />
                    &#8212; Steps to take to avoid running out of money.<br />
                    &#8212; How to build an income-paying portfolio of fund investments from scratch.<br />
                    &#8212; How to withdraw a sustainable income from your portfolio.<br />
                    &#8212; How annuities work and whether they have a role for you.<br />
                    &#8212; How to make the most of the tax rules.<br />
                    &#8212; The contribution made by the State Pension.<br />
                    &#8212; When to seek professional advice.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/your-retirement-salary-how-to-use-your-lifetime-of-pension-savings-to-pay-yourself-an-income-in-your-retirement-richard-dyson-abridged/">Your Retirement Salary : How to use your lifetime of pension savings to pay yourself an income in your retirement &#8211; Richard Dyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investing with Impact : Why Finance is a Force for Good &#8211; Jeremy Balkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Investing with Impact: Why Finance Is a Force for Good outlines the roadmap to reinvigorating a skeptical public and demoralized financial services industry by making the case that, contrary to popular misconception, finance is not the cause of the world&#8217;s problems; in fact, it can provide the solution. Author Jeremy Balkin presents the case that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/">Investing with Impact : Why Finance is a Force for Good &#8211; Jeremy Balkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Investing with Impact: Why Finance Is a Force for Good outlines the roadmap to reinvigorating a skeptical public and demoralized financial services industry by making the case that, contrary to popular misconception, finance is not the cause of the world&#8217;s problems; in fact, it can provide the solution. Author Jeremy Balkin presents the case that the finance industry can improve the state of the world by positively influencing the allocation of capital.  Investing With Impact explains the methodology of Balkin&#8217;s 6 E Paradigm, opening the toolbox to this revolutionary framework for the first time. In so doing, Balkin expands the impact investment universe, enabling mainstream capital to flow where opportunities generate positive investment returns and have demonstrable social impact.  Described by the Huffington Post as the &#8220;Anti-Wolf of Wall Street,&#8221; Balkin is challenging the status quo on Wall Street by leading the intellectual debate embracing the $1 trillion frontier impact investment market opportunity. The book demonstrates conclusively that, if we can change the culture in finance, we can change the world for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/investing-with-impact-why-finance-is-a-force-for-good-jeremy-balkin-abridged/">Investing with Impact : Why Finance is a Force for Good &#8211; Jeremy Balkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The best-selling index investing &#8220;bible&#8221; offers new information and is updated to reflect the latest market data The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the classic guide to getting smart about the market. Legendary mutual fund veteran John C. Bogle reveals his key to getting more out of investing: low-cost index funds. Bogle describes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/">The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The best-selling index investing &#8220;bible&#8221; offers new information and is updated to reflect the latest market data The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the classic guide to getting smart about the market. Legendary mutual fund veteran John C. Bogle reveals his key to getting more out of investing: low-cost index funds. Bogle describes the simplest and most effective investment strategy for building wealth over the long term: buy and hold, at very low cost, a mutual fund that tracks the S&#038;P 500 Stock Index. Such an index portfolio is the only investment that guarantees your fair share of stock market returns. This strategy is favored by Warren Buffett, who has endorsed this best selling 10th Anniversary Edition. The book shows you how to make index investing work for you and help you achieve your financial goals, cut through the hype to see what&#8217;s really in your best interest, and analyze the metrics that truly matter. You&#8217;ll gain candid insight from some of the world&#8217;s best financial minds: not only Warren Buffett, but Benjamin Graham, Paul Samuelson, Burton Malkiel, and others.<br />
                    Updated with current data and laced with two new chapters on asset allocation and retirement investing, the new Little Book of Common Sense Investing gives you a solid strategy for building your financial future. * Build a broadly diversified, low-cost portfolio without the risks of individual stocks, manager selection, and sector rotation * Forget the fads and focus on what works in the real world * Emphasize business reality over market expectations * Understand how index investing is the only game that assures your fair share of stock market returns Too many investors trade franticly, turning a winners game into a losers game, while index investing allows you to sit back and let the market do the work for you. Learn how to harness the magic of compounding returns while avoiding the tyranny of compounding costs. Bogle describes his simple method for developing rational expectations for future market returns, and what he sees coming over the next decade.  The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the guidebook to your financial future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/">The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019    </p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review    </p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.    </p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.    </p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.    </p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits and Other Writings &#8211; Philip A. Fisher, Introduction by Kenneth L. Fisher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits-and-other-writings-philip-a-fisher-introduction-by-kenneth-l-fisher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits-and-other-writings-philip-a-fisher-introduction-by-kenneth-l-fisher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Widely respected and admired, Philip Fisher is among the most influential investors of all time. His investment philosophies, introduced almost forty years ago, are not only studied and applied by today&#8217;s financiers and investors, but are also regarded by many as gospel. This book is invaluable reading and has been since it was first published [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits-and-other-writings-philip-a-fisher-introduction-by-kenneth-l-fisher-abridged/">Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits and Other Writings &#8211; Philip A. Fisher, Introduction by Kenneth L. Fisher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Widely respected and admired, Philip Fisher is among the most influential investors of all time. His investment philosophies, introduced almost forty years ago, are not only studied and applied by today&#8217;s financiers and investors, but are also regarded by many as gospel. This book is invaluable reading and has been since it was first published in 1958. The updated paperback retains the investment wisdom of the original edition and includes the perspectives of the author&#8217;s son Ken Fisher, an investment guru in his own right in an expanded preface and introduction &#8220;I sought out Phil Fisher after reading his Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits&#8230;A thorough understanding of the business, obtained by using Phil&#8217;s techniques&#8230;enables one to make intelligent investment commitments.&#8221; Warren Buffet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits-and-other-writings-philip-a-fisher-introduction-by-kenneth-l-fisher-abridged/">Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits and Other Writings &#8211; Philip A. Fisher, Introduction by Kenneth L. Fisher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Heart of the Deal : How to Invest and Negotiate like a Real Estate Mogul &#8211; Anthony Lolli, With Benjamin Platt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-heart-of-the-deal-how-to-invest-and-negotiate-like-a-real-estate-mogul-anthony-lolli-with-benjamin-platt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-heart-of-the-deal-how-to-invest-and-negotiate-like-a-real-estate-mogul-anthony-lolli-with-benjamin-platt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The founder and CEO of Rapid Realty, New York City&#8217;s largest rental-based real estate brokerage, shares his story, his advice, and his tips for building a successful career in the ever-growing and lucrative world of real estate. Anthony Lolli got his real estate license at age nineteen. By twenty-three, he was a millionaire and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-heart-of-the-deal-how-to-invest-and-negotiate-like-a-real-estate-mogul-anthony-lolli-with-benjamin-platt-abridged/">The Heart of the Deal : How to Invest and Negotiate like a Real Estate Mogul &#8211; Anthony Lolli, With Benjamin Platt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The founder and CEO of Rapid Realty, New York City&#8217;s largest rental-based real estate brokerage, shares his story, his advice, and his tips for building a successful career in the ever-growing and lucrative world of real estate.    </p>
<p>                    Anthony Lolli got his real estate license at age nineteen. By twenty-three, he was a millionaire and the head of a swiftly growing company that would become one of the largest real estate brokerages in New York and a national franchise sensation. Now, he&#8217;s sharing the secrets behind his success.     </p>
<p>                    Filled with insights into Lolli&#8217;s inspirational rags-to-riches rise to the top and bursting with practical advice for real estate newcomers and veterans alike, The Heart of the Deal is essential reading for anyone with big dreams and the drive to make them come true. Learn how to set smart goals, negotiate like a pro, analyze properties and neighborhoods, overcome objections, and much more.      </p>
<p>                    Whether you want to become a top-performing broker or a savvy property investor, or simply master real estate management tactics designed to help you achieve your financial goals, Lolli&#8217;s grounded guidance will put you on the right path.      </p>
<p>                    Most importantly, The Heart of the Deal will teach you how to utilize all of these strategies to build a lucrative career without sacrificing your humanity in the process. At all times, Lolli keeps one central premise in mind: that the heart of every deal isn&#8217;t money-it&#8217;s people.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-heart-of-the-deal-how-to-invest-and-negotiate-like-a-real-estate-mogul-anthony-lolli-with-benjamin-platt-abridged/">The Heart of the Deal : How to Invest and Negotiate like a Real Estate Mogul &#8211; Anthony Lolli, With Benjamin Platt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WHAT IF YOU HAD AN ANGEL ON YOUR SIDE?&#8221;Terrific advice from a master of the angel investing game. Brian Cohen reveals the art and craft of raising angel money. An investment in this book will payoff a thousandfold.&#8221; &#8212; DR. HOWARD MORGAN, founder andpartner at First Round Capital When you connect with the right angel [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/">What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WHAT IF YOU HAD AN ANGEL ON YOUR SIDE?&#8221;Terrific advice from a master of the angel investing game. Brian Cohen reveals the art and craft of raising angel money. An investment in this book will payoff a thousandfold.&#8221; &#8212; DR. HOWARD MORGAN, founder andpartner at First Round Capital    </p>
<p>                    When you connect with the right angel investor, it&#8217;s like finding a new best friend&#8211;you just have to know what makes him or her happy.    </p>
<p>                    Smart funding is waiting for smart founders. Raising funds is all about connecting with the investor who&#8217;s right for you&#8211;and What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know shows you exactly how to succeed.    </p>
<p>                    Veteran early-stage investor Brian Cohen knows how to spot a great company destined for success, and in this groundbreaking book he offers soup-to-nuts guidance for anyentrepreneur seeking to launch an invention, a product, or a great new idea into a receptive marketplace.    </p>
<p>                    As chairman of the board of directors of the New York Angels, Cohen is one of the most engaged angel investors out there today. The first investor in Pinterest, he describes exactly what angels want to see, hear, and feelbefore they take out their checkbooks:    </p>
<p>                    A clear exit strategy before the startup even launchesFacts that turn &#8220;due&#8221; diligence into &#8220;do&#8221; diligenceAuthenticity&#8211;&#8220;save your spinning for the fitness center&#8221;Proof that you &#8220;live inside the customer&#8217;s head&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Cohen gives invaluable insight into how the most successful angels view due diligence, friends and family money, crowdfunding, team building, scalability, iteration, exit strategies&#8211;and much more.    </p>
<p>                    This one-of-a-kind book provides a rare look inside the minds of people who are in the business of funding businesses just like yours.    </p>
<p>                    Read What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know to get your best shot at funding for your product after your very first pitch.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR WHAT EVERY ANGEL INVESTOR WANTS YOU TO KNOW:&#8221;Brian Cohen is truly the entrepreneur&#8217;s best friend. Cohen and Kador haven distilled their first-hand experiences into an intensely personal, highly readablejourney into the mind of angels that should be kept at the bedside of every startup CEO.&#8221; &#8212; DAVID S. ROSE, founder, New York Angels, and CEO, Gust    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Meet one of the fundamental building blocks of the entrepreneurial scene. In one easy-to-read package, readers now have the wisdom of Brian Cohen, perhaps themost well-connected investor/entrepreneur in New York.&#8221; &#8212; MURAT AKTIHANOGLU, founder and managing director, Entrepreneurs Roundtable Accelerator    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know gives you an actionable checklist for success in fund-raising and entrepreneurship. Cohen and Kador provide anexhilarating ride for those who want to pilot their own business.&#8221; &#8212; REED HOLDEN, serial entrepreneur and author of Negotiating with Backbone    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Personal insights from a seasoned angel investor. An important addition to the reading list for today&#8217;s entrepreneurs.&#8221; &#8212; SCOTT CASE, CEO, Startup America Partnership    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know is a must-read for entrepreneurs and investors who want to fi nance startup dreams&#8211;an accessible, jargon-free,practical primer.&#8221; &#8212; WHITNEY JOHNSON, author of Dare, Dream, Do: Remarkable Things Happen When You Dare to Dream and cofounder, Rose Park Advisors    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;While [this] book is anecdotal, [the authors] discuss in depth how angels view a potential investment as well as how they evaluate its prospects. This is the book&#8217;s strength. Recommended. All levels of students, entrepreneurs, practitioners.&#8221; &#8212; CHOICE</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-every-angel-investor-wants-you-to-know-an-insider-reveals-how-to-get-smart-funding-for-your-billion-dollar-idea-brian-cohen-john-kador-abridged/">What Every Angel Investor Wants You to Know: An Insider Reveals How to Get Smart Funding for Your Billion Dollar Idea &#8211; Brian Cohen, John Kador (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Education of a Value Investor : My Transformative Quest for Wealth, Wisdom, and Enlightenment &#8211; Guy Spier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-education-of-a-value-investor-my-transformative-quest-for-wealth-wisdom-and-enlightenment-guy-spier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-education-of-a-value-investor-my-transformative-quest-for-wealth-wisdom-and-enlightenment-guy-spier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What happens when a young Wall Street investment banker spends a small fortune to have lunch with Warren Buffett? He becomes a real value investor. In this fascinating inside story, Guy Spier details his career from Harvard MBA to hedge fund manager. But the path was not so straightforward. Spier reveals his transformation from a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-a-value-investor-my-transformative-quest-for-wealth-wisdom-and-enlightenment-guy-spier-abridged/">The Education of a Value Investor : My Transformative Quest for Wealth, Wisdom, and Enlightenment &#8211; Guy Spier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What happens when a young Wall Street investment banker spends a small fortune to have lunch with Warren Buffett? He becomes a real value investor. In this fascinating inside story, Guy Spier details his career from Harvard MBA to hedge fund manager. But the path was not so straightforward. Spier reveals his transformation from a Gordon Gekko wannabe, driven by greed, to a sophisticated investor who enjoys success without selling his soul to the highest bidder. Spier&#8217;s journey is similar to the thousands that flock to Wall Street every year with their shiny new diplomas, aiming to be King of Wall Street. Yet what Guy realized just in the nick of time was that the King really lived 1,500 miles away in Omaha, Nebraska. Spier determinedly set out to create a new career in his own way. Along the way he learned some powerful lessons which include: why the right mentors and partners are critical to long term success on Wall Street; why a topnotch education can sometimes get in the way of your success; that real learning doesn&#8217;t begin until you are on your own; and how the best lessons from Warren Buffett have less to do with investing and more to do with being true to yourself.<br />
                    Spier also reveals some of his own winning investment strategies, detailing deals that were winners but also what he learned from deals that went south. Part memoir, part Wall Street advice, and part how-to, Guy Spier takes readers on a ride through Wall Street but more importantly provides those that want to take a different path with the insight, guidance, and inspiration they need to carve out their own definition of success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-a-value-investor-my-transformative-quest-for-wealth-wisdom-and-enlightenment-guy-spier-abridged/">The Education of a Value Investor : My Transformative Quest for Wealth, Wisdom, and Enlightenment &#8211; Guy Spier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Snowball : Warren Buffett and the Business of Life &#8211; Alice Schroeder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-snowball-warren-buffett-and-the-business-of-life-alice-schroeder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-snowball-warren-buffett-and-the-business-of-life-alice-schroeder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Recounting the life and times of one of the most respected men in the world, The Snowball is the most fascinating financial success story of our time. Warren Buffett, the legendary Omaha investor has never written a memoir, but finally has given Alice Schroeder unprecedented access to him and all those closest to his work, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-snowball-warren-buffett-and-the-business-of-life-alice-schroeder-abridged/">The Snowball : Warren Buffett and the Business of Life &#8211; Alice Schroeder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Recounting the life and times of one of the most respected men in the world, The Snowball is the most fascinating financial success story of our time. Warren Buffett, the legendary Omaha investor has never written a memoir, but finally has given Alice Schroeder unprecedented access to him and all those closest to his work, opinions, struggles, triumphs, follies and wisdom. The result is this personally revealing and complete biography of &#8216;The Oracle of Omaha&#8217;, indispensable reading for those who wish to know the man behind the outstanding achievements.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-snowball-warren-buffett-and-the-business-of-life-alice-schroeder-abridged/">The Snowball : Warren Buffett and the Business of Life &#8211; Alice Schroeder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Myths of Innovation &#8211; Scott Berkun (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this new paperback edition of the classic bestseller, you&#8217;ll be taken on a hilarious, fast-paced ride through the history of ideas. Author Scott Berkun will show you how to transcend the false stories that many business experts, scientists, and much of pop culture foolishly use to guide their thinking about how ideas change the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/">The Myths of Innovation &#8211; Scott Berkun (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this new paperback edition of the classic bestseller, you&#8217;ll be taken on a hilarious, fast-paced ride through the history of ideas. Author Scott Berkun will show you how to transcend the false stories that many business experts, scientists, and much of pop culture foolishly use to guide their thinking about how ideas change the world. With four new chapters on putting the ideas in the book to work, updated references and over 50 corrections and improvements, now is the time to get past the myths, and change the world. You&#8217;ll have fun while you learn:  * Where ideas come from * The true history of history * Why most people don&#8217;t like ideas * How great managers make ideas thrive * The importance of problem finding * The simple plan (new for paperback)  Since its initial publication, this classic bestseller has been discussed on NPR, MSNBC, CNBC, and at Yale University, MIT, Carnegie Mellon University, Microsoft, Apple, Intel, Google, Amazon.com, and other major media, corporations, and universities around the world. It has changed the way thousands of leaders and creators understand the world.<br />
                    Now in an updated and expanded paperback edition, it&#8217;s a fantastic time to explore or rediscover this powerful view of the world of ideas. &#8220;Sets us free to try and change the world.&#8221; &#8211;Guy Kawasaki, Author of Art of The Start &#8220;Small, simple, powerful: an innovative book about innovation.&#8221; &#8211;Don Norman, author of Design of Everyday Things &#8220;Insightful, inspiring, evocative, and just plain fun to read. It&#8217;s totally great.&#8221; &#8211;John Seely Brown, Former Director, Xerox Palo Alto Research Center (PARC) &#8220;Methodically and entertainingly dismantling the cliches that surround the process of innovation.&#8221; &#8211;Scott Rosenberg, author of Dreaming in Code; cofounder of Salon.com &#8220;Will inspire you to come up with breakthrough ideas of your own.&#8221; &#8211;Alan Cooper, Father of Visual Basic and author of The Inmates are Running the Asylum &#8220;Brimming with insights and historical examples, Berkun&#8217;s book not only debunks widely held myths about innovation, it also points the ways toward making your new ideas stick.&#8221; &#8211;Tom Kelley, GM, IDEO; author of The Ten Faces of Innovation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-myths-of-innovation-scott-berkun-abridged/">The Myths of Innovation &#8211; Scott Berkun (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Outsmarting the Crowd : A Value Investor&#8217;s Guide to Starting, Building, and Keeping a Family Fortune &#8211; Bogumil K Baranowski, Foreword by Francois D Sicart (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/outsmarting-the-crowd-a-value-investors-guide-to-starting-building-and-keeping-a-family-fortune-bogumil-k-baranowski-foreword-by-francois-d-sicart-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/outsmarting-the-crowd-a-value-investors-guide-to-starting-building-and-keeping-a-family-fortune-bogumil-k-baranowski-foreword-by-francois-d-sicart-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WE ARE WIRED TO FAIL WITH MONEY AND INVESTING. Do You Have $1 on You? BEFORE YOU START READING, please reach for your wallet. Take out a one-dollar bill. Do you have it? Look at it, hold it up, put it in front of you. Now imagine you save $1 each month (which few do). [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsmarting-the-crowd-a-value-investors-guide-to-starting-building-and-keeping-a-family-fortune-bogumil-k-baranowski-foreword-by-francois-d-sicart-abridged/">Outsmarting the Crowd : A Value Investor&#8217;s Guide to Starting, Building, and Keeping a Family Fortune &#8211; Bogumil K Baranowski, Foreword by Francois D Sicart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WE ARE WIRED TO FAIL WITH MONEY AND INVESTING.     </p>
<p>                    Do You Have $1 on You? BEFORE YOU START READING, please reach for your wallet. Take out a one-dollar bill. Do you have it? Look at it, hold it up, put it in front of you.    </p>
<p>                    Now imagine you save $1 each month (which few do). Imagine that your $1 earns 7% annually on average over thirty years. At the end of the thirty years you will have almost $1,200.    </p>
<p>                    Needless to say, if you put away $1,000 each month, you&#8217;d have almost $1.2 million in thirty years.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s secondary if you are just starting your family fortune&#8211;or if you already have it and want to keep it and grow it.    </p>
<p>                    If you do nothing with that dollar, inflation will eat away at its value. It will be worth less than two quarters in twenty-five years and less than a single quarter in fifty years and a nickel in one hundred years.    </p>
<p>                    Can you afford to do nothing? Do I have your attention?    </p>
<p>                    Most books misinform, or intimidate the reader, and often are not backed by real life experience.    </p>
<p>                    This book is a one of a kind, comprehensive, straightforward, and easy to follow guide to investing. It&#8217;s written by an experienced investor trained in the value investing, Buffett-Graham school of thought.    </p>
<p>                    Like no other book, it covers both the intellectual and emotional discipline needed to be a successful investor. It provides the proper philosophy, shows the path, and emphasizes the principles required to keep and grow your wealth over a lifetime.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Over more than a decade, Bogumil has assiduously assembled a set of rules from the writings and the speeches of the world&#8217;s most lastingly successful investors: these rules have become his chosen investment discipline. [&#8230;] He has written a great road map for young investors as well as a thoughtful and very readable guide to spare older neophytes the most common investment mistakes.&#8221; &#8211; François D. Sicart, Founder and Chairman of Tocqueville Asset Management.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Now comes his book. Obviously, Bogumil was augmenting what we were teaching him over the years about the investment process with extensive readings by the great thinkers on this subject. Unlike some of these tomes, however, Bogumil&#8217;s &#8220;Outsmarting the Crowd&#8221; is an easily digestible, common sense approach to a subject that is too often wrapped in jargon made to make it appear more difficult and less intuitive than it actually is.&#8221; &#8211; Robert W. Kleinschmidt, President, Chief Executive Officer and Chief Investment Officer of Tocqueville Asset Management.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/outsmarting-the-crowd-a-value-investors-guide-to-starting-building-and-keeping-a-family-fortune-bogumil-k-baranowski-foreword-by-francois-d-sicart-abridged/">Outsmarting the Crowd : A Value Investor&#8217;s Guide to Starting, Building, and Keeping a Family Fortune &#8211; Bogumil K Baranowski, Foreword by Francois D Sicart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crushing It in Apartments and Commercial Real Estate : How a Small Investor Can Make It Big &#8211; Brian H Murray (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crushing-it-in-apartments-and-commercial-real-estate-how-a-small-investor-can-make-it-big-brian-h-murray-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crushing-it-in-apartments-and-commercial-real-estate-how-a-small-investor-can-make-it-big-brian-h-murray-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Think apartments and commercial real estate are just for the big boys? Think again. Brian Murray was not an investment pro when he bought his first commercial property. He was a teacher looking to build some side income. Armed with his passion for business and a lot of common sense, he developed a simple yet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crushing-it-in-apartments-and-commercial-real-estate-how-a-small-investor-can-make-it-big-brian-h-murray-abridged/">Crushing It in Apartments and Commercial Real Estate : How a Small Investor Can Make It Big &#8211; Brian H Murray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Think apartments and commercial real estate are just for the big boys? Think again.    </p>
<p>                    Brian Murray was not an investment pro when he bought his first commercial property. He was a teacher looking to build some side income. Armed with his passion for business and a lot of common sense, he developed a simple yet highly effective approach to investing that he still uses today at his multimillion-dollar real estate company.     </p>
<p>                    Crushing It in Apartments and Commercial Real Estate is a beginner&#8217;s guide to investing based on Murray&#8217;s experience bootstrapping his way from newbie investor to award-winning CEO of Washington Street Properties. Murray shares the secrets to his success through straightforward, actionable advice that will help you get started no matter what your experience level, or how much cash you have on hand. You&#8217;ll learn how to:     </p>
<p>                      Find and creatively finance commercial property Grow a portfolio without any help from outside investors and without taking on excessive debt Use your small-investor status as a competitive advantage over corporate investors Identify simple, practical ways to increase profits while keeping costs low      </p>
<p>                    Murray also shares real-life stories that reveal exactly how he grew his business, and the hard lessons he learned along the way (so you don&#8217;t have to). Whether you already invest in real estate and want to go bigger, or you&#8217;ve never owned a property, this book gives you the tools and wisdom you need to crush it in apartments and commercial real estate.    </p>
<p>                    Brian Murray is the founder and CEO of Washington Street Properties, a commercial real estate investment company that has been ranked on the Inc. 5000 list of the fastest-growing private companies in the United States for three years in a row. In 2015, Murray was recognized with a Gold Stevie Award for Executive of the Year in the Real Estate Industry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crushing-it-in-apartments-and-commercial-real-estate-how-a-small-investor-can-make-it-big-brian-h-murray-abridged/">Crushing It in Apartments and Commercial Real Estate : How a Small Investor Can Make It Big &#8211; Brian H Murray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutionary Groups & Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. To manage the risks and spread the benefits, we have to act now, and in the interest of stakeholders everywhere&#8217; Andrew McAfee, Co-Founder, MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy, MIT, USA    </p>
<p>                    We are on the brink of the Fourth Industrial Revolution. And this one will be unlike any other in human history.    </p>
<p>                    Characterized by new technologies fusing the physical, digital and biological worlds, the Fourth Industrial Revolution will impact all disciplines, economies and industries &#8211; and it will do so at an unprecedented rate. World Economic Forum data predicts that by 2025 we will see: commercial use of nanomaterials 200 times stronger than steel and a million times thinner than human hair; the first transplant of a 3D-printed liver; 10% of all cars on US roads being driverless; and much more besides.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Industrial Revolution, Schwab outlines the key technologies driving this revolution, discusses the major impacts on governments, businesses, civil society and individuals, and offers bold ideas for what can be done to shape a better future for all.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The technologies of the Fourth Industrial Revolution are extraordinary. Leadership has to be equally extraordinary to manage the complexities of systemic change&#8217; Eric Schmidt, Technical Advisor, Alphabet, USA</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Berkshire Beyond Buffett : The Enduring Value of Values &#8211; Lawrence A. Cunningham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Governance & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Berkshire Hathaway, the $300 billion conglomerate that Warren Buffett built, is among the world&#8217;s largest and most famous corporations. Yet, for all its power and celebrity, few people understand Berkshire, and many assume it cannot survive without Buffett. This book proves them wrong. In a comprehensive portrait of the corporate culture that unites Berkshire&#8217;s subsidiaries, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/">Berkshire Beyond Buffett : The Enduring Value of Values &#8211; Lawrence A. Cunningham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Berkshire Hathaway, the $300 billion conglomerate that Warren Buffett built, is among the world&#8217;s largest and most famous corporations. Yet, for all its power and celebrity, few people understand Berkshire, and many assume it cannot survive without Buffett. This book proves them wrong. In a comprehensive portrait of the corporate culture that unites Berkshire&#8217;s subsidiaries, Lawrence A. Cunningham unearths the traits that assure the conglomerate&#8217;s continued prosperity. Riveting stories of each subsidiary&#8217;s origins, triumphs, and journey to Berkshire reveal how managers generate economic value from intangibles like thrift, integrity, entrepreneurship, autonomy, and a sense of permanence. Rich with lessons for those wishing to profit from the Berkshire model, this engaging book is a valuable read for entrepreneurs, business owners, managers, family business members, and investors, and it is an important resource for scholars of corporate stewardship. General readers will enjoy learning how an iconoclastic businessman transformed a struggling textile company into a corporate legacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/berkshire-beyond-buffett-the-enduring-value-of-values-lawrence-a-cunningham-abridged/">Berkshire Beyond Buffett : The Enduring Value of Values &#8211; Lawrence A. Cunningham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Money : Know More, Make More, Give More: Learn how to make more money and transform your life &#8211; Rob Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to get to the stage &#8211; soon &#8211; where you are truly financially independent, able to use your money in the way you&#8217;d like, and be completely confident in your ability to take care of yourself and your family? That is a universal desire, but many of us regard wealth and financial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/">Money : Know More, Make More, Give More: Learn how to make more money and transform your life &#8211; Rob Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you want to get to the stage &#8211; soon &#8211; where you are truly financially independent, able to use your money in the way you&#8217;d like, and be completely confident in your ability to take care of yourself and your family?     </p>
<p>                    That is a universal desire, but many of us regard wealth and financial independence as a goal which we&#8217;ll likely never achieve &#8211; there are just too many bills that need paying and there is a widespread belief that the money game is rigged. Even people who win the lottery or inherit money often seem to wind up losing it. The evidence suggests you can&#8217;t win a game that you don&#8217;t understand &#8211; even if you start out winning &#8211; because you never understood the game in the first place.    </p>
<p>                    So how can you win with money? How can you create independent wealth and hold on to it? This inspiring book by self-made multi-millionaire Rob Moore explains the rules of the game, shares simple tricks for managing money better, details how to create a plan for an ambitious future, and shows you the very best way to become a millionaire &#8211; to think and behave like one!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-know-more-make-more-give-more-learn-how-to-make-more-money-and-transform-your-life-rob-moore-abridged/">Money : Know More, Make More, Give More: Learn how to make more money and transform your life &#8211; Rob Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Poor Charlie&#8217;s Almanack : The Wit and Wisdom of Charles T. Munger &#8211; Charles T Munger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/poor-charlies-almanack-the-wit-and-wisdom-of-charles-t-munger-charles-t-munger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/poor-charlies-almanack-the-wit-and-wisdom-of-charles-t-munger-charles-t-munger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/poor-charlies-almanack-the-wit-and-wisdom-of-charles-t-munger-charles-t-munger-abridged/">Poor Charlie&#8217;s Almanack : The Wit and Wisdom of Charles T. Munger &#8211; Charles T Munger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/poor-charlies-almanack-the-wit-and-wisdom-of-charles-t-munger-charles-t-munger-abridged/">Poor Charlie&#8217;s Almanack : The Wit and Wisdom of Charles T. Munger &#8211; Charles T Munger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commodities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jim Paul&#8217;s meteoric rise took him from a small town in Northern Kentucky to governor of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, yet he lost it all-his fortune, his reputation, and his job-in one fatal attack of excessive economic hubris. In this honest, frank analysis, Paul and Brendan Moynihan revisit the events that led to Paul&#8217;s disastrous [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/">What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jim Paul&#8217;s meteoric rise took him from a small town in Northern Kentucky to governor of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, yet he lost it all-his fortune, his reputation, and his job-in one fatal attack of excessive economic hubris. In this honest, frank analysis, Paul and Brendan Moynihan revisit the events that led to Paul&#8217;s disastrous decision and examine the psychological factors behind bad financial practices in several economic sectors.  This book-winner of a 2014 Axiom Business Book award gold medal-begins with the unbroken string of successes that helped Paul achieve a jet-setting lifestyle and land a key spot with the Chicago Mercantile Exchange. It then describes the circumstances leading up to Paul&#8217;s $1.6 million loss and the essential lessons he learned from it-primarily that, although there are as many ways to make money in the markets as there are people participating in them, all losses come from the same few sources. Investors lose money in the markets either because of errors in their analysis or because of psychological barriers preventing the application of analysis.<br />
                    While all analytical methods have some validity and make allowances for instances in which they do not work, psychological factors can keep an investor in a losing position, causing him to abandon one method for another in order to rationalize the decisions already made. Paul and Moynihan&#8217;s cautionary tale includes strategies for avoiding loss tied to a simple framework for understanding, accepting, and dodging the dangers of investing, trading, and speculating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/">What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
