<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Public Speaking Guides Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/public-speaking-guides/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/public-speaking-guides/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Public Speaking Guides Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/public-speaking-guides/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Speaker, Leader, Champion: Succeed at Work Through the Power of Public Speaking, featuring the prize-winning speeches of Toastmasters World Champions &#8211; Jeremey Donovan, Ryan Avery (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/speaker-leader-champion-succeed-at-work-through-the-power-of-public-speaking-featuring-the-prize-winning-speeches-of-toastmasters-world-champions-jeremey-donovan-ryan-avery-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Speaking Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/speaker-leader-champion-succeed-at-work-through-the-power-of-public-speaking-featuring-the-prize-winning-speeches-of-toastmasters-world-champions-jeremey-donovan-ryan-avery-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The secrets of superb public speaking-based on the best of the best of Toastmasters Toastmasters, a name synonymous with public speaking, is dedicated to developing its members&#8217; communication and leadership skills. Now Distinguished Toastmaster Jeremey Donovan and Public Speaking World Champion Ryan Avery break down the winning speeches from Toastmasters&#8217; prestigious annual competition-providing you with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/speaker-leader-champion-succeed-at-work-through-the-power-of-public-speaking-featuring-the-prize-winning-speeches-of-toastmasters-world-champions-jeremey-donovan-ryan-avery-abridged/">Speaker, Leader, Champion: Succeed at Work Through the Power of Public Speaking, featuring the prize-winning speeches of Toastmasters World Champions &#8211; Jeremey Donovan, Ryan Avery (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The secrets of superb public speaking-based on the best of the best of Toastmasters    </p>
<p>                    Toastmasters, a name synonymous with public speaking, is dedicated to developing its members&#8217; communication and leadership skills.    </p>
<p>                     Now Distinguished Toastmaster Jeremey Donovan and Public Speaking World Champion Ryan Avery break down the winning speeches from Toastmasters&#8217; prestigious annual competition-providing you with tips and techniques guaranteed to improve your speaking, presentation, and communication skills. They also include a special section of insights and advice for readers who aspire to become serious public speaking competitors.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Speaker, Leader, Champion demystifies what makes a presentation extraordinary.This engaging, actionable book will teach you how to go from appreciating a powerful speech to delivering one yourself.&#8221;<br />
                    -Adam Grant, professor at the Wharton School at the University of Pennsylvania and New York Times bestselling author of Give and Take    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Whether you present in the boardroom, classroom, or lunchroom, the guidance will help you become a more confident, authentic, and engaging speaker.&#8221;<br />
                    -Matt Abrahams, strategic communication lecturer at the Stanford University Graduate School of Business and author of Speaking Up Without Freaking Out    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;To change the world, you need to lead. To lead, you need to communicate. To communicate, you need this book.&#8221;<br />
                    -Presiyan Vasilev, 2013 World Champion of Public Speaking    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book translates the secret sauce of public speaking into easy-to-use tips.&#8221;<br />
                    -Zoe Chance, assistant professor of marketing at the Yale University School of Management</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/speaker-leader-champion-succeed-at-work-through-the-power-of-public-speaking-featuring-the-prize-winning-speeches-of-toastmasters-world-champions-jeremey-donovan-ryan-avery-abridged/">Speaker, Leader, Champion: Succeed at Work Through the Power of Public Speaking, featuring the prize-winning speeches of Toastmasters World Champions &#8211; Jeremey Donovan, Ryan Avery (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Five Stars : The Communication Secrets to Get from Good to Great &#8211; Carmine Gallo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/five-stars-the-communication-secrets-to-get-from-good-to-great-carmine-gallo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Speaking Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/five-stars-the-communication-secrets-to-get-from-good-to-great-carmine-gallo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to master the art of persuasion&#8211;from the bestselling author of Talk Like TED. Ideas don&#8217;t sell themselves. As the forces of globalization, automation, and artificial intelligence combine to disrupt every field, having a good idea isn&#8217;t good enough. Mastering the ancient art of persuasion is the key to standing out, getting ahead, and achieving [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/five-stars-the-communication-secrets-to-get-from-good-to-great-carmine-gallo-abridged/">Five Stars : The Communication Secrets to Get from Good to Great &#8211; Carmine Gallo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to master the art of persuasion&#8211;from the bestselling author of Talk Like TED.    </p>
<p>                    Ideas don&#8217;t sell themselves. As the forces of globalization, automation, and artificial intelligence combine to disrupt every field, having a good idea isn&#8217;t good enough. Mastering the ancient art of persuasion is the key to standing out, getting ahead, and achieving greatness in the modern world. Communication is no longer a &#8220;soft&#8221; skill&#8211;it is the human edge that will make you unstoppable, irresistible, and irreplaceable&#8211;earning you that perfect rating, that fifth star.     </p>
<p>                    In Five Stars, Carmine Gallo breaks down Aristotle&#8217;s ancient formula of persuasion to inspire contemporary audiences. As the nature of work changes and technology carries things across the globe in a moment, communication skills become more valuable&#8211;not less. When people express their ideas effectively, they&#8217;re more likely to win dream jobs, sell products, build brands, and trigger movements.     </p>
<p>                    Gallo interviews neuroscientists, economists, and leaders from NASA astronauts to Navy SEALS. His conversations with billionaires who built companies like Google, Nike and Airbnb reveals how great leaders captivate our imagination and ignite our dreams. Gallo will help you unlock into your innate emotional and social skills, develop your public speaking talent to communicate your ideas with confidence, and build empathy with your listeners. This is your moment. Five Stars is your competitive advantage.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/five-stars-the-communication-secrets-to-get-from-good-to-great-carmine-gallo-abridged/">Five Stars : The Communication Secrets to Get from Good to Great &#8211; Carmine Gallo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>As We Speak : How to Make Your Point and Have It Stick &#8211; Peter Meyers, Shann Nix (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/as-we-speak-how-to-make-your-point-and-have-it-stick-peter-meyers-shann-nix-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Speaking Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/as-we-speak-how-to-make-your-point-and-have-it-stick-peter-meyers-shann-nix-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical and empowering guide to public speaking and becoming a more effective, persuasive communicator in all areas of life. The world is full of brilliant people whose ideas are never heard. This book is designed to make sure that you&#8217;re not one of them. Even for the most self-confident among us, public speaking can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/as-we-speak-how-to-make-your-point-and-have-it-stick-peter-meyers-shann-nix-abridged/">As We Speak : How to Make Your Point and Have It Stick &#8211; Peter Meyers, Shann Nix (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical and empowering guide to public speaking and becoming a more effective, persuasive communicator in all areas of life.     </p>
<p>                    The world is full of brilliant people whose ideas are never heard. This book is designed to make sure that you&#8217;re not one of them.     </p>
<p>                    Even for the most self-confident among us, public speaking can be a nerve-racking ordeal. Whether you are speaking to a large audience, within a group, or in a oneon- one conversation, the way in which you communicate ideas, as much as the ideas themselves, can determine success or failure.     </p>
<p>                    In this invaluable guide from two of today&#8217;s most sought-after communication experts, you&#8217;ll learn to master three core principles that you can apply in a wide variety of situations:     </p>
<p>                    Content: Construct a clear and lucid architecture of ideas that will lead your listener through a memorable emotional experience.     </p>
<p>                    Delivery: Use your voice and body in ways that engage your audience and naturally support your message.     </p>
<p>                    State: Bring yourself into peak performance condition. The way you feel when you perform is the most frequently overlooked component of communication.     </p>
<p>                    Accessible, inspiring, and laden with useful tips, As We Speak will help you discover your authentic voice and learn to convey your ideas in the most powerful and unforgettable way possible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/as-we-speak-how-to-make-your-point-and-have-it-stick-peter-meyers-shann-nix-abridged/">As We Speak : How to Make Your Point and Have It Stick &#8211; Peter Meyers, Shann Nix (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Be Right : &#8230; in a world gone wrong &#8211; James O&#8217;Brien (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Speaking Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The voice of reason in a world that won&#8217;t shut up. The Sunday Times Bestseller Winner of the Parliamentary Book Awards Every day, James O&#8217;Brien listens to people blaming hard-working immigrants for stealing their jobs while scrounging benefits, and pointing their fingers at the EU and feminists for destroying Britain. But what makes James&#8217;s daily [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/">How To Be Right : &#8230; in a world gone wrong &#8211; James O&#8217;Brien (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The voice of reason in a world that won&#8217;t shut up.    </p>
<p>                    The Sunday Times Bestseller<br />
                    Winner of the Parliamentary Book Awards    </p>
<p>                    Every day, James O&#8217;Brien listens to people blaming hard-working immigrants for stealing their jobs while scrounging benefits, and pointing their fingers at the EU and feminists for destroying Britain. But what makes James&#8217;s daily LBC show such essential listening &#8211; and has made James a standout social media star &#8211; is the incisive way he punctures their assumptions and dismantles their arguments live on air, every single morning.    </p>
<p>                    In the bestselling How To Be Right, James provides a hilarious and invigorating guide to talking to people with unchallenged opinions. With chapters on every lightning-rod issue, James shows how people have been fooled into thinking the way they do, and in each case outlines the key questions to ask to reveal fallacies, inconsistencies and double standards.    </p>
<p>                    If you ever get cornered by ardent Brexiteers, Daily Mail disciples or corporate cronies, this book is your conversation survival guide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/">How To Be Right : &#8230; in a world gone wrong &#8211; James O&#8217;Brien (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Public Speaking : The Original Tool for Improving Public Oration &#8211; Dale Carnegie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-public-speaking-the-original-tool-for-improving-public-oration-dale-carnegie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Non-Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Speaking Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-public-speaking-the-original-tool-for-improving-public-oration-dale-carnegie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Originally published in 1915, Dale Carnegie&#8217;s The Art of Public Speaking has been the go-to guide for those who want to better their speaking abilities for more than a century. Do you have trouble getting up in front of an audience? Are you struggling to get your point across? Public speaking can be nerve-wracking, especially [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-public-speaking-the-original-tool-for-improving-public-oration-dale-carnegie-abridged/">The Art of Public Speaking : The Original Tool for Improving Public Oration &#8211; Dale Carnegie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Originally published in 1915, Dale Carnegie&#8217;s The Art of Public Speaking has been the go-to guide for those who want to better their speaking abilities for more than a century.    </p>
<p>                    Do you have trouble getting up in front of an audience? Are you struggling to get your point across? Public speaking can be nerve-wracking, especially if you&#8217;re a naturally nervous person or if you&#8217;re underprepared.    </p>
<p>                    Featured within this classic manual are hundreds of tips and tricks on how to become an efficient and effective public speaker. The sections included address:    </p>
<p>                    Tone<br />
                    Delivery<br />
                    Enthusiasm<br />
                    Confidence<br />
                    Concentration<br />
                    Charm<br />
                    Precision<br />
                    Gesturing<br />
                    Preparation<br />
                    And much more!    </p>
<p>                    Stop putting your audience to sleep. Pick up your copy of The Art of Public Speaking and learn to captivate any audience today!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-public-speaking-the-original-tool-for-improving-public-oration-dale-carnegie-abridged/">The Art of Public Speaking : The Original Tool for Improving Public Oration &#8211; Dale Carnegie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Steal the Show &#8211; Michael Port (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/steal-the-show-michael-port-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Speaking Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/steal-the-show-michael-port-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Wall Street Journal, USA Today, and Publishers Weekly bestseller. A powerful way to master every performance in your career and life from a top business coach and former professional actor. Every interaction is a performance, and much of our success&#8211;professional and personal&#8211;hinges on being able to inspire an audience. And while some people seem [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/steal-the-show-michael-port-abridged/">Steal the Show &#8211; Michael Port (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Wall Street Journal,  USA Today, and Publishers Weekly bestseller. A powerful way to master every performance in your career and life from a top business coach and former professional actor.    </p>
<p>                    Every interaction is a performance, and much of our success&#8211;professional and personal&#8211;hinges on being able to inspire an audience. And while some people seem to be naturals in the spotlight, this ability very rarely derives from talent alone.    </p>
<p>                    Confident communication is a skill, and anyone can learn how to do it.    </p>
<p>                    In Steal the Show, New York Times best-selling author, top-rated corporate speaker, and former professional actor Michael Port teaches you how to make the most of your own moments in the spotlight. He makes it easy to give your presentations a clear focus, engage your listeners, manage your nerves, play the right role in every situation to give your message maximum impact, and much more.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his MFA training at the prestigious Graduate Acting Program at New York University, Port has engineered a system that the non-actor can use to ensure his or her voice is heard when it matters most.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;An indispensable guide for introverts and extroverts alike.&#8221;&#8211; Inc. Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/steal-the-show-michael-port-abridged/">Steal the Show &#8211; Michael Port (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>TED Talks : The official TED guide to public speaking: Tips and tricks for giving unforgettable speeches and presentations &#8211; Chris Anderson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ted-talks-the-official-ted-guide-to-public-speaking-tips-and-tricks-for-giving-unforgettable-speeches-and-presentations-chris-anderson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Speaking Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ted-talks-the-official-ted-guide-to-public-speaking-tips-and-tricks-for-giving-unforgettable-speeches-and-presentations-chris-anderson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is not just the most insightful book ever written on public speaking-it&#8217;s also a brilliant, profound look at how to communicate&#8217; &#8211; Adam Grant, author of ORIGINALS In Ted Talks Chris Anderson, Head of TED, reveals the inside secrets of how to give a first-class presentation. Where books like Talk Like TED and TED [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ted-talks-the-official-ted-guide-to-public-speaking-tips-and-tricks-for-giving-unforgettable-speeches-and-presentations-chris-anderson-abridged/">TED Talks : The official TED guide to public speaking: Tips and tricks for giving unforgettable speeches and presentations &#8211; Chris Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is not just the most insightful book  ever written on public speaking-it&#8217;s also a brilliant, profound look at  how to communicate&#8217; &#8211; Adam Grant, author of ORIGINALS    </p>
<p>                    In Ted Talks Chris Anderson, Head of TED, reveals the inside secrets of how to give a first-class presentation. Where books like Talk Like TED and TED Talks Storytelling whetted the appetite, here is the official TED guide to public speaking from the man who put TED talks on the world&#8217;s stage. &#8216;Nobody in the world better understands the art and science of public speaking than Chris Anderson. He is absolutely the best person to have written this book&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert.    </p>
<p>                    Anderson shares his five key techniques to presentation success: Connection, Narration, Explanation, Persuasion and Revelation (plus the three to avoid). He also answers the most frequently asked questions about giving a talk, from &#8216;What should I wear?&#8217; to &#8216;How do I handle my nerves?&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    Ted Talks is also full of presentation tips from such TED notable speakers as Sir Ken Robinson, Bill Gates, Mary Roach, Amy Cuddy, Elizabeth Gilbert, Dan Gilbert, Amanda Palmer, Matt Ridley and many more. This is a lively, fun read with great practical application from the man who knows what goes into a truly memorable speech. In Ted Talks Anderson pulls back the TED curtain for anyone who wants to learn how to prepare an exceptional presentation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ted-talks-the-official-ted-guide-to-public-speaking-tips-and-tricks-for-giving-unforgettable-speeches-and-presentations-chris-anderson-abridged/">TED Talks : The official TED guide to public speaking: Tips and tricks for giving unforgettable speeches and presentations &#8211; Chris Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
