<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Anatomy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/anatomy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/anatomy/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Anatomy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/anatomy/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Genome : The Autobiography of a Species in 23 Chapters &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anatomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Ridley leaps from chromosome to chromosome in a handy summation of our ever increasing understanding of the roles that genes play in disease, behavior, sexual differences, and even intelligence. . . . . He addresses not only the ethical quandaries faced by contemporary scientists but the reductionist danger in equating inheritability with inevitability.&#8221; &#8212; The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/">Genome : The Autobiography of a Species in 23 Chapters &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Ridley leaps from chromosome to chromosome in a handy summation of our ever increasing understanding of the roles that genes play in disease, behavior, sexual differences, and even intelligence. . . . . He addresses not only the ethical quandaries faced by contemporary scientists but the reductionist danger in equating inheritability with inevitability.&#8221; &#8212; The New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    The genome&#8217;s been mapped. But what does it mean? Matt Ridley&#8217;s Genome is the book that explains it all: what it is, how it works, and what it portends for the future    </p>
<p>                    Arguably the most significant scientific discovery of the new century, the mapping of the twenty-three pairs of chromosomes that make up the human genome raises almost as many questions as it answers. Questions that will profoundly impact the way we think about disease, about longevity, and about free will. Questions that will affect the rest of your life.    </p>
<p>                    Genome offers extraordinary insight into the ramifications of this incredible breakthrough. By picking one newly discovered gene from each pair of chromosomes and telling its story, Matt Ridley recounts the history of our species and its ancestors from the dawn of life to the brink of future medicine. From Huntington&#8217;s disease to cancer, from the applications of gene therapy to the horrors of eugenics, Ridley probes the scientific, philosophical, and moral issues arising as a result of the mapping of the genome. It will help you understand what this scientific milestone means for you, for your children, and for humankind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genome-the-autobiography-of-a-species-in-23-chapters-matt-ridley-abridged/">Genome : The Autobiography of a Species in 23 Chapters &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sports Gene : Inside the Science of Extraordinary Athletic Performance &#8211; David Epstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sports-gene-inside-the-science-of-extraordinary-athletic-performance-david-epstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anatomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sports-gene-inside-the-science-of-extraordinary-athletic-performance-david-epstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller &#8211; with a new afterword about early specialization in youth sports &#8211; from the author of Range: Why Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World. The debate is as old as physical competition. Are stars like Usain Bolt, Michael Phelps, and Serena Williams genetic freaks put on Earth to dominate their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sports-gene-inside-the-science-of-extraordinary-athletic-performance-david-epstein-abridged/">The Sports Gene : Inside the Science of Extraordinary Athletic Performance &#8211; David Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller &#8211; with a new afterword about early specialization in youth sports &#8211; from the author of Range: Why Generalists Triumph in a Specialized World.     </p>
<p>                     The debate is as old as physical competition. Are stars like Usain Bolt, Michael Phelps, and Serena Williams genetic freaks put on Earth to dominate their respective sports? Or are they simply normal people who overcame their biological limits through sheer force of will and obsessive training?    </p>
<p>                     In this controversial and engaging exploration of athletic success and the so-called 10,000-hour rule, David Epstein tackles the great nature vs. nurture debate and traces how far science has come in solving it. Through on-the-ground reporting from below the equator and above the Arctic Circle, revealing conversations with leading scientists and Olympic champions, and interviews with athletes who have rare genetic mutations or physical traits, Epstein forces us to rethink the very nature of athleticism.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sports-gene-inside-the-science-of-extraordinary-athletic-performance-david-epstein-abridged/">The Sports Gene : Inside the Science of Extraordinary Athletic Performance &#8211; David Epstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, With Brendan Buhler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anatomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Allergies, asthma, obesity, acne: these are just a few of the conditions that may be caused&#8211;and someday cured&#8211;by the microscopic life inside us. The key is to understand how this groundbreaking science influences your health, mood, and more. In just the last few years, scientists have shown how the microscopic life within our bodies&#8211; particularly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/">Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, With Brendan Buhler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Allergies, asthma, obesity, acne: these are just a few of the conditions that may be caused&#8211;and someday cured&#8211;by the microscopic life inside us. The key is to understand how this groundbreaking science influences your health, mood, and more.     </p>
<p>                    In just the last few years, scientists have shown how the microscopic life within our bodies&#8211; particularly within our intestines&#8211;has an astonishing impact on our lives. Your health, mood, sleep patterns, eating preferences&#8211;even your likelihood of getting bitten by mosquitoes&#8211;can be traced in part to the tiny creatures that live on and inside of us.     </p>
<p>                    In Follow Your Gut,  pioneering scientist Rob Knight pairs with award-winning science journalist Brendan Buhler to explain&#8211;with good humor and easy-to-grasp examples&#8211;why these new findings matter to everyone. They lead a detailed tour of the previously unseen world inside our bodies, calling out the diseases and conditions believed to be most directly impacted by them.     </p>
<p>                    With a practical eye toward deeper knowledge and better decisions, they also explore the known effects of antibiotics, probiotics, diet choice and even birth method on our children&#8217;s lifelong health. Ultimately, this pioneering book explains how to learn about your own microbiome and take steps toward understanding and improving your health, using the latest research as a guide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/follow-your-gut-the-enormous-impact-of-tiny-microbes-rob-knight-with-brendan-buhler-abridged/">Follow Your Gut : The Enormous Impact of Tiny Microbes &#8211; Rob Knight, With Brendan Buhler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
