<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Psychology Of Ageing Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/psychology-of-ageing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/psychology-of-ageing/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Psychology Of Ageing Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/psychology-of-ageing/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Women Rowing North : Navigating Life&#8217;s Currents and Flourishing As We Age &#8211; Mary Pipher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/women-rowing-north-navigating-lifes-currents-and-flourishing-as-we-age-mary-pipher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: The Elderly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maturation & Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/women-rowing-north-navigating-lifes-currents-and-flourishing-as-we-age-mary-pipher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller * USA Today Bestseller * Los Angeles Times Bestseller * Publishers Weekly Bestseller The instant New York Times bestseller from the author of Reviving Ophelia&#8211;a guide to wisdom, authenticity, and bliss for women as they age. Women growing older contend with ageism, misogyny, and loss. Yet as Mary Pipher shows, most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-rowing-north-navigating-lifes-currents-and-flourishing-as-we-age-mary-pipher-abridged/">Women Rowing North : Navigating Life&#8217;s Currents and Flourishing As We Age &#8211; Mary Pipher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller * USA Today Bestseller * Los Angeles Times Bestseller * Publishers Weekly Bestseller     </p>
<p>                    The instant New York Times bestseller from the author of Reviving Ophelia&#8211;a guide to wisdom, authenticity, and bliss for women as they age.     </p>
<p>                    Women growing older contend with ageism, misogyny, and loss. Yet as Mary Pipher shows, most older women are deeply happy and filled with gratitude for the gifts of life. Their struggles help them grow into the authentic, empathetic, and wise people they have always wanted to be.     </p>
<p>                    In Women Rowing North, Pipher offers a timely examination of the cultural and developmental issues women face as they age. Drawing on her own experience as daughter, sister, mother, grandmother, caregiver, clinical psychologist, and cultural anthropologist, she explores ways women can cultivate resilient responses to the challenges they face. &#8220;If we can keep our wits about us, think clearly, and manage our emotions skillfully,&#8221; Pipher writes, &#8220;we will experience a joyous time of our lives. If we have planned carefully and packed properly, if we have good maps and guides, the journey can be transcendent.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-rowing-north-navigating-lifes-currents-and-flourishing-as-we-age-mary-pipher-abridged/">Women Rowing North : Navigating Life&#8217;s Currents and Flourishing As We Age &#8211; Mary Pipher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Maturation & Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the New York Times bestseller The Plant Paradox comes a groundbreaking plan for living a long, healthy, happy life. From the moment we are born, our cells begin to age. But aging does not have to mean decline. World-renowned surgeon Dr. Steven Gundry has been treating mature patients for most of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the New York Times bestseller The Plant Paradox comes a groundbreaking plan for living a long, healthy, happy life.    </p>
<p>                    From the moment we are born, our cells begin to age. But aging does not have to mean decline. World-renowned surgeon Dr. Steven Gundry has been treating mature patients for most of his career. He knows that everyone thinks they want to live forever, until they hit middle age and witness the suffering of their parents and even their peers. So how do we solve the paradox of wanting to live to a ripe old age-but enjoy the benefits of youth?    </p>
<p>                    This groundbreaking book holds the answer. Working with thousands of patients, Dr. Gundry has discovered that the &#8220;diseases of aging&#8221; we most fear are not simply a function of age; rather, they are a byproduct of the way we have lived over the decades. In The Longevity Paradox, he maps out a new approach to aging well-one that is based on supporting the health of the &#8220;oldest&#8221; parts of us: the microorganisms that live within our bodies.    </p>
<p>                    Our gut bugs-the bacteria that make up the microbiome-largely determine our health over the years. From diseases like cancer and Alzheimer&#8217;s to common ailments like arthritis to our weight and the appearance of our skin, these bugs are in the driver&#8217;s seat, controlling our quality of life as we age.    </p>
<p>                    The good news is, it&#8217;s never too late to support these microbes and give them what they need to help them-and you-thrive. In The Longevity Paradox, Dr. Gundry outlines a nutrition and lifestyle plan to support gut health and live well for decades to come. A progressive take on the new science of aging, The Longevity Paradox offers an action plan to prevent and reverse disease as well as simple hacks to help anyone look and feel younger and more vital.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-longevity-paradox-how-to-die-young-at-a-ripe-old-age-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Longevity Paradox : How to Die Young at a Ripe Old Age &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the creator of Bulletproof coffee and the bestselling author of Head Strong and The Bulletproof Diet comes a plan to bypass plateaus and &#8216;up&#8217; your game at every age. Dave Asprey suffered countless symptoms of ageing as a young man, which sparked a lifelong burning desire to grow younger with each birthday. For more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/">Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the creator of Bulletproof coffee and the bestselling author of Head Strong and The Bulletproof Diet comes a plan to bypass plateaus and &#8216;up&#8217; your game at every age.    </p>
<p>                              Dave Asprey suffered countless symptoms of ageing as a young man, which sparked a lifelong burning desire to grow younger with each birthday. For more than twenty years, he has been on a quest to find innovative, science-backed methods to upgrade human biology and redefine the limits of the mind, body, and spirit. The results speak for themselves. Now in his forties, Dave is smarter, happier, and more fit and successful than ever before.    </p>
<p>                              In Super Human, he shows how this is level of health and performance possible for all of us. While we assume we will peak in middle age and then decline, Asprey&#8217;s research reveals there is another way. It is possible to make changes on the sub-cellular level to dramatically extend life span. And the tools to live longer also give you more energy and brainpower right now.    </p>
<p>                              The answers lie in Dave&#8217;s Seven Pillars of Ageing that contribute to degeneration and disease while diminishing your performance in the moment. Using simple interventions &#8211; like diet, sleep, light, exercise, and little-known but powerful hacks from ozone therapy to proper jaw alignment, you can decelerate cellular ageing and supercharge your body&#8217;s ability to heal and rejuvenate.    </p>
<p>                              A self-proclaimed human guinea pig, Asprey arms readers with practical advice to maximize their lives at every age with his signature mix of science-geek wonder, candour, and enthusiasm. Getting older no longer has to mean decline. Now it&#8217;s an opportunity to become Super Human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/">Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Successful Aging : A Neuroscientist Explores the Power and Potential of Our Lives &#8211; Daniel J. Levitin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/successful-aging-a-neuroscientist-explores-the-power-and-potential-of-our-lives-daniel-j-levitin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/successful-aging-a-neuroscientist-explores-the-power-and-potential-of-our-lives-daniel-j-levitin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT TOP 10 BESTSELLER *New York Times *USAToday *Washington Post *LA Times Debunks the idea that aging inevitably brings infirmity and unhappiness and instead offers a trove of practical, evidence-based guidance for living longer and better. &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, author of When and Drive SUCCESSFUL AGING delivers powerful insights: &#8211; Debunking the myth that memory [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/successful-aging-a-neuroscientist-explores-the-power-and-potential-of-our-lives-daniel-j-levitin-abridged/">Successful Aging : A Neuroscientist Explores the Power and Potential of Our Lives &#8211; Daniel J. Levitin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>INSTANT TOP 10 BESTSELLER *New York Times *USAToday *Washington Post *LA Times     </p>
<p>                    Debunks the idea that aging inevitably brings infirmity and unhappiness and instead offers a trove of practical, evidence-based guidance for living longer and better.<br />
                    &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, author of When and Drive     </p>
<p>                    SUCCESSFUL AGING delivers powerful insights:<br />
                     &#8211; Debunking the myth that memory always declines with age<br />
                     &#8211; Confirming that health span&#8211;not life span&#8211;is what matters<br />
                     &#8211; Proving that sixty-plus years is a unique and newly recognized developmental stage<br />
                     &#8211; Recommending that people look forward to joy, as reminiscing doesn&#8217;t promote health     </p>
<p>                     Levitin looks at the science behind what we all can learn from those who age joyously, as well as how to adapt our culture to take full advantage of older people&#8217;s wisdom and experience. Throughout his exploration of what aging really means, using research from developmental neuroscience and the psychology of individual differences, Levitin reveals resilience strategies and practical, cognitive- enhancing tricks everyone should do as they age.     </p>
<p>                     Successful Aging inspires a powerful new approach to how readers think about our final decades, and it will revolutionize the way we plan for old age as individuals, family members, and citizens within a society where the average life expectancy continues to rise.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/successful-aging-a-neuroscientist-explores-the-power-and-potential-of-our-lives-daniel-j-levitin-abridged/">Successful Aging : A Neuroscientist Explores the Power and Potential of Our Lives &#8211; Daniel J. Levitin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
