<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Public Health &amp; Preventive Medicine Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/public-health-preventive-medicine/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/public-health-preventive-medicine/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Public Health &amp; Preventive Medicine Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/public-health-preventive-medicine/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</title>
		<link>/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Giving Up Smoking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Respiratory Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Funding & Policy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19. Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19.    </p>
<p>                    Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns and border closings causing widespread business closures, economic collapse, and massive unemployment; and an unprecedented curtailment of civil liberties and freedoms in the name of keeping people safe by locking them up in their homes.    </p>
<p>                    We are now living in a world that is increasingly ruled, not by our democratic systems and institutions, but by public health fiat, carried out by politicians who rule by instilling fear and panic.    </p>
<p>                    In The Truth About COVID-19, Dr. Mercola and Cummins reveal new and emerging evidence that:    </p>
<p>                    The SARS-CoV-2 virus was, indeed, lab-engineered and emerged from a negligently managed bioweapons lab in Wuhan, China<br />
                    The global pandemic was long anticipated by global elites who have used it to facilitate and hide the largest upward transfer of wealth in human history<br />
                    PCR testing, case counts, morbidity, and vaccine safety and efficacy data have been widely manipulated and misrepresented<br />
                    Obesity, diabetes, and heart disease are known to worsen COVID-19 outcomes, but the junk food industry continues to push its agenda at the expense of public health<br />
                    Safe, simple, and inexpensive treatment and prevention for COVID-19 have been censored and suppressed to create a clear path for vaccine acceptance<br />
                    Effectiveness of the vaccines has been wildly exaggerated and major safety questions have gone unanswered    </p>
<p>                    The good news in all of this is that we can take control of our health and that, together, we have the power to unite and fight back for our health, democracy, and freedom. The time is now for a global awakening. As Dr. Mercola and Cummins remind us, this is the fight of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epidemiology & Medical Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than three hundred infectious diseases have emerged or reemerged in new territory during the past fifty years, and ninety percent of epidemiologists expect that one of them will cause a disruptive, deadly pandemic sometime in the next two generations. To reveal how that might happen, Sonia Shah tracks each stage of cholera&#8217;s dramatic journey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/">Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than three hundred infectious diseases have emerged or reemerged in new territory during the past fifty years, and ninety percent of epidemiologists expect that one of them will cause a disruptive, deadly pandemic sometime in the next two generations. To reveal how that might happen, Sonia Shah tracks each stage of cholera&#8217;s dramatic journey from harmless microbe to world-changing pandemic, from its 1817 emergence in the South Asian hinterlands to its rapid dispersal across the nineteenth-century world and its latest beachhead in Haiti. She reports on the pathogens following in cholera&#8217;s footsteps, from the MRSA bacterium that besieges her own family to the never-before-seen killers emerging from China&#8217;s wet markets, the surgical wards of New Delhi, the slums of Port-au-Prince, and the suburban backyards of the East Coast. A deep-dive into the convoluted science, strange politics, and checkered history of one of the world&#8217;s deadliest diseases, Pandemic reveals what the next epidemic might look like&#8211;and what we can do to prevent it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/">Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal & Public Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Moneyball meets medicine in this remarkable chronicle of one of the greatest scientific quests of our time&#8211;the groundbreaking program to answer the most essential question for humanity: how do we live and die?&#8211;and the visionary mastermind behind it. Medical doctor and economist Christopher Murray began the Global Burden of Disease studies to gain a truer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/">Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Moneyball meets medicine in this remarkable chronicle of one of the greatest scientific quests of our time&#8211;the groundbreaking program to answer the most essential question for humanity: how do we live and die?&#8211;and the visionary mastermind behind it.    </p>
<p>                    Medical doctor and economist Christopher Murray began the Global Burden of Disease studies to gain a truer understanding of how we live and how we die. While it is one of the largest scientific projects ever attempted&#8211;as breathtaking as the first moon landing or the Human Genome Project&#8211;the questions it answers are meaningful for every one of us: What are the world&#8217;s health problems? Who do they hurt? How much? Where? Why?    </p>
<p>                    Murray argues that the ideal existence isn&#8217;t simply the longest but the one lived well and with the least illness. Until we can accurately measure how people live and die, we cannot understand what makes us sick or do much to improve it. Challenging the accepted wisdom of the WHO and the UN, the charismatic and controversial health maverick has made enemies&#8211;and some influential friends, including Bill Gates who gave Murray a $100 million grant.    </p>
<p>                    In Epic Measures, journalist Jeremy N. Smith offers an intimate look at Murray and his groundbreaking work. From ranking countries&#8217; healthcare systems (the U.S. is 37th) to unearthing the shocking reality that world governments are funding developing countries at only 30% of the potential maximum efficiency when it comes to health, Epic Measures introduces a visionary leader whose unwavering determination to improve global health standards has already changed the way the world addresses issues of health and wellness, sets policy, and distributes funding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/">Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Administration & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Equipment & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nursing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Telemedicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy & Therapeutics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A trip to the doctor is almost a guarantee of misery. You&#8217;ll make an appointment months in advance. You&#8217;ll probably wait for several hours until you hear &#8220;the doctor will see you now&#8221;,but only for fifteen minutes! Then you&#8217;ll wait even longer for lab tests, the results of which you&#8217;ll likely never see, unless they [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/">The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A trip to the doctor is almost a guarantee of misery. You&#8217;ll make an appointment months in advance. You&#8217;ll probably wait for several hours until you hear &#8220;the doctor will see you now&#8221;,but only for fifteen minutes! Then you&#8217;ll wait even longer for lab tests, the results of which you&#8217;ll likely never see, unless they indicate further (and more invasive) tests, most of which will probably prove unnecessary (much like physicals themselves). And your bill will be astronomical.In  The Patient Will See You Now , Eric Topol, one of the nation&#8217;s top physicians, shows why medicine does not have to be that way. Instead, you could use your smartphone to get rapid test results from one drop of blood, monitor your vital signs both day and night, and use an artificially intelligent algorithm to receive a diagnosis without having to see a doctor, all at a small fraction of the cost imposed by our modern healthcare system. The change is powered by what Topol calls medicine&#8217;s &#8220;Gutenberg moment.&#8221; Much as the printing press took learning out of the hands of a priestly class, the mobile internet is doing the same for medicine, giving us unprecedented control over our healthcare. With smartphones in hand, we are no longer beholden to an impersonal and paternalistic system in which &#8220;doctor knows best.&#8221; Medicine has been digitized, Topol argues now it will be democratized. Computers will replace physicians for many diagnostic tasks, citizen science will give rise to citizen medicine, and enormous data sets will give us new means to attack conditions that have long been incurable. Massive, open, online medicine, where diagnostics are done by Facebook-like comparisons of medical profiles, will enable real-time, real-world research on massive populations. There&#8217;s no doubt the path forward will be complicated: the medical establishment will resist these changes, and digitized medicine inevitably raises serious issues surrounding privacy. Nevertheless, the result,better, cheaper, and more human health care,will be worth it.Provocative and engrossing,  The Patient Will See You Now  is essential reading for anyone who thinks they deserve better health care. That is, for all of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/">The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Case against Fluoride : How Hazardous Waste Ended Up in Our Drinking Water and the Bad Science and Powerful Politics That Keep It There &#8211; Paul Connett, James Beck, Spedding Micklem, Foreword by Albert W. Burgstahler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pollution & Threats To The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Environmental Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When the U.S. Public Health Service endorsed water fluoridation in 1950, there was little evidence of its safety. Now, six decades later and after most countries have rejected the practice, more than 70 percent of Americans, as well as 200 million people worldwide, are drinking fluoridated water. The Center for Disease Control and the American [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/">The Case against Fluoride : How Hazardous Waste Ended Up in Our Drinking Water and the Bad Science and Powerful Politics That Keep It There &#8211; Paul Connett, James Beck, Spedding Micklem, Foreword by Albert W. Burgstahler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When the U.S. Public Health Service endorsed water fluoridation in 1950, there was little evidence of its safety. Now, six decades later and after most countries have rejected the practice, more than 70 percent of Americans, as well as 200 million people worldwide, are drinking fluoridated water. The Center for Disease Control and the American Dental Association continue to promote it&#8211;and even mandatory statewide water fluoridation&#8211;despite increasing evidence that it is not only unnecessary, but potentially hazardous to human health.    </p>
<p>                    In this timely and important book, Dr. Paul Connett, Dr. James Beck, and Dr. H. Spedding Micklem take a new look at the science behind water fluoridation and argue that just because the dental and medical establishments endorse a public health measure doesn&#8217;t mean it&#8217;s safe. In the case of water fluoridation, the chemicals that go into the drinking water that more than 180 million people drink each day are not even pharmaceutical grade, but rather a hazardous waste product of the phosphate fertilizer industry. It is illegal to dump this waste into the sea or local surface water, and yet it is allowed in our drinking water. To make matters worse, this program receives no oversight from the Food and Drug Administration, and the Environmental Protection Agency takes no responsibility for the practice. And from an ethical standpoint, say the authors, water fluoridation is a bad medical practice: individuals are being forced to take medication without their informed consent, there is no control over the dose, and no monitoring of possible side effects.    </p>
<p>                    At once painstakingly documented and also highly readable, The Case Against Fluoride brings new research to light, including links between fluoride and harm to the brain, bones, and endocrine system, and argues that the evidence that fluoridation reduces tooth decay is surprisingly weak.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-fluoride-how-hazardous-waste-ended-up-in-our-drinking-water-and-the-bad-science-and-powerful-politics-that-keep-it-there-paul-connett-james-beck-spedding-micklem-foreword-by/">The Case against Fluoride : How Hazardous Waste Ended Up in Our Drinking Water and the Bad Science and Powerful Politics That Keep It There &#8211; Paul Connett, James Beck, Spedding Micklem, Foreword by Albert W. Burgstahler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do You Believe in Magic? : Vitamins, Supplements, and All Things Natural: A Look Behind the Curtain &#8211; Dr Paul A Offit (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-you-believe-in-magic-vitamins-supplements-and-all-things-natural-a-look-behind-the-curtain-dr-paul-a-offit-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-you-believe-in-magic-vitamins-supplements-and-all-things-natural-a-look-behind-the-curtain-dr-paul-a-offit-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Medical expert Paul A. Offit, M.D., offers a scathing exposé of the alternative medicine industry, revealing how even though some popular therapies are remarkably helpful due to the placebo response, many of them are ineffective, expensive, and even deadly. Dr. Offit reveals how alternative medicine&#8211;an unregulated industry under no legal obligation to prove its claims [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-you-believe-in-magic-vitamins-supplements-and-all-things-natural-a-look-behind-the-curtain-dr-paul-a-offit-abridged/">Do You Believe in Magic? : Vitamins, Supplements, and All Things Natural: A Look Behind the Curtain &#8211; Dr Paul A Offit (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Medical expert Paul A. Offit, M.D., offers a scathing exposé of the alternative medicine industry, revealing how even though some popular therapies are remarkably helpful due to the placebo response, many of them are ineffective, expensive, and even deadly.    </p>
<p>                    Dr. Offit reveals how alternative medicine&#8211;an unregulated industry under no legal obligation to prove its claims or admit its risks&#8211;can actually be harmful to our health.    </p>
<p>                    Using dramatic real-life stories, Offit separates the sense from the nonsense, showing why any therapy&#8211;alternative or traditional&#8211;should be scrutinized. He also shows how some nontraditional methods can do a great deal of good, in some cases exceeding therapies offered by conventional practitioners.    </p>
<p>                    An outspoken advocate for science-based health advocacy who is not afraid to take on media celebrities who promote alternative practices, Dr. Offit advises, &#8220;There&#8217;s no such thing as alternative medicine. There&#8217;s only medicine that works and medicine that doesn&#8217;t.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-you-believe-in-magic-vitamins-supplements-and-all-things-natural-a-look-behind-the-curtain-dr-paul-a-offit-abridged/">Do You Believe in Magic? : Vitamins, Supplements, and All Things Natural: A Look Behind the Curtain &#8211; Dr Paul A Offit (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dreams & Their Interpretation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The latest book from Dr Rangan Chatterjee, HAPPY MIND, HAPPY LIFE, is available for pre-order now! __________________________________________________________________________________ FROM THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STRESS SOLUTION &#8216;Small changes make a big difference &#8211; we can all benefit from reading this&#8217; &#8211; Jamie Oliver Everyone has the opportunity to live and feel better and in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/">The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The latest book from Dr Rangan Chatterjee, HAPPY MIND, HAPPY LIFE, is available for pre-order now!<br />
                    __________________________________________________________________________________    </p>
<p>                    FROM THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE STRESS SOLUTION    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Small changes make a big difference &#8211; we can all benefit from reading this&#8217; &#8211; Jamie Oliver    </p>
<p>                    Everyone has the opportunity to live and feel better and in his Sunday Times bestselling book, The 4 Pillar Plan, BBC One&#8217;s Dr Rangan Chatterjee creates an easily accessible plan for taking control of your health and your life.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Chatterjee believes that everyday health revolves around the following four pillars: relaxation, food, movement and sleep. By making small, achievable changes in each of these key areas you can create and maintain good health &#8211; and avoid illness. Top tips in each area include:     </p>
<p>                    * an electronic &#8216;sabbath&#8217; once a week<br />
                     * 12 hours every day without food<br />
                     * exposure to sunlight first thing each morning<br />
                     * walking at least 10,000 steps a day    </p>
<p>                    Based on cutting edge research and his own two decades&#8217; worth of experience as a doctor, this book contains fascinating case studies from real patients and is an inspiring and easy-to-follow guide to better health and happiness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-pillar-plan-how-to-relax-eat-move-and-sleep-your-way-to-a-longer-healthier-life-dr-rangan-chatterjee-abridged/">The 4 Pillar Plan : How to Relax, Eat, Move and Sleep Your Way to a Longer, Healthier Life &#8211; Dr Rangan Chatterjee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insurance & Actuarial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicolegal Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller/Washington Post Notable Book of 2017/NPR Best Books of 2017/Wall Street Journal Best Books of 2017 &#8220;This book will serve as the definitive guide to the past and future of health care in America.&#8221;-Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene At a moment of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/">An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller/Washington Post Notable Book of 2017/NPR Best Books of 2017/Wall Street Journal Best Books of 2017     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This book will serve as the definitive guide to the past and future of health care in America.&#8221;-Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene      </p>
<p>                    At a moment of drastic political upheaval, An American Sickness is a shocking investigation into our dysfunctional healthcare system &#8211; and offers practical solutions to its myriad problems.    </p>
<p>                     In these troubled times, perhaps no institution has unraveled more quickly and more completely than American medicine. In only a few decades, the medical system has been overrun by organizations seeking to exploit for profit the trust that vulnerable and sick Americans place in their healthcare. Our politicians have proven themselves either unwilling or incapable of reining in the increasingly outrageous costs faced by patients, and market-based solutions only seem to funnel larger and larger sums of our money into the hands of corporations. Impossibly high insurance premiums and inexplicably large bills have become facts of life; fatalism has set in. Very quickly Americans have been made to accept paying more for less. How did things get so bad so fast?     </p>
<p>                     Breaking down this monolithic business into the individual industries-the hospitals, doctors, insurance companies, and drug manufacturers-that together constitute our healthcare system, Rosenthal exposes the recent evolution of American medicine as never before. How did healthcare, the caring endeavor, become healthcare, the highly profitable industry? Hospital systems, which are managed by business executives, behave like predatory lenders, hounding patients and seizing their homes. Research charities are in bed with big pharmaceutical companies, which surreptitiously profit from the donations made by working people. Patients receive bills in code, from entrepreneurial doctors they never even saw.     </p>
<p>                     The system is in tatters, but we can fight back. Dr. Elisabeth Rosenthal doesn&#8217;t just explain the symptoms, she diagnoses and treats the disease itself. In clear and practical terms, she spells out exactly how to decode medical doublespeak, avoid the pitfalls of the pharmaceuticals racket, and get the care you and your family deserve. She takes you inside the doctor-patient relationship and to hospital C-suites, explaining step-by-step the workings of a system badly lacking transparency. This is about what we can do, as individual patients, both to navigate the maze that is American healthcare and also to demand far-reaching reform. An American Sickness is the frontline defense against a healthcare system that no longer has our well-being at heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/an-american-sickness-how-healthcare-became-big-business-and-how-you-can-take-it-back-elisabeth-rosenthal-abridged/">An American Sickness : How Healthcare Became Big Business and How You Can Take It Back &#8211; Elisabeth Rosenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health    </p>
<p>                    Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, bacteria and human cells have co-existed in a relationship that has ensured the health and equilibrium of our body. But now, much like the natural world outside of us, our internal environment is being irrevocably destroyed. The culprit: some of our most revered medical advances &#8211; antibiotics &#8211; which appear to be linked to the epidemics of asthma, eczema, obesity, certain forms of cancer, and other diseases plaguing modern society.    </p>
<p>                    In a book that stands as the Silent Spring of its day, Blaser sounds a provocative alarm that we ignore at our peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription: A Disruptive Solution for Health Care &#8211; Clayton Christensen, Jerome Grossman, Jason Hwang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Administration & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking prescription for health care reform&#8211;from a legendaryleader in innovation . . . Our health care system is in critical condition. Each year, fewer Americans can afford it, fewer businesses can provide it, and fewer government programs can promise it for future generations. We need a cure, and we need it now. Harvard Business [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/">The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription: A Disruptive Solution for Health Care &#8211; Clayton Christensen, Jerome Grossman, Jason Hwang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking prescription for health care reform&#8211;from a legendaryleader in innovation . . .    </p>
<p>                    Our health care system is in critical condition. Each year, fewer Americans can afford it, fewer businesses can provide it, and fewer government programs can promise it for future generations.    </p>
<p>                    We need a cure, and we need it now.    </p>
<p>                    Harvard Business School&#8217;s Clayton M. Christensen-whose bestselling The Innovator&#8217;s Dilemma revolutionized the business world-presents The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription, a comprehensive analysis of the strategies that will improvehealth care and make it affordable.    </p>
<p>                    Christensen applies the principles of disruptive innovation to the broken health care system with two pioneers in the field-Dr. Jerome Grossman and Dr. Jason Hwang. Together, they examine arange of symptoms and offer proven solutions.    </p>
<p>                    YOU&#8217;LL DISCOVER HOW    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Precision medicine&#8221; reduces costs and makes good on the promise of personalized careDisruptive business models improve quality, accessibility, and affordability by changing the way hospitals and doctors workPatient networks enable better treatment of chronic diseasesEmployers can change the roles they play in health care to compete effectively in the era of globalizationInsurance and regulatory reforms stimulate disruption in health care</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innovators-prescription-a-disruptive-solution-for-health-care-clayton-christensen-jerome-grossman-jason-hwang-abridged/">The Innovator&#8217;s Prescription: A Disruptive Solution for Health Care &#8211; Clayton Christensen, Jerome Grossman, Jason Hwang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Escape : Health, Wealth, and the Origins of Inequality &#8211; Angus Deaton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-great-escape-health-wealth-and-the-origins-of-inequality-angus-deaton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Safety Law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-escape-health-wealth-and-the-origins-of-inequality-angus-deaton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The world is a better place than it used to be. People are healthier, wealthier, and live longer. Yet the escapes from destitution by so many has left gaping inequalities between people and nations. In The Great Escape, Angus Deaton&#8211;one of the foremost experts on economic development and on poverty&#8211;tells the remarkable story of how, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-escape-health-wealth-and-the-origins-of-inequality-angus-deaton-abridged/">The Great Escape : Health, Wealth, and the Origins of Inequality &#8211; Angus Deaton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world is a better place than it used to be. People are healthier, wealthier, and live longer. Yet the escapes from destitution by so many has left gaping inequalities between people and nations. In The Great Escape, Angus Deaton&#8211;one of the foremost experts on economic development and on poverty&#8211;tells the remarkable story of how, beginning 250 years ago, some parts of the world experienced sustained progress, opening up gaps and setting the stage for today&#8217;s disproportionately unequal world. Deaton takes an in-depth look at the historical and ongoing patterns behind the health and wealth of nations, and addresses what needs to be done to help those left behind. Deaton describes vast innovations and wrenching setbacks: the successes of antibiotics, pest control, vaccinations, and clean water on the one hand, and disastrous famines and the HIV/AIDS epidemic on the other. He examines the United States, a nation that has prospered but is today experiencing slower growth and increasing inequality. He also considers how economic growth in India and China has improved the lives of more than a billion people. Deaton argues that international aid has been ineffective and even harmful.<br />
                    He suggests alternative efforts&#8211;including reforming incentives to drug companies and lifting trade restrictions&#8211;that will allow the developing world to bring about its own Great Escape. Demonstrating how changes in health and living standards have transformed our lives, The Great Escape is a powerful guide to addressing the well-being of all nations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-escape-health-wealth-and-the-origins-of-inequality-angus-deaton-abridged/">The Great Escape : Health, Wealth, and the Origins of Inequality &#8211; Angus Deaton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Immunity &#8211; William E. Paul (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A leading figure in immunology takes readers inside the remarkably powerful human immune system. Winner of the CHOICE Outstanding Academic Title of the Choice ACRL The immune system has incredible power to protect us from the ravages of infection. Boosted by vaccines, it can protect us from diseases such as measles. However, the power of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/">Immunity &#8211; William E. Paul (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A leading figure in immunology takes readers inside the remarkably powerful human immune system.    </p>
<p>                    Winner of the CHOICE Outstanding Academic Title of the Choice ACRL    </p>
<p>                    The immune system has incredible power to protect us from the ravages of infection. Boosted by vaccines, it can protect us from diseases such as measles. However, the power of the immune system is a double-edged sword: an overactive immune system can wreak havoc, destroying normal tissue and causing diseases such as type I diabetes, rheumatoid arthritis, and multiple sclerosis. The consequences of an impaired immune system, on the other hand, are all too evident in the agonies of AIDS.    </p>
<p>                    Packed with illustrations, stories from Dr. William E. Paul&#8217;s distinguished career, and fascinating accounts of scientific discovery, Immunity presents the three laws of the human immune system-universality, tolerance, and appropriateness-and explains how the system both protects and harms us. From the tale of how smallpox was overcome and the lessons of the Ebola epidemic to the hope that the immune system can be used to treat or prevent cancer, Dr. Paul argues that we must take advantage of cutting-edge technologies and promising new tools in immunological research.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/immunity-william-e-paul-abridged/">Immunity &#8211; William E. Paul (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Put an end to dieting and replace weight-loss struggles with this easy approach to a healthy, plant-based lifestyle, from the bestselling author of How Not to Die. Every month seems to bring a trendy new diet or a new fad to try in order to lose weight &#8211; but these diets aren&#8217;t making us any [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/">How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Put an end to dieting and replace weight-loss struggles with this easy approach to a healthy, plant-based lifestyle,  from the bestselling author of How Not to Die.    </p>
<p>                    Every month seems to bring a trendy new diet or a new fad to try in order to lose weight &#8211; but these diets aren&#8217;t making us any happier or healthier. As obesity rates and associated disease and impairments continue to rise, it&#8217;s time for a different approach.    </p>
<p>                    How Not to Diet is a treasure trove of buried data and cutting-edge dietary research that Dr Michael Greger has translated into accessible, actionable advice with exciting tools and tricks that will help you to safely lose weight and eliminate unwanted body fat &#8211; for good.    </p>
<p>                    Dr Greger, renowned nutrition expert, physician, and founder of the NutritionFacts website, explores the many causes of obesity &#8211; from our genes to the portions on our plate to other environmental factors &#8211; and the many consequences, from diabetes to cancer to mental health issues. From there, Dr Greger breaks down a variety of approaches to weight loss, honing in on the optimal criteria that enable success, including: a diet high in fibre and water, a diet low in fat, salt, and sugar, and diet full of anti-inflammatory foods.    </p>
<p>                    How Not to Diet then goes beyond food to explore the many other weight-loss accelerators available to us in our body&#8217;s systems, revealing how plant-based meals can be eaten at specific times to maximize our bodies&#8217; natural fat-burning activities. Dr Greger provides a clear plan not only for the ultimate weight loss diet, but also the approach we must take to unlock its greatest efficacy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-diet-the-groundbreaking-science-of-healthy-permanent-weight-loss-michael-greger-abridged/">How Not to Diet : The Groundbreaking Science of Healthy, Permanent Weight Loss &#8211; Michael Greger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
