<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Illness &amp; Addiction: Social Aspects Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/illness-addiction-social-aspects/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/illness-addiction-social-aspects/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Illness &amp; Addiction: Social Aspects Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/illness-addiction-social-aspects/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</title>
		<link>/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Giving Up Smoking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Respiratory Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Funding & Policy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19. Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Multiple New York Times best-selling author Dr. Joseph Mercola and Ronnie Cummins, founder and director of the Organic Consumers Association, team up to expose the truth-and end the madness-about COVID-19.    </p>
<p>                    Since early 2020, the world has experienced a series of catastrophic events-a global pandemic caused by what appears to be an engineered coronavirus; international lockdowns and border closings causing widespread business closures, economic collapse, and massive unemployment; and an unprecedented curtailment of civil liberties and freedoms in the name of keeping people safe by locking them up in their homes.    </p>
<p>                    We are now living in a world that is increasingly ruled, not by our democratic systems and institutions, but by public health fiat, carried out by politicians who rule by instilling fear and panic.    </p>
<p>                    In The Truth About COVID-19, Dr. Mercola and Cummins reveal new and emerging evidence that:    </p>
<p>                    The SARS-CoV-2 virus was, indeed, lab-engineered and emerged from a negligently managed bioweapons lab in Wuhan, China<br />
                    The global pandemic was long anticipated by global elites who have used it to facilitate and hide the largest upward transfer of wealth in human history<br />
                    PCR testing, case counts, morbidity, and vaccine safety and efficacy data have been widely manipulated and misrepresented<br />
                    Obesity, diabetes, and heart disease are known to worsen COVID-19 outcomes, but the junk food industry continues to push its agenda at the expense of public health<br />
                    Safe, simple, and inexpensive treatment and prevention for COVID-19 have been censored and suppressed to create a clear path for vaccine acceptance<br />
                    Effectiveness of the vaccines has been wildly exaggerated and major safety questions have gone unanswered    </p>
<p>                    The good news in all of this is that we can take control of our health and that, together, we have the power to unite and fight back for our health, democracy, and freedom. The time is now for a global awakening. As Dr. Mercola and Cummins remind us, this is the fight of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-covid-19-exposing-the-great-reset-lockdowns-vaccine-passports-and-the-new-normal-doctor-joseph-mercola-ronnie-cummins-foreword-by-robert-f-kennedy/">The Truth About COVID-19 : Exposing The Great Reset, Lockdowns, Vaccine Passports, and the New Normal &#8211; Doctor Joseph Mercola, Ronnie Cummins, Foreword by Robert F. Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Age of Anxiety &#8211; Scott Stossel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/my-age-of-anxiety-scott-stossel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-age-of-anxiety-scott-stossel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER and SHORTLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME BOOK PRIZE 2015 As recently as thirty-five years ago, anxiety did not exist as a diagnostic category. Today, it is the most common form of officially classified mental illness. Scott Stossel gracefully guides us across the terrain of an affliction that is pervasive yet too [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-age-of-anxiety-scott-stossel-abridged/">My Age of Anxiety &#8211; Scott Stossel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER and SHORTLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME BOOK PRIZE 2015     </p>
<p>                    As recently as thirty-five years ago, anxiety did not exist as a diagnostic category. Today, it is the most common form of officially classified mental illness. Scott Stossel gracefully guides us across the terrain of an affliction that is pervasive yet too often misunderstood.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his own long-standing battle with anxiety, Stossel presents an astonishing history, at once intimate and authoritative, of the efforts to understand the condition from medical, cultural, philosophical and experiential perspectives. He ranges from the earliest medical reports of Galen and Hippocrates, through later observations by Robert Burton and Soren Kierkegaard, to the investigations by great nineteenth-century scientists, such as Charles Darwin, William James and Sigmund Freud, as they began to explore its sources and causes, to the latest research by neuroscientists and geneticists. Stossel reports on famous individuals who struggled with anxiety, as well as the afflicted generations of his own family. His portrait of anxiety reveals not only the emotion&#8217;s myriad manifestations and the anguish it produces, but also the countless psychotherapies, medications and other (often outlandish) treatments that have been developed to counteract it. Stossel vividly depicts anxiety&#8217;s human toll &#8211; its crippling impact, its devastating power to paralyse &#8211; while at the same time exploring how those who suffer from it find ways to manage and control it.    </p>
<p>                    My Age of Anxiety is learned and empathetic, humorous and inspirational, offering the reader great insight into the biological, cultural and environmental factors that contribute to the affliction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-age-of-anxiety-scott-stossel-abridged/">My Age of Anxiety &#8211; Scott Stossel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epidemiology & Medical Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than three hundred infectious diseases have emerged or reemerged in new territory during the past fifty years, and ninety percent of epidemiologists expect that one of them will cause a disruptive, deadly pandemic sometime in the next two generations. To reveal how that might happen, Sonia Shah tracks each stage of cholera&#8217;s dramatic journey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/">Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than three hundred infectious diseases have emerged or reemerged in new territory during the past fifty years, and ninety percent of epidemiologists expect that one of them will cause a disruptive, deadly pandemic sometime in the next two generations. To reveal how that might happen, Sonia Shah tracks each stage of cholera&#8217;s dramatic journey from harmless microbe to world-changing pandemic, from its 1817 emergence in the South Asian hinterlands to its rapid dispersal across the nineteenth-century world and its latest beachhead in Haiti. She reports on the pathogens following in cholera&#8217;s footsteps, from the MRSA bacterium that besieges her own family to the never-before-seen killers emerging from China&#8217;s wet markets, the surgical wards of New Delhi, the slums of Port-au-Prince, and the suburban backyards of the East Coast. A deep-dive into the convoluted science, strange politics, and checkered history of one of the world&#8217;s deadliest diseases, Pandemic reveals what the next epidemic might look like&#8211;and what we can do to prevent it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/">Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal & Public Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Moneyball meets medicine in this remarkable chronicle of one of the greatest scientific quests of our time&#8211;the groundbreaking program to answer the most essential question for humanity: how do we live and die?&#8211;and the visionary mastermind behind it. Medical doctor and economist Christopher Murray began the Global Burden of Disease studies to gain a truer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/">Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Moneyball meets medicine in this remarkable chronicle of one of the greatest scientific quests of our time&#8211;the groundbreaking program to answer the most essential question for humanity: how do we live and die?&#8211;and the visionary mastermind behind it.    </p>
<p>                    Medical doctor and economist Christopher Murray began the Global Burden of Disease studies to gain a truer understanding of how we live and how we die. While it is one of the largest scientific projects ever attempted&#8211;as breathtaking as the first moon landing or the Human Genome Project&#8211;the questions it answers are meaningful for every one of us: What are the world&#8217;s health problems? Who do they hurt? How much? Where? Why?    </p>
<p>                    Murray argues that the ideal existence isn&#8217;t simply the longest but the one lived well and with the least illness. Until we can accurately measure how people live and die, we cannot understand what makes us sick or do much to improve it. Challenging the accepted wisdom of the WHO and the UN, the charismatic and controversial health maverick has made enemies&#8211;and some influential friends, including Bill Gates who gave Murray a $100 million grant.    </p>
<p>                    In Epic Measures, journalist Jeremy N. Smith offers an intimate look at Murray and his groundbreaking work. From ranking countries&#8217; healthcare systems (the U.S. is 37th) to unearthing the shocking reality that world governments are funding developing countries at only 30% of the potential maximum efficiency when it comes to health, Epic Measures introduces a visionary leader whose unwavering determination to improve global health standards has already changed the way the world addresses issues of health and wellness, sets policy, and distributes funding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/epic-measures-one-doctor-seven-billion-patients-jeremy-n-smith-abridged/">Epic Measures : One Doctor. Seven Billion Patients. &#8211; Jeremy N. Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crisis in the Red Zone : The Story of the Deadliest Ebola Outbreak in History, and of the Viruses to Come &#8211; Richard Preston (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An urgent wake-up call about the future of emerging viruses and a gripping account of the doctors and scientists fighting to protect us, told through the story of the deadly 2013-2014 Ebola epidemic &#8220;Crisis in the Red Zone reads like a thriller. That the story it tells is all true [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/">Crisis in the Red Zone : The Story of the Deadliest Ebola Outbreak in History, and of the Viruses to Come &#8211; Richard Preston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An urgent wake-up call about the future of emerging viruses and a gripping account of the doctors and scientists fighting to protect us, told through the story of the deadly 2013-2014 Ebola epidemic &#8220;Crisis in the Red Zone reads like a thriller. That the story it tells is all true makes it all more terrifying.&#8221;&#8211;Elizabeth Kolbert, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Sixth Extinction From the #1 bestselling author of The Hot Zone, now a National Geographic original miniseries . . . This time, Ebola started with a two-year-old child who likely had contact with a wild creature and whose entire family quickly fell ill and died. The ensuing global drama activated health professionals in North America, Europe, and Africa in a desperate race against time to contain the viral wildfire. By the end&#8211;as the virus mutated into its deadliest form, and spread farther and faster than ever before&#8211;30,000 people would be infected, and the dead would be spread across eight countries on three continents. In this taut and suspenseful medical drama, Richard Preston deeply chronicles the pandemic, in which we saw for the first time the specter of Ebola jumping continents, crossing the Atlantic, and infecting people in America. Rich in characters and conflict&#8211;physical, emotional, and ethical&#8211;Crisis in the Red Zone is an immersion in one of the great public health calamities of our time. Preston writes of doctors and nurses in the field putting their own lives on the line, of government bureaucrats and NGO administrators moving, often fitfully, to try to contain the outbreak, and of pharmaceutical companies racing to develop drugs to combat the virus. He also explores the charged ethical dilemma over who should and did receive the rare doses of an experimental treatment when they became available at the peak of the disaster. Crisis in the Red Zone makes clear that the outbreak of 2013-2014 is a harbinger of further, more severe outbreaks, and of emerging viruses heretofore unimagined&#8211;in any country, on any continent. In our ever more interconnected world, with roads and towns cut deep into the jungles of equatorial Africa, viruses both familiar and undiscovered are being unleashed into more densely populated areas than ever before. The more we discover about the virosphere, the more we realize its deadly potential. Crisis in the Red Zone is an exquisitely timely book, a stark warning of viral outbreaks to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/">Crisis in the Red Zone : The Story of the Deadliest Ebola Outbreak in History, and of the Viruses to Come &#8211; Richard Preston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dreamland : The True Tale of America&#8217;s Opiate Epidemic &#8211; Sam Quinones (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dreamland-the-true-tale-of-americas-opiate-epidemic-sam-quinones-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drug & Substance Abuse: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drugs Trade / Drug Trafficking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dreamland-the-true-tale-of-americas-opiate-epidemic-sam-quinones-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the NBCC Award for General Nonfiction Named on Amazon&#8217;s Best Books of the Year 2015&#8211;Michael Botticelli, U.S. Drug Czar (Politico) Favorite Book of the Year&#8211;Angus Deaton, Nobel Prize Economics (Bloomberg/WSJ) Best Books of 2015&#8211;Matt Bevin, Governor of Kentucky (WSJ) Books of the Year&#8211;Slate.com&#8217;s 10 Best Books of 2015&#8211;Entertainment Weekly&#8217;s 10 Best Books of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dreamland-the-true-tale-of-americas-opiate-epidemic-sam-quinones-abridged/">Dreamland : The True Tale of America&#8217;s Opiate Epidemic &#8211; Sam Quinones (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the NBCC Award for General Nonfiction    </p>
<p>                    Named on Amazon&#8217;s Best Books of the Year 2015&#8211;Michael Botticelli, U.S. Drug Czar (Politico) Favorite Book of the Year&#8211;Angus Deaton, Nobel Prize Economics (Bloomberg/WSJ) Best Books of 2015&#8211;Matt Bevin, Governor of Kentucky (WSJ) Books of the Year&#8211;Slate.com&#8217;s 10 Best Books of 2015&#8211;Entertainment Weekly&#8217;s 10 Best Books of 2015 &#8211;Buzzfeed&#8217;s 19 Best Nonfiction Books of 2015&#8211;The Daily Beast&#8217;s Best Big Idea Books of 2015&#8211;Seattle Times&#8217; Best Books of 2015&#8211;Boston Globe&#8217;s Best Books of 2015&#8211;St. Louis Post-Dispatch&#8217;s Best Books of 2015&#8211;The Guardian&#8217;s The Best Book We Read All Year&#8211;Audible&#8217;s Best Books of 2015&#8211;Texas Observer&#8217;s Five Books We Loved in 2015&#8211;Chicago Public Library&#8217;s Best Nonfiction Books of 2015     </p>
<p>                    From a small town in Mexico to the boardrooms of Big Pharma to main streets nationwide, an explosive and shocking account of addiction in the heartland of America.     </p>
<p>                    In 1929, in the blue-collar city of Portsmouth, Ohio, a company built a swimming pool the size of a football field; named Dreamland, it became the vital center of the community. Now, addiction has devastated Portsmouth, as it has hundreds of small rural towns and suburbs across America&#8211;addiction like no other the country has ever faced. How that happened is the riveting story of Dreamland.     </p>
<p>                    With a great reporter&#8217;s narrative skill and the storytelling ability of a novelist, acclaimed journalist Sam Quinones weaves together two classic tales of capitalism run amok whose unintentional collision has been catastrophic. The unfettered prescribing of pain medications during the 1990s reached its peak in Purdue Pharma&#8217;s campaign to market OxyContin, its new, expensive&#8211;extremely addictive&#8211;miracle painkiller. Meanwhile, a massive influx of black tar heroin&#8211;cheap, potent, and originating from one small county on Mexico&#8217;s west coast, independent of any drug cartel&#8211;assaulted small town and mid-sized cities across the country, driven by a brilliant, almost unbeatable marketing and distribution system. Together these phenomena continue to lay waste to communities from Tennessee to Oregon, Indiana to New Mexico.     </p>
<p>                    Introducing a memorable cast of characters&#8211;pharma pioneers, young Mexican entrepreneurs, narcotics investigators, survivors, and parents&#8211;Quinones shows how these tales fit together. Dreamland is a revelatory account of the corrosive threat facing America and its heartland.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dreamland-the-true-tale-of-americas-opiate-epidemic-sam-quinones-abridged/">Dreamland : The True Tale of America&#8217;s Opiate Epidemic &#8211; Sam Quinones (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Eating Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A TIME magazine Must-Read Book of the Year Ever wonder what your therapist is thinking? Now you can find out, as therapist and New York Times bestselling author Lori Gottlieb takes us behind the scenes of her practice &#8211; where her patients are looking for answers (and so is she). When a personal crisis causes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/">Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A TIME magazine Must-Read Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Ever wonder what your therapist is thinking? Now you can find out, as therapist and New York Times bestselling author Lori Gottlieb takes us behind the scenes of her practice &#8211; where her patients are looking for answers (and so is she).    </p>
<p>                    When a personal crisis causes her world to come crashing down, Lori Gottlieb &#8211; an experienced therapist with a thriving practice in Los Angeles &#8211; is suddenly adrift. Enter Wendell, himself a veteran therapist with an unconventional style, whose sessions with Gottlieb will prove transformative for her.    </p>
<p>                    As Gottlieb explores the inner chambers of her own patients&#8217; lives &#8211; a self-absorbed Hollywood producer, a young newlywed diagnosed with a terminal illness, a senior citizen who feels she has nothing to live for, and a self-destructive twenty-something who can&#8217;t stop hooking up with the wrong guys &#8211; she finds that the questions they are struggling with are the very questions she is bringing to Wendell.    </p>
<p>                    Taking place over one year, and beginning with the devastating event that lands her in Wendell&#8217;s office, Maybe You Should Talk to Someone offers a rare and candid insight into a profession that is conventionally bound with rules and secrecy. Told with charm and compassion, vulnerability and humour, it&#8217;s also the story of an incredible relationship between two therapists, and a disarmingly funny and illuminating account of our own mysterious inner lives, as well as our power to transform them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/">Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No One Cares About Crazy People : My Family and the Heartbreak of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Ron Powers (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/no-one-cares-about-crazy-people-my-family-and-the-heartbreak-of-mental-illness-in-america-ron-powers-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/no-one-cares-about-crazy-people-my-family-and-the-heartbreak-of-mental-illness-in-america-ron-powers-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Extraordinary and courageous . . . No doubt if everyone were to read this book, the world would change.&#8221;&#8212;New York Times Book Review New York Times-bestselling author Ron Powers&#8217; critically acclaimed narrative of the social history of mental illness in America paired with the deeply personal story of his two sons&#8217; battles with schizophrenia. From [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-one-cares-about-crazy-people-my-family-and-the-heartbreak-of-mental-illness-in-america-ron-powers-abridged/">No One Cares About Crazy People : My Family and the Heartbreak of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Ron Powers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Extraordinary and courageous . . . No doubt if everyone were to read this book, the world would change.&#8221;&#8212;New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    New York Times-bestselling author Ron Powers&#8217; critically acclaimed narrative of the social history of mental illness in America paired with the deeply personal story of his two sons&#8217; battles with schizophrenia.    </p>
<p>                    From the centuries of torture of &#8220;lunatiks&#8221; at Bedlam Asylum to the infamous eugenics era to the follies of the anti-psychiatry movement to the current landscape in which too many families struggle alone to manage afflicted love ones, Powers limns our fears and myths about mental illness and the fractured public policies that have resulted.     </p>
<p>                    Braided with that history is the moving story of Powers&#8217;s beloved son Kevin&#8211;spirited, endearing, and gifted&#8211;who triumphed even while suffering from schizophrenia until finally he did not, and the story of his courageous surviving son Dean, who is also schizophrenic.     </p>
<p>                    A blend of history, biography, memoir, and current affairs ending with a consideration of where we might go from here, this is a thought-provoking look at a dreaded illness that has long been misunderstood.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-one-cares-about-crazy-people-my-family-and-the-heartbreak-of-mental-illness-in-america-ron-powers-abridged/">No One Cares About Crazy People : My Family and the Heartbreak of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Ron Powers (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epidemiology & Medical Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmacology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated with bonus material, including a new foreword and afterword with new research, this New York Times bestseller is essential reading for a time when mental health is constantly in the news. In this astonishing and startling book, award-winning science and history writer Robert Whitaker investigates a medical mystery: Why has the number of disabled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/">Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated with bonus material, including a new foreword and afterword with new research, this New York Times bestseller is essential reading for a time when mental health is constantly in the news.     </p>
<p>                    In this astonishing and startling book, award-winning science and history writer Robert Whitaker investigates a medical mystery: Why has the number of disabled mentally ill in the United States tripled over the past two decades?     </p>
<p>                    Interwoven with Whitaker&#8217;s groundbreaking analysis of the merits of psychiatric medications are the personal stories of children and adults swept up in this epidemic. As Anatomy of an Epidemic reveals, other societies have begun to alter their use of psychiatric medications and are now reporting much improved outcomes . . . so why can&#8217;t such change happen here in the United States? Why have the results from these long-term studies&#8211;all of which point to the same startling conclusion&#8211;been kept from the public?     </p>
<p>                    Our nation has been hit by an epidemic of disabling mental illness, and yet, as Anatomy of an Epidemic reveals, the medical blueprints for curbing that epidemic have already been drawn up.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Anatomy of an Epidemic     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The timing of Robert Whitaker&#8217;s Anatomy of an Epidemic, a comprehensive and highly readable history of psychiatry in the United States, couldn&#8217;t be better.&#8221;&#8211;Salon     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Anatomy of an Epidemic offers some answers, charting controversial ground with mystery-novel pacing.&#8221;&#8211;TIME     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Lucid, pointed and important, Anatomy of an Epidemic should be required reading for anyone considering extended use of psychiatric medicine. Whitaker is at the height of his powers.&#8221; &#8211;Greg Critser, author of Generation Rx</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/">Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On Immunity : An Inoculation &#8211; Eula Biss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-immunity-an-inoculation-eula-biss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-immunity-an-inoculation-eula-biss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;On Immunity is a book I&#8217;ve recommended too many times to count&#8211;a searching, empathetic, ultimately unassailable argument, not just for vaccination but for thoroughly acknowledging our interdependence, and for all that becomes necessary and possible once we do. Written before COVID, it nonetheless speaks directly to the concerns of the pandemic era&#8211;to the fact that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-immunity-an-inoculation-eula-biss-abridged/">On Immunity : An Inoculation &#8211; Eula Biss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;On Immunity is a book I&#8217;ve recommended too many times to count&#8211;a searching, empathetic, ultimately unassailable argument, not just for vaccination but for thoroughly acknowledging our interdependence, and for all that becomes necessary and possible once we do. Written before COVID, it nonetheless speaks directly to the concerns of the pandemic era&#8211;to the fact that we are dangerous as well as vulnerable, to the way collective well-being and individual self-interest are configured at odds to one another when they are fundamentally intertwined.&#8221;&#8211;Jia Tolentino     </p>
<p>                    In this bold, fascinating book, Eula Biss addresses our fear of the government, the medical establishment, and what may be in our children&#8217;s air, food, mattresses, medicines, and vaccines. Reflecting on her own experience as a new mother, she suggests that we cannot immunize our children, or ourselves, against the world. As she explores the metaphors surrounding immunity, Biss extends her conversations with other mothers to meditations on the myth of Achilles, Voltaire&#8217;s Candide, Bram Stoker&#8217;s Dracula, Rachel Carson&#8217;s Silent Spring, Susan Sontag&#8217;s AIDS and Its Metaphors, and beyond. On Immunity is an inoculation against our fear and a moving account of how we are all interconnected-our bodies and our fates.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-immunity-an-inoculation-eula-biss-abridged/">On Immunity : An Inoculation &#8211; Eula Biss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author). We are in the grip of a food [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author).<br />
                       We are in the grip of a food crisis. Obesity has become a leading cause of preventable death, after only smoking. For nearly half a century we&#8217;ve been trying to pin the blame somewhere, fat, carbs, sugar, wheat, high-fructose corn syrup. But that search has been in vain, because the food problem that&#8217;s killing us is not a nutrient problem. It&#8217;s a behavioural problem, and it&#8217;s caused by the changing flavour of the food we eat.<br />
                       Ever since the 1940s, with the rise of industrialized food production, we have been gradually leeching the taste out of what we grow. Simultaneously, we have taken great leaps forward in technology, creating a flavour industry, worth billions annually; in an attempt to put back the tastes we&#8217;ve engineered out of our food. The result is a cuisine that increasingly resembles the paragon of flavour manipulation: Doritos. As food becomes increasingly bland, we dress it up with calories and flavour chemicals to make it delicious again. We have rewired our palates and our brains, and the results are making us sick and killing us.<br />
                       With in-depth historical and scientific research, The Dorito Effect casts the food crisis in a fascinating new light, weaving an enthralling tale of how we got to this point and where we are headed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
