<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Legal Profession: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/legal-profession-general/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/legal-profession-general/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Legal Profession: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/legal-profession-general/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Secret Barrister : Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken &#8211; The Secret Barrister</title>
		<link>/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Law & Procedure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Ethics & Professional Conduct]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times number one bestseller. Winner of the Books are My Bag Non-Fiction Award. Shortlisted for Waterstones Book of the Year. Shortlisted for Specsavers Non-Fiction Book of the Year. You may not wish to think about it, but one day you or someone you love will almost certainly appear in a criminal courtroom. You [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister/">The Secret Barrister : Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken &#8211; The Secret Barrister</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times number one bestseller.<br />
                    Winner of the Books are My Bag Non-Fiction Award.<br />
                    Shortlisted for Waterstones Book of the Year.<br />
                    Shortlisted for Specsavers Non-Fiction Book of the Year.</p>
<p>                    You may not wish to think about it, but one day you or someone you love will almost certainly appear in a criminal courtroom. You might be a juror, a victim, a witness or &#8211; perhaps through no fault of your own &#8211; a defendant. Whatever your role, you&#8217;d expect a fair trial.</p>
<p>                      I&#8217;m a barrister. I work in the criminal justice system, and every day I see how fairness is not guaranteed. Too often the system fails those it is meant to protect. The innocent are wronged and the guilty allowed to walk free.</p>
<p>                    In The Secret Barrister: Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken I want to share some stories from my daily life to show you how the system is broken, who broke it and why we should start caring before it&#8217;s too late.</p>
<p>                    A Sunday Times top ten bestseller for twenty-four weeks.<br />
                    &#8216;Eye-opening, funny and horrifying&#8217; &#8211; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Everyone who has any interest in public life should read it&#8217; &#8211; Daily Mail</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister/">The Secret Barrister : Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken &#8211; The Secret Barrister</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lawyers, Liars, and the Art of Storytelling : Using Stories to Advocate, Influence, and Persuade &#8211; Jonathan Shapiro (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lawyers-liars-and-the-art-of-storytelling-using-stories-to-advocate-influence-and-persuade-jonathan-shapiro-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Procedure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jurisprudence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lawyers-liars-and-the-art-of-storytelling-using-stories-to-advocate-influence-and-persuade-jonathan-shapiro-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nobody I know is funnier, smarter, or has a wider breadth of references than my friend Jonathan Shapiro. This book is a bit of a miracle: informative, insightful, poetic, and funny. -Paul Reiser, comedian, actor, and bestselling author Using famous real-life court transcripts, television scripts, and story after story, Lawyers, Liars, and the Art of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lawyers-liars-and-the-art-of-storytelling-using-stories-to-advocate-influence-and-persuade-jonathan-shapiro-abridged/">Lawyers, Liars, and the Art of Storytelling : Using Stories to Advocate, Influence, and Persuade &#8211; Jonathan Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nobody I know is funnier, smarter, or has a wider breadth of references than my friend Jonathan Shapiro. This book is a bit of a miracle: informative, insightful, poetic, and funny. -Paul Reiser, comedian, actor, and bestselling author  Using famous real-life court transcripts, television scripts, and story after story, Lawyers, Liars, and the Art of Storytelling shows the reader how to get their message across and the result they want using the time-tested elements and basic structure of great stories. Part how-to manual, part memoir, always entertaining and never lecture, this book provides storytelling lessons gleaned from years of trial practice and television writing, wrapped in-what else?-great stories.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lawyers-liars-and-the-art-of-storytelling-using-stories-to-advocate-influence-and-persuade-jonathan-shapiro-abridged/">Lawyers, Liars, and the Art of Storytelling : Using Stories to Advocate, Influence, and Persuade &#8211; Jonathan Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Beloved World &#8211; Sonia Sotomayor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/my-beloved-world-sonia-sotomayor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Courts & Procedure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hispanic & Latino Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-beloved-world-sonia-sotomayor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A &#8220;searching and emotionally intimate memoir&#8221; (The New York Times) told with a candor never before undertaken by a sitting Justice. This &#8220;powerful defense of empathy&#8221; (The Washington Post) is destined to become a classic of self-invention and self-discovery. The first Hispanic and third woman appointed to the United States Supreme Court, Sonia Sotomayor has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-beloved-world-sonia-sotomayor-abridged/">My Beloved World &#8211; Sonia Sotomayor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A &#8220;searching and emotionally intimate memoir&#8221; (The New York Times) told with a candor never before undertaken by a sitting Justice. This &#8220;powerful defense of empathy&#8221; (The Washington Post) is destined to become a classic of self-invention and self-discovery.     </p>
<p>                    The first Hispanic and third woman appointed to the United States Supreme Court, Sonia Sotomayor has become an instant American icon.     </p>
<p>                    In this story of human triumph that &#8220;hums with hope and exhilaration&#8221; (NPR), she recounts her life from a Bronx housing project to the federal bench, a journey that offers an inspiring testament to her own extraordinary determination and the power of believing in oneself.     </p>
<p>                    Here is the story of a precarious childhood, with an alcoholic father (who would die when she was nine) and a devoted but overburdened mother, and of the refuge a little girl took from the turmoil at home with her passionately spirited paternal grandmother. But it was when she was diagnosed with juvenile diabetes that the precocious Sonia recognized she must ultimately depend on herself. She would learn to give herself the insulin shots she needed to survive and soon imagined a path to a different life.     </p>
<p>                    With only television characters for her professional role models, and little understanding of what was involved, she determined to become a lawyer, a dream that would sustain her on an unlikely course, from valedictorian of her high school class to the highest honors at Princeton, Yale Law School, the New York County District Attorney&#8217;s office, private practice, and appointment to the Federal District Court before the age of forty.     </p>
<p>                    Along the way we see how she was shaped by her invaluable mentors, a failed marriage, and the modern version of extended family she has created from cherished friends and their children. Through her still-astonished eyes, America&#8217;s infinite possibilities are envisioned anew in this warm and honest book.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-beloved-world-sonia-sotomayor-abridged/">My Beloved World &#8211; Sonia Sotomayor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Notorious RBG : The Life and Times of Ruth Bader Ginsburg &#8211; Irin Carmon, Shana Knizhnik (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/notorious-rbg-the-life-and-times-of-ruth-bader-ginsburg-irin-carmon-shana-knizhnik-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/notorious-rbg-the-life-and-times-of-ruth-bader-ginsburg-irin-carmon-shana-knizhnik-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8220;The authors make this unassuming, most studious woman come pulsing to life&#8230;Notorious RBG may be a playful project, but it asks to be read seriously&#8230;That I responded so personally to it is a testimony to [its] storytelling and panache.&#8221;- Jennifer Senior, New York Times Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg never [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/notorious-rbg-the-life-and-times-of-ruth-bader-ginsburg-irin-carmon-shana-knizhnik-abridged/">Notorious RBG : The Life and Times of Ruth Bader Ginsburg &#8211; Irin Carmon, Shana Knizhnik (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER  &#8220;The authors make this unassuming, most studious woman come pulsing to life&#8230;Notorious RBG may be a playful project, but it asks to be read seriously&#8230;That I responded so personally to it is a testimony to [its] storytelling and panache.&#8221;- Jennifer Senior, New York Times  Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg never asked for fame-she has only tried to make the world a little better and a little freer.  But nearly a half-century into her career, something funny happened to the octogenarian: she won the internet. Across America, people who weren&#8217;t even born when Ginsburg first made her name as a feminist pioneer are tattooing themselves with her face, setting her famously searing dissents to music, and making viral videos in tribute.  Notorious RBG, inspired by the Tumblr that amused the Justice herself and brought to you by its founder and an award-winning feminist journalist, is more than just a love letter. It draws on intimate access to Ginsburg&#8217;s family members, close friends, colleagues, and clerks, as well an interview with the Justice herself.<br />
                    An original hybrid of reported narrative, annotated dissents, rare archival photos and documents, and illustrations, the book tells a never-before-told story of an unusual and transformative woman who transcends generational divides. As the country struggles with the unfinished business of gender equality and civil rights, Ginsburg stands as a testament to how far we can come with a little chutzpah.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/notorious-rbg-the-life-and-times-of-ruth-bader-ginsburg-irin-carmon-shana-knizhnik-abridged/">Notorious RBG : The Life and Times of Ruth Bader Ginsburg &#8211; Irin Carmon, Shana Knizhnik (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tomorrow&#8217;s Lawyers : An Introduction to Your Future &#8211; Richard Susskind (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tomorrows-lawyers-an-introduction-to-your-future-richard-susskind-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advocacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[IT & Communications Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tomorrows-lawyers-an-introduction-to-your-future-richard-susskind-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tomorrow&#8217;s Lawyers predicts that we are at the beginning of a period of fundamental transformation in law: a time in which we will see greater change than we have seen in the past two centuries. Where the future of the legal service will be a world of internet-based global businesses, online document production, commoditized service, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tomorrows-lawyers-an-introduction-to-your-future-richard-susskind-abridged/">Tomorrow&#8217;s Lawyers : An Introduction to Your Future &#8211; Richard Susskind (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tomorrow&#8217;s Lawyers  predicts that we are at the beginning of a period of fundamental transformation in law: a time in which we will see greater change than we have seen in the past two centuries. Where the future of the legal service will be a world of internet-based global businesses, online document production, commoditized service, legal process outsourcing, and web based simulation practice. Legal markets will be liberalized, with new jobs for lawyers<br />
                    and new employers too. This book is a definitive guide to this future &#8211; for young and aspiring lawyers, and for all who want to modernize our legal and justice systems. It introduces the new legal landscape and offers practical guidance for those who intend to build careers and businesses in law.    </p>
<p>                     Tomorrow&#8217;s Lawyers  is divided into three parts. The first is an updated restatement of Richard Susskind&#8217;s views on the future of legal services, as laid out in his previous bestselling works,  The Future of Law ,  Transforming the Law, and  The End of Lawyers? . He identifies key drivers of change, such as the economic downturn, and considers how these will impact on the legal marketplace. In the second part, Susskind sketches out the new legal landscape as<br />
                    he predicts it, including the changing role of law firms, and in-house lawyers, with virtual hearings and online dispute resolution. The third part focuses on the prospects for aspiring lawyers, predicting what new jobs and new employers there will be, and equipping prospective lawyers with penetrating questions to put to their<br />
                    current and future employers.    </p>
<p>                    This new edition has been fully updated to include an introduction to online dispute resolution, Susskind&#8217;s views on the debates surrounding artificial intelligence and its role in the legal world, a new analysis of new jobs available for lawyers, and a retrospective evaluation of The Future of Law  , Susskind&#8217;s prediction published in 1996 about the future of legal services.    </p>
<p>                    This is the essential introduction to the future of law for those who want to succeed in the rapidly changing legal landscape.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tomorrows-lawyers-an-introduction-to-your-future-richard-susskind-abridged/">Tomorrow&#8217;s Lawyers : An Introduction to Your Future &#8211; Richard Susskind (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Unwinding of the Miracle : A Memoir of Life, Death, and Everything That Comes After &#8211; Julie Yip-Williams (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Read with Jenna Book Club Pick as Featured on Today &#8211; As a young mother facing a terminal diagnosis, Julie Yip-Williams began to write her story, a story like no other. What began as the chronicle of an imminent and early death became something much more&#8211;a powerful exhortation to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/">The Unwinding of the Miracle : A Memoir of Life, Death, and Everything That Comes After &#8211; Julie Yip-Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Read with Jenna Book Club Pick as Featured on Today &#8211; As a young mother facing a terminal diagnosis, Julie Yip-Williams began to write her story, a story like no other. What began as the chronicle of an imminent and early death became something much more&#8211;a powerful exhortation to the living.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;An exquisitely moving portrait of the daily stuff of life.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review (Editors&#8217; Choice) NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY The New York Times Book Review &#8211; Time &#8211; Real Simple &#8211; Good Housekeeping  That Julie Yip-Williams survived infancy was a miracle. Born blind in Vietnam, she narrowly escaped euthanasia at the hands of her grandmother, only to flee with her family the political upheaval of her country in the late 1970s. Loaded into a rickety boat with three hundred other refugees, Julie made it to Hong Kong and, ultimately, America, where a surgeon at UCLA gave her partial sight. She would go on to become a Harvard-educated lawyer, with a husband, a family, and a life she had once assumed would be impossible. Then, at age thirty-seven, with two little girls at home, Julie was diagnosed with terminal metastatic colon cancer, and a different journey began.  The Unwinding of the Miracle is the story of a vigorous life refracted through the prism of imminent death. When she was first diagnosed, Julie Yip-Williams sought clarity and guidance through the experience and, finding none, began to write her way through it&#8211;a chronicle that grew beyond her imagining. Motherhood, marriage, the immigrant experience, ambition, love, wanderlust, tennis, fortune-tellers, grief, reincarnation, jealousy, comfort, pain, the marvel of the body in full rebellion&#8211;this book is as sprawling and majestic as the life it records. It is inspiring and instructive, delightful and shattering. It is a book of indelible moments, seared deep&#8211;an incomparable guide to living vividly by facing hard truths consciously.  With humor, bracing honesty, and the cleansing power of well-deployed anger, Julie Yip-Williams set the stage for her lasting legacy and one final miracle: the story of her life. Praise for The Unwinding of the Miracle  &#8220;Everything worth understanding and holding on to is in this book. . . . A miracle indeed.&#8221;&#8211;Kelly Corrigan, New York Times bestselling author &#8220;A beautifully written, moving, and compassionate chronicle that deserves to be read and absorbed widely.&#8221;&#8211;Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/">The Unwinding of the Miracle : A Memoir of Life, Death, and Everything That Comes After &#8211; Julie Yip-Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret Barrister : Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken &#8211; The Secret Barrister (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Law & Procedure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Ethics & Professional Conduct]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times number one bestseller. Winner of the Books are My Bag Non-Fiction Award. Shortlisted for Waterstones Book of the Year. Shortlisted for Specsavers Non-Fiction Book of the Year. You may not wish to think about it, but one day you or someone you love will almost certainly appear in a criminal courtroom. You [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister-abridged/">The Secret Barrister : Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken &#8211; The Secret Barrister (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times number one bestseller.<br />
                    Winner of the Books are My Bag Non-Fiction Award.<br />
                    Shortlisted for Waterstones Book of the Year.<br />
                    Shortlisted for Specsavers Non-Fiction Book of the Year.    </p>
<p>                    You may not wish to think about it, but one day you or someone you love will almost certainly appear in a criminal courtroom. You might be a juror, a victim, a witness or &#8211; perhaps through no fault of your own &#8211; a defendant. Whatever your role, you&#8217;d expect a fair trial.    </p>
<p>                      I&#8217;m a barrister. I work in the criminal justice system, and every day I see how fairness is not guaranteed. Too often the system fails those it is meant to protect. The innocent are wronged and the guilty allowed to walk free.    </p>
<p>                    In The Secret Barrister: Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken I want to share some stories from my daily life to show you how the system is broken, who broke it and why we should start caring before it&#8217;s too late.    </p>
<p>                    A Sunday Times top ten bestseller for twenty-four weeks.<br />
                    &#8216;Eye-opening, funny and horrifying&#8217; &#8211; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Everyone who has any interest in public life should read it&#8217; &#8211; Daily Mail</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister-abridged/">The Secret Barrister : Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken &#8211; The Secret Barrister (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
