<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>World War 2 Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/world-war-2-books/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/world-war-2-books/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>World War 2 Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/world-war-2-books/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Born Survivors : The incredible true story of three pregnant mothers and their courage and determination to survive in the concentration camps &#8211; Wendy Holden</title>
		<link>/born-survivors-the-incredible-true-story-of-three-pregnant-mothers-and-their-courage-and-determination-to-survive-in-the-concentration-camps-wendy-holden/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holocaust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/born-survivors-the-incredible-true-story-of-three-pregnant-mothers-and-their-courage-and-determination-to-survive-in-the-concentration-camps-wendy-holden/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller now updated with a new foreword Among millions of Holocaust victims sent to Auschwitz II-Birkenau in 1944, Priska, Rachel, and Anka each passed through its infamous gates with a secret. Strangers to each other, they were newly pregnant, and facing an uncertain fate without their husbands. Alone, scared, and with so [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/born-survivors-the-incredible-true-story-of-three-pregnant-mothers-and-their-courage-and-determination-to-survive-in-the-concentration-camps-wendy-holden/">Born Survivors : The incredible true story of three pregnant mothers and their courage and determination to survive in the concentration camps &#8211; Wendy Holden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller now updated with a new foreword</p>
<p>                    Among millions of Holocaust victims sent to Auschwitz II-Birkenau in 1944, Priska, Rachel, and Anka each passed through its infamous gates with a secret. Strangers to each other, they were newly pregnant, and facing an uncertain fate without their husbands. Alone, scared, and with so many loved ones already lost to the Nazis, these young women were privately determined to hold on to all they had left: their lives, and those of their unborn babies.</p>
<p>                    That the gas chambers ran out of Zyklon-B just after the babies were born, before they and their mothers could be exterminated, is just one of several miracles that allowed them all to survive and rebuild their lives after World War II. Born Survivors follows the mothers&#8217; incredible journey &#8211; first to Auschwitz, where they each came under the murderous scrutiny of Dr. Josef Mengele; then to a German slave labour camp where, half-starved and almost worked to death, they struggled to conceal their condition; and finally, as the Allies closed in, their hellish 17-day train journey with thousands of other prisoners to the Mauthausen death camp in Austria. Hundreds died along the way but the courage and kindness of strangers, including guards and civilians, helped save these women and their children.</p>
<p>                    Sixty-five years later, the three &#8216;miracle babies&#8217; met for the first time at Mauthausen for the anniversary of the liberation that ultimately saved them. United by their remarkable experiences of survival against all odds, they now consider each other &#8220;siblings of the heart.&#8221; In Born Survivors, Wendy Holden brings all three stories together for the first time to mark their seventieth birthdays and the seventieth anniversary of the ending of the war.</p>
<p>                    A heart-stopping account of how three mothers and their newborns fought to survive the Holocaust, Born Survivors is also a life-affirming celebration of our capacity to care and to love amid inconceivable cruelty.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/born-survivors-the-incredible-true-story-of-three-pregnant-mothers-and-their-courage-and-determination-to-survive-in-the-concentration-camps-wendy-holden/">Born Survivors : The incredible true story of three pregnant mothers and their courage and determination to survive in the concentration camps &#8211; Wendy Holden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stalingrad &#8211; Antony Beevor</title>
		<link>/stalingrad-antony-beevor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Battles & Campaigns]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stalingrad-antony-beevor/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The classic international million copy bestseller recounting the epic turning point of the second world war In October 1942, a Panzer officer wrote &#8216;Stalingrad is no longer a town&#8230; Animals flee this hell; the hardest stones cannot bear it for long; only men endure&#8217;. The battle for Stalingrad became the focus of Hitler and Stalin&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stalingrad-antony-beevor/">Stalingrad &#8211; Antony Beevor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The classic international million copy bestseller recounting the epic turning point of the second world war</p>
<p>                    In October 1942, a Panzer officer wrote &#8216;Stalingrad is no longer a town&#8230; Animals flee this hell; the hardest stones cannot bear it for long; only men endure&#8217;. </p>
<p>                    The battle for Stalingrad became the focus of Hitler and Stalin&#8217;s determination to win the gruesome, vicious war on the eastern front. The citizens of Stalingrad endured unimaginable hardship; the battle, with fierce hand-to-hand fighting in each room of each building,  was brutally destructive to both armies. But the eventual victory of the Red Army, and the failure of Hitler&#8217;s Operation Barbarossa, was the first defeat of Hitler&#8217;s territorial ambitions in Europe, and the start of his decline.</p>
<p>                    An extraordinary story of tactical genius, civilian bravery and the nature of war itself, which changed how history is written, Stalingrad is a testament to the vital role of the Soviet war effort.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A superb re-telling. Beevor combines a soldier&#8217;s understanding of war&#8217;s realities with the narrative techniques of a novelist . . . This is a book that lets the reader look into the face of battle&#8217; Orlando Figes, Sunday Telegraph </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A brilliantly researched tour de force of military history&#8217; Sarah Bradford, The Times</p>
<p>                    Antony Beevor is the renowned author of Stalingrad, which won the Samuel Johnson Prize, the Wolfson Prize for History and the Hawthornden Prize for Literature, and Berlin, which received the first Longman-History Today Trustees&#8217; Award. His books have sold nearly four million copies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stalingrad-antony-beevor/">Stalingrad &#8211; Antony Beevor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bomber Command: Reflections of War: Live to Die Another Day (June 1942 &#8211; Summer 1943) &#8211; Martin Bowman</title>
		<link>/bomber-command-reflections-of-war-live-to-die-another-day-june-1942-summer-1943-martin-bowman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Air Forces & Warfare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bomber-command-reflections-of-war-live-to-die-another-day-june-1942-summer-1943-martin-bowman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This massive work provides a comprehensive insight to the experiences of Bomber Commands pilots and aircrew throughout World War Two. From the early wartime years when the RAFs first attempts to avenge Germanys onslaught were bedeviled by poor navigation and inaccurate bombing, to the final winning onslaught that finally tamed Hitler in his Berlin lair, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bomber-command-reflections-of-war-live-to-die-another-day-june-1942-summer-1943-martin-bowman/">Bomber Command: Reflections of War: Live to Die Another Day (June 1942 &#8211; Summer 1943) &#8211; Martin Bowman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This massive work provides a comprehensive insight to the experiences of Bomber Commands pilots and aircrew throughout World War Two. From the early wartime years when the RAFs first attempts to avenge Germanys onslaught were bedeviled by poor navigation and inaccurate bombing, to the final winning onslaught that finally tamed Hitler in his Berlin lair, these volumes trace the true experiences of the men who flew the bombers. Hundreds of first-hand accounts are punctuated by the authors background information that put each narrative into wartime perspective. Every aspect of Bomber Commands operational duties are covered; day and night bombing, precision low-level strikes, mass raids and operations throughout all wartime theaters. Contributions are from RAF personnel who flew the commands different aircraft from the early Blenheims and Stirlings to the later Lancasters and Mosquitoes. Each volume is full of accounts that tell of the camaraderie amongst the crews, moments of sheer terror and the stoic humor that provided the critical bond. The five volumes of this work provide the most vivid and comprehensive work on the outstanding part played by RAF Bomber Command in their vital role in the destruction of the Third Reich.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bomber-command-reflections-of-war-live-to-die-another-day-june-1942-summer-1943-martin-bowman/">Bomber Command: Reflections of War: Live to Die Another Day (June 1942 &#8211; Summer 1943) &#8211; Martin Bowman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bombs Away : The Story of a Bomber Team &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/bombs-away-the-story-of-a-bomber-team-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bombs-away-the-story-of-a-bomber-team-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A magnificent volume of short novels and an essential World War II report from one of America&#8217;s great twentieth-century writers A Penguin Classic On the heels of the enormous success of his masterwork The Grapes of Wrath and at the height of the American war effort John Steinbeck, one of the most prolific and influential [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bombs-away-the-story-of-a-bomber-team-john-steinbeck/">Bombs Away : The Story of a Bomber Team &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A magnificent volume of short novels and an essential World War II report from one of America&#8217;s great twentieth-century writers </p>
<p>                    A Penguin Classic </p>
<p>                    On the heels of the enormous success of his masterwork The Grapes of Wrath and at the height of the American war effort John Steinbeck, one of the most prolific and influential literary figures of his generation, wrote Bombs Away, a nonfiction account of his experiences with U.S. Army Air Force bomber crews during World War II. Now, for the first time since its original publication in 1942, Penguin Classics presents this exclusive edition of Steinbeck&#8217;s introduction to the then-nascent U.S. Army Air Force and its bomber crew&#8211;the essential core unit behind American air power that Steinbeck described as the greatest team in the world. </p>
<p>                    For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bombs-away-the-story-of-a-bomber-team-john-steinbeck/">Bombs Away : The Story of a Bomber Team &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Battle for Spain : The Spanish Civil War 1936-1939 &#8211; Antony Beevor</title>
		<link>/the-battle-for-spain-the-spanish-civil-war-1936-1939-antony-beevor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spanish Civil War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-battle-for-spain-the-spanish-civil-war-1936-1939-antony-beevor/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of STALINGRAD and BERLIN: THE DOWNFALL on the Spanish Civil War, drawing on masses of newly discovered material from the Spanish, Russian and German archives. The civil war that tore Spain apart between 1936 and 1939 and attracted liberals and socialists from across the world to support the cause against Franco was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-battle-for-spain-the-spanish-civil-war-1936-1939-antony-beevor/">The Battle for Spain : The Spanish Civil War 1936-1939 &#8211; Antony Beevor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of STALINGRAD and BERLIN: THE DOWNFALL on the Spanish Civil War, drawing on masses of newly discovered material from the Spanish, Russian and German archives.    </p>
<p>                    The civil war that tore Spain apart between 1936 and 1939 and attracted liberals and socialists from across the world to support the cause against Franco was one of the most hard-fought and bitterest conflicts of the 20th century: a war of atrocities and political genocide and a military testing ground before WWII for the Russians, Italians and Germans, whose Condor Legion so notoriously destroyed Guernica.    </p>
<p>                    Antony Beevor&#8217;s account narrates the origins of the Civil War and its violent and dramatic course from the coup d&#8217;etat in July 1936 through the savage fighting of the next three years which ended in catastrophic defeat for the Republicans in 1939. And he succeeds especially well in unravelling the complex political and regional forces that played such an important part in the origins and history of the war.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-battle-for-spain-the-spanish-civil-war-1936-1939-antony-beevor/">The Battle for Spain : The Spanish Civil War 1936-1939 &#8211; Antony Beevor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>SAS Italian Job : The Secret Mission to Storm a Forbidden Nazi Fortress &#8211; Damien Lewis</title>
		<link>/sas-italian-job-the-secret-mission-to-storm-a-forbidden-nazi-fortress-damien-lewis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[War & Defence Operations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sas-italian-job-the-secret-mission-to-storm-a-forbidden-nazi-fortress-damien-lewis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Sunday Times No.1 bestselling author Damien Lewis&#8217; SAS mission series: &#8216;One of the great untold stories of WWII&#8217; &#8211; Bear Grylls on SAS Ghost Patrol &#8216;The untold story&#8217; &#8211; Daily Mail on SAS Nazi Hunters &#8216;A tale of bravery against desperate odds&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Times on Churchill&#8217;s Secret Warriors &#8216;True adventures laced with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sas-italian-job-the-secret-mission-to-storm-a-forbidden-nazi-fortress-damien-lewis/">SAS Italian Job : The Secret Mission to Storm a Forbidden Nazi Fortress &#8211; Damien Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Praise for Sunday Times No.1 bestselling author Damien Lewis&#8217; SAS mission series:</p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the great untold stories of WWII&#8217; &#8211; Bear Grylls on SAS Ghost Patrol</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The untold story&#8217; &#8211; Daily Mail on SAS Nazi Hunters</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A tale of bravery against desperate odds&#8217; &#8211; Sunday Times on Churchill&#8217;s Secret Warriors</p>
<p>                    &#8216;True adventures laced with staggering bravery and sacrifice&#8217; &#8211; Sun on Hunting the Nazi Bomb</p>
<p>                    An impossible mission in wartime Italy: the next explosive bestseller from Damien Lewis.</p>
<p>                    In the hard-fought winter of 1944 the Allies advanced northwards through Italy, but stalled on the fearsome mountainous defences of the Gothic Line. Two men were parachuted in, in an effort to break the deadlock. Their mission: to penetrate deep into enemy territory and lay waste to the Germans&#8217; impregnable headquarters.</p>
<p>                    At the eleventh hour mission commanders radioed for David &#8216;The Mad Piper&#8217; Kilpatrick to be flown in, resplendent in his tartan kilt. They wanted this fearless war hero to lead the assault, piping Highland Laddie as he went &#8211; so leaving an indelible British signature to deter Nazi reprisals.</p>
<p>                    As the column of raiders formed up, there was shocking news. High command radioed through an order to stand down, having assessed the chances of success at little more than zero. But in defiance of orders, and come hell or high-water, they were going in.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sas-italian-job-the-secret-mission-to-storm-a-forbidden-nazi-fortress-damien-lewis/">SAS Italian Job : The Secret Mission to Storm a Forbidden Nazi Fortress &#8211; Damien Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Once There Was a War &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/once-there-was-a-war-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/once-there-was-a-war-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic &#8220;Age can never dull this kind of writing,&#8221; writes the Chicago Tribune of John Steinbeck&#8217;s dispatches from World War II, filed for the New York Herald Tribune in 1943, which vividly captured the human side of war. Writing from England in the midst of the London blitz, North Africa, and Italy, Steinbeck [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/once-there-was-a-war-john-steinbeck/">Once There Was a War &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Age can never dull this kind of writing,&#8221; writes the Chicago Tribune of John Steinbeck&#8217;s dispatches from World War II, filed for the New York Herald Tribune in 1943, which vividly captured the human side of war. Writing from England in the midst of the London blitz, North Africa, and Italy, Steinbeck focuses on the people as opposed to the battles, portraying everyone from the guys in the bomber crew to Bob Hope on his USO tour. He eats and drinks with soldiers behind enemy lines, talks with them, and fights beside them. First published in book form in 1958, these writings, now with a new introduction by Mark Bowden, create an unforgettable portrait of life in wartime that continues to resonate with truth and humanity.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/once-there-was-a-war-john-steinbeck/">Once There Was a War &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Killing the Rising Sun : How America Vanquished World War II Japan &#8211; Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Martin Dugard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/killing-the-rising-sun-how-america-vanquished-world-war-ii-japan-bill-oreilly-martin-dugard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/killing-the-rising-sun-how-america-vanquished-world-war-ii-japan-bill-oreilly-martin-dugard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The powerful and riveting new book in the multimillion-selling Killing series by Bill O&#8217;Reilly and Martin Dugard Autumn 1944. World War II is nearly over in Europe but is escalating in the Pacific, where American soldiers face an opponent who will go to any length to avoid defeat. The Japanese army follows the samurai code [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/killing-the-rising-sun-how-america-vanquished-world-war-ii-japan-bill-oreilly-martin-dugard-abridged/">Killing the Rising Sun : How America Vanquished World War II Japan &#8211; Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Martin Dugard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The powerful and riveting new book in the multimillion-selling Killing series by Bill O&#8217;Reilly and Martin Dugard     </p>
<p>                    Autumn 1944. World War II is nearly over in Europe but is escalating in the Pacific, where American soldiers face an opponent who will go to any length to avoid defeat. The Japanese army follows the samurai code of Bushido, stipulating that surrender is a form of dishonor. Killing the Rising Sun takes readers to the bloody tropical-island battlefields of Peleliu and Iwo Jima and to the embattled Philippines, where General Douglas MacArthur has made a triumphant return and is plotting a full-scale invasion of Japan.     </p>
<p>                    Across the globe in Los Alamos, New Mexico, Dr. J. Robert Oppenheimer and his team of scientists are preparing to test the deadliest weapon known to mankind. In Washington, DC, FDR dies in office and Harry Truman ascends to the presidency, only to face the most important political decision in history: whether to use that weapon. And in Tokyo, Emperor Hirohito, who is considered a deity by his subjects, refuses to surrender, despite a massive and mounting death toll. Told in the same page-turning style of Killing Lincoln, Killing Kennedy, Killing Jesus, Killing Patton, and Killing Reagan, this epic saga details the final moments of World War II like never before.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/killing-the-rising-sun-how-america-vanquished-world-war-ii-japan-bill-oreilly-martin-dugard-abridged/">Killing the Rising Sun : How America Vanquished World War II Japan &#8211; Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Martin Dugard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Seventh Million : The Israelis and the Holocaust &#8211; Tom Segev, Translated by Professor Haim Watzman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-seventh-million-the-israelis-and-the-holocaust-tom-segev-translated-by-professor-haim-watzman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holocaust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-seventh-million-the-israelis-and-the-holocaust-tom-segev-translated-by-professor-haim-watzman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Seventh Million is the first book to show the decisive impact of the Holocaust on the identity, ideology, and politics of Israel. Drawing on diaries, interviews, and thousands of declassified documents, Segev reconsiders the major struggles and personalities of Israel&#8217;s past, including Ben-Gurion, Begin, and Nahum Goldmann, and argues that the nation&#8217;s legacy has, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-million-the-israelis-and-the-holocaust-tom-segev-translated-by-professor-haim-watzman-abridged/">The Seventh Million : The Israelis and the Holocaust &#8211; Tom Segev, Translated by Professor Haim Watzman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Seventh Million is the first book to show the decisive impact of the Holocaust on the identity, ideology, and politics of Israel. Drawing on diaries, interviews, and thousands of declassified documents, Segev reconsiders the major struggles and personalities of Israel&#8217;s past, including Ben-Gurion, Begin, and Nahum Goldmann, and argues that the nation&#8217;s legacy has, at critical moments&#8211;the Exodus affair, the Eichmann trial, the case of John Demjanjuk&#8211;have been molded and manipulated in accordance with the ideological requirements of the state. The Seventh Million uncovers a vast and complex story and reveals how the bitter events of decades past continue to shape the experiences not just of individuals but of a nation. Translated by Haim Watzman.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-million-the-israelis-and-the-holocaust-tom-segev-translated-by-professor-haim-watzman-abridged/">The Seventh Million : The Israelis and the Holocaust &#8211; Tom Segev, Translated by Professor Haim Watzman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Woman of No Importance : The Untold Story of Virginia Hall, WWII&#8217;s Most Dangerous Spy &#8211; Sonia Purnell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-woman-of-no-importance-the-untold-story-of-virginia-hall-wwiis-most-dangerous-spy-sonia-purnell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-woman-of-no-importance-the-untold-story-of-virginia-hall-wwiis-most-dangerous-spy-sonia-purnell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A METICULOUS HISTORY THAT READS LIKE A THRILLER&#8217; BEN MACINTYRE, TEN BEST BOOKS TO READ ABOUT WORLD WAR II An astounding story of heroism, spycraft, resistance and personal triumph over shocking adversity. &#8216;A rousing tale of derring-do&#8217; THE TIMES * &#8216;Riveting&#8217; MICK HERRON * &#8216;Superb&#8217; IRISH TIMES THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER In September 1941, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-woman-of-no-importance-the-untold-story-of-virginia-hall-wwiis-most-dangerous-spy-sonia-purnell-abridged/">A Woman of No Importance : The Untold Story of Virginia Hall, WWII&#8217;s Most Dangerous Spy &#8211; Sonia Purnell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A METICULOUS HISTORY THAT READS LIKE A THRILLER&#8217; BEN MACINTYRE, TEN BEST BOOKS TO READ ABOUT WORLD WAR II    </p>
<p>                        An astounding story of heroism, spycraft, resistance and personal triumph over shocking adversity.    </p>
<p>                       &#8216;A rousing tale of derring-do&#8217; THE TIMES   *   &#8216;Riveting&#8217; MICK HERRON   *   &#8216;Superb&#8217; IRISH TIMES    </p>
<p>                                                                           THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    In September 1941, a young American woman strides up the steps of a hotel in Lyon, Vichy France. Her papers say she is a journalist. Her wooden leg is disguised by a determined gait and a distracting beauty. She is there to spark the resistance.    </p>
<p>                    By 1942 Virginia Hall was the Gestapo&#8217;s most urgent target, having infiltrated Vichy command, trained civilians in guerrilla warfare and sprung soldiers from Nazi prison camps. The first woman to go undercover for British SOE, her intelligence changed the course of the war &#8211; but her fight was still not over.     </p>
<p>                    This is a spy history like no other, telling the story of the hunting accident that disabled her, the discrimination she fought and the secret life that helped her triumph over shocking adversity.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A cracking story about an extraordinarily brave woman&#8217; TELEGRAPH    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Gripping &#8230; superb &#8230; a rounded portrait of a complicated, resourceful, determined and above all brave woman&#8217; IRISH TIMES    </p>
<p>                    WINNER of the PLUTARCH AWARD FOR BEST BIOGRAPHY</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-woman-of-no-importance-the-untold-story-of-virginia-hall-wwiis-most-dangerous-spy-sonia-purnell-abridged/">A Woman of No Importance : The Untold Story of Virginia Hall, WWII&#8217;s Most Dangerous Spy &#8211; Sonia Purnell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
