<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Industry &amp; Industrial Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/industry-industrial-studies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/industry-industrial-studies/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Industry &amp; Industrial Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/industry-industrial-studies/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: The Elderly]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pensions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface* Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time? Many of us have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*A new edition of the international bestseller (a #1 bestseller in Japan), featuring a new preface*    </p>
<p>                    Does the thought of working for 60 or 70 years fill you with dread? Or can you see the potential for a more stimulating future as a result of having so much extra time?     </p>
<p>                    Many of us have been raised on the traditional notion of a three-stage approach to our working lives: education, followed by work and then retirement.  But this well-established pathway is already beginning to collapse &#8211; life expectancy is rising, final-salary pensions are vanishing, and increasing numbers of people are juggling multiple careers. Whether you are 18, 45 or 60, you will need to do things very differently from previous generations and learn to structure your life in completely new ways.    </p>
<p>                    The 100-Year Life is here to help.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the unique pairing of their experience in psychology and economics, Lynda Gratton and Andrew J. Scott offer a broad-ranging analysis as well as a raft of solutions, showing how to rethink your finances, your education, your career and your relationships and create a fulfilling 100-year life.     </p>
<p>                    * How can you fashion a career and life path that defines you and your values and creates a shifting balance between work and leisure?    </p>
<p>                    * What are the most effective ways of boosting your physical and mental health over a longer and more dynamic lifespan?    </p>
<p>                    * How can you make the most of your intangible assets &#8211; such as family and friends &#8211; as you build a productive, longer life?    </p>
<p>                    * In a multiple-stage life how can you learn to make the transitions that will be so crucial and experiment with new ways of living, working and learning?    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award and featuring a new preface, The 100-Year Life is a wake-up call that describes what to expect and considers the choices and options that you will face. It is also fundamentally a call to action for individuals, politicians, firms and governments and offers the clearest demonstration that a 100-year life can be a wonderful and inspiring one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-100-year-life-living-and-working-in-an-age-of-longevity-lynda-gratton-andrew-j-scott-abridged/">The 100-Year Life : Living and Working in an Age of Longevity &#8211; Lynda Gratton, Andrew J. Scott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ta-Ra-Ra-Boom-De-Ay : The dodgy business of popular music &#8211; Simon Napier-Bell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ta-ra-ra-boom-de-ay-the-dodgy-business-of-popular-music-simon-napier-bell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music Reviews & Criticism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ta-ra-ra-boom-de-ay-the-dodgy-business-of-popular-music-simon-napier-bell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Legendary rock manager Simon Napier-Bell take you inside the (dodgy) world of popular music &#8211; not just a creative industry, but a business that has made people rich beyond their wildest dreams. He balances seductive anecdotes &#8211; pulling back the curtain on the gritty and absurd side of the industry &#8211; with an insightful exploration [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ta-ra-ra-boom-de-ay-the-dodgy-business-of-popular-music-simon-napier-bell-abridged/">Ta-Ra-Ra-Boom-De-Ay : The dodgy business of popular music &#8211; Simon Napier-Bell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Legendary rock manager Simon Napier-Bell take you inside the (dodgy) world of popular music &#8211; not just a creative industry, but a business that has made people rich beyond their wildest dreams. He balances seductive anecdotes &#8211; pulling back the curtain on the gritty and absurd side of the industry &#8211; with an insightful exploration of the relationship between creativity and money. This book describes the evolution of the industry from 1713 &#8211; the year parliament granted writers ownership over what they wrote &#8211; to today, when a global, 100 billion pound industry is controlled by just three major players: Sony, Universal and Warner. Inside you will uncover some little-known facts about the industry, including:     </p>
<p>                    How a formula for writing hit songs in the 1900s helped create 50,000 of the best-known songs of all time<br />
                    How infighting in the American pre-war music industry shut down traditional radio and created an opening for country music, race records and rock&#8217;n&#8217;roll<br />
                    How Jewish immigrants and black jazz musicians dancing cheek-to-cheek created a template for all popular music that followed<br />
                    How rock tours became the biggest, quickest, sleaziest and most profitable ventures the music industry has ever seen<br />
                    After reading Ta-Ra-Ra-Boom-De-Ay, you&#8217;ll never listen to music in the same way again</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ta-ra-ra-boom-de-ay-the-dodgy-business-of-popular-music-simon-napier-bell-abridged/">Ta-Ra-Ra-Boom-De-Ay : The dodgy business of popular music &#8211; Simon Napier-Bell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Spider Network : The Wild Story of a Maths Genius and One of the Greatest Scams in Financial History &#8211; David Enrich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fraud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times Business Book of the Year! &#8216;Will snare you in its web of deceit &#8230; A brilliant investigative expose&#8217; &#8211; Harlan Coben, bestselling thriller author &#8216;Reads like a fast-paced John le Carre thriller, and never lets up&#8217; &#8211; New York Times book review The Spider Network is the almost-unbelievable and darkly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/">The Spider Network : The Wild Story of a Maths Genius and One of the Greatest Scams in Financial History &#8211; David Enrich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times Business Book of the Year!    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Will snare you in its web of deceit &#8230; A brilliant investigative expose&#8217; &#8211; Harlan Coben, bestselling thriller author     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Reads like a fast-paced John le Carre thriller, and never lets up&#8217; &#8211; New York Times book review     </p>
<p>                    The Spider Network is the almost-unbelievable and darkly entertaining inside account of the Libor scandal &#8211; one of the biggest, farthest-reaching financial scams since the global financial crisis &#8211; written by the only journalist with access to Tom Hayes before he was sentenced to fourteen years in prison.   Full of exclusive details, and with ramifications that stretch right across the British establishment, this is a gripping, real-life story of outlandish characters and reckless greed in the City of London.     </p>
<p>                    By turns a rollicking account of the scandal and also a provocative examination of a financial system that was crooked throughout, The Spider Network is a perfect read for fans of The Wolf of Wall Street and The Big Short.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/">The Spider Network : The Wild Story of a Maths Genius and One of the Greatest Scams in Financial History &#8211; David Enrich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Other Technologies & Applied Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TheNew York Timesbestselling &#8220;manifesto for the future that is grounded in practical solutions addressing the world&#8217;s most pressing concerns: overpopulation, food, water, energy, education, health care and freedom&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal). Since the dawn of humanity, a privileged few have lived in stark contrast to the hardscrabble majority. Conventional wisdom says this gap cannot [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/">Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TheNew York Timesbestselling &#8220;manifesto for the future that is grounded in practical solutions addressing the world&#8217;s most pressing concerns: overpopulation, food, water, energy, education, health care and freedom&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).     </p>
<p>                    Since the dawn of humanity, a privileged few have lived in stark contrast to the hardscrabble majority. Conventional wisdom says this gap cannot be closed. But it is closing-fast.     </p>
<p>                    InAbundance, space entrepreneur turned innovation pioneer Peter H. Diamandis and award-winning science writer Steven Kotler document how progress in artificial intelligence, robotics, digital manufacturing synthetic biology, and other exponentially growing technologies will enable us to make greater gains in the next two decades than we have in the previous 200 years. We will soon have the ability to meet and exceed the basic needs of every person on the planet. Abundance for all is within our grasp.     </p>
<p>                    Breaking down human needs by category-water, food, energy, healthcare, education, freedom-Diamandis and Kotler introduce us to innovators and industry captains making tremendous strides in each area. &#8220;Not only isAbundancea riveting page-turner&#8230;but it&#8217;s a book that gives us a future worth fighting for. And even more than that, it shows us our place in that fight&#8221; (The Christian Science Monitor).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/">Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Human/Machine : The Future of our Partnership with Machines &#8211; Daniel Newman, Olivier Blanchard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Will the workplace of the future be overrun by machines and robots? Are the new frontiers of artificial intelligence (AI) on the cusp of dethroning us in efficiency, intelligence and innovative potential? Automation and AI will augment our human world and potential. The winners of the future of work are those that harness the power [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/">Human/Machine : The Future of our Partnership with Machines &#8211; Daniel Newman, Olivier Blanchard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Will the workplace of the future be overrun by machines and robots? Are the new frontiers of artificial intelligence (AI) on the cusp of dethroning us in efficiency, intelligence and innovative potential? Automation and AI will augment our human world and potential.     </p>
<p>                    The winners of the future of work are those that harness the power of machines to their advantage. Human/Machine is the only guide you need to understand the fourth industrial revolution. It sets out a road map to the challenges ahead, but also unlocks the wondrous opportunities that it offers.     </p>
<p>                    Human/Machine explores how we will work symbiotically with machines, detailing how institutions, companies, individuals and education providers will evolve to integrate seamlessly with new technologies. With exclusive case studies, this book offers a glimpse into the future and details how top companies are already thriving on this very special relationship. From gamification in job training to project management teams integrated with bots and predictive technologies that fix problems in the supply chain before they happen, the authors deliver a powerful manifesto for the adoption and celebration of automation and AI. In a much more fluid, skills-based economy, we will all need to prove our worth and future-proof our skills base. This book offers a blueprint to avoid being left behind and unearth the opportunities unique to human-machine partnership ecosystems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/">Human/Machine : The Future of our Partnership with Machines &#8211; Daniel Newman, Olivier Blanchard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vaporized : Solid Strategies for Success in a Dematerialized World &#8211; Robert Tercek, Foreword by Nicholas Negroponte (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/vaporized-solid-strategies-for-success-in-a-dematerialized-world-robert-tercek-foreword-by-nicholas-negroponte-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/vaporized-solid-strategies-for-success-in-a-dematerialized-world-robert-tercek-foreword-by-nicholas-negroponte-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If you&#8217;re in the information business (and we all are in the information business), Tercek&#8217;s urgent manifesto will help you see the future, so you can prepare for it.&#8221; &#8211; Seth Godin Brace yourself for enormous changes ahead. Familiar fixtures of the economic landscape, including retail stores, physical products, corporations and even human workers, are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vaporized-solid-strategies-for-success-in-a-dematerialized-world-robert-tercek-foreword-by-nicholas-negroponte-abridged/">Vaporized : Solid Strategies for Success in a Dematerialized World &#8211; Robert Tercek, Foreword by Nicholas Negroponte (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;If you&#8217;re in the information business (and we all are in the information business), Tercek&#8217;s urgent manifesto will help you see the future, so you can prepare for it.&#8221; &#8211; Seth Godin    </p>
<p>                    Brace yourself for enormous changes ahead. Familiar fixtures of the economic landscape, including retail stores, physical products, corporations and even human workers, are about to be vaporized-replaced by digital information.     </p>
<p>                    A novel combination of new technologies-  mobile, cloud, crowd, artificial intelligence &#8212; are reconfiguring every economic sector and industrial system on the planet. Even industries that were long considered immune to digital transformation are suddenly vulnerable to rapid dematerialization: now automobiles, hotels, health care, and higher education can be replaced by an app-enabled marketplace.    </p>
<p>                    The process of vaporization is relentless and all-pervasive. For consumers this change is as bewildering as it is exhilarating.  For CEOs of old-school firms, the change is terrifying.  But for startup Internet companies, it&#8217;s the greatest landgrab since the Gold Rush.    </p>
<p>                    In Vaporized, innovation expert Robert Tercek shows us how this process works and takes us to the front line of digital transformation. Tercek provides an essential guide to this vaporized world, with proven strategies for those who want to master the process.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vaporized-solid-strategies-for-success-in-a-dematerialized-world-robert-tercek-foreword-by-nicholas-negroponte-abridged/">Vaporized : Solid Strategies for Success in a Dematerialized World &#8211; Robert Tercek, Foreword by Nicholas Negroponte (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since his New York Times op-ed column debuted in 2011, Mark Bittman has emerged as one of our most impassioned and opinionated observers of the food landscape. The Times&#8217; only dedicated opinion columnist covering the food beat, Bittman routinely makes readers think twice about how the food we eat is produced, distributed, and cooked, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/">A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since his New York Times op-ed column debuted in 2011, Mark Bittman has emerged as one of our most impassioned and opinionated observers of the food landscape. The Times&#8217; only dedicated opinion columnist covering the food beat, Bittman routinely makes readers think twice about how the food we eat is produced, distributed, and cooked, and shines a bright light on the profound impact that diet&#8211;both good and bad&#8211;can have on our health and that of the planet.     </p>
<p>                     In A Bone to Pick, Mark&#8217;s most memorable and thought-provoking columns are compiled into a single volume for the first time. As abundant and safe as the American food supply appears to be, the state of our health reveals the presence of staggering deficiencies in both the system that produces food and the forces that regulate it. Bittman leaves no issue unexamined; agricultural practices, government legislation, fad diets, and corporate greed all come under scrutiny and show that the issues governing what ends up in our market basket and on our tables are both complex and often deliberately confusing. Unabashedly opinionated and invariably thought provoking, Bittman&#8217;s columns have helped readers decipher arcane policy, unpack scientific studies, and deflate affronts to common sense when it comes to determining what &#8220;eating well&#8221; truly means. As urgent as the situation is, Mark contends that we can be optimistic about the future of our food and its impact on our health, as slow-food movements, better school-lunch programs, and even &#8220;healthy fast food&#8221; become part of the norm.     </p>
<p>                     At once inspiring, enraging, and enlightening, A Bone to Pick is an essential resource for every reader eager to understand not only the complexities inherent in the American food system, but also the many opportunities that exist to improve it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/">A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Industries of the Future &#8211; Alec Ross (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-industries-of-the-future-alec-ross-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-industries-of-the-future-alec-ross-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book answers the question: &#8216;What&#8217;s next?&#8217; The Internet had a world-changing impact on businesses and the global community over the twenty years from 1994 to 2014. In the next ten years, change will happen even faster. As Hillary Clinton&#8217;s Senior Advisor for Innovation, Alec Ross travelled nearly a million miles to forty-one countries, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-industries-of-the-future-alec-ross-abridged/">The Industries of the Future &#8211; Alec Ross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book answers the question: &#8216;What&#8217;s next?&#8217; The Internet had a world-changing impact on businesses and the global community over the twenty years from 1994 to 2014. In the next ten years, change will happen even faster.     </p>
<p>                    As Hillary Clinton&#8217;s Senior Advisor for Innovation, Alec Ross travelled nearly a million miles to forty-one countries, the equivalent of two round-trips to the moon. From refugee camps in the Congo and Syrian war zones, to visiting the world&#8217;s most powerful people in business and government, Ross&#8217;s travels amounted to a four-year masterclass in the changing nature of innovation.     </p>
<p>                    In The Industries of the Future, Ross distils his observations on the forces that are changing the world. He highlights the best opportunities for progress and explains how countries thrive or sputter. Ross examines the specific fields that will most shape our economic future over the next ten years, including robotics, artificial intelligence, the commercialization of genomics, cybercrime and the impact of digital technology.     </p>
<p>                    Blending storytelling and economic analysis, he answers questions on how we will need to adapt. Ross gives readers a vivid and informed perspective on how sweeping global trends are affecting the ways we live, now and tomorrow.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-industries-of-the-future-alec-ross-abridged/">The Industries of the Future &#8211; Alec Ross (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alibaba : The House That Jack Ma Built &#8211; Duncan Clark (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An engrossing, insider&#8217;s account of how a teacher built one of the world&#8217;s most valuable companies-rivaling Walmart and Amazon-and forever reshaped the global economy In just a decade and a half, Jack Ma, a man from modest beginnings who started out as an English teacher, founded Alibaba and built it into one of the world&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/">Alibaba : The House That Jack Ma Built &#8211; Duncan Clark (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An engrossing, insider&#8217;s account of how a teacher built one of the world&#8217;s most valuable companies-rivaling Walmart and Amazon-and forever reshaped the global economy  In just a decade and a half, Jack Ma, a man from modest beginnings who started out as an English teacher, founded Alibaba and built it into one of the world&#8217;s largest companies, an e-commerce empire on which hundreds of millions of Chinese consumers depend. In 2014, Alibaba&#8217;s $25 billion IPO was the largest global IPO in history. A Rockefeller of his time, who is courted by CEOs and presidents around the world, Jack is an icon for China&#8217;s booming private sector and the gatekeeper to hundreds of millions of middle-class consumers. Duncan Clark first met Jack in 1999 in the small apartment where Jack founded Alibaba. Granted unprecedented access to a wealth of new material, including exclusive interviews, Clark draws on his own experience as an early adviser to Alibaba as well as his two decades in China chronicling the Internet&#8217;s impact on the country to create an authoritative, compelling narrative account of Alibaba&#8217;s rise.<br />
                    How did Jack overcome his humble origins and early failures to achieve massive success with Alibaba? How did he outsmart rival entrepreneurs from both China and Silicon Valley? Can Alibaba maintain its 80 percent market share? As it forges ahead into finance and entertainment, are there limits to Alibaba&#8217;s ambitions? How does the Chinese government view its rise? Will Alibaba expand farther overseas, including into the United States?  Clark tells Alibaba&#8217;s tale in the context of China&#8217;s momentous economic and social changes, illuminating an unlikely corporate titan as never before.  Advance Praise For Alibaba  &#8220;Anybody who thinks the Chinese just copy or steal technology from the West should read this book and think again. Jack Ma is part Bill Gates, part Steve Jobs, part Larry Page, part Sergey Brin, and part Mark Zuckerberg, all rolled into one.&#8221;-Sir Martin Sorrell, CEO of WPP &#8220;Duncan Clark gets into the heart and soul of Alibaba and its founder, Jack Ma, who deftly maneuvered through the discontinuities and barriers in China to create one of the greatest companies in the world. China has thrived under the leadership of Jack Ma.<br />
                    This book is a must-read for anyone who wants to understand the present China and the heartbeat of a great entrepreneur.&#8221;-Tim Draper, founder of Draper Associates, DFJ, and Draper University  &#8220;This book provides excellent insight into the world of Jack Ma, perhaps the most famous of the leaders of the new economy in China. Duncan Clark is a real China &#8216;Old Hand,&#8217; unique in his knowledge of the Jack Ma generation. This book is definitely on the short list for those who wish to understand the Chinese economy today.&#8221;-Ken Wilcox, Chairman Emeritus, Silicon Valley Bank</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alibaba-the-house-that-jack-ma-built-duncan-clark-abridged/">Alibaba : The House That Jack Ma Built &#8211; Duncan Clark (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Barbarians At The Gate &#8211; Bryan Burrough, John Helyar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/barbarians-at-the-gate-bryan-burrough-john-helyar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Takeovers, Mergers & Buy-outs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/barbarians-at-the-gate-bryan-burrough-john-helyar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The battle for the control of RJR Nabisco in the Autumn of 1988, which became the largest and most dramatic corporate takeover in American history, sent shock-waves through the international business world and became a symbol of the greed, excess and egotism of the eighties. Barbarians at the Gate recounts this two-month battle with breathtaking [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/barbarians-at-the-gate-bryan-burrough-john-helyar-abridged/">Barbarians At The Gate &#8211; Bryan Burrough, John Helyar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The battle for the control of RJR Nabisco in the Autumn of 1988, which became the largest and most dramatic corporate takeover in American history, sent shock-waves through the international business world and became a symbol of the greed, excess and egotism of the eighties.     </p>
<p>                    Barbarians at the Gate recounts this two-month battle with breathtaking pace and flair, and transports back to the Wall Street empire before it crumbled, through the boardroom doors, into the midnight meetings, the betrayals, the deal makers and publicity flaks, into a world where &#8211; as Nabisco CEO Ross Johnson put it &#8211; &#8216;a few million dollars are lost in the sands of time&#8217;.     </p>
<p>                    Twenty years on, the world is once again recovering from a period of financial extravagance and irresponsibility. This revised edition brings the ultimate business thriller up to date for a new generation of readers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/barbarians-at-the-gate-bryan-burrough-john-helyar-abridged/">Barbarians At The Gate &#8211; Bryan Burrough, John Helyar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film The Wolf of Wall Street is about the finance industry&#8217;s greediest adults, Kevin Roose&#8217;s Young Money is a look at those wolves as cubs&#8217; Amazon.com &#8216;Best Book of the Month&#8217; Every year, thousands of eager graduates are hired by the world&#8217;s financial giants, where they&#8217;re taught the secrets of making obscene [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/">Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film The Wolf of Wall Street is about the finance industry&#8217;s greediest adults, Kevin Roose&#8217;s Young Money is a look at those wolves as cubs&#8217; Amazon.com &#8216;Best Book of the Month&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Every year, thousands of eager graduates are hired by the world&#8217;s financial giants, where they&#8217;re taught the secrets of making obscene amounts of money &#8212; as well as how to dress, talk, date, drink, and schmooze like real financiers. Young Money is the exclusive, inside story of this well-guarded world.<br />
                    Investigative reporter Kevin Roose shadows eight rookies as they are exposed to the exhausting workloads, huge bonuses, and recreational drugs that have always characterized Wall Street life. But they experience something new, too: an industry forever changed by the massive financial collapse of 2008. And as they get their Wall Street educations, they face hard questions about morality, prestige, and the value of their work.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A great new read that doubles as a post-crash update to Michael Lewis&#8217; Liar&#8217;s Poker &#8211; Mother Jones    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fun fast read that will make you laugh out loud&#8217; Fortune Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/">Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control  chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Secrets of Sand Hill Road : Venture Capital-and How to Get It &#8211; Scott Kupor, Foreword by Eric Ries (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/secrets-of-sand-hill-road-venture-capital-and-how-to-get-it-scott-kupor-foreword-by-eric-ries-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/secrets-of-sand-hill-road-venture-capital-and-how-to-get-it-scott-kupor-foreword-by-eric-ries-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Worth far more than its cover price &#8230; I wish I&#8217;d had it available to me when I was first looking for startup funding&#8217; &#8212; Eric Ries Every startup needs capital, and ambitious startups seek it on Sand Hill Road &#8211; Silicon Valley&#8217;s dream street for entrepreneurs. That&#8217;s where you&#8217;ll find the biggest names in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secrets-of-sand-hill-road-venture-capital-and-how-to-get-it-scott-kupor-foreword-by-eric-ries-abridged/">Secrets of Sand Hill Road : Venture Capital-and How to Get It &#8211; Scott Kupor, Foreword by Eric Ries (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Worth far more than its cover price &#8230; I wish I&#8217;d had it available to me when I was first looking for startup funding&#8217; &#8212; Eric Ries    </p>
<p>                    Every startup needs capital, and ambitious startups seek it on Sand Hill Road &#8211; Silicon Valley&#8217;s dream street for entrepreneurs. That&#8217;s where you&#8217;ll find the biggest names in venture capital, including the famed VC firm Andreessen Horowitz, where lawyer-turned-entrepreneur-turned-VC Scott Kupor serves as managing partner.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re trying to get a new company off the ground or scale an existing business to the next level, you need to understand how VCs think. Secrets of Sand Hill Road is the first book that shows you exactly how VCs decide where and how much to invest. It will help you get the best possible deal and make the most of your relationships with VCs. You&#8217;ll learn, for instance:    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why most VCs typically invest in only one startup in a given business category<br />
                    &#8212; Why the talent you need most when raising venture capital is your storytelling ability<br />
                    &#8212; How to handle a &#8216;down round&#8217;, when you have to raise funds at a lower valuation than in your previous round<br />
                    &#8212; Why bridge financing (reopening your last round to existing investors) is generally a bad idea<br />
                    &#8212; What to do when VCs get too entangled in the day-to-day operations of your business<br />
                    &#8212; Why you need to build relationships with potential acquirers long before you decide to sell    </p>
<p>                    Filled with Kupor&#8217;s firsthand experiences, insider advice, and practical takeaways, Secrets of Sand Hill Road is the guide you need to turn yourstartup into the next unicorn.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secrets-of-sand-hill-road-venture-capital-and-how-to-get-it-scott-kupor-foreword-by-eric-ries-abridged/">Secrets of Sand Hill Road : Venture Capital-and How to Get It &#8211; Scott Kupor, Foreword by Eric Ries (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employment & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a rational explanation of the ways in which the AI revolution will affect us all. Tackling the implications of Artificial Intelligence on growth, productivity, inflation and the distribution of wealth and power, THE AI ECONOMY also examines coming changes to the the way we educate, work and spend our leisure time.    </p>
<p>                    A fundamentally optimistic view which will help you plan for changing times, this book explains AI and leads you towards a more certain future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drugs Trade / Drug Trafficking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organized Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everything drug cartels do to survive and prosper they&#8217;ve learnt from big business &#8211; brand value and franchising from McDonald&#8217;s, supply chain management from Walmart, diversification from Coca-Cola. Whether it&#8217;s human resourcing, R&#038;D, corporate social responsibility, off-shoring, problems with e-commerce or troublesome changes in legislation, the drug lords face the same strategic concerns companies like [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/">Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everything drug cartels do to survive and prosper they&#8217;ve learnt from big business &#8211; brand value and franchising from McDonald&#8217;s, supply chain management from Walmart, diversification from Coca-Cola. Whether it&#8217;s human resourcing, R&#038;D, corporate social responsibility, off-shoring, problems with e-commerce or troublesome changes in legislation, the drug lords face the same strategic concerns companies like Ryanair or Apple. So when the drug cartels start to think like big business, the only way to understand them is using economics.     </p>
<p>                    In Narconomics, Tom Wainwright meets everyone from coca farmers in secret Andean locations, deluded heads of state in presidential palaces, journalists with a price on their head, gang leaders who run their empires from dangerous prisons and teenage hitmen on city streets &#8211; all in search of the economic truth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/">Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blowout : Corrupted Democracy, Rogue State Russia, and the Richest, Most Destructive Industry on Earth &#8211; Rachel Maddow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blowout-corrupted-democracy-rogue-state-russia-and-the-richest-most-destructive-industry-on-earth-rachel-maddow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blowout-corrupted-democracy-rogue-state-russia-and-the-richest-most-destructive-industry-on-earth-rachel-maddow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Big Oil and Gas Versus Democracy&#8211;Winner Take All &#8220;A rollickingly well-written book, filled with fascinating, exciting, and alarming stories about the impact of the oil and gas industry on the world today.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review In 2010, the words &#8220;earthquake swarm&#8221; entered the lexicon in Oklahoma. That [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blowout-corrupted-democracy-rogue-state-russia-and-the-richest-most-destructive-industry-on-earth-rachel-maddow-abridged/">Blowout : Corrupted Democracy, Rogue State Russia, and the Richest, Most Destructive Industry on Earth &#8211; Rachel Maddow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Big Oil and Gas Versus Democracy&#8211;Winner Take All     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A rollickingly well-written book, filled with fascinating, exciting, and alarming stories about the impact of the oil and gas industry on the world today.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review     </p>
<p>                     In 2010, the words &#8220;earthquake swarm&#8221; entered the lexicon in Oklahoma. That same year, a trove of Michael Jackson memorabilia&#8211;including his iconic crystal-encrusted white glove&#8211;was sold at auction for over $1 million to a guy who was, officially, just the lowly forestry minister of the tiny nation of Equatorial Guinea. And in 2014, revolutionaries in Ukraine raided the palace of their ousted president and found a zoo of peacocks, gilded toilets, and a floating restaurant modeled after a Spanish galleon. Unlikely as it might seem, there is a thread connecting these events, and Rachel Maddow follows it to its crooked source: the unimaginably lucrative and equally corrupting oil and gas industry.     </p>
<p>                     With her trademark black humor, Maddow takes us on a switchback journey around the globe, revealing the greed and incompetence of Big Oil and Gas along the way, and drawing a surprising conclusion about why the Russian government hacked the 2016 U.S. election. She deftly shows how Russia&#8217;s rich reserves of crude have, paradoxically, stunted its growth, forcing Vladimir Putin to maintain his power by spreading Russia&#8217;s rot into its rivals, its neighbors, the West&#8217;s most important alliances, and the United States. Chevron, BP, and a host of other industry players get their star turn, most notably ExxonMobil and the deceptively well-behaved Rex Tillerson. The oil and gas industry has weakened democracies in developed and developing countries, fouled oceans and rivers, and propped up authoritarian thieves and killers. But being outraged at it is, according to Maddow, &#8220;like being indignant when a lion takes down and eats a gazelle. You can&#8217;t really blame the lion. It&#8217;s in her nature.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                      Blowout is a call to contain the lion: to stop subsidizing the wealthiest businesses on earth, to fight for transparency, and to check the influence of the world&#8217;s most destructive industry and its enablers. The stakes have never been higher. As Maddow writes, &#8220;Democracy either wins this one or disappears.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blowout-corrupted-democracy-rogue-state-russia-and-the-richest-most-destructive-industry-on-earth-rachel-maddow-abridged/">Blowout : Corrupted Democracy, Rogue State Russia, and the Richest, Most Destructive Industry on Earth &#8211; Rachel Maddow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
