<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>European History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/european-history/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/european-history/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>European History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/european-history/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Angel&#8217;s Game : The Cemetery of Forgotten Books 2 &#8211; Carlos Ruiz Zafón</title>
		<link>/the-angels-game-the-cemetery-of-forgotten-books-2-carlos-ruiz-zafon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antiques & Collectables: Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ephemera & Printed Matter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction In Translation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manuscripts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-angels-game-the-cemetery-of-forgotten-books-2-carlos-ruiz-zafon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The stunning new novel from the internationally bestselling author of THE SHADOW OF THE WIND. In an abandoned mansion at the heart of Barcelona, a young man &#8211; David Martin &#8211; makes his living by writing sensationalist novels under a pseudonym. The survivor of a troubled childhood, he has taken refuge in the world of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-angels-game-the-cemetery-of-forgotten-books-2-carlos-ruiz-zafon/">The Angel&#8217;s Game : The Cemetery of Forgotten Books 2 &#8211; Carlos Ruiz Zafón</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The stunning new novel from the internationally bestselling author of THE SHADOW OF THE WIND.    </p>
<p>                    In an abandoned mansion at the heart of Barcelona, a young man &#8211; David Martin &#8211; makes his living by writing sensationalist novels under a pseudonym. The survivor of a troubled childhood, he has taken refuge in the world of books, and spends his nights spinning baroque tales about the city&#8217;s underworld. But perhaps his dark imaginings are not as strange as they seem, for in a locked room deep within the house letters hinting at the mysterious death of the previous owner. Like a slow poison, the history of the place seeps into his bones as he struggles with an impossible love.     </p>
<p>                    Then David receives the offer of a lifetime: he is to write a book with the power to change hearts and minds. In return, he will receive a fortune, perhaps more. But as David begins the work, he realises that there is a connection between this haunting book and the shadows that surround his home&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-angels-game-the-cemetery-of-forgotten-books-2-carlos-ruiz-zafon/">The Angel&#8217;s Game : The Cemetery of Forgotten Books 2 &#8211; Carlos Ruiz Zafón</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Russian Journal &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steinbeck and Capa&#8217;s account of their journey through Cold War Russia is a classic piece of reportage and travel writing. A Penguin Classic Just after the Iron Curtain fell on Eastern Europe, Pulitzer Prize-winning author John Steinbeck and acclaimed war photographer Robert Capa ventured into the Soviet Union to report for the New York Herald [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/">A Russian Journal &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steinbeck and Capa&#8217;s account of their journey through Cold War Russia is a classic piece of reportage and travel writing. </p>
<p>                    A Penguin Classic </p>
<p>                    Just after the Iron Curtain fell on Eastern Europe, Pulitzer Prize-winning author John Steinbeck and acclaimed war photographer Robert Capa ventured into the Soviet Union to report for the New York Herald Tribune. This rare opportunity took the famous travelers not only to Moscow and Stalingrad &#8211; now Volgograd &#8211; but through the countryside of the Ukraine and the Caucasus. Hailed by the New York Times as superb when it first appeared in 1948, A Russian Journal is the distillation of their journey and remains a remarkable memoir and unique historical document.</p>
<p>                    What they saw and movingly recorded in words and on film was what Steinbeck called the great other side there &#8230; the private life of the Russian people. Unlike other Western reporting about Russia at the time, A Russian Journal is free of ideological obsessions. Rather, Steinbeck and Capa recorded the grim realities of factory workers, government clerks, and peasants, as they emerged from the rubble of World War II&#8211;represented here in Capa&#8217;s stirring photographs alongside Steinbeck&#8217;s masterful prose. Through it all, we are given intimate glimpses of two artists at the height of their powers, answering their need to document human struggle. This edition features an introduction by Steinbeck scholar Susan Shillinglaw.</p>
<p>                     For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/">A Russian Journal &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Reformation : A History &#8211; Diarmaid Macculloch</title>
		<link>/the-reformation-a-history-diarmaid-macculloch/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Protestantism & Protestant Churches]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-reformation-a-history-diarmaid-macculloch/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The National Book Critics Circle Award-winning history of the Reformation&#8211;from the New York Times bestselling author of Christianity At a time when men and women were prepared to kill&#8211;and be killed&#8211;for their faith, the Protestant Reformation tore the Western world apart. Acclaimed as the definitive account of these epochal events, Diarmaid MacCulloch&#8217;s award-winning history brilliantly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-reformation-a-history-diarmaid-macculloch/">The Reformation : A History &#8211; Diarmaid Macculloch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The National Book Critics Circle Award-winning history of the Reformation&#8211;from the New York Times bestselling author of Christianity      </p>
<p>                     At a time when men and women were prepared to kill&#8211;and be killed&#8211;for their faith, the Protestant Reformation tore the Western world apart. Acclaimed as the definitive account of these epochal events, Diarmaid MacCulloch&#8217;s award-winning history brilliantly re-creates the religious battles of priests, monarchs, scholars, and politicians&#8211;from the zealous Martin Luther and his Ninety-Five Theses to the polemical John Calvin to the radical Igantius Loyola, from the tortured Thomas Cranmer to the ambitious Philip II.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing together the many strands of the Reformation and Counter-Reformation, and ranging widely across Europe and the New World, MacCulloch reveals as never before how these dramatic upheavals affected everyday lives&#8211;overturning ideas of love, sex, death, and the supernatural, and shaping the modern age.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-reformation-a-history-diarmaid-macculloch/">The Reformation : A History &#8211; Diarmaid Macculloch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bomber Command: Reflections of War: Live to Die Another Day (June 1942 &#8211; Summer 1943) &#8211; Martin Bowman</title>
		<link>/bomber-command-reflections-of-war-live-to-die-another-day-june-1942-summer-1943-martin-bowman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Air Forces & Warfare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bomber-command-reflections-of-war-live-to-die-another-day-june-1942-summer-1943-martin-bowman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This massive work provides a comprehensive insight to the experiences of Bomber Commands pilots and aircrew throughout World War Two. From the early wartime years when the RAFs first attempts to avenge Germanys onslaught were bedeviled by poor navigation and inaccurate bombing, to the final winning onslaught that finally tamed Hitler in his Berlin lair, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bomber-command-reflections-of-war-live-to-die-another-day-june-1942-summer-1943-martin-bowman/">Bomber Command: Reflections of War: Live to Die Another Day (June 1942 &#8211; Summer 1943) &#8211; Martin Bowman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This massive work provides a comprehensive insight to the experiences of Bomber Commands pilots and aircrew throughout World War Two. From the early wartime years when the RAFs first attempts to avenge Germanys onslaught were bedeviled by poor navigation and inaccurate bombing, to the final winning onslaught that finally tamed Hitler in his Berlin lair, these volumes trace the true experiences of the men who flew the bombers. Hundreds of first-hand accounts are punctuated by the authors background information that put each narrative into wartime perspective. Every aspect of Bomber Commands operational duties are covered; day and night bombing, precision low-level strikes, mass raids and operations throughout all wartime theaters. Contributions are from RAF personnel who flew the commands different aircraft from the early Blenheims and Stirlings to the later Lancasters and Mosquitoes. Each volume is full of accounts that tell of the camaraderie amongst the crews, moments of sheer terror and the stoic humor that provided the critical bond. The five volumes of this work provide the most vivid and comprehensive work on the outstanding part played by RAF Bomber Command in their vital role in the destruction of the Third Reich.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bomber-command-reflections-of-war-live-to-die-another-day-june-1942-summer-1943-martin-bowman/">Bomber Command: Reflections of War: Live to Die Another Day (June 1942 &#8211; Summer 1943) &#8211; Martin Bowman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Battle for Spain : The Spanish Civil War 1936-1939 &#8211; Antony Beevor</title>
		<link>/the-battle-for-spain-the-spanish-civil-war-1936-1939-antony-beevor/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spanish Civil War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-battle-for-spain-the-spanish-civil-war-1936-1939-antony-beevor/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of STALINGRAD and BERLIN: THE DOWNFALL on the Spanish Civil War, drawing on masses of newly discovered material from the Spanish, Russian and German archives. The civil war that tore Spain apart between 1936 and 1939 and attracted liberals and socialists from across the world to support the cause against Franco was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-battle-for-spain-the-spanish-civil-war-1936-1939-antony-beevor/">The Battle for Spain : The Spanish Civil War 1936-1939 &#8211; Antony Beevor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of STALINGRAD and BERLIN: THE DOWNFALL on the Spanish Civil War, drawing on masses of newly discovered material from the Spanish, Russian and German archives.    </p>
<p>                    The civil war that tore Spain apart between 1936 and 1939 and attracted liberals and socialists from across the world to support the cause against Franco was one of the most hard-fought and bitterest conflicts of the 20th century: a war of atrocities and political genocide and a military testing ground before WWII for the Russians, Italians and Germans, whose Condor Legion so notoriously destroyed Guernica.    </p>
<p>                    Antony Beevor&#8217;s account narrates the origins of the Civil War and its violent and dramatic course from the coup d&#8217;etat in July 1936 through the savage fighting of the next three years which ended in catastrophic defeat for the Republicans in 1939. And he succeeds especially well in unravelling the complex political and regional forces that played such an important part in the origins and history of the war.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-battle-for-spain-the-spanish-civil-war-1936-1939-antony-beevor/">The Battle for Spain : The Spanish Civil War 1936-1939 &#8211; Antony Beevor</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Children of the Night : The Strange and Epic Story of Modern Romania &#8211; Paul Kenyon</title>
		<link>/children-of-the-night-the-strange-and-epic-story-of-modern-romania-paul-kenyon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/children-of-the-night-the-strange-and-epic-story-of-modern-romania-paul-kenyon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A vivid, brilliant, darkly humorous and horrifying history of some of the strangest dictators that Europe has ever seen. &#8216;A witty and page-turning narrative full of grotesque characters&#8217; Misha Glenny &#8216;Kenyon relates all this with verve [and] humour&#8230; He patiently untangles the complicated webs of loyalty and enmity&#8217; Literary Review &#8216;Absolutely essential reading for anyone [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/children-of-the-night-the-strange-and-epic-story-of-modern-romania-paul-kenyon/">Children of the Night : The Strange and Epic Story of Modern Romania &#8211; Paul Kenyon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A vivid, brilliant, darkly humorous and horrifying history of some of the strangest dictators that Europe has ever seen. &#8216;A witty and page-turning narrative full of grotesque characters&#8217; Misha Glenny</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Kenyon relates all this with verve [and] humour&#8230; He patiently untangles the complicated webs of loyalty and enmity&#8217; Literary Review</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Absolutely essential reading for anyone interested in Romania past and present&#8217; John Simpson</p>
<p>                    Balanced precariously on the shifting fault line between East and West, Romania&#8217;s schizophrenic, often violent past is one of the great untold stories of modern Europe.</p>
<p>                    The country that gave us Vlad Dracula, and whose citizens consider themselves descendants of ancient Rome, has traditionally preferred the status of enigmatic outsider. But this beautiful and unexplored land has experienced some of the most disastrous leaderships of the last century.</p>
<p>                    After a relatively benign period led by a dutiful King and his vivacious British-born Queen, the country oscillated wildly. Its interwar rulers form a gallery of bizarre characters and extreme movements: the corrupt and mentally unbalanced King Carol; the fascist death cult led by Corneliu Codreanu; the vain General Ion Antonescu, who seized power in 1940 and led the country into a catastrophic alliance with Nazi Germany. After 1945 power was handed to Romania&#8217;s tiny communist party, under which it experienced severe repression, purges and collectivisation.</p>
<p>                    Then in 1965, Nicolae Ceausescu came to power. And thus began the strangest dictatorship of all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/children-of-the-night-the-strange-and-epic-story-of-modern-romania-paul-kenyon/">Children of the Night : The Strange and Epic Story of Modern Romania &#8211; Paul Kenyon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gulag Archipelago &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn</title>
		<link>/the-gulag-archipelago-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Endurance & Survival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories Of Heroism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gulag-archipelago-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>[The Gulag Archipelago] helped to bring down an empire. Its importance can hardly be exaggerated&#8217; Doris Lessing, Sunday Telegraph WITH A NEW FOREWORD BY JORDAN B. PETERSON A vast canvas of camps, prisons, transit centres and secret police, of informers and spies and interrogators but also of everyday heroism, The Gulag Archipelago is Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gulag-archipelago-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/">The Gulag Archipelago &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>[The Gulag Archipelago] helped to bring down an empire. Its importance can hardly be exaggerated&#8217; Doris Lessing, Sunday Telegraph</p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                            WITH A NEW FOREWORD BY JORDAN B. PETERSON</p>
<p>                    A vast canvas of camps, prisons, transit centres and secret police, of informers and spies and interrogators but also of everyday heroism, The Gulag Archipelago is Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s grand masterwork. Based on the testimony of some 200 survivors, and on the recollection of Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s own eleven years in labour camps and exile, it chronicles the story of those at the heart of the Soviet Union who opposed Stalin, and for whom the key to survival lay not in hope but in despair.</p>
<p>                    A thoroughly researched document and a feat of literary and imaginative power, this edition of The Gulag Archipelago was abridged into one volume at the author&#8217;s wish and with his full co-operation.</p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                  &#8216;Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s masterpiece&#8230;The Gulag Archipelago helped create the world we live in today&#8217; Anne Applebaum</p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                          THE OFFICIALLY APPROVED ABRIDGEMENT OF THE GULAG ARCHIPELAGO VOLUMES I, II &#038; III</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gulag-archipelago-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/">The Gulag Archipelago &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gulag Archipelago: Experiment in Literary Investigation v. 3 &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn</title>
		<link>/the-gulag-archipelago-experiment-in-literary-investigation-v-3-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Penology & Punishment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gulag-archipelago-experiment-in-literary-investigation-v-3-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;BEST NONFICTION BOOK OF THE 20TH CENTURY.&#8221; &#8211;Time Volume 3 of the Nobel Prize winner&#8217;s towering masterpiece: Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s moving account of resistance within the Soviet labor camps and his own release after eight years. Features a new foreword by Anne Applebaum. &#8220;The greatest and most powerful single indictment of a political regime ever leveled in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gulag-archipelago-experiment-in-literary-investigation-v-3-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/">The Gulag Archipelago: Experiment in Literary Investigation v. 3 &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;BEST NONFICTION BOOK OF THE 20TH CENTURY.&#8221; &#8211;Time    </p>
<p>                    Volume 3 of the Nobel Prize winner&#8217;s towering masterpiece: Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s moving account of resistance within the Soviet labor camps and his own release after eight years. Features a new foreword by Anne Applebaum.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The greatest and most powerful single indictment of a political regime ever leveled in modern times.&#8221; &#8211;George F. Kennan    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;It is impossible to name a book that had a greater effect on the political and moral consciousness of the late twentieth century.&#8221; &#8211;David Remnick, New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s masterpiece. . . . The Gulag Archipelago helped create the world we live in today.&#8221; &#8211;Anne Applebaum, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of Gulag: A History, from the foreword    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gulag-archipelago-experiment-in-literary-investigation-v-3-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/">The Gulag Archipelago: Experiment in Literary Investigation v. 3 &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Darkening Age : The Christian Destruction of the Classical World &#8211; Catherine Nixey</title>
		<link>/the-darkening-age-the-christian-destruction-of-the-classical-world-catherine-nixey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ancient History: To C 500 CE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Institutions & Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Church]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early History: C 500 To C 1450/1500]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Religion]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-darkening-age-the-christian-destruction-of-the-classical-world-catherine-nixey/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Darkening Age, Catherine Nixey tells the little-known &#8211; and deeply shocking &#8211; story of how a militant religion deliberately tried to extinguish the teachings of the Classical world, ushering in unquestioning adherence to the &#8216;one true faith&#8217;. The Roman Empire had been generous in embracing and absorbing new creeds. But with the coming [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-darkening-age-the-christian-destruction-of-the-classical-world-catherine-nixey/">The Darkening Age : The Christian Destruction of the Classical World &#8211; Catherine Nixey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Darkening Age, Catherine Nixey tells the little-known &#8211; and deeply shocking &#8211; story of how a militant religion deliberately tried to extinguish the teachings of the Classical world, ushering in unquestioning adherence to the &#8216;one true faith&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    The Roman Empire had been generous in embracing and absorbing new creeds.  But with the coming of Christianity, everything changed.  This new faith, despite preaching peace, was violent, ruthless and intolerant.  And once it became the religion of empire, its zealous adherents set about the destruction of the old gods.  Their altars were upturned, their temples demolished and their statues hacked to pieces.  Books, including great works of philosophy and science, were consigned to the pyre.  It was an annihilation.    </p>
<p>                    A Book of the Year in the Daily Telegraph, the Spectator, the Observer, and BBC History Magazine<br />
                    A New York Times Book Review Editors&#8217; Choice<br />
                    Winner of the Royal Society of Literature Jerwood Award for Nonfiction    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-darkening-age-the-christian-destruction-of-the-classical-world-catherine-nixey/">The Darkening Age : The Christian Destruction of the Classical World &#8211; Catherine Nixey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gulag Archipelago: Experiment in Literary Investigation v. 1 &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn</title>
		<link>/the-gulag-archipelago-experiment-in-literary-investigation-v-1-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Penology & Punishment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gulag-archipelago-experiment-in-literary-investigation-v-1-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;BEST NONFICTION BOOK OF THE 20TH CENTURY.&#8221; &#8211;Time Volume 1 of the gripping epic masterpiece, Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s chilling report of his arrest and interrogation, which exposed to the world the vast bureaucracy of secret police that haunted Soviet society. Features a new foreword by Anne Applebaum. &#8220;The greatest and most powerful single indictment of a political [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gulag-archipelago-experiment-in-literary-investigation-v-1-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/">The Gulag Archipelago: Experiment in Literary Investigation v. 1 &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;BEST NONFICTION BOOK OF THE 20TH CENTURY.&#8221; &#8211;Time    </p>
<p>                    Volume 1 of the gripping epic masterpiece, Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s chilling report of his arrest and interrogation, which exposed to the world the vast bureaucracy of secret police that haunted Soviet society. Features a new foreword by Anne Applebaum.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The greatest and most powerful single indictment of a political regime ever leveled in modern times.&#8221; &#8211;George F. Kennan    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;It is impossible to name a book that had a greater effect on the political and moral consciousness of the late twentieth century.&#8221; &#8211;David Remnick, The New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s masterpiece. . . . The Gulag Archipelago helped create the world we live in today.&#8221; &#8211;Anne Applebaum, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of Gulag: A History, from the foreword    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gulag-archipelago-experiment-in-literary-investigation-v-1-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/">The Gulag Archipelago: Experiment in Literary Investigation v. 1 &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gulag Archipelago: Experiment in Literary Investigation v. 2 &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn</title>
		<link>/the-gulag-archipelago-experiment-in-literary-investigation-v-2-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Penology & Punishment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gulag-archipelago-experiment-in-literary-investigation-v-2-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;BEST NONFICTION BOOK OF THE 20TH CENTURY.&#8221; &#8211;Time Volume 2 of the Nobel Prize-winner&#8217;s towering masterpiece: the story of Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s entrance into the Soviet prison camps, where he would remain for nearly a decade. Features a new foreword by Anne Applebaum. &#8220;The greatest and most powerful single indictment of a political regime ever leveled in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gulag-archipelago-experiment-in-literary-investigation-v-2-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/">The Gulag Archipelago: Experiment in Literary Investigation v. 2 &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;BEST NONFICTION BOOK OF THE 20TH CENTURY.&#8221; &#8211;Time    </p>
<p>                    Volume 2 of the Nobel Prize-winner&#8217;s towering masterpiece: the story of Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s entrance into the Soviet prison camps, where he would remain for nearly a decade. Features a new foreword by Anne Applebaum.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The greatest and most powerful single indictment of a political regime ever leveled in modern times.&#8221; &#8211;George F. Kennan    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;It is impossible to name a book that had a greater effect on the political and moral consciousness of the late twentieth century.&#8221; &#8211;David Remnick, The New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s masterpiece. . . . The Gulag Archipelago helped create the world we live in today.&#8221; &#8211;Anne Applebaum, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of Gulag: A History, from the foreword    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gulag-archipelago-experiment-in-literary-investigation-v-2-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn/">The Gulag Archipelago: Experiment in Literary Investigation v. 2 &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Year of Living Danishly : Uncovering the Secrets of the World&#8217;s Happiest Country &#8211; Helen Russell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel With Children / Family Holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* NOW WITH A NEW CHAPTER * &#8216;A hugely enjoyable romp through the pleasures and pitfalls of setting up home in a foreign land.&#8217;- Guardian Given the opportunity of a new life in rural Jutland, Helen Russell discovered a startling statistic: Denmark, land of long dark winters, cured herring, Lego and pastries, was the happiest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/">The Year of Living Danishly : Uncovering the Secrets of the World&#8217;s Happiest Country &#8211; Helen Russell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* NOW WITH A NEW CHAPTER *    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A hugely enjoyable romp through the pleasures and pitfalls of setting up home in a foreign land.&#8217;- Guardian    </p>
<p>                    Given the opportunity of a new life in rural Jutland, Helen Russell discovered a startling statistic: Denmark, land of long dark winters, cured herring, Lego and pastries, was the happiest place on earth.    </p>
<p>                    Keen to know their secrets, Helen gave herself a year to uncover the formula for Danish happiness.    </p>
<p>                    From childcare, education, food and interior design to SAD and taxes, The Year of Living Danishly records a funny, poignant journey, showing us what the Danes get right, what they get wrong, and how we might all live a little more Danishly ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    In this new edition, six years on Helen reveals how her life and family have changed, and explores how Denmark, too &#8211; or. her understanding of it &#8211; has shifted. It&#8217;s a messy and flawed place, she concludes &#8211; but can still be a model for a better way of living.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-year-of-living-danishly-uncovering-the-secrets-of-the-worlds-happiest-country-helen-russell-abridged/">The Year of Living Danishly : Uncovering the Secrets of the World&#8217;s Happiest Country &#8211; Helen Russell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Spy and the Traitor : The Greatest Espionage Story of the Cold War &#8211; Ben MacIntyre (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cold War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*The No.1 Sunday Times Bestseller* *A BBC Between the Covers book club pick* *Shortlisted for the 2018 Baillie Gifford Prize* &#8216;THE BEST TRUE SPY STORY I HAVE EVER READ&#8217; JOHN LE CARRE An exciting Cold War story about a KGB double agent, by one of Britain&#8217;s greatest historians and the ultimate gift for anyone who [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/">The Spy and the Traitor : The Greatest Espionage Story of the Cold War &#8211; Ben MacIntyre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*The No.1 Sunday Times Bestseller*<br />
                    *A BBC Between the Covers book club pick*<br />
                    *Shortlisted for the 2018 Baillie Gifford Prize*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;THE BEST TRUE SPY STORY I HAVE EVER READ&#8217; JOHN LE CARRE        </p>
<p>                    An exciting Cold War story about a KGB double agent, by one of Britain&#8217;s greatest historians and the ultimate gift for anyone who loves a good spy thriller!    </p>
<p>                    On a warm July evening in 1985, a middle-aged man stood on the pavement of a busy avenue in the heart of Moscow, holding a plastic carrier bag. In his grey suit and tie, he looked like any other Soviet citizen. The bag alone was mildly conspicuous, printed with the red logo of Safeway, the British supermarket.    </p>
<p>                    The man was a spy. A senior KGB officer, for more than a decade he had supplied his British spymasters with a stream of priceless secrets from deep within the Soviet intelligence machine. No spy had done more to damage the KGB. The Safeway bag was a signal: to activate his escape plan to be smuggled out of Soviet Russia. So began one of the boldest and most extraordinary episodes in the history of spying. Ben Macintyre reveals a tale of espionage, betrayal and raw courage that changed the course of the Cold War forever&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    BEN MACINTYRE&#8217;S NEXT BOOK AGENT SONYA IS AVAILABLE TO BUY NOW</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spy-and-the-traitor-the-greatest-espionage-story-of-the-cold-war-ben-macintyre-abridged/">The Spy and the Traitor : The Greatest Espionage Story of the Cold War &#8211; Ben MacIntyre (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alexander the Great &#8211; Philip Freeman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alexander-the-great-philip-freeman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alexander-the-great-philip-freeman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Alexander the Great (Alexander III of Macedon) was one of history&#8217;s great generals, a man studied by Caesar and Napoleon, among hundreds of others. He was born to the king of Macedon and educated by Aristotle, whose inquiring mind Alexander appreciated. After his father, Philip II, was assassinated, the 19-year-old Alexander succeeded to the throne [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alexander-the-great-philip-freeman-abridged/">Alexander the Great &#8211; Philip Freeman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Alexander the Great (Alexander III of Macedon) was one of history&#8217;s great generals, a man studied by Caesar and Napoleon, among hundreds of others. He was born to the king of Macedon and educated by Aristotle, whose inquiring mind Alexander appreciated. After his father, Philip II, was assassinated, the 19-year-old Alexander succeeded to the throne and swiftly consolidated power. Over the next 13 years until his death at age 32, Alexander created one of the great empires of history, covering an area as far south as Egypt and as far east as Afghanistan and India. Most of the world that he conquered had been the province of the Persian Empire. Upon his death his empire was broken up and ruled by his generals, the best known were the Ptolemies, who ruled Egypt until Cleopatra was defeated by Caesar. Alexandria, Egypt and many other Alexandrias throughout that part of the world were named in his honour.     </p>
<p>                    Alexander&#8217;s greatest influence was not his leadership (his empire was eventually conquered by Rome), but spreading Greek culture throughout the lands east of the Mediterranean. He is the reason that gold coins from Afghanistan depicted Greek gods and heroes until as recently as several centuries ago. It is because of Alexander that St. Paul, a Jew who lived in modern-day Syria before travelling to modern-day Israel, spoke Greek, and it is because of Alexander that the earliest Christian documents, including the scriptures, were written in Greek.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alexander-the-great-philip-freeman-abridged/">Alexander the Great &#8211; Philip Freeman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Madness and Civilization : A History of Insanity in the Age of Reason &#8211; Michel Foucault (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/madness-and-civilization-a-history-of-insanity-in-the-age-of-reason-michel-foucault-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deconstructionism, Structuralism, Post-structuralism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy, From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/madness-and-civilization-a-history-of-insanity-in-the-age-of-reason-michel-foucault-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michel Foucault examines the archeology of madness in the West from 1500 to 1800 &#8211; from the late Middle Ages, when insanity was still considered part of everyday life and fools and lunatics walked the streets freely, to the time when such people began to be considered a threat, asylums were first built, and walls [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/madness-and-civilization-a-history-of-insanity-in-the-age-of-reason-michel-foucault-abridged/">Madness and Civilization : A History of Insanity in the Age of Reason &#8211; Michel Foucault (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michel Foucault examines the archeology of madness in the West from 1500 to 1800 &#8211; from the late Middle Ages, when insanity was still considered part of everyday life and fools and lunatics walked the streets freely, to the time when such people began to be considered a threat, asylums were first built, and walls were erected between the insane and the rest of humanity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/madness-and-civilization-a-history-of-insanity-in-the-age-of-reason-michel-foucault-abridged/">Madness and Civilization : A History of Insanity in the Age of Reason &#8211; Michel Foucault (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Napoleon&#8217;S Buttons : How 17 Molecules Changed History &#8211; Penny Le Couteur, Jay Burreson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum & Theoretical Chemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Napoleon&#8217;s Buttons is the fascinating account of seventeen groups of molecules that have greatly influenced the course of history. These molecules provided the impetus for early exploration, and made possible the voyages of discovery that ensued. The molecules resulted in grand feats of engineering and spurred advances in medicine and law; they determined what we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/">Napoleon&#8217;S Buttons : How 17 Molecules Changed History &#8211; Penny Le Couteur, Jay Burreson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Napoleon&#8217;s Buttons is the fascinating account of seventeen groups of molecules that have greatly influenced the course of history. These molecules provided the impetus for early exploration, and made possible the voyages of discovery that ensued. The molecules resulted in grand feats of engineering and spurred advances in medicine and law; they determined what we now eat, drink, and wear. A change as small as the position of an atom can lead to enormous alterations in the properties of a substance-which, in turn, can result in great historical shifts.     </p>
<p>                     With lively prose and an eye for colorful and unusual details, Le Couteur and Burreson offer a novel way to understand the shaping of civilization and the workings of our contemporary world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/">Napoleon&#8217;S Buttons : How 17 Molecules Changed History &#8211; Penny Le Couteur, Jay Burreson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gulag Archipelago 1918-1956 : An Experiment in Literary Investigation &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-gulag-archipelago-1918-1956-an-experiment-in-literary-investigation-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Penology & Punishment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gulag-archipelago-1918-1956-an-experiment-in-literary-investigation-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The official, one-volume edition, authorized by Solzhenitsyn &#8220;BEST NONFICTION BOOK OF THE 20TH CENTURY&#8221; &#8211;Time The Nobel Prize winner&#8217;s towering masterpiece of world literature, the searing record of four decades of terror and oppression, in one abridged volume (authorized by the author). Features a new foreword by Anne Applebaum. &#8220;It is impossible to name a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gulag-archipelago-1918-1956-an-experiment-in-literary-investigation-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn-abridged/">The Gulag Archipelago 1918-1956 : An Experiment in Literary Investigation &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The official, one-volume edition, authorized by Solzhenitsyn    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;BEST NONFICTION BOOK OF THE 20TH CENTURY&#8221; &#8211;Time    </p>
<p>                    The Nobel Prize winner&#8217;s towering masterpiece of world literature, the searing record of four decades of terror and oppression, in one abridged volume (authorized by the author). Features a new foreword by Anne Applebaum.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;It is impossible to name a book that had a greater effect on the political and moral consciousness of the late twentieth century.&#8221; &#8211;David Remnick, The New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his own experiences before, during and after his eleven years of incarceration and exile, on evidence provided by more than 200 fellow prisoners, and on Soviet archives, Solzhenitsyn reveals with torrential narrative and dramatic power the entire apparatus of Soviet repression, the state within the state that once ruled all-powerfully with its creation by Lenin in 1918. Through truly Shakespearean portraits of its victims-this man, that woman, that child-we encounter the secret police operations, the labor camps and prisons, the uprooting or extermination of whole populations, the &#8220;welcome&#8221; that awaited Russian soldiers who had been German prisoners of war. Yet we also witness astounding moral courage, the incorruptibility with which the occasional individual or a few scattered groups, all defenseless, endured brutality and degradation. And Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s genius has transmuted this grisly indictment into a literary miracle.    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The greatest and most powerful single indictment of a political regime ever leveled in modern times.&#8221; &#8211;George F. Kennan    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Solzhenitsyn&#8217;s masterpiece. &#8230; The Gulag Archipelago helped create the world we live in today.&#8221; &#8211;Anne Applebaum, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of Gulag: A History, from the foreword</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gulag-archipelago-1918-1956-an-experiment-in-literary-investigation-aleksandr-solzhenitsyn-abridged/">The Gulag Archipelago 1918-1956 : An Experiment in Literary Investigation &#8211; Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An unburdening, a witness statement and a thriller all at the same time &#8230; electrifying.&#8217; The Times I have to assume that there is a very real chance that Putin or members of his regime will have me killed some day. If I&#8217;m killed, you will know who did it. When my enemies read this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/">Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An unburdening, a witness statement and a thriller all at the same time &#8230; electrifying.&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    I have to assume that there is a very real chance that Putin or members of his regime will have me killed some day. If I&#8217;m killed, you will know who did it. When my enemies read this book, they will know that you know.    </p>
<p>                    A Sunday Times and New York Times bestseller. A true-life thriller by one of Putin&#8217;s Most Wanted.    </p>
<p>                    In November 2009, the young lawyer Sergei Magnitsky was beaten to death by eight police officers in a freezing cell in a Moscow prison. His crime? Testifying against Russian officials who were involved in a conspiracy to steal $230 million of taxes.    </p>
<p>                    Red Notice is a searing expose of the whitewash of this imprisonment and murder. The killing hasn&#8217;t been investigated. It hasn&#8217;t been punished. Bill Browder is still campaigning for justice for his late lawyer and friend. This is his explosive journey from the heady world of finance in New York and London in the 1990s, through battles with ruthless oligarchs in turbulent post-Soviet Union Moscow, to the shadowy heart of the Kremlin.    </p>
<p>                    With fraud, bribery, corruption and torture exposed at every turn, Red Notice is a shocking political roller-coaster.<br />
                    __________________    </p>
<p>                    Reads like a classic thriller, with an everyman hero alone and in danger in a hostile foreign city &#8230; but it&#8217;s all true, and it&#8217;s a story that needs to be told.&#8217; Lee Child    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A shocking true-life thriller.&#8217; Tom Stoppard    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A riveting account&#8230; it is a powerful story and Browder tells it skilfully.&#8217; The Washington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/">Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chernobyl : History of a Tragedy &#8211; Serhii Plokhy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chernobyl-history-of-a-tragedy-serhii-plokhy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nuclear Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nuclear Power & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Postwar 20th Century History, From C 1945 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Disasters]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chernobyl-history-of-a-tragedy-serhii-plokhy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*WINNER OF THE BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION 2018* *WINNER OF THE PUSHKIN HOUSE BOOK PRIZE 2019* &#8216;As moving as it is painstakingly researched. . . a cracking read&#8217; Viv Groskop, Observer &#8216;A riveting account of human error and state duplicity. . . rightly being hailed as a classic&#8217; Hannah Betts, Daily Telegraph On 26 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chernobyl-history-of-a-tragedy-serhii-plokhy-abridged/">Chernobyl : History of a Tragedy &#8211; Serhii Plokhy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*WINNER OF THE BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION 2018*<br />
                    *WINNER OF THE PUSHKIN HOUSE BOOK PRIZE 2019*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;As moving as it is painstakingly researched. . . a cracking read&#8217; Viv Groskop, Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A riveting account of human error and state duplicity. . . rightly being hailed as a classic&#8217; Hannah Betts, Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    On 26 April 1986 at 1.23am a reactor at the Chernobyl Nuclear Power  Plant in Soviet Ukraine exploded. While the authorities scrambled to  understand what was occurring, workers, engineers, firefighters and  those living in the area were abandoned to their fate. The blast put the  world on the brink of nuclear annihilation, contaminating over half of  Europe with radioactive fallout.    </p>
<p>                    In Chernobyl, award-winning  historian Serhii Plokhy draws on recently opened archives to recreate  these events in all their drama. A moment by moment account of the heroes, perpetrators and victims of a tragedy, Chernobyl is the first full account of a gripping, unforgettable Cold War story.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling history of the 1986 disaster and its aftermath . . .  plunges the reader into the sweaty, nervous tension of the Chernobyl  control room on that fateful night when human frailty and design flaws  combined to such devastating effect&#8217; Daniel Beer, Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Haunting &#8230; near-Tolstoyan. His voice is humane and inflected with nostalgia&#8217; Roland Elliott Brown, Spectator     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Extraordinary,  vividly written, powerful storytelling &#8230; the first full-scale history  of the world&#8217;s worst nuclear disaster, one of the defining moments in  the Cold War, told minute by minute&#8217; Victor Sebestyen Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Plays out like a classical tragedy &#8230; fascinating&#8217; Julian Evans, Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Here at last is the monumental history the disaster deserves&#8217; Julie McDowall, The Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chernobyl-history-of-a-tragedy-serhii-plokhy-abridged/">Chernobyl : History of a Tragedy &#8211; Serhii Plokhy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Queen of Fashion : What Marie Antoinette Wore to the Revolution &#8211; Caroline Weber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/queen-of-fashion-what-marie-antoinette-wore-to-the-revolution-caroline-weber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Royalty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fashion & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fashion & Textiles: Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Fashion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutions, Uprisings, Rebellions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/queen-of-fashion-what-marie-antoinette-wore-to-the-revolution-caroline-weber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Washington Post Book World Best Book of the Year When her carriage first crossed over from her native Austria into France, fourteen-year-old Marie Antoinette was taken out, stripped naked before an entourage, and dressed in French attire to please the court of her new king. For a short while, the young girl played the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/queen-of-fashion-what-marie-antoinette-wore-to-the-revolution-caroline-weber-abridged/">Queen of Fashion : What Marie Antoinette Wore to the Revolution &#8211; Caroline Weber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Washington Post Book World Best Book of the Year     </p>
<p>                    When her carriage first crossed over from her native Austria into France, fourteen-year-old Marie Antoinette was taken out, stripped naked before an entourage, and dressed in French attire to please the court of her new king. For a short while, the young girl played the part.     </p>
<p>                    But by the time she took the throne, everything had changed. In Queen of Fashion,  Caroline Weber tells of the radical restyling that transformed the young queen into an icon and shaped the future of the nation. With her riding gear, her white furs, her pouf hairstyles, and her intricate ballroom disguises, Marie Antoinette came to embody&#8211;gloriously and tragically&#8211;all the extravagance of the monarchy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/queen-of-fashion-what-marie-antoinette-wore-to-the-revolution-caroline-weber-abridged/">Queen of Fashion : What Marie Antoinette Wore to the Revolution &#8211; Caroline Weber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The House of Rothschild : Money&#8217;s Prophets 1798-1848 &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his rich and nuanced portrait of the remarkable, elusive Rothschild family, Oxford scholar and bestselling author Niall Ferguson uncovers the secrets behind the family&#8217;s phenomenal economic success. He reveals for the first time the details of the family&#8217;s vast political network, which gave it access to and influence over many of the greatest statesmen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The House of Rothschild : Money&#8217;s Prophets 1798-1848 &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his rich and nuanced portrait of the remarkable, elusive Rothschild  family, Oxford scholar and bestselling author Niall Ferguson uncovers  the secrets behind the family&#8217;s phenomenal economic success. He reveals  for the first time the details of the family&#8217;s vast political network,  which gave it access to and influence over many of the greatest  statesmen of the age. And he tells a family saga, tracing the importance  of unity and the profound role of Judaism in the lives of a dynasty  that rose from the confines of the Frankfurt ghetto and later used its  influence to assist oppressed Jews throughout Europe. A definitive work  of impeccable scholarship with a thoroughly engaging narrative, &#8216;The  House of Rothschild&#8217; is a biography of the rarest kind, in which  mysterious and fascinating historical figures finally spring to life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The House of Rothschild : Money&#8217;s Prophets 1798-1848 &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Germany : Memories of a Nation &#8211; Dr Neil MacGregor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/germany-memories-of-a-nation-dr-neil-macgregor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Styles]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/germany-memories-of-a-nation-dr-neil-macgregor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Neil MacGregor, the author of A History of the World in 100 Objects, this is a view of Germany like no other For the past 140 years, Germany has been the central power in continental Europe. Twenty-five years ago a new German state came into being. How much do we really understand this new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/germany-memories-of-a-nation-dr-neil-macgregor-abridged/">Germany : Memories of a Nation &#8211; Dr Neil MacGregor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Neil MacGregor, the author of A History of the World in 100 Objects, this is a view of Germany like no other    </p>
<p>                    For the past 140 years, Germany has been the central power in continental Europe. Twenty-five years ago a new German state came into being. How much do we really understand this new Germany, and how do its people now understand themselves?    </p>
<p>                    Neil MacGregor argues that uniquely for any European country, no coherent, over-arching narrative of Germany&#8217;s history can be constructed, for in Germany both geography and history have always been unstable. Its frontiers have constantly floated. Koenigsberg, home to the greatest German philosopher, Immanuel Kant, is now Kaliningrad, Russia; Strasbourg, in whose cathedral Johann Wolfgang von Goethe, Germany&#8217;s greatest writer, discovered the distinctiveness of his country&#8217;s art and history, now lies within the borders of France. For most of the five hundred years covered by this book Germany has been composed of many separate political units, each with a distinct history. And any comfortable national story Germans might have told themselves before 1914 was destroyed by the events of the following thirty years.    </p>
<p>                    German history may be inherently fragmented, but it contains a large number of widely shared memories, awarenesses and experiences; examining some of these is the purpose of this book. Beginning with the fifteenth-century invention of modern printing by Gutenberg, MacGregor chooses objects and ideas, people and places which still resonate in the new Germany &#8211; porcelain from Dresden and rubble from its ruins, Bauhaus design and the German sausage, the crown of Charlemagne and the gates of Buchenwald &#8211; to show us something of its collective imagination. There has never been a book about Germany quite like it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/germany-memories-of-a-nation-dr-neil-macgregor-abridged/">Germany : Memories of a Nation &#8211; Dr Neil MacGregor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Modern History: C 1450/1500 To C 1700]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Napoleonic Wars]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutions, Uprisings, Rebellions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Napoleonic triumph of a book, irresistibly galloping with the momentum of a cavalry charge&#8217; Simon Sebag Montefiore &#8216;Simply dynamite&#8217; Bernard Cornwell From Andrew Roberts, author of the bestsellers The Storm of War and Churchill: Walking with Destiny, this is the definitive modern biography of Napoleon. Napoleon Bonaparte lived one of the most extraordinary of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/">Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Napoleonic triumph of a book, irresistibly galloping with the  momentum of a cavalry charge&#8217;   Simon Sebag Montefiore<br />
                    &#8216;Simply dynamite&#8217; Bernard Cornwell    </p>
<p>                    From Andrew Roberts, author of the bestsellers The Storm of War and Churchill: Walking with Destiny, this is the definitive modern biography of Napoleon.    </p>
<p>                    Napoleon Bonaparte lived one of the most extraordinary of all human lives. In the space of just twenty years, from October 1795 when as a young artillery captain he cleared the streets of Paris of insurrectionists, to his final defeat at the (horribly mismanaged) battle of Waterloo in June 1815, Napoleon transformed France and Europe. After seizing power in a coup d&#8217;etat he ended the corruption and incompetence into which the Revolution had descended. In a series of dazzling battles he reinvented the art of warfare; in peace, he completely remade the laws of France, modernised her systems of education and administration, and presided over a flourishing of the beautiful &#8216;Empire style&#8217; in the arts. The impossibility of defeating his most persistent enemy, Great Britain, led him to make draining and ultimately fatal expeditions into Spain and Russia, where half a million Frenchmen died and his Empire began to unravel.    </p>
<p>                    More than any other modern biographer, Andrew Roberts conveys Napoleon&#8217;s tremendous energy, both physical and intellectual, and the attractiveness of his personality, even to his enemies. He has walked 53 of Napoleon&#8217;s 60 battlefields, and has absorbed the gigantic new French edition of Napoleon&#8217;s letters, which allows a complete re-evaluation of this exceptional man. He overturns many received opinions, including the myth of a great romance with Josephine: she took a lover immediately after their marriage, and, as Roberts shows, he had three times as many mistresses as he acknowledged.    </p>
<p>                    Of the climactic Battle of Leipzig in 1813, as the fighting closed around them, a French sergeant-major wrote, &#8216;No-one who has not experienced it can have any idea of the enthusiasm that burst forth among the half-starved, exhausted soldiers when the Emperor was there in person. If all were demoralised and he appeared, his presence was like an electric shock. All shouted &#8220;Vive l&#8217;Empereur!&#8221; and everyone charged blindly into the fire.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    The reader of this biography will understand why this was so.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleon-the-great-andrew-roberts-abridged/">Napoleon the Great &#8211; Andrew Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Without a Face : The Unlikely Rise of Vladimir Putin &#8211; Masha Gessen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-man-without-a-face-the-unlikely-rise-of-vladimir-putin-masha-gessen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-without-a-face-the-unlikely-rise-of-vladimir-putin-masha-gessen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When Vladimir Putin, an unimportant, low-level KGB operative, was rushed to power by a group of Oligarchs in 1999, he was a man without a history. Within a few brief years, Putin had dismantled Russia&#8217;s media, wrested control and wealth from the country&#8217;s burgeoning business class, and decimated the fragile mechanisms of democracy. Virtually every [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-without-a-face-the-unlikely-rise-of-vladimir-putin-masha-gessen-abridged/">The Man Without a Face : The Unlikely Rise of Vladimir Putin &#8211; Masha Gessen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When Vladimir Putin, an unimportant,  low-level KGB operative, was rushed to power by a group of Oligarchs in 1999, he was a man without a history. Within a few brief years, Putin had dismantled Russia&#8217;s media, wrested control and wealth from the country&#8217;s burgeoning business class, and decimated the fragile mechanisms of democracy.  Virtually every obstacle to his unbridled control was removed and every opposing voice silenced, with political rivals and critics driven into exile or to the grave.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on information and sources no other writer has tapped, Masha Gessen&#8217;s fearless account charts Putin&#8217;s rise from the boy who had scrapped his way through post-war Leningrad schoolyards, to the &#8216;faceless&#8217; man who manoeuvred his way into absolute &#8211; and absolutely corrupt &#8211; power.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-without-a-face-the-unlikely-rise-of-vladimir-putin-masha-gessen-abridged/">The Man Without a Face : The Unlikely Rise of Vladimir Putin &#8211; Masha Gessen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ukraine Crisis : What It Means for the West &#8211; Andrew Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ukraine-crisis-what-it-means-for-the-west-andrew-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Armed Conflict]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ukraine-crisis-what-it-means-for-the-west-andrew-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A leading Ukraine specialist and firsthand witness to the 2014 Kiev Uprising analyzes the world&#8217;s newest flashpoint The aftereffects of the February 2014 Uprising in Ukraine are still reverberating around the world. The consequences of the popular rebellion and Russian President Putin&#8217;s attempt to strangle it remain uncertain. In this book, Andrew Wilson combines a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ukraine-crisis-what-it-means-for-the-west-andrew-wilson-abridged/">Ukraine Crisis : What It Means for the West &#8211; Andrew Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A leading Ukraine specialist and firsthand witness to the 2014 Kiev Uprising analyzes the world&#8217;s newest flashpoint    </p>
<p>                     The aftereffects of the February 2014 Uprising in Ukraine are still reverberating around the world. The consequences of the popular rebellion and Russian President Putin&#8217;s attempt to strangle it remain uncertain. In this book, Andrew Wilson combines a spellbinding, on-the-scene account of the Kiev Uprising with a deeply informed analysis of what precipitated the events, what has developed in subsequent months, and why the story is far from over.    </p>
<p>                     Wilson situates Ukraine&#8217;s February insurgence within Russia&#8217;s expansionist ambitions throughout the previous decade. He reveals how President Putin&#8217;s extravagant spending to develop soft power in all parts of Europe was aided by wishful thinking in the EU and American diplomatic inattention, and how Putin&#8217;s agenda continues to be widely misunderstood in the West. The author then examines events in the wake of the Uprising-the military coup in Crimea, the election of President Petro Poroshenko, the Malaysia Airlines tragedy, rising tensions among all of Russia&#8217;s neighbors, both friend and foe, and more. Ukraine Crisis provides an important, accurate record of events that unfolded in Ukraine in 2014. It also rings a clear warning that the unresolved problems of the region have implications well beyond Ukrainian borders.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ukraine-crisis-what-it-means-for-the-west-andrew-wilson-abridged/">Ukraine Crisis : What It Means for the West &#8211; Andrew Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Secondhand Time : The Last of the Soviets &#8211; Svetlana Alexievich, Translated by Bela Shayevich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/secondhand-time-the-last-of-the-soviets-svetlana-alexievich-translated-by-bela-shayevich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/secondhand-time-the-last-of-the-soviets-svetlana-alexievich-translated-by-bela-shayevich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A symphonic oral history about the disintegration of the Soviet Union and the emergence of a new Russia, from Svetlana Alexievich, winner of the Nobel Prize in Literature NAMED ONE OF THE TEN BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY THE WASHINGTON POST AND PUBLISHERS WEEKLY &#8211; LOS ANGELES TIMES BOOK [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secondhand-time-the-last-of-the-soviets-svetlana-alexievich-translated-by-bela-shayevich-abridged/">Secondhand Time : The Last of the Soviets &#8211; Svetlana Alexievich, Translated by Bela Shayevich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A symphonic oral history about the disintegration of the Soviet Union and the emergence of a new Russia, from Svetlana Alexievich, winner of the Nobel Prize in Literature    </p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE TEN BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY THE WASHINGTON POST AND PUBLISHERS WEEKLY &#8211; LOS ANGELES TIMES BOOK PRIZE WINNER    </p>
<p>                     NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY<br />
                    The New York Times &#8211; The Washington Post &#8211; The Boston Globe &#8211; The Wall Street Journal &#8211; NPR &#8211; Financial Times &#8211; Kirkus Reviews    </p>
<p>                     When the Swedish Academy awarded Svetlana Alexievich the Nobel Prize, it cited her for inventing &#8220;a new kind of literary genre,&#8221; describing her work as &#8220;a history of emotions&#8211;a history of the soul.&#8221; Alexievich&#8217;s distinctive documentary style, combining extended individual monologues with a collage of voices, records the stories of ordinary women and men who are rarely given the opportunity to speak, whose experiences are often lost in the official histories of the nation.     </p>
<p>                     In Secondhand Time,  Alexievich chronicles the demise of communism. Everyday Russian citizens recount the past thirty years, showing us what life was like during the fall of the Soviet Union and what it&#8217;s like to live in the new Russia left in its wake. Through interviews spanning 1991 to 2012, Alexievich takes us behind the propaganda and contrived media accounts, giving us a panoramic portrait of contemporary Russia and Russians who still carry memories of oppression, terror, famine, massacres&#8211;but also of pride in their country, hope for the future, and a belief that everyone was working and fighting together to bring about a utopia. Here is an account of life in the aftermath of an idea so powerful it once dominated a third of the world.     </p>
<p>                     A magnificent tapestry of the sorrows and triumphs of the human spirit woven by a master, Secondhand Time tells the stories that together make up the true history of a nation. &#8220;Through the voices of those who confided in her,&#8221; The Nation writes, &#8220;Alexievich tells us about human nature, about our dreams, our choices, about good and evil&#8211;in a word, about ourselves.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Svetlana Alexievich and Secondhand Time     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The nonfiction volume that has done the most to deepen the emotional understanding of Russia during and after the collapse of the Soviet Union of late is Svetlana Alexievich&#8217;s oral history Secondhand Time.&#8221;&#8211;David Remnick, The New Yorker</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/secondhand-time-the-last-of-the-soviets-svetlana-alexievich-translated-by-bela-shayevich-abridged/">Secondhand Time : The Last of the Soviets &#8211; Svetlana Alexievich, Translated by Bela Shayevich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sunflower : On the Possibilities and Limits of Forgiveness &#8211; Simon Wiesenthal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sunflower-on-the-possibilities-and-limits-of-forgiveness-simon-wiesenthal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holocaust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewish Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sunflower-on-the-possibilities-and-limits-of-forgiveness-simon-wiesenthal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Holocaust survivor&#8217;s surprising and thought-provoking study of forgiveness, justice, compassion, and human responsibility, featuring contributions from the Dalai Lama, Harry Wu, Cynthia Ozick, Primo Levi, and more. While imprisoned in a Nazi concentration camp, Simon Wiesenthal was taken one day from his work detail to the bedside of a dying member of the SS. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sunflower-on-the-possibilities-and-limits-of-forgiveness-simon-wiesenthal-abridged/">The Sunflower : On the Possibilities and Limits of Forgiveness &#8211; Simon Wiesenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Holocaust survivor&#8217;s surprising and thought-provoking study of forgiveness, justice, compassion, and human responsibility, featuring contributions from the Dalai Lama, Harry Wu, Cynthia Ozick, Primo Levi, and more.     </p>
<p>                    While imprisoned in a Nazi concentration camp, Simon Wiesenthal was taken one day from his work detail to the bedside of a dying member of the SS. Haunted by the crimes in which he had participated, the soldier wanted to confess to&#8211;and obtain absolution from&#8211;a Jew. Faced with the choice between compassion and justice, silence and truth, Wiesenthal said nothing. But even years after the way had ended, he wondered: Had he done the right thing? What would you have done in his place?     </p>
<p>                    In this important book, fifty-three distinguished men and women respond to Wiesenthal&#8217;s questions. They are theologians, political leaders, writers, jurists, psychiatrists, human rights activists, Holocaust survivors, and victims of attempted genocides in Bosnia, Cambodia, China and Tibet. Their responses, as varied as their experiences of the world, remind us that Wiesenthal&#8217;s questions are not limited to events of the past.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sunflower-on-the-possibilities-and-limits-of-forgiveness-simon-wiesenthal-abridged/">The Sunflower : On the Possibilities and Limits of Forgiveness &#8211; Simon Wiesenthal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blowout : Corrupted Democracy, Rogue State Russia, and the Richest, Most Destructive Industry on Earth &#8211; Rachel Maddow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blowout-corrupted-democracy-rogue-state-russia-and-the-richest-most-destructive-industry-on-earth-rachel-maddow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blowout-corrupted-democracy-rogue-state-russia-and-the-richest-most-destructive-industry-on-earth-rachel-maddow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Big Oil and Gas Versus Democracy&#8211;Winner Take All &#8220;A rollickingly well-written book, filled with fascinating, exciting, and alarming stories about the impact of the oil and gas industry on the world today.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review In 2010, the words &#8220;earthquake swarm&#8221; entered the lexicon in Oklahoma. That [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blowout-corrupted-democracy-rogue-state-russia-and-the-richest-most-destructive-industry-on-earth-rachel-maddow-abridged/">Blowout : Corrupted Democracy, Rogue State Russia, and the Richest, Most Destructive Industry on Earth &#8211; Rachel Maddow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Big Oil and Gas Versus Democracy&#8211;Winner Take All     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A rollickingly well-written book, filled with fascinating, exciting, and alarming stories about the impact of the oil and gas industry on the world today.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review     </p>
<p>                     In 2010, the words &#8220;earthquake swarm&#8221; entered the lexicon in Oklahoma. That same year, a trove of Michael Jackson memorabilia&#8211;including his iconic crystal-encrusted white glove&#8211;was sold at auction for over $1 million to a guy who was, officially, just the lowly forestry minister of the tiny nation of Equatorial Guinea. And in 2014, revolutionaries in Ukraine raided the palace of their ousted president and found a zoo of peacocks, gilded toilets, and a floating restaurant modeled after a Spanish galleon. Unlikely as it might seem, there is a thread connecting these events, and Rachel Maddow follows it to its crooked source: the unimaginably lucrative and equally corrupting oil and gas industry.     </p>
<p>                     With her trademark black humor, Maddow takes us on a switchback journey around the globe, revealing the greed and incompetence of Big Oil and Gas along the way, and drawing a surprising conclusion about why the Russian government hacked the 2016 U.S. election. She deftly shows how Russia&#8217;s rich reserves of crude have, paradoxically, stunted its growth, forcing Vladimir Putin to maintain his power by spreading Russia&#8217;s rot into its rivals, its neighbors, the West&#8217;s most important alliances, and the United States. Chevron, BP, and a host of other industry players get their star turn, most notably ExxonMobil and the deceptively well-behaved Rex Tillerson. The oil and gas industry has weakened democracies in developed and developing countries, fouled oceans and rivers, and propped up authoritarian thieves and killers. But being outraged at it is, according to Maddow, &#8220;like being indignant when a lion takes down and eats a gazelle. You can&#8217;t really blame the lion. It&#8217;s in her nature.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                      Blowout is a call to contain the lion: to stop subsidizing the wealthiest businesses on earth, to fight for transparency, and to check the influence of the world&#8217;s most destructive industry and its enablers. The stakes have never been higher. As Maddow writes, &#8220;Democracy either wins this one or disappears.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blowout-corrupted-democracy-rogue-state-russia-and-the-richest-most-destructive-industry-on-earth-rachel-maddow-abridged/">Blowout : Corrupted Democracy, Rogue State Russia, and the Richest, Most Destructive Industry on Earth &#8211; Rachel Maddow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
