<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Game Theory Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/game-theory/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/game-theory/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Game Theory Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/game-theory/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Infinite Game : From the bestselling author of Start With Why &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-infinite-game-from-the-bestselling-author-of-start-with-why-simon-sinek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-infinite-game-from-the-bestselling-author-of-start-with-why-simon-sinek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER The New York Times-bestselling author of Start With Why, Leaders Eat Last, and Together Is Better offers a bold new approach to business strategy by asking one question: are you playing the finite game or the infinite game? In The Infinite Game, Sinek applies game theory to explore how great businesses [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-infinite-game-from-the-bestselling-author-of-start-with-why-simon-sinek-abridged/">The Infinite Game : From the bestselling author of Start With Why &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The New York Times-bestselling author of Start With Why, Leaders Eat Last, and Together Is Better offers a bold new approach to business strategy by asking one question: are you playing the finite game or the infinite game?     </p>
<p>                    In The Infinite Game, Sinek applies game theory to explore how great businesses achieve long-lasting success. He finds that building long-term value and healthy, enduring growth &#8211; that playing the infinite game &#8211; is the only thing that matters to your business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-infinite-game-from-the-bestselling-author-of-start-with-why-simon-sinek-abridged/">The Infinite Game : From the bestselling author of Start With Why &#8211; Simon Sinek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The million copy international bestseller, critically acclaimed and translated into over 25 languages. As influential today as when it was first published, The Selfish Gene has become a classic exposition of evolutionary thought. Professor Dawkins articulates a gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution &#8211; a view giving centre stage to these persistent units of information, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The million copy international bestseller, critically acclaimed and translated into over 25 languages.    </p>
<p>                    As influential today as when it was first published, The Selfish Gene  has become a classic exposition of evolutionary thought. Professor Dawkins articulates a gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution &#8211; a view giving centre stage to these persistent units of information, and in which organisms can be seen as vehicles for their replication. This imaginative, powerful, and stylistically brilliant work not only brought the insights of Neo-Darwinism to a wide audience, but galvanized the biology<br />
                    community, generating much debate and stimulating whole new areas of research. Forty years later, its insights remain as relevant today as on the day it was published.     </p>
<p>                    This 40th anniversary edition includes a new epilogue from the author discussing the continuing relevance of these ideas in evolutionary biology today, as well as the original prefaces and foreword, and extracts from early reviews.     </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Logic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why do Internet, financial service, and beer commercials dominate Super Bowl advertising? How do political ceremonies establish authority? Why does repetition characterize anthems and ritual speech? Why were circular forms favored for public festivals during the French Revolution? This book answers these questions using a single concept: common knowledge. Game theory shows that in order [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/">Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why do Internet, financial service, and beer commercials dominate Super Bowl advertising? How do political ceremonies establish authority? Why does repetition characterize anthems and ritual speech? Why were circular forms favored for public festivals during the French Revolution? This book answers these questions using a single concept: common knowledge. Game theory shows that in order to coordinate its actions, a group of people must form &#8220;common knowledge.&#8221; Each person wants to participate only if others also participate. Members must have knowledge of each other, knowledge of that knowledge, knowledge of the knowledge of that knowledge, and so on. Michael Chwe applies this insight, with striking erudition, to analyze a range of rituals across history and cultures. He shows that public ceremonies are powerful not simply because they transmit meaning from a central source to each audience member but because they let audience members know what other members know. For instance, people watching the Super Bowl know that many others are seeing precisely what they see and that those people know in turn that many others are also watching.<br />
                    This creates common knowledge, and advertisers selling products that depend on consensus are willing to pay large sums to gain access to it. Remarkably, a great variety of rituals and ceremonies, such as formal inaugurations, work in much the same way. By using a rational-choice argument to explain diverse cultural practices, Chwe argues for a close reciprocal relationship between the perspectives of rationality and culture. He illustrates how game theory can be applied to an unexpectedly broad spectrum of problems, while showing in an admirably clear way what game theory might hold for scholars in the social sciences and humanities who are not yet acquainted with it. In a new afterword, Chwe delves into new applications of common knowledge, both in the real world and in experiments, and considers how generating common knowledge has become easier in the digital age.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/">Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beautiful Game Theory : How Soccer Can Help Economics &#8211; Ignacio Palacios-Huerta (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beautiful-game-theory-how-soccer-can-help-economics-ignacio-palacios-huerta-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football (Soccer, Association Football)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beautiful-game-theory-how-soccer-can-help-economics-ignacio-palacios-huerta-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A wealth of research in recent decades has seen the economic approach to human behavior extended over many areas previously considered to belong to sociology, political science, law, and other fields. Research has also shown that economics can provide insight into many aspects of sports, including soccer. Beautiful Game Theory is the first book that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beautiful-game-theory-how-soccer-can-help-economics-ignacio-palacios-huerta-abridged/">Beautiful Game Theory : How Soccer Can Help Economics &#8211; Ignacio Palacios-Huerta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A wealth of research in recent decades has seen the economic approach to human behavior extended over many areas previously considered to belong to sociology, political science, law, and other fields. Research has also shown that economics can provide insight into many aspects of sports, including soccer. Beautiful Game Theory is the first book that uses soccer to test economic theories and document novel human behavior.  In this brilliant and entertaining book, Ignacio Palacios-Huerta illuminates economics through the world&#8217;s most popular sport. He offers unique and often startling insights into game theory and microeconomics, covering topics such as mixed strategies, discrimination, incentives, and human preferences. He also looks at finance, experimental economics, behavioral economics, and neuroeconomics. Soccer provides rich data sets and environments that shed light on universal economic principles in interesting and useful ways.  Essential reading for students, researchers, and sports enthusiasts, Beautiful Game Theory is the first book to show what soccer can do for economics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beautiful-game-theory-how-soccer-can-help-economics-ignacio-palacios-huerta-abridged/">Beautiful Game Theory : How Soccer Can Help Economics &#8211; Ignacio Palacios-Huerta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Beautiful Mind &#8211; Sylvia Nasar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-beautiful-mind-sylvia-nasar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-beautiful-mind-sylvia-nasar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Beautiful Mind is Sylvia Nasar&#8217;s award-winning biography about the mystery of the human mind, the triumph over incredible adversity, and the healing power of love. At the age of thirty-one, John Nash, mathematical genius, suffered a devastating breakdown and was diagnosed with schizophrenia. Yet after decades of leading a ghost-like existence, he was to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-beautiful-mind-sylvia-nasar-abridged/">A Beautiful Mind &#8211; Sylvia Nasar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Beautiful Mind is Sylvia Nasar&#8217;s award-winning biography about the mystery of the human mind, the triumph over incredible adversity, and the healing power of love.    </p>
<p>                    At the age of thirty-one, John Nash, mathematical genius, suffered a devastating breakdown and was diagnosed with schizophrenia. Yet after decades of leading a ghost-like existence, he was to re-emerge to win a Nobel Prize and world acclaim. A Beautiful Mind has inspired the Oscar-winning film directed by Ron Howard and featuring Russell Crowe in the lead role of John Nash.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-beautiful-mind-sylvia-nasar-abridged/">A Beautiful Mind &#8211; Sylvia Nasar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
