<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Web Graphics &amp; Design Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/web-graphics-design/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/web-graphics-design/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Web Graphics &amp; Design Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/web-graphics-design/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>You Should Test That : Conversion Optimization for More Leads, Sales and Profit or The Art and Science of Optimized Marketing &#8211; Chris Goward (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to convert website visitors into customers Part science and part art, conversion optimization is designed to turn visitors into customers. Carefully developed testing procedures are necessary to help you fine-tune images, headlines, navigation, colors, buttons, and every other element, creating a website that encourages visitors to take the action you seek. This book [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/">You Should Test That : Conversion Optimization for More Leads, Sales and Profit or The Art and Science of Optimized Marketing &#8211; Chris Goward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to convert website visitors into customers Part science and part art, conversion optimization is designed to turn visitors into customers. Carefully developed testing procedures are necessary to help you fine-tune images, headlines, navigation, colors, buttons, and every other element, creating a website that encourages visitors to take the action you seek. This book guides you through creating an optimization strategy that supports your business goals, using appropriate analytics tools, generating quality testing ideas, running online experiments, and making the adjustments that work.<br />
                    * Conversion optimization is part science and part art; this guide provides step-by-step guidance to help you optimize your website for maximum conversion rates * Explains how to analyze data, prioritize experiment opportunities, and choose the right testing methods * Helps you learn what to adjust, how to do it, and how to analyze the results * Features hands-on exercises, case studies, and a full-color insert reinforcing key tactics * Author has used these techniques to assist Fortune 500 clients You Should Test That explains both the &#8220;why&#8221; and the &#8220;how&#8221; of conversion optimization, helping you maximize the value of your website.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-should-test-that-conversion-optimization-for-more-leads-sales-and-profit-or-the-art-and-science-of-optimized-marketing-chris-goward-abridged/">You Should Test That : Conversion Optimization for More Leads, Sales and Profit or The Art and Science of Optimized Marketing &#8211; Chris Goward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lean UX : Creating Great Products with Agile Teams &#8211; Jeff Gothelf, Josh Seiden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lean UX is synonymous with modern product design and development. By combining human-centric design, agile ways of working, and a strong business sense, designers, product managers, developers, and scrum masters around the world are making Lean UX the leading approach for digital product teams today In the third edition of this award-winning book, authors Jeff [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/">Lean UX : Creating Great Products with Agile Teams &#8211; Jeff Gothelf, Josh Seiden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lean UX is synonymous with modern product design and development. By combining human-centric design, agile ways of working, and a strong business sense, designers, product managers, developers, and scrum masters around the world are making Lean UX the leading approach for digital product teams today    </p>
<p>                    In the third edition of this award-winning book, authors Jeff Gothelf and Josh Seiden help you focus on the product experience rather than deliverables. You&#8217;ll learn tactics for integrating user experience design, product discovery, agile methods, and product management. And you&#8217;ll discover how to drive your design in short, iterative cycles to assess what works best for businesses and users. Lean UX guides you through this change&#8211;for the better.    </p>
<p>                    Facilitate the Lean UX process with your team with the Lean UX Canvas<br />
                    Ensure every project starts with clear customer-centric success criteria<br />
                    Understand the role of the designer on an agile team<br />
                    Write and contribute design and experiment stories to the backlog<br />
                    Ensure design work takes place in every sprint<br />
                    Build product discovery into the team&#8217;s &#8220;velocity&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/">Lean UX : Creating Great Products with Agile Teams &#8211; Jeff Gothelf, Josh Seiden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>User experience (UX) strategy lies at the intersection of UX design and business strategy, but until now, there hasn&#8217;t been an easy-to-apply framework for executing it. This hands-on guide introduces lightweight product strategy tools and techniques to help you and your team devise innovative digital solutions that people want. Author Jaime Levy shows UX/UI designers, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/">UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>User experience (UX) strategy lies at the intersection of UX design and business strategy, but until now, there hasn&#8217;t been an easy-to-apply framework for executing it. This hands-on guide introduces lightweight product strategy tools and techniques to help you and your team devise innovative digital solutions that people want.    </p>
<p>                    Author Jaime Levy shows UX/UI designers, product managers, entrepreneurs, and aspiring strategists simple to advanced methods that can be applied right away. You&#8217;ll gain valuable perspective through business cases and historical context. This second edition includes new real-world examples, updated techniques, and a chapter on conducting qualitative online user research.    </p>
<p>                    Define value propositions and validate target users through provisional personas and customer discovery techniques<br />
                    Explore marketplace opportunities by conducting competitive research and analysis<br />
                    Design experiments using rapid prototypes that are focused on the business model<br />
                    Conduct online user research to gain valuable insights quickly on any budget<br />
                    Test business ideas and validate marketing channels by running online advertising and landing page campaigns</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ux-strategy-product-strategy-techniques-for-devising-innovative-digital-solutions-jaime-levy-abridged/">UX Strategy : Product Strategy Techniques for Devising Innovative Digital Solutions &#8211; Jaime Levy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blog, Inc. : Blogging for Passion, Profit, and to Create Community &#8211; Joy Deangdeelert Cho, Foreword by Grace Bonney, Contributions by Meg Mateo Ilasco (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphical & Digital Media Applications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With roughly 95,000 blogs launched worldwide every 24 hours (BlogPulse), making a fledgling site stand out isn&#8217;t easy. This authoritative handbook gives creative hopefuls a leg up. Joy Cho, of the award-winning Oh Joy!, offers expert advice on starting and growing a blog, from design and finance to overcoming blogger&#8217;s block, attracting readers, and more. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/">Blog, Inc. : Blogging for Passion, Profit, and to Create Community &#8211; Joy Deangdeelert Cho, Foreword by Grace Bonney, Contributions by Meg Mateo Ilasco (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With roughly 95,000 blogs launched worldwide every 24 hours (BlogPulse), making a fledgling site stand out isn&#8217;t easy. This authoritative handbook gives creative hopefuls a leg up. Joy Cho, of the award-winning Oh Joy!, offers expert advice on starting and growing a blog, from design and finance to overcoming blogger&#8217;s block, attracting readers, and more. With a foreword from Grace Bonney of Design*Sponge plus expert interviews, this book will fine-tune what the next generation of bloggers shares with the world. Learn how to design your site, choose the right platform, attract a fan base, finance your blog, maintain work/life balance, manage comments, find content inspiration, overcome blogger&#8217;s block, choose the right ads, develop a voice, protect your work, create a media kit, leverage your social network, take better photographs, set up an affiliate program, partner with sponsors, build community, go full-time with your blog, and more!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blog-inc-blogging-for-passion-profit-and-to-create-community-joy-deangdeelert-cho-foreword-by-grace-bonney-contributions-by-meg-mateo-ilasco-abridged/">Blog, Inc. : Blogging for Passion, Profit, and to Create Community &#8211; Joy Deangdeelert Cho, Foreword by Grace Bonney, Contributions by Meg Mateo Ilasco (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>100 Things Every Designer Needs to Know About People &#8211; Susan Weinschenk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Desktop Publishing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WE DESIGN TO ELICIT RESPONSES from people. We want them to buy something, read more, or take action of some kind. Designing without understanding what makes people act the way they do is like exploring a new city without a map: results will be haphazard, confusing, and inefficient. This book combines real science and research [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/">100 Things Every Designer Needs to Know About People &#8211; Susan Weinschenk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WE DESIGN TO ELICIT RESPONSES from people. We want them to buy something, read more, or take action of some kind. Designing without understanding what makes people act the way they do is like exploring a new city without a map: results will be haphazard, confusing, and inefficient. This book combines real science and research with practical examples to deliver a guide every designer needs. With this book you&#8217;ll design more intuitive and engaging apps, software, websites and products that match the way people think, decide and behave.    </p>
<p>                      INCREASE THE EFFECTIVENESS OF YOUR PRODUCTS.    </p>
<p>                      Apply psychology and behavioral science to your designs.    </p>
<p>                      Here are some of the questions this book will answer:    </p>
<p>                      * What grabs and holds attention.    </p>
<p>                      * What makes memories stick?    </p>
<p>                      * What is more important, peripheral or central vision?    </p>
<p>                      * Can you predict the types of errors people will make?    </p>
<p>                      * What is the limit to someone&#8217;s social circle?    </p>
<p>                      * What line length for text is best?    </p>
<p>                      * Are some fonts better than others?    </p>
<p>                      These are just a few of the questions that the book answers in its deep-dive exploration of what makes people tick.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/">100 Things Every Designer Needs to Know About People &#8211; Susan Weinschenk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
