<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>True Stories Of Heroism, Endurance &amp; Survival Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/true-stories-of-heroism-endurance-survival/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/true-stories-of-heroism-endurance-survival/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>True Stories Of Heroism, Endurance &amp; Survival Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/true-stories-of-heroism-endurance-survival/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Desert and the Sea : 977 Days Captive on the Somali Pirate Coast &#8211; Michael Scott Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-desert-and-the-sea-977-days-captive-on-the-somali-pirate-coast-michael-scott-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories Of Heroism, Endurance & Survival]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-desert-and-the-sea-977-days-captive-on-the-somali-pirate-coast-michael-scott-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Scott Moore, a journalist and the author of Sweetness and Blood, incorporates personal narrative and rigorous investigative journalism in this profound and revelatory memoir of his three-year captivity by Somali pirates-a riveting,thoughtful, and emotionally resonant exploration of foreign policy, religious extremism, and the costs of survival. In January 2012, having covered a Somali pirate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-desert-and-the-sea-977-days-captive-on-the-somali-pirate-coast-michael-scott-moore-abridged/">The Desert and the Sea : 977 Days Captive on the Somali Pirate Coast &#8211; Michael Scott Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Scott Moore, a journalist and the author of Sweetness and Blood, incorporates personal narrative and rigorous investigative journalism in this profound and revelatory memoir of his three-year captivity by Somali pirates-a riveting,thoughtful, and emotionally resonant exploration of foreign policy, religious extremism, and the costs of survival.    </p>
<p>                    In January 2012, having covered a Somali pirate trial in Hamburg for Spiegel Online International-and funded by a grant from the Pulitzer Center on Crisis Reporting-Michael Scott Moore traveled to the Horn of Africa to write about piracy and ways to end it. In a terrible twist of fate, Moore himself was kidnapped and subsequently held captive by Somali pirates. Subjected to conditions that break even the strongest spirits-physical injury, starvation, isolation, terror-Moore&#8217;s survival is a testament to his indomitable strength of mind. In September 2014, after 977 days, he walked free when his ransom was put together by the help of several US and German institutions, friends, colleagues, and his strong-willed mother.     </p>
<p>                    Yet Moore&#8217;s own struggle is only part of the story: The Desert and the Sea falls at the intersection of reportage, memoir, and history. Caught between Muslim pirates, the looming threat of Al-Shabaab, and the rise of ISIS, Moore observes the worlds that surrounded him-the economics and history of piracy; the effects of post-colonialism; the politics of hostage negotiation and ransom; while also conjuring the various faces of Islam-and places his ordeal in the context of the larger political and historical issues.               </p>
<p>                    A sort of Catch-22 meets Black Hawk Down, The Desert and the Sea is written with dark humor, candor, and a journalist&#8217;s clinical distance and eye for detail. Moore offers an intimate and otherwise inaccessible view of life as we cannot fathom it, brilliantly weaving his own experience as a hostage with the social, economic, religious, and political factors creating it. The Desert and the Sea is wildly compelling and a book that will take its place next to titles like Den of Lions and Even Silence Has an End.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-desert-and-the-sea-977-days-captive-on-the-somali-pirate-coast-michael-scott-moore-abridged/">The Desert and the Sea : 977 Days Captive on the Somali Pirate Coast &#8211; Michael Scott Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Boys In The Boat : An Epic Journey to the Heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin &#8211; Daniel James Brown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Boating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olympic Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rowing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories Of Heroism, Endurance & Survival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Sports & Recreations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year, this is the bestselling story about a rowing team&#8217;s quest for Olympic gold in Nazi Germany. Cast aside by his family at an early age, abandoned and left to fend for himself in the woods of Washington State, young Joe Rantz turns to rowing as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/">The Boys In The Boat : An Epic Journey to the Heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin &#8211; Daniel James Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year, this is the bestselling story about a rowing team&#8217;s quest for Olympic gold in Nazi Germany.     </p>
<p>                    Cast aside by his family at an early age, abandoned and left to fend for himself in the woods of Washington State, young Joe Rantz turns to rowing as a way of escaping his past.    </p>
<p>                     What follows is an extraordinary journey, as Joe and eight other working-class boys exchange the sweat and dust of life in 1930s America for the promise of glory at the heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin. Stroke by stroke, a remarkable young man strives to regain his shattered self-regard, to dare again to trust in others &#8211; and to find his way back home.    </p>
<p>                     Told against the backdrop of the Great Depression, Daniel James Brown&#8217;s The Boys in the Boat is narrative non-fiction of the first order; a personal story full of lyricism and unexpected beauty that rises above the grand sweep of history, and captures instead the purest essence of what it means to be alive.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;I really can&#8217;t rave enough about this book . . . I read the last fifty pages with white knuckles, and the last twenty-five with tears in my eyes&#8217; &#8211; David Laskin, author of The Children&#8217;s Blizzard and The Long Way Home.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/">The Boys In The Boat : An Epic Journey to the Heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin &#8211; Daniel James Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
