<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Applied Mathematics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/applied-mathematics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/applied-mathematics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Applied Mathematics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/applied-mathematics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>A Mind for Numbers : How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra) &#8211; Barbara Oakley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The companion book to COURSERA(R)&#8217;s wildly popular massive open online course Learning How to Learn Whether you are a student struggling to fulfill a math or science requirement, or you are embarking on a career change that requires a new skill set, A Mind for Numbers offers the tools you need to get a better [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/">A Mind for Numbers : How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra) &#8211; Barbara Oakley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The companion book to COURSERA(R)&#8217;s wildly popular massive open online course Learning How to Learn     </p>
<p>                    Whether you are a student struggling to fulfill a math or science requirement, or you are embarking on a career change that requires a new skill set, A Mind for Numbers offers the tools you need to get a better grasp of that intimidating material. Engineering professor Barbara Oakley knows firsthand how it feels to struggle with math. She flunked her way through high school math and science courses, before enlisting in the army immediately after graduation. When she saw how her lack of mathematical and technical savvy severely limited her options&#8211;both to rise in the military and to explore other careers&#8211;she returned to school with a newfound determination to re-tool her brain to master the very subjects that had given her so much trouble throughout her entire life.     </p>
<p>                     In A Mind for Numbers, Dr. Oakley lets us in on the secrets to learning effectively&#8211;secrets that even dedicated and successful students wish they&#8217;d known earlier. Contrary to popular belief, math requires creative, as well as analytical, thinking. Most people think that there&#8217;s only one way to do a problem, when in actuality, there are often a number of different solutions&#8211;you just need the creativity to see them. For example, there are more than three hundred different known proofs of the Pythagorean Theorem. In short, studying a problem in a laser-focused way until you reach a solution is not an effective way to learn. Rather, it involves taking the time to step away from a problem and allow the more relaxed and creative part of the brain to take over. The learning strategies in this book apply not only to math and science, but to any subject in which we struggle. We all have what it takes to excel in areas that don&#8217;t seem to come naturally to us at first, and learning them does not have to be as painful as we might think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/">A Mind for Numbers : How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra) &#8211; Barbara Oakley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Not to Be Wrong : The Hidden Maths of Everyday Life &#8211; Jordan Ellenberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-not-to-be-wrong-the-hidden-maths-of-everyday-life-jordan-ellenberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematical Foundations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-not-to-be-wrong-the-hidden-maths-of-everyday-life-jordan-ellenberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER The maths we learn in school can seem like an abstract set of rules, laid down by the ancients and not to be questioned. In fact, Jordan Ellenberg shows us, maths touches on everything we do, and a little mathematical knowledge reveals the hidden structures that lie beneath the world&#8217;s messy [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-be-wrong-the-hidden-maths-of-everyday-life-jordan-ellenberg-abridged/">How Not to Be Wrong : The Hidden Maths of Everyday Life &#8211; Jordan Ellenberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The maths we learn in school can seem like an abstract set of rules, laid down by the ancients and not to be questioned. In fact, Jordan Ellenberg shows us, maths touches on everything we do, and a little mathematical knowledge reveals the hidden structures that lie beneath the world&#8217;s messy and chaotic surface. In How Not to be Wrong, Ellenberg explores the mathematician&#8217;s method of analyzing life, from the everyday to the cosmic, showing us which numbers to defend, which ones to ignore, and when to change the equation entirely. Along the way, he explains calculus in a single page, describes Goedel&#8217;s theorem using only one-syllable words, and reveals how early you actually need to get to the airport.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-not-to-be-wrong-the-hidden-maths-of-everyday-life-jordan-ellenberg-abridged/">How Not to Be Wrong : The Hidden Maths of Everyday Life &#8211; Jordan Ellenberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Mathematics of Love : Patterns, Proofs, and the Search for the Ultimate Equation &#8211; Hannah Fry (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-mathematics-of-love-patterns-proofs-and-the-search-for-the-ultimate-equation-hannah-fry-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-mathematics-of-love-patterns-proofs-and-the-search-for-the-ultimate-equation-hannah-fry-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this must-have for anyone who wants to better understand their love life, a mathematician pulls back the curtain and reveals the hidden patterns&#8211;from dating sites to divorce, sex to marriage&#8211;behind the rituals of love. The roller coaster of romance is hard to quantify; defining how lovers might feel from a set of simple equations [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mathematics-of-love-patterns-proofs-and-the-search-for-the-ultimate-equation-hannah-fry-abridged/">The Mathematics of Love : Patterns, Proofs, and the Search for the Ultimate Equation &#8211; Hannah Fry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this must-have for anyone who wants to better understand their love life, a mathematician pulls back the curtain and reveals the hidden patterns&#8211;from dating sites to divorce, sex to marriage&#8211;behind the rituals of love.     </p>
<p>                    The roller coaster of romance is hard to quantify; defining how lovers might feel from a set of simple equations is impossible. But that doesn&#8217;t mean that mathematics isn&#8217;t a crucial tool for understanding love.     </p>
<p>                    Love, like most things in life, is full of patterns. And mathematics is ultimately the study of patterns&#8211;from predicting the weather to the fluctuations of the stock market, the movement of planets or the growth of cities. These patterns twist and turn and warp and evolve just as the rituals of love do.     </p>
<p>                    In The Mathematics of Love, Dr. Hannah Fry takes the reader on a fascinating journey through the patterns that define our love lives, applying mathematical formulas to the most common yet complex questions pertaining to love: What&#8217;s the chance of finding love? What&#8217;s the probability that it will last? How do online dating algorithms work, exactly? Can game theory help us decide who to approach in a bar? At what point in your dating life should you settle down?     </p>
<p>                    From evaluating the best strategies for online dating to defining the nebulous concept of beauty, Dr. Fry proves&#8211;with great insight, wit, and fun&#8211;that math is a surprisingly useful tool to negotiate the complicated, often baffling, sometimes infuriating, always interesting, mysteries of love.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-mathematics-of-love-patterns-proofs-and-the-search-for-the-ultimate-equation-hannah-fry-abridged/">The Mathematics of Love : Patterns, Proofs, and the Search for the Ultimate Equation &#8211; Hannah Fry (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Soccermatics : Mathematical Adventures in the Beautiful Game Pro-Edition &#8211; David Sumpter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/soccermatics-mathematical-adventures-in-the-beautiful-game-pro-edition-david-sumpter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Football (Soccer, Association Football)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/soccermatics-mathematical-adventures-in-the-beautiful-game-pro-edition-david-sumpter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Football looked at in a very different way&#8217; Pat Nevin, former Chelsea and Everton star and football media analyst Football &#8211; the most mathematical of sports. From shot statistics and league tables to the geometry of passing and managerial strategy, the modern game is filled with numbers, patterns and shapes. How do we make sense [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/soccermatics-mathematical-adventures-in-the-beautiful-game-pro-edition-david-sumpter-abridged/">Soccermatics : Mathematical Adventures in the Beautiful Game Pro-Edition &#8211; David Sumpter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Football looked at in a very different way&#8217; Pat Nevin, former Chelsea and Everton star and football media analyst    </p>
<p>                    Football &#8211; the most mathematical of sports. From shot statistics and league tables to the geometry of passing and managerial strategy, the modern game is filled with numbers, patterns and shapes. How do we make sense of them? The answer lies in the mathematical models applied in biology, physics and economics.     </p>
<p>                    Soccermatics brings football and mathematics together in a mind-bending synthesis, using numbers to help reveal the inner workings of the beautiful game.    </p>
<p>                    This new and expanded edition analyses the current big-name players and teams using mathematics, and meets the professionals working inside football who use numbers and statistics to boost performance.    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to the world of mathematical modelling, expressed brilliantly by David Sumpter through the prism of football. No matter who you follow &#8211; from your local non-league side to the big boys of the Premiership, La Liga, the Bundesliga, Serie A or the MLS &#8211; you&#8217;ll be amazed at what mathematics has to teach us about the world&#8217;s favourite sport.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/soccermatics-mathematical-adventures-in-the-beautiful-game-pro-edition-david-sumpter-abridged/">Soccermatics : Mathematical Adventures in the Beautiful Game Pro-Edition &#8211; David Sumpter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Pursuit of the Unknown &#8211; Ian Stewart (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-pursuit-of-the-unknown-ian-stewart-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Calculus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relativity Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wave Mechanics (vibration & Acoustics)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-pursuit-of-the-unknown-ian-stewart-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most people are familiar with history&#8217;s great equations: Newton&#8217;s Law of Gravity, for instance, or Einstein&#8217;s theory of relativity. But the way these mathematical breakthroughs have contributed to human progress is seldom appreciated. In In Pursuit of the Unknown, celebrated mathematician Ian Stewart untangles the roots of our most important mathematical statements to show that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-pursuit-of-the-unknown-ian-stewart-abridged/">In Pursuit of the Unknown &#8211; Ian Stewart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most people are familiar with history&#8217;s great equations: Newton&#8217;s Law of Gravity, for instance, or Einstein&#8217;s theory of relativity. But the way these mathematical breakthroughs have contributed to human progress is seldom appreciated. In In Pursuit of the Unknown, celebrated mathematician Ian Stewart untangles the roots of our most important mathematical statements to show that equations have long been a driving force behind nearly every aspect of our lives. Using seventeen of our most crucial equations&#8211;including the Wave Equation that allowed engineers to measure a building&#8217;s response to earthquakes, saving countless lives, and the Black-Scholes model, used by bankers to track the price of financial derivatives over time&#8211;Stewart illustrates that many of the advances we now take for granted were made possible by mathematical discoveries. An approachable, lively, and informative guide to the mathematical building blocks of modern life, In Pursuit of the Unknown is a penetrating exploration of how we have also used equations to make sense of, and in turn influence, our world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-pursuit-of-the-unknown-ian-stewart-abridged/">In Pursuit of the Unknown &#8211; Ian Stewart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
