<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Peace Studies &amp; Conflict Resolution Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/peace-studies-conflict-resolution/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/peace-studies-conflict-resolution/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Peace Studies &amp; Conflict Resolution Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/peace-studies-conflict-resolution/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Blueprint for Revolution : How to Use Rice Pudding, Lego Men, and Other Nonviolent Techniques to Galvanize Communities, Overthrow Dictators, or Simply Change the World &#8211; Srdja Popovic, Matthew Miller (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blueprint-for-revolution-how-to-use-rice-pudding-lego-men-and-other-nonviolent-techniques-to-galvanize-communities-overthrow-dictators-or-simply-change-the-world-srdja-popovic-matthew-miller/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blueprint-for-revolution-how-to-use-rice-pudding-lego-men-and-other-nonviolent-techniques-to-galvanize-communities-overthrow-dictators-or-simply-change-the-world-srdja-popovic-matthew-miller/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An urgent and accessible handbook for peaceful protesters, activists, and community organizers&#8211;anyone trying to defend their rights, hold their government accountable, or change the world Blueprint for Revolution will teach you how to &#8211; make oppression backfire by playing your opponents&#8217; strongest card against them &#8211; identify the &#8220;almighty pillars of power&#8221; in order to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blueprint-for-revolution-how-to-use-rice-pudding-lego-men-and-other-nonviolent-techniques-to-galvanize-communities-overthrow-dictators-or-simply-change-the-world-srdja-popovic-matthew-miller/">Blueprint for Revolution : How to Use Rice Pudding, Lego Men, and Other Nonviolent Techniques to Galvanize Communities, Overthrow Dictators, or Simply Change the World &#8211; Srdja Popovic, Matthew Miller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An urgent and accessible handbook for peaceful protesters, activists, and community organizers&#8211;anyone trying to defend their rights, hold their government accountable, or change the world  Blueprint for Revolution will teach you how to<br />
                     &#8211; make oppression backfire by playing your opponents&#8217; strongest card against them<br />
                     &#8211; identify the &#8220;almighty pillars of power&#8221; in order to shift the balance of control<br />
                     &#8211; dream big, but start small: learn how to pick battles you can win<br />
                     &#8211; listen to what people actually care about in order to incorporate their needs into your revolutionary vision<br />
                     &#8211; master the art of compromise to bring together even the most disparate groups<br />
                     &#8211; recognize your allies and view your enemies as potential partners<br />
                     &#8211; use humor to make yourself heard, defuse potentially violent situations, and &#8220;laugh your way to victory&#8221;  Praise for Blueprint for Revolution &#8220;The title is no exaggeration. Otpor&#8217;s methods . . . have been adopted by democracy movements around the world. The Egyptian opposition used them to topple Hosni Mubarak. In Lebanon, the Serbs helped the Cedar Revolution extricate the country from Syrian control. In Maldives, their methods were the key to overthrowing a dictator who had held power for thirty years. In many other countries, people have used what Canvas teaches to accomplish other political goals, such as fighting corruption or protecting the environment.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times &#8220;A clear, well-constructed, and easily applicable set of principles for any David facing any Goliath (sans slingshot, of course) . . . By the end of Blueprint,  the idea that a punch is no match for a punch line feels like anything but a joke.&#8221;&#8211;The Boston Globe &#8220;An entertaining primer on the theory and practice of peaceful protest.&#8221;&#8211;The Guardian  &#8220;With this wonderful book, Srdja Popovic is inspiring ordinary people facing injustice and oppression to use this tool kit to challenge their oppressors and create something much better. When I was growing up, we dreamed that young people could bring down those who misused their power and create a more just and democratic society. For Srdja Popovic, living in Belgrade in 1998, this same dream was potentially a much more dangerous idea. But with an extraordinarily courageous group of students that formed Otpor!, Srdja used imagination, invention, cunning, and lots of humor to create a movement that not only succeeded in toppling the brutal dictator Slobodan Milosevic but has become a blueprint for nonviolent revolution around the world. Srdja rules!&#8221;&#8211;Peter Gabriel  &#8220;Blueprint for Revolution is not only a spirited guide to changing the world but a breakthrough in the annals of advice for those who seek justice and democracy. It asks (and not heavy-handedly): As long as you want to change the world, why not do it joyfully? It&#8217;s not just funny. It&#8217;s seriously funny. No joke.&#8221;&#8211;Todd Gitlin, author of The Sixties and Occupy Nation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blueprint-for-revolution-how-to-use-rice-pudding-lego-men-and-other-nonviolent-techniques-to-galvanize-communities-overthrow-dictators-or-simply-change-the-world-srdja-popovic-matthew-miller/">Blueprint for Revolution : How to Use Rice Pudding, Lego Men, and Other Nonviolent Techniques to Galvanize Communities, Overthrow Dictators, or Simply Change the World &#8211; Srdja Popovic, Matthew Miller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Growth]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why our democracies need urgent reform, before it&#8217;s too late A generation after the fall of the Berlin Wall, the world is once again on the edge of chaos. Demonstrations have broken out from Belgium to Brazil led by angry citizens demanding a greater say in their political and economic future, better education, heathcare and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/">Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why our democracies need urgent reform, before it&#8217;s too late    </p>
<p>                    A generation after the fall of the Berlin Wall, the world is once again on the edge of chaos. Demonstrations have broken out from Belgium to Brazil led by angry citizens demanding a greater say in their political and economic future, better education, heathcare and living standards. The bottom line of this outrage is the same; people are demanding their governments do more to improve their lives faster, something which policymakers are unable to deliver under conditions of anaemic growth. Rising income inequality and a stagnant economy are threats to both the developed and the developing world, and leaders can no longer afford to ignore this gathering storm.    </p>
<p>                    In Edge of Chaos, Dambisa Moyo sets out the new political and economic challenges facing the world, and the specific, radical solutions needed to resolve these issues and reignite global growth. Dambisa enumerates the four headwinds of demographics, inequality, commodity scarcity and technological innovation that are driving social and economic unrest, and argues for a fundamental retooling of democratic capitalism to address current problems and deliver better outcomes in the future. In the twenty-first century, a crisis in one country can quickly become our own, and fragile economies produce a fragile international community. Edge of Chaos is a warning for advanced and emerging nations alike: we must reverse the dramatic erosion in growth, or face the consequences of a fragmented and unstable global future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/edge-of-chaos-dambisa-moyo-abridged/">Edge of Chaos &#8211; Dambisa Moyo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man, the State, and War : A Theoretical Analysis &#8211; Kenneth Waltz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What are the causes of war? To answer this question, Professor Waltz examines the ideas of major thinkers throughout the history of Western civilization. He explores works both by classic political philosophers, such as St. Augustine, Hobbes, Kant, and Rousseau, and by modern psychologists and anthropologists to discover ideas intended to explain war among states [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/">Man, the State, and War : A Theoretical Analysis &#8211; Kenneth Waltz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What are the causes of war? To answer this question, Professor Waltz examines the ideas of major thinkers throughout the history of Western civilization. He explores works both by classic political philosophers, such as St. Augustine, Hobbes, Kant, and Rousseau, and by modern psychologists and anthropologists to discover ideas intended to explain war among states and related prescriptions for peace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/">Man, the State, and War : A Theoretical Analysis &#8211; Kenneth Waltz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of the most important books of our modern era&#8221; -Amb. Jaime de Bourbon For anyone struggling with conflict, this book can transform you. Negotiating the Nonnegotiable takes you on a journey into the heart and soul of conflict, providing unique insight into the emotional undercurrents that too often sweep us out to sea. With [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/">Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of the most important books of our modern era&#8221; -Amb. Jaime de Bourbon    </p>
<p>                    For anyone struggling with conflict, this book can transform you. Negotiating the Nonnegotiable takes you on a journey into the heart and soul of conflict, providing unique insight into the emotional undercurrents that too often sweep us out to sea. With vivid stories of his closed-door sessions with warring political groups, disputing businesspeople, and families in crisis, Daniel Shapiro presents a universally applicable method to successfully navigate conflict.  A deep, provocative book to reflect on and wrestle with, this book can change your life.    </p>
<p>                     Be warned: This book is not a quick fix. Real change takes work. You will learn how to master five emotional dynamics that can sabotage conflict outside your awareness:    </p>
<p>                    1. Vertigo: How can you avoid      getting emotionally consumed in conflict?<br />
                    2. Repetition compulsion: How can you stop      repeating the same conflicts again and again?<br />
                    3. Taboos: How can you discuss      sensitive issues at the heart of the conflict?<br />
                    4. Assault on the sacred: What should you do if      your values feel threatened?<br />
                    5. Identity politics: What can you do if      others use politics against you?     </p>
<p>                    In our era of discontent, this is just the book we need to resolve conflict in our own lives and in the world around us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/negotiating-the-nonnegotiable-how-to-resolve-your-most-emotionally-charged-conflicts-daniel-shapiro-abridged/">Negotiating the Nonnegotiable : How to Resolve Your Most Emotionally Charged Conflicts &#8211; Daniel Shapiro (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mighty Be Our Powers : How Sisterhood, Prayer, and Sex Changed a Nation at War &#8211; Carol Mithers, Leymah Gbowee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mighty-be-our-powers-how-sisterhood-prayer-and-sex-changed-a-nation-at-war-carol-mithers-leymah-gbowee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mighty-be-our-powers-how-sisterhood-prayer-and-sex-changed-a-nation-at-war-carol-mithers-leymah-gbowee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The winner of the Nobel Peace Prize shares her inspirational, powerful story of how a group of women working together created an unstoppable force that brought peace to Liberia. As a young woman, Leymah Gbowee was broken by the Liberian civil war, a brutal conflict that destroyed her country and claimed the lives of countless [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mighty-be-our-powers-how-sisterhood-prayer-and-sex-changed-a-nation-at-war-carol-mithers-leymah-gbowee-abridged/">Mighty Be Our Powers : How Sisterhood, Prayer, and Sex Changed a Nation at War &#8211; Carol Mithers, Leymah Gbowee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The winner of the Nobel Peace Prize shares her inspirational, powerful story of how a group of women working together created an unstoppable force that brought peace to Liberia.     </p>
<p>                     As a young woman, Leymah Gbowee was broken by the Liberian civil war, a brutal conflict that destroyed her country and claimed the lives of countless relatives and friends. Propelled by her realization that it is women and girls who suffer most during conflicts, she found the courage to turn her bitterness into action.     </p>
<p>                     She helped organize and then lead the Liberian Mass Action for Peace, which brought together Christian and Muslim women in a nonviolent movement that engaged in public protest, confronted Liberia&#8217;s ruthless president and rebel warlords, and even held a sex strike.     </p>
<p>                     With an army of women, Gbowee helped lead her nation to peace-and became an international leader who changed history, won the Nobel Peace Prize for her work, and fiercely advocates for girls&#8217; empowerment and leadership. Mighty Be Our Powers is the gripping chronicle of a journey from hopelessness to liberation that will touch all who dream of a better world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mighty-be-our-powers-how-sisterhood-prayer-and-sex-changed-a-nation-at-war-carol-mithers-leymah-gbowee-abridged/">Mighty Be Our Powers : How Sisterhood, Prayer, and Sex Changed a Nation at War &#8211; Carol Mithers, Leymah Gbowee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Anatomy of Peace : How to Resolve the Heart of Conflict &#8211; The Arbinger Institute (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-anatomy-of-peace-how-to-resolve-the-heart-of-conflict-the-arbinger-institute-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-anatomy-of-peace-how-to-resolve-the-heart-of-conflict-the-arbinger-institute-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Anatomy of Peace will instil hope and inspire reconciliation. Through a series of moving stories about once-bitter enemies reunited, it shows us how we routinely misunderstand the causes of conflict &#8211; and perpetuate the very problems we&#8217;re trying to solve. The Anatomy of Peace shows you how to: &#8211; Focus on helping things go [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-anatomy-of-peace-how-to-resolve-the-heart-of-conflict-the-arbinger-institute-abridged/">The Anatomy of Peace : How to Resolve the Heart of Conflict &#8211; The Arbinger Institute (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Anatomy of Peace will instil hope and inspire reconciliation. Through a series of moving stories about once-bitter enemies reunited, it shows us how we routinely misunderstand the causes of conflict &#8211; and perpetuate the very problems we&#8217;re trying to solve. The Anatomy of Peace shows you how to:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Focus on helping things go right, rather than &#8216;fixing&#8217; things that go wrong<br />
                    &#8211; Think about others as people with fears of their own, not obstacles in your way<br />
                    &#8211; Stop worrying about how the world sees you<br />
                    &#8211; Learn to move away from blame and bitterness</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-anatomy-of-peace-how-to-resolve-the-heart-of-conflict-the-arbinger-institute-abridged/">The Anatomy of Peace : How to Resolve the Heart of Conflict &#8211; The Arbinger Institute (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
