<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Anthropology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/anthropology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/anthropology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Anthropology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/anthropology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Debt : The First 5000 Years &#8211; David Graeber</title>
		<link>/debt-the-first-5000-years-david-graeber/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Laws Of Specific Jurisdictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/debt-the-first-5000-years-david-graeber/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The groundbreaking international best-seller that turns everything you think about money, debt, and society on its head&#8211;from the &#8220;brilliant, deeply original political thinker&#8221; David Graeber (Rebecca Solnit, author of Men Explain Things to Me) Before there was money, there was debt. For more than 5,000 years, since the beginnings of the first agrarian empires, humans [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/debt-the-first-5000-years-david-graeber/">Debt : The First 5000 Years &#8211; David Graeber</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The groundbreaking international best-seller that turns everything you think about money, debt, and society on its head&#8211;from the &#8220;brilliant, deeply original political thinker&#8221; David Graeber (Rebecca Solnit, author of Men Explain Things to Me) </p>
<p>                    Before there was money, there was debt. For more than 5,000 years, since the beginnings of the first agrarian empires, humans have used elaborate credit systems to buy and sell goods&#8211;that is, long before the invention of coins or cash. It is in this era that we also first encounter a society divided into debtors and creditors&#8211;which lives on in full force to this day. </p>
<p>                     So says anthropologist David Graeber in a stunning reversal of conventional wisdom. He shows that arguments about debt and debt forgiveness have been at the center of political debates from Renaissance Italy to Imperial China, as well as sparking innumerable insurrections. He also brilliantly demonstrates that the language of the ancient works of law and religion (words like &#8220;guilt,&#8221; &#8220;sin,&#8221; and &#8220;redemption&#8221;) derive in large part from ancient debates about debt, and shape even our most basic ideas of right and wrong. </p>
<p>                     We are still fighting these battles today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/debt-the-first-5000-years-david-graeber/">Debt : The First 5000 Years &#8211; David Graeber</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Horse, the Wheel, and Language : How Bronze-Age Riders from the Eurasian Steppes Shaped the Modern World &#8211; David W. Anthony</title>
		<link>/the-horse-the-wheel-and-language-how-bronze-age-riders-from-the-eurasian-steppes-shaped-the-modern-world-david-w-anthony/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ancient History: To C 500 CE]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical & Comparative Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prehistoric Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-horse-the-wheel-and-language-how-bronze-age-riders-from-the-eurasian-steppes-shaped-the-modern-world-david-w-anthony/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Roughly half the world&#8217;s population speaks languages derived from a shared linguistic source known as Proto-Indo-European. But who were the early speakers of this ancient mother tongue, and how did they manage to spread it around the globe? Until now their identity has remained a tantalizing mystery to linguists, archaeologists, and even Nazis seeking the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-horse-the-wheel-and-language-how-bronze-age-riders-from-the-eurasian-steppes-shaped-the-modern-world-david-w-anthony/">The Horse, the Wheel, and Language : How Bronze-Age Riders from the Eurasian Steppes Shaped the Modern World &#8211; David W. Anthony</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Roughly half the world&#8217;s population speaks languages derived from a shared linguistic source known as Proto-Indo-European. But who were the early speakers of this ancient mother tongue, and how did they manage to spread it around the globe? Until now their identity has remained a tantalizing mystery to linguists, archaeologists, and even Nazis seeking the roots of the Aryan race. The Horse, the Wheel, and Language lifts the veil that has long shrouded these original Indo-European speakers, and reveals how their domestication of horses and use of the wheel spread language and transformed civilization. Linking prehistoric archaeological remains with the development of language, David Anthony identifies the prehistoric peoples of central Eurasia&#8217;s steppe grasslands as the original speakers of Proto-Indo-European, and shows how their innovative use of the ox wagon, horseback riding, and the warrior&#8217;s chariot turned the Eurasian steppes into a thriving transcontinental corridor of communication, commerce, and cultural exchange.<br />
                    He explains how they spread their traditions and gave rise to important advances in copper mining, warfare, and patron-client political institutions, thereby ushering in an era of vibrant social change. Anthony also describes his fascinating discovery of how the wear from bits on ancient horse teeth reveals the origins of horseback riding. The Horse, the Wheel, and Language solves a puzzle that has vexed scholars for two centuries&#8211;the source of the Indo-European languages and English&#8211;and recovers a magnificent and influential civilization from the past.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-horse-the-wheel-and-language-how-bronze-age-riders-from-the-eurasian-steppes-shaped-the-modern-world-david-w-anthony/">The Horse, the Wheel, and Language : How Bronze-Age Riders from the Eurasian Steppes Shaped the Modern World &#8211; David W. Anthony</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Third Chimpanzee : The Evolution and Future of the Human Animal &#8211; Jared M Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-third-chimpanzee-the-evolution-and-future-of-the-human-animal-jared-m-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-third-chimpanzee-the-evolution-and-future-of-the-human-animal-jared-m-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Wonderful&#8230;.Jared Diamond conducts his fascinating study of our behavior and origins with a naturalist&#8217;s eye and a philosopher&#8217;s cunning.&#8221; &#8211;Diane Ackerman, author of A Natural History of the Senses In this fascinating, provocative, passionate, funny, endlessly entertaining work, renowned Pulitzer Prize-winning author and scientist Jared Diamond, author of Gun, Germs, and Steel, explores how the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-chimpanzee-the-evolution-and-future-of-the-human-animal-jared-m-diamond-abridged/">The Third Chimpanzee : The Evolution and Future of the Human Animal &#8211; Jared M Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Wonderful&#8230;.Jared Diamond conducts his fascinating study of our behavior and origins with a naturalist&#8217;s eye and a philosopher&#8217;s cunning.&#8221; &#8211;Diane Ackerman, author of A Natural History of the Senses    </p>
<p>                    In this fascinating, provocative, passionate, funny, endlessly entertaining work, renowned Pulitzer Prize-winning author and scientist Jared Diamond, author of Gun, Germs, and Steel, explores how the extraordinary human animal, in a remarkably short time, developed the capacity to rule the world . . . and the means to irrevocably destroy it.     </p>
<p>                    We human beings share 98 percent of our genes with chimpanzees. Yet humans are the dominant species on the planet&#8211;having founded civilizations and religions, developed intricate and diverse forms of communication, learned science, built cities, and created breathtaking works of art&#8211;while chimps remain animals concerned primarily with the basic necessities of survival. What is it about that two percent difference in DNA that has created such a divergence between evolutionary cousins?     </p>
<p>                    The Third Chimpanzee is a tour de force, an iconoclastic, compelling, sometimes alarming look at the unique and marvelous creature that is the human animal.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-chimpanzee-the-evolution-and-future-of-the-human-animal-jared-m-diamond-abridged/">The Third Chimpanzee : The Evolution and Future of the Human Animal &#8211; Jared M Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food    </p>
<p>                    There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; whole grains are healthy, whole grains are a disaster; eat everything in moderation; eat only certain foods&#8212;and on and on. In 100 Million Years of Food, biological anthropologist Stephen Le explains how cuisines of different cultures are a result of centuries of evolution, finely tuned to our biology and surroundings. Today many cultures have strayed from their ancestral diets, relying instead on mass-produced food often made with chemicals that may be contributing to a rise in so-called Western diseases, such as cancer, heart disease, and obesity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Science Of Kissing : What Our Lips Are Telling Us &#8211; Sheril Kirshenbaum (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-science-of-kissing-what-our-lips-are-telling-us-sheril-kirshenbaum-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology & Animal Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-science-of-kissing-what-our-lips-are-telling-us-sheril-kirshenbaum-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When did humans begin to kiss? Why is kissing integral to some cultures and alien to others? Do good kissers make the best lovers? And is that expensive lip-plumping gloss worth it? Sheril Kirshenbaum, a marine biologist and science journalist, tackles these questions and more in THE SCIENCE OF KISSING. It&#8217;s everything you always wanted [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-of-kissing-what-our-lips-are-telling-us-sheril-kirshenbaum-abridged/">The Science Of Kissing : What Our Lips Are Telling Us &#8211; Sheril Kirshenbaum (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When did humans begin to kiss? Why is kissing integral to some cultures and alien to others? Do good kissers make the best lovers? And is that expensive lip-plumping gloss worth it? Sheril Kirshenbaum, a marine biologist and science journalist, tackles these questions and more in THE SCIENCE OF KISSING. It&#8217;s everything you always wanted to know about kissing but either haven&#8217;t asked, can&#8217;t find out, or didn&#8217;t realize you should understand. Sheril&#8217;s a serious scientist, and the material here is informed by the results of the latest studies and theories, but she&#8217;s also got an engaging, delightful voice and offers information with a light, humorous touch. Topics range from the kind of kissing men like to do (as distinct from women), to what animals can teach us about the kiss, to whether or not the true art of kissing was lost sometime in the Dark Ages, to what, really, makes us kiss. Employing an interdisciplinary approach&#8211;drawing upon classical history, evolutionary biology, psychology, popular culture, and more&#8211;Kirshenbaum&#8217;s winning book will appeal to romantics and armchair scientists alike.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-of-kissing-what-our-lips-are-telling-us-sheril-kirshenbaum-abridged/">The Science Of Kissing : What Our Lips Are Telling Us &#8211; Sheril Kirshenbaum (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma : The Search for a Perfect Meal in a Fast-Food World (reissued) &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What shall we have for dinner? Such a simple question has grown to have a very complicated answer. We can eat almost anything nature has to offer, but deciding what we should eat stirs anxiety. Should we choose the organic apple or the conventional? If organic, local or imported? Wild fish or farmed? Low-carb or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/">The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma : The Search for a Perfect Meal in a Fast-Food World (reissued) &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What shall we have for dinner? Such a simple question has grown to have a very complicated answer. We can eat almost anything nature has to offer, but deciding what we should eat stirs anxiety. Should we choose the organic apple or the conventional? If organic, local or imported? Wild fish or farmed? Low-carb or low-cal? As the American culture of fast food and unlimited choice invades the world, Pollan follows his next meal from land to table, tracing the origin of everything consumed and the implications for ourselves and our planet. His astonishing findings will shock all who care about what they put on their plate.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/">The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma : The Search for a Perfect Meal in a Fast-Food World (reissued) &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Beyond Culture &#8211; Edward T. Hall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/beyond-culture-edward-t-hall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/beyond-culture-edward-t-hall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned American anthropologist comes a proud celebration of human capacities. For too long, people have taken their own ways of life for granted, ignoring the vast, international cultural community that srrounds them. Humankind must now embark on the difficult journey beyond culture, to the discovery of a lost self a sense of perspective. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-culture-edward-t-hall-abridged/">Beyond Culture &#8211; Edward T. Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From a renowned American anthropologist comes a proud celebration of human capacities. For too long, people have taken their own ways of life for granted, ignoring the vast, international cultural community that srrounds them. Humankind must now embark on the difficult journey beyond culture, to the discovery of a lost self a sense of perspective. By holding up a mirror, Hall permits us to see the awesome grip of unconscious culture. With concrete examples ranging from James Joyce&#8217;s Finnegans Wake to the mating habits of the bowerbird of New Guinea, Hall shows us ourselves. Beyond Culture is a book about self-discovery; it is a voyage we all must embark on if mankind is to survive.     </p>
<p>                    Fascinating and emotionally challenging. . . . The book&#8217;s graceful, non-technical style and the many illuminating, real-life illustrations make it a delight to read. &#8211;Library Journal    </p>
<p>                    Hall&#8217;s book helps us to rethink our values. . . . We come away from it exhilarated. &#8211;Ashley Montagu     </p>
<p>                    In this penetrating analysis of the culturally determined yet &#8216;unconscious&#8217; attitudes that mold our thought, feeling, communication and behavior. . . . Hall makes explicit taken-for-granted linguistic patterns, body rhythms, personality dynamics, educational goals. . . . Many of Hall&#8217;s ideas are original and incisive . . . [and] should reward careful readers with new ways of thinking about themselves and others. &#8211;Publishers Weekly    </p>
<p>                    A fascintaing book which stands beside The Hidden Dimension and The Silent Language to prove Hall one of the most original anthropologists of our era. &#8211;Paul Bohannan</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/beyond-culture-edward-t-hall-abridged/">Beyond Culture &#8211; Edward T. Hall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Grid : The Fraying Wires Between Americans and Our Energy Future &#8211; Gretchen Bakke (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electricity, Electromagnetism & Magnetism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Power Generation & Distribution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory look at our national power grid&#8211;how it developed, its current flaws, and how it must be completely reimagined for our fast-approaching energy future. America&#8217;s electrical grid, an engineering triumph of the twentieth century, is turning out to be a poor fit for the present. It&#8217;s not just that the grid has grown old [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/">The Grid : The Fraying Wires Between Americans and Our Energy Future &#8211; Gretchen Bakke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory look at our national power grid&#8211;how it developed, its current flaws, and how it must be completely reimagined for our fast-approaching energy future.     </p>
<p>                    America&#8217;s electrical grid, an engineering triumph of the twentieth century, is turning out to be a poor fit for the present. It&#8217;s not just that the grid has grown old and is now in dire need of basic repair. Today, as we invest great hope in new energy sources&#8211;solar, wind, and other alternatives&#8211;the grid is what stands most firmly in the way of a brighter energy future. If we hope to realize this future, we need to reimagine the grid according to twenty-first-century values. It&#8217;s a project which forces visionaries to work with bureaucrats, legislators with storm-flattened communities, moneymen with hippies, and the left with the right. And though it might not yet be obvious, this revolution is already well under way.     </p>
<p>                     Cultural anthropologist Gretchen Bakke unveils the many facets of America&#8217;s energy infrastructure, its most dynamic moments and its most stable ones, and its essential role in personal and national life. The grid, she argues, is an essentially American artifact, one which developed with us: a product of bold expansion, the occasional foolhardy vision, some genius technologies, and constant improvisation. Most of all, her focus is on how Americans are changing the grid right now, sometimes with gumption and big dreams and sometimes with legislation or the brandishing of guns.     </p>
<p>                    The Grid tells&#8211;entertainingly, perceptively&#8211;the story of what has been called the largest machine in the world: its fascinating history, its problematic present, and its potential role in a brighter, cleaner future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/">The Grid : The Fraying Wires Between Americans and Our Energy Future &#8211; Gretchen Bakke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bartering Mindset : A Mostly Forgotten Framework for Mastering Your Next Negotiation &#8211; Brian Gunia (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Specific Areas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We use money to solve our everyday problems, and it generally works well. Despite its economic benefits, however, money has a psychological downside: it trains us to think about negotiations narrow-mindedly, leading us to negotiate badly. Suggesting that we need a non-monetary mindset to negotiate better, The Bartering Mindset shows us how to look outside [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/">The Bartering Mindset : A Mostly Forgotten Framework for Mastering Your Next Negotiation &#8211; Brian Gunia (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We use money to solve our everyday problems, and it generally works well. Despite its economic benefits, however, money has a psychological downside: it trains us to think about negotiations narrow-mindedly, leading us to negotiate badly. Suggesting that we need a non-monetary mindset to negotiate better, The Bartering Mindset shows us how to look outside the monetary economy &#8211; to the bartering economies of the past, where people traded what they had for what they needed. The book argues that, because of the economic difficulties associated with bartering, barterers had to use a more sophisticated form of negotiation &#8211; a strategic approach that can make us master negotiators today.    </p>
<p>                    This book immerses readers in the assumptions made by barterers, collectively referred to as the &#8220;bartering mindset,&#8221; and then demonstrates how to apply this mindset to modern, monetary negotiations. The Bartering Mindset concludes that our individual, organizational, and social problems fester for a predictable reason: we apply a monetary mindset to our negotiations, leading to suboptimal thinking, counterproductive behaviors, and disappointing outcomes. By offering the bartering mindset as an alternative, this book will help people negotiate better and thrive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/">The Bartering Mindset : A Mostly Forgotten Framework for Mastering Your Next Negotiation &#8211; Brian Gunia (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Silo Effect : Why Every Organisation Needs to Disrupt Itself to Survive &#8211; Gillian Tett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-silo-effect-why-every-organisation-needs-to-disrupt-itself-to-survive-gillian-tett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-silo-effect-why-every-organisation-needs-to-disrupt-itself-to-survive-gillian-tett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ever since civilised society began, we have felt the need to classify, categorise and specialise. It can make things more efficient, and help give the leaders of any organisation a sense of confidence that they have the right people focusing on the right tasks. But it can also be catastrophic, leading to tunnel vision and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-silo-effect-why-every-organisation-needs-to-disrupt-itself-to-survive-gillian-tett-abridged/">The Silo Effect : Why Every Organisation Needs to Disrupt Itself to Survive &#8211; Gillian Tett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ever  since civilised society began, we have felt the need to classify,  categorise and specialise. It can make things more efficient, and help  give the leaders of any organisation a sense of confidence that they  have the right people focusing on the right tasks. But it can also be  catastrophic, leading to tunnel vision and tribalism. Most importantly  it can create a structural fog, with the full picture of where an  organisation is heading hidden from view. It is incredibly widespread:  the chances are these &#8216;silos&#8217; are rife in any organisation or  profession, whether your business, or your local school or hospital.    </p>
<p>                    Across  industries and cultures, as this brilliant and penetrating book shows,  silos have the power to collapse companies and destabilise financial  markets, yet they still dominate the workplace. They blind and confuse  us, often making modern institutions act in risky, silly and damaging  ways.    </p>
<p>                    Gillian Tett has spent years covering financial markets and  business, but she&#8217;s also a trained anthropologist, having completed a  doctorate at Cambridge University and conducted field work in Tibet and  Tajikistan. She&#8217;s no stranger to questioning the assumptions and  practices of a culture. Those in question &#8211; financial trading desks,  urban police forces, surgical teams within medical clinics, software  debuggers and consumer product engineers &#8211; have practices and rituals as  ordered and intricate as those of any far-flung tribe.    </p>
<p>                    In The Silo Effect,  she uses an anthropological lens to explore how individuals, teams and  whole organisations often work in silos of thought, process and product.  With examples drawn from a range of fascinating areas &#8211; the New York  Fire Department and Facebook to the Bank of England and Sony &#8211; these  narratives illustrate not just how foolishly people can behave when they  are mastered by silos but also how the brightest institutions and  individuals can master them. The Silo Effect is a sharp,  visionary and inspiring work with the insight, prescriptions and power  to remove our organisational blinders and transform the way we think for  the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-silo-effect-why-every-organisation-needs-to-disrupt-itself-to-survive-gillian-tett-abridged/">The Silo Effect : Why Every Organisation Needs to Disrupt Itself to Survive &#8211; Gillian Tett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Your Brain On Parasites : How Tiny Creatures Manipulate Our Behavior and Shape Society &#8211; Kathleen McAuliffe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-your-brain-on-parasites-how-tiny-creatures-manipulate-our-behavior-and-shape-society-kathleen-mcauliffe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Microbiology & Virology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Parasitology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-your-brain-on-parasites-how-tiny-creatures-manipulate-our-behavior-and-shape-society-kathleen-mcauliffe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Engrossing &#8230; [An] expedition through the hidden and sometimes horrifying microbial domain.&#8221; -Wall Street Journal &#8220;Fascinating-and full of the kind of factoids you can&#8217;t wait to share.&#8221; -Scientific American Parasites can live only inside another animal and, as Kathleen McAuliffe reveals, these tiny organisms have many evolutionary motives for manipulating the behavior of their hosts. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-brain-on-parasites-how-tiny-creatures-manipulate-our-behavior-and-shape-society-kathleen-mcauliffe-abridged/">This Is Your Brain On Parasites : How Tiny Creatures Manipulate Our Behavior and Shape Society &#8211; Kathleen McAuliffe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Engrossing &#8230; [An] expedition through the hidden and sometimes horrifying microbial domain.&#8221; -Wall Street Journal    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Fascinating-and full of the kind of factoids you can&#8217;t wait to share.&#8221; -Scientific American    </p>
<p>                     Parasites can live only inside another animal and, as Kathleen McAuliffe reveals, these tiny organisms have many evolutionary motives for manipulating the behavior of their hosts. With astonishing precision, parasites can coax rats to approach cats, spiders to transform the patterns of their webs, and fish to draw the attention of birds that then swoop down to feast on them. We humans are hardly immune to their influence. Organisms we pick up from our own pets are strongly suspected of changing our personality traits and contributing to recklessness and impulsivity-even suicide. Germs that cause colds and the flu may alter our behavior even before symptoms become apparent.    </p>
<p>                     Parasites influence our species on the cultural level, too. Drawing on a huge body of research, McAuliffe argues that our dread of contamination is an evolved defense against parasites. The horror and revulsion we are programmed to feel when we come in contact with people who appear diseased or dirty helped pave the way for civilization, but may also be the basis for major divisions in societies that persist to this day. This Is Your Brain on Parasites is both a journey into cutting-edge science and a revelatory examination of what it means to be human.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;If you&#8217;ve ever doubted the power of microbes to shape society and offer us a grander view of life, read on and find yourself duly impressed.&#8221; -Heather Havrilesky, Bookforum</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-your-brain-on-parasites-how-tiny-creatures-manipulate-our-behavior-and-shape-society-kathleen-mcauliffe-abridged/">This Is Your Brain On Parasites : How Tiny Creatures Manipulate Our Behavior and Shape Society &#8211; Kathleen McAuliffe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Is Sex Fun? : The Evolution of Human Sexuality &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fascinating insight into how human sexuality came to be the way it is now &#8211; Jared Diamond explains why we are different from the animal kingdom. Why are humans one of the few species to have sex in private? Why do humans have sex any day of the month or year, including when the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/">Why Is Sex Fun? : The Evolution of Human Sexuality &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fascinating insight into how human sexuality came to be the way it is now &#8211; Jared Diamond explains why we are different from the animal kingdom.    </p>
<p>                    Why are humans one of the few species to have sex in private? Why do humans have sex any day of the month or year, including when the female is pregnant, beyond her reproductive years, or between her fertile cycles? Why are human females one of the few mammals to go through menopause?    </p>
<p>                    Human sexuality seems normal to us but it is bizarre by the standards of other animals. Jared Diamond argues that our strange sex lives were as crucial to our rise to human status as were our large brains. He also describes the battle of the sexes in the human and animal world over parental care, and why sex differences in the genetic value of parental care provide a biological basis for the all-too-familiar different attitudes of men and women towards extramarital sex.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/">Why Is Sex Fun? : The Evolution of Human Sexuality &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Makes Us Human? &#8211; Edited by Charles Pasternak (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-makes-us-human-edited-by-charles-pasternak-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance, C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-makes-us-human-edited-by-charles-pasternak-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In What Makes us Human? some of the world&#8217;s most brilliant thinkers answer this perennial puzzle. Is it our imagination or our knack for cooking? Is it because we are social, scientific, or spiritual? Exploring the true nature of human nature, What Makes us Human? sheds new light on how and why our ancestors produced [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-makes-us-human-edited-by-charles-pasternak-abridged/">What Makes Us Human? &#8211; Edited by Charles Pasternak (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In What Makes us Human? some of the world&#8217;s    </p>
<p>                    most brilliant thinkers answer this perennial    </p>
<p>                    puzzle. Is it our imagination or our knack for    </p>
<p>                    cooking? Is it because we are social, scientific,    </p>
<p>                    or spiritual? Exploring the true nature of human    </p>
<p>                    nature, What Makes us Human? sheds new    </p>
<p>                    light on how and why our ancestors produced    </p>
<p>                    such clever, talented, and unlikely progeny.    </p>
<p>                    With contributions by Susan Blackmore, Robin    </p>
<p>                    Dunbar, Stephen Oppenheimer, Ian Tattersall, and    </p>
<p>                    more.For all to enjoy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-makes-us-human-edited-by-charles-pasternak-abridged/">What Makes Us Human? &#8211; Edited by Charles Pasternak (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Social Intelligence : The New Science of Human Relationships &#8211; Daniel Goleman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/social-intelligence-the-new-science-of-human-relationships-daniel-goleman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/social-intelligence-the-new-science-of-human-relationships-daniel-goleman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Emotional Intelligence was an international phenomenon, appearing on the New York Times bestseller list for over a year and selling more than 5 million copies worldwide. Now, once again, Daniel Goleman has written a groundbreaking synthesis of the latest findings in biology and brain science, revealing that we are &#8216;wired to connect&#8217; and the surprisingly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-intelligence-the-new-science-of-human-relationships-daniel-goleman-abridged/">Social Intelligence : The New Science of Human Relationships &#8211; Daniel Goleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Emotional Intelligence was an international phenomenon, appearing on the New York Times bestseller list for over a year and selling more than 5 million copies worldwide. Now, once again, Daniel Goleman has written a groundbreaking synthesis of the latest findings in biology and brain science, revealing that we are &#8216;wired to connect&#8217; and the surprisingly deep impact of our relationships on every aspect our lives.    </p>
<p>                    Far more than we are consciously aware, our daily encounters with parents, spouses, bosses, and even strangers, shape our brains and affect cells throughout our bodies, down to the level of our genes &#8211; for good or ill. In Social Intelligence, Daniel Goleman explores an emerging new science with startling implications for our interpersonal world. Its most fundamental discovery: we are designed for sociability, constantly engaged in a &#8216;neural ballet&#8217; that connects us brain-to-brain with those around us.    </p>
<p>                    Goleman explains the surprising accuracy of first impressions, the basis of charisma and emotional power, the complexity of sexual attraction, and how we detect lies. He describes the &#8216;dark side&#8217; of social intelligence, from narcissism to Machiavellianism and psychopathy. He also reveals our astonishing capacity for &#8216;mindsight&#8217;, as well as the tragedy of those, like autistic children, whose mindsight is impaired.    </p>
<p>                    In this book Daniel Goleman delivers his most heartening news with powerful conviction: we humans have a built-in bias toward empathy, cooperation and altruism &#8211; provided we develop the social intelligence to nurture these capacities in ourselves and others.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-intelligence-the-new-science-of-human-relationships-daniel-goleman-abridged/">Social Intelligence : The New Science of Human Relationships &#8211; Daniel Goleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Culture Code : An Ingenious Way to Understand Why People Around the World Live and Buy as They Do &#8211; Clotaire Rapaille (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-culture-code-an-ingenious-way-to-understand-why-people-around-the-world-live-and-buy-as-they-do-clotaire-rapaille-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-culture-code-an-ingenious-way-to-understand-why-people-around-the-world-live-and-buy-as-they-do-clotaire-rapaille-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why are people around the world so very different? What makes us live, buy, even love as we do? The answers are in the codes. In The Culture Code, internationally revered cultural anthropologist and marketing expert Clotaire Rapaille reveals for the first time the techniques he has used to improve profitability and practices for dozens [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-culture-code-an-ingenious-way-to-understand-why-people-around-the-world-live-and-buy-as-they-do-clotaire-rapaille-abridged/">The Culture Code : An Ingenious Way to Understand Why People Around the World Live and Buy as They Do &#8211; Clotaire Rapaille (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why are people around the world so very different? What makes us live, buy, even love as we do? The answers are in the codes. In The Culture Code, internationally revered cultural anthropologist and marketing expert Clotaire Rapaille reveals for the first time the techniques he has used to improve profitability and practices for dozens of Fortune 100 companies. His groundbreaking revelations shed light not just on business but on the way every human being acts and lives around the world. Rapaille&#8217;s breakthrough notion is that we acquire a silent system of codes as we grow up within our culture. These codes&#8211;the Culture Code&#8211;are what make us American, or German, or French, and they invisibly shape how we behave in our personal lives, even when we are completely unaware of our motives. What&#8217;s more, we can learn to crack the codes that guide our actions and achieve new understanding of why we do the things we do. Rapaille has used the Culture Code to help Chrysler build the PT Cruiser&#8211;the most successful American car launch in recent memory. He has used it to help Procter &#038; Gamble design its advertising campaign for Folger&#8217;s coffee &#8211; one of the longest lasting and most successful campaigns in the annals of advertising. He has used it to help companies as diverse as GE, AT&#038;T, Boeing, Honda, Kellogg, and L&#8217;Oréal improve their bottom line at home and overseas. And now, in The Culture Code, he uses it to reveal why Americans act distinctly like Americans, and what makes us different from the world around us. In The Culture Code, Dr. Rapaille decodes two dozen of our most fundamental archetypes&#8211;ranging from sex to money to health to America itself&#8211;to give us &#8220;a new set of glasses&#8221; with which to view our actions and motivations. Why are we so often disillusioned by love? Why is fat a solution rather than a problem? Why do we reject the notion of perfection? Why is fast food in our lives to stay? The answers are in the Codes. Understanding the Codes gives us unprecedented freedom over our lives. It lets us do business in dramatically new ways. And it finally explains why people around the world really are different, and reveals the hidden clues to understanding us all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-culture-code-an-ingenious-way-to-understand-why-people-around-the-world-live-and-buy-as-they-do-clotaire-rapaille-abridged/">The Culture Code : An Ingenious Way to Understand Why People Around the World Live and Buy as They Do &#8211; Clotaire Rapaille (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nutrition and Physical Degeneration : A Comparison of Primitive and Modern Diets and Their Effects &#8211; Weston Price (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/nutrition-and-physical-degeneration-a-comparison-of-primitive-and-modern-diets-and-their-effects-weston-price-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organic Gardening]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/nutrition-and-physical-degeneration-a-comparison-of-primitive-and-modern-diets-and-their-effects-weston-price-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A compendium of ancestral wisdom, Weston Price&#8217;s &#8216;Nutrition and Physical Degeneration&#8217; is considered to be a masterpiece by many nutrition researchers who followed in his footsteps.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nutrition-and-physical-degeneration-a-comparison-of-primitive-and-modern-diets-and-their-effects-weston-price-abridged/">Nutrition and Physical Degeneration : A Comparison of Primitive and Modern Diets and Their Effects &#8211; Weston Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A compendium of ancestral wisdom, Weston Price&#8217;s &#8216;Nutrition and Physical Degeneration&#8217; is considered to be a masterpiece by many nutrition researchers who followed in his footsteps.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nutrition-and-physical-degeneration-a-comparison-of-primitive-and-modern-diets-and-their-effects-weston-price-abridged/">Nutrition and Physical Degeneration : A Comparison of Primitive and Modern Diets and Their Effects &#8211; Weston Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A specialist on social insects writes about the origins and implications of our own vast social organisation, and the ways in which our ethnic and national distinctions mirror those of other animals. In this paradigm-shattering book, biologist Mark W. Moffett draws on findings in psychology, sociology and anthropology to explain the social adaptations that bind [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/">The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A specialist on social insects writes about the origins and implications of our own vast social organisation, and the ways in which our ethnic and national distinctions mirror those of other animals.     </p>
<p>                    In this paradigm-shattering book, biologist Mark W. Moffett draws on findings in psychology, sociology and anthropology to explain the social adaptations that bind societies. He explores how the tension between identity and anonymity defines how societies develop, function, and fail. In the vein of Guns, Germs, and Steel and Sapiens, The Human Swarm reveals how mankind created sprawling civilizations of unrivalled complexity &#8211; and what it will take to sustain them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-human-swarm-how-our-societies-arise-thrive-and-fall-mark-w-moffett-abridged/">The Human Swarm : How Our Societies Arise, Thrive, and Fall &#8211; Mark W. Moffett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
