<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Management Of Specific Areas Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/management-of-specific-areas/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/management-of-specific-areas/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Management Of Specific Areas Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/management-of-specific-areas/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Value Proposition Design : How to Create Products and Services Customers Want &#8211; Alexander Osterwalder, Yves Pigneur, Gregory Bernarda, Alan Smith, Trish Papadakos (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Specific Areas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The authors of the international bestseller Business Model Generation explain how to create value propositions customers can&#8217;t resist Value Proposition Design helps you tackle the core challenge of every business &#8211; creating compelling products and services customers want to buy. This highly practical book, paired with its online companion, will teach you the processes and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/">Value Proposition Design : How to Create Products and Services Customers Want &#8211; Alexander Osterwalder, Yves Pigneur, Gregory Bernarda, Alan Smith, Trish Papadakos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The authors of the international bestseller Business Model Generation explain how to create value propositions customers can&#8217;t resist    </p>
<p>                     Value Proposition Design helps you tackle the core challenge of every business &#8211; creating compelling products and services customers want to buy. This highly practical book, paired with its online companion, will teach you the processes and tools you need to create products that sell.    </p>
<p>                    Using the same stunning visual format as the authors&#8217; global bestseller, Business Model Generation, this sequel explains how to use the &#8220;Value Proposition Canvas&#8221; to design, test, create, and manage products and services customers actually want.    </p>
<p>                    Value Proposition Design is for anyone who has been frustrated by new product meetings based on hunches and intuitions; it&#8217;s for anyone who has watched an expensive new product launch fail in the market. The book will help you understand the patterns of great value propositions, get closer to customers, and avoid wasting time with ideas that won&#8217;t work. You&#8217;ll learn the simple process of designing and testing value propositions, that perfectly match customers&#8217; needs and desires.    </p>
<p>                    In addition the book gives you exclusive access to an online companion on Strategyzer.com. You will be able to assess your work, learn from peers, and download pdfs, checklists, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Value Proposition Design is an essential companion to the &#8220;Business Model Canvas&#8221; from Business Model Generation, a tool embraced globally by startups and large corporations such as MasterCard, 3M, Coca Cola, GE, Fujitsu, LEGO, Colgate-Palmolive, and many more.<br />
                    Value Proposition Design gives you a proven methodology for success, with value propositions that sell, embedded in profitable business models.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/value-proposition-design-how-to-create-products-and-services-customers-want-alexander-osterwalder-yves-pigneur-gregory-bernarda-alan-smith-trish-papadakos-abridged/">Value Proposition Design : How to Create Products and Services Customers Want &#8211; Alexander Osterwalder, Yves Pigneur, Gregory Bernarda, Alan Smith, Trish Papadakos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hire With Your Head : Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Outstanding Diverse Teams &#8211; Lou Adler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Specific Areas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Discover the secrets of one of the world&#8217;s leading talent acquisition experts In the newly revised Fourth Edition of Hire With Your Head: Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Great Teams, influential recruiting and hiring expert Lou Adler delivers a practical guide to consistently identifying and hiring the best people and scaling that process throughout your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/">Hire With Your Head : Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Outstanding Diverse Teams &#8211; Lou Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Discover the secrets of one of the world&#8217;s leading talent acquisition experts    </p>
<p>                     In the newly revised Fourth Edition of Hire With Your Head: Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Great Teams, influential recruiting and hiring expert Lou Adler delivers a practical guide to consistently identifying and hiring the best people and scaling that process throughout your company.    </p>
<p>                     This book will help you address your hiring and recruitment issues, not just by making you more efficient, but also by reforming your entire process to align with how top talent actually look for new jobs, compare offers, and select opportunities.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll discover:    </p>
<p>                    Discover what it takes to ensure more Win-Win Hiring outcomes by hiring for the anniversary date rather than the start date<br />
                    How to use a &#8220;High Tech, High Touch&#8221; approach to raise the talent bar<br />
                    Expand the talent pool to include more outstanding, high potential and diverse talent by defining work as a series of key performance objectives    </p>
<p>                     Perfect for hiring managers, recruiters, and HR and business leaders, Hire with Your Head is a must-read resource for anyone seeking to improve their ability to find, attract, and retain the top talent the world has to offer.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hire-with-your-head-using-performance-based-hiring-to-build-outstanding-diverse-teams-lou-adler-abridged/">Hire With Your Head : Using Performance-Based Hiring to Build Outstanding Diverse Teams &#8211; Lou Adler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bartering Mindset : A Mostly Forgotten Framework for Mastering Your Next Negotiation &#8211; Brian Gunia (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Specific Areas]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We use money to solve our everyday problems, and it generally works well. Despite its economic benefits, however, money has a psychological downside: it trains us to think about negotiations narrow-mindedly, leading us to negotiate badly. Suggesting that we need a non-monetary mindset to negotiate better, The Bartering Mindset shows us how to look outside [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/">The Bartering Mindset : A Mostly Forgotten Framework for Mastering Your Next Negotiation &#8211; Brian Gunia (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We use money to solve our everyday problems, and it generally works well. Despite its economic benefits, however, money has a psychological downside: it trains us to think about negotiations narrow-mindedly, leading us to negotiate badly. Suggesting that we need a non-monetary mindset to negotiate better, The Bartering Mindset shows us how to look outside the monetary economy &#8211; to the bartering economies of the past, where people traded what they had for what they needed. The book argues that, because of the economic difficulties associated with bartering, barterers had to use a more sophisticated form of negotiation &#8211; a strategic approach that can make us master negotiators today.    </p>
<p>                    This book immerses readers in the assumptions made by barterers, collectively referred to as the &#8220;bartering mindset,&#8221; and then demonstrates how to apply this mindset to modern, monetary negotiations. The Bartering Mindset concludes that our individual, organizational, and social problems fester for a predictable reason: we apply a monetary mindset to our negotiations, leading to suboptimal thinking, counterproductive behaviors, and disappointing outcomes. By offering the bartering mindset as an alternative, this book will help people negotiate better and thrive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bartering-mindset-a-mostly-forgotten-framework-for-mastering-your-next-negotiation-brian-gunia-abridged/">The Bartering Mindset : A Mostly Forgotten Framework for Mastering Your Next Negotiation &#8211; Brian Gunia (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
