<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Paediatric Medicine Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/paediatric-medicine/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/paediatric-medicine/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Paediatric Medicine Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/paediatric-medicine/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Uniquely Human : A Different Way of Seeing Autism &#8211; PH D Barry M Prizant, With Thomas Fields-Meyer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/uniquely-human-a-different-way-of-seeing-autism-ph-d-barry-m-prizant-with-thomas-fields-meyer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paediatric Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/uniquely-human-a-different-way-of-seeing-autism-ph-d-barry-m-prizant-with-thomas-fields-meyer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Autism Society of America&#8217;s Dr. Temple Grandin Award for the Outstanding Literary Work in Autism A groundbreaking book on autism, by one of the world&#8217;s leading experts, who portrays autism as a unique way of being human&#8211;this is &#8220;required reading&#8230;.Breathtakingly simple and profoundly positive&#8221; (Chicago Tribune). Autism therapy typically focuses on ridding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/uniquely-human-a-different-way-of-seeing-autism-ph-d-barry-m-prizant-with-thomas-fields-meyer-abridged/">Uniquely Human : A Different Way of Seeing Autism &#8211; PH D Barry M Prizant, With Thomas Fields-Meyer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Autism Society of America&#8217;s Dr. Temple Grandin Award for the Outstanding Literary Work in Autism     </p>
<p>                     A groundbreaking book on autism, by one of the world&#8217;s leading experts, who portrays autism as a unique way of being human&#8211;this is &#8220;required reading&#8230;.Breathtakingly simple and profoundly positive&#8221; (Chicago Tribune).     </p>
<p>                    Autism therapy typically focuses on ridding individuals of &#8220;autistic&#8221; symptoms such as difficulties interacting socially, problems in communicating, sensory challenges, and repetitive behavior patterns. Now Dr. Barry M. Prizant offers a new and compelling paradigm: the most successful approaches to autism don&#8217;t aim at fixing a person by eliminating symptoms, but rather seeking to understand the individual&#8217;s experience and what underlies the behavior.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A must-read for anyone touched by autism&#8230; Dr. Prizant&#8217;s Uniquely Human is a crucial step in promoting better understanding and a more humane approach&#8221; (Associated Press). Instead of classifying &#8220;autistic&#8221; behaviors as signs of pathology, Dr. Prizant sees them as part of a range of strategies to cope with a world that feels chaotic and overwhelming. Rather than curb these behaviors, it&#8217;s better to enhance abilities, build on strengths, and offer supports that will lead to more desirable behavior and a better quality of life.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A remarkable approach to autism&#8230;.A truly impactful, necessary book&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review), Uniquely Human offers inspiration and practical advice drawn from Dr. Prizant&#8217;s four-decade career. It conveys a deep respect for people with autism and their own unique qualities. Filled with humanity and wisdom, Uniquely Human &#8220;should reassure parents and caregivers of kids with autism and any other disability that their kids are not broken, but, indeed, special&#8221; (Booklist, starred review).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/uniquely-human-a-different-way-of-seeing-autism-ph-d-barry-m-prizant-with-thomas-fields-meyer-abridged/">Uniquely Human : A Different Way of Seeing Autism &#8211; PH D Barry M Prizant, With Thomas Fields-Meyer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Childhood Disrupted : How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal &#8211; Donna Jackson Nakazawa (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paediatric Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A &#8220;courageous, compassionate, and rigorous every-person&#8217;s guide&#8221; (Christina Bethell, PhD, Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health) that shows the link between Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACEs) and diseases, and how to cope and heal from these emotional traumas. Your biography becomes your biology. The emotional trauma we suffer as children not only shapes our emotional [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/">Childhood Disrupted : How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal &#8211; Donna Jackson Nakazawa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A &#8220;courageous, compassionate, and rigorous every-person&#8217;s guide&#8221; (Christina Bethell, PhD, Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health) that shows the link between Adverse Childhood Experiences (ACEs)  and diseases, and how to cope and heal from these emotional traumas.    </p>
<p>                    Your biography becomes your biology. The emotional trauma we suffer as children not only shapes our emotional lives as adults, but it also affects our physical health, longevity, and overall well-being. Scientists now know on a bio-chemical level exactly how parents&#8217; chronic fights, divorce, death in the family, being bullied or hazed, and growing up with a hypercritical, alcoholic, or mentally ill parent can leave permanent, physical &#8220;fingerprints&#8221; on our brains.    </p>
<p>                    When children encounter sudden or chronic adversity, stress hormones cause powerful changes in the body, altering the body&#8217;s chemistry. The developing immune system and brain react to this chemical barrage by permanently resetting children&#8217;s stress response to &#8220;high,&#8221; which in turn can have a devastating impact on their mental and physical health as they grow up.    </p>
<p>                    Donna Jackson Nakazawa shares stories from people who have recognized and overcome their adverse experiences, shows why some children are more immune to stress than others, and explains why women are at particular risk. &#8220;Groundbreaking&#8221; (Tara Brach, PhD, author of Radical Acceptance) in its research, inspiring in its clarity, Childhood Disrupted explains how you can reset your biology-and help your loved ones find ways to heal. &#8220;A truly important gift of understanding-illuminates the heartbreaking costs of childhood trauma and like good medicine offers the promising science of healing and prevention&#8221; (Jack Kornfield, author of A Path With Heart).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/childhood-disrupted-how-your-biography-becomes-your-biology-and-how-you-can-heal-donna-jackson-nakazawa-abridged/">Childhood Disrupted : How Your Biography Becomes Your Biology, and How You Can Heal &#8211; Donna Jackson Nakazawa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
