<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Medical Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/medical/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/medical/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Medical Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/medical/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Moment of Lift : How Empowering Women Changes the World &#8211; Melinda Gates (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-moment-of-lift-how-empowering-women-changes-the-world-melinda-gates-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-moment-of-lift-how-empowering-women-changes-the-world-melinda-gates-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We need this message more than ever&#8217; Malala Yousafzai The right to: Spend your own money. Go to school. Earn an income. Access contraceptives. Work outside the home. Walk outside the home. Choose whom to marry. Get a loan. Start a business. Own property. Divorce a husband. See a doctor. Drive a car. All of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moment-of-lift-how-empowering-women-changes-the-world-melinda-gates-abridged/">The Moment of Lift : How Empowering Women Changes the World &#8211; Melinda Gates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We need this message more than ever&#8217; Malala Yousafzai    </p>
<p>                    The right to:<br />
                    Spend your own money. Go to school. Earn an income. Access contraceptives. Work outside the home. Walk outside the home. Choose whom to marry. Get a loan. Start a business. Own property. Divorce a husband. See a doctor. Drive a car.<br />
                    All of these rights are denied to women in some parts of the world.    </p>
<p>                    A Sunday Times bestselling debut from Melinda Gates, a timely and necessary call to action for women&#8217;s empowerment.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;How can we summon a moment of lift for human beings &#8211; and especially for women? Because when you lift up women, you lift up humanity.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    In this moving and compelling book, Melinda shares the stories of the inspiring people she&#8217;s met during her work and travels around the world and the lessons she&#8217;s learned from them. As she writes in the introduction, &#8220;That is why I had to write this book &#8211; to share the stories of people who have given focus and urgency to my life. I want all of us to see ways we can lift women up where we live.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Melinda&#8217;s unforgettable narrative is backed by startling data as she presents the issues that most need our attention &#8211; from child marriage to lack of access to contraceptives to gender inequity in the workplace. And, for the first time, she writes about her personal life and the road to equality in her own marriage. Throughout, she shows how there has never been more opportunity to change the world &#8211; and ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    When we lift others up, they lift us up, too.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-moment-of-lift-how-empowering-women-changes-the-world-melinda-gates-abridged/">The Moment of Lift : How Empowering Women Changes the World &#8211; Melinda Gates (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 5 AM Club : Own Your Morning. Elevate Your Life. &#8211; Robin Sharma (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-5-am-club-own-your-morning-elevate-your-life-robin-sharma-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations & Safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-5-am-club-own-your-morning-elevate-your-life-robin-sharma-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Legendary leadership and elite performance expert Robin Sharma introduced The 5am Club concept over twenty years ago, based on a revolutionary morning routine that has helped his clients maximize their productivity, activate their best health and bulletproof their serenity in this age of overwhelming complexity. Now, in this life-changing book, handcrafted by the author over [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-am-club-own-your-morning-elevate-your-life-robin-sharma-abridged/">The 5 AM Club : Own Your Morning. Elevate Your Life. &#8211; Robin Sharma (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Legendary leadership and elite performance expert Robin Sharma introduced The 5am Club concept over twenty years ago, based on a revolutionary morning routine that has helped his clients maximize their productivity, activate their best health and bulletproof their serenity in this age of overwhelming complexity.    </p>
<p>                              Now, in this life-changing book, handcrafted by the author over a rigorous four-year period, you will discover the early-rising habit that has helped so many accomplish epic results while upgrading their happiness, helpfulness and feelings of aliveness.    </p>
<p>                              Through an enchanting-and often amusing-story about two struggling strangers who meet an eccentric tycoon who becomes their secret mentor, The 5am Club will walk you through:    </p>
<p>                    How great geniuses, business titans and the world&#8217;s wisest people start their mornings to produce astonishing achievements<br />
                    A little-known formula you can use instantly to wake up early feeling inspired, focused and flooded with a fiery drive to get the most out of each day<br />
                    A step-by-step method to protect the quietest hours of daybreak so you have time for exercise, self-renewal and personal growth<br />
                    A neuroscience-based practice proven to help make it easy to rise while most people are sleeping, giving you precious time for yourself to think, express your creativity and begin the day peacefully instead of being rushed<br />
                    &#8216;Insider-only&#8217; tactics to defend your gifts, talents and dreams against digital distraction and trivial diversions so you enjoy fortune, influence and a magnificent impact on the world    </p>
<p>                              Part manifesto for mastery, part playbook for genius-grade productivity and part companion for a life lived beautifully, The 5am Club is a work that will transform your life. Forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-5-am-club-own-your-morning-elevate-your-life-robin-sharma-abridged/">The 5 AM Club : Own Your Morning. Elevate Your Life. &#8211; Robin Sharma (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is Going to Hurt : Secret Diaries of a Junior Doctor &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-going-to-hurt-secret-diaries-of-a-junior-doctor-adam-kay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Optometry / Opticians]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-going-to-hurt-secret-diaries-of-a-junior-doctor-adam-kay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now A Major BBC Series Starring Ben Whishaw. The multi-million copy bestseller and Book of the Year at The National Book Awards. &#8216;Painfully funny. The pain and the funniness somehow add up to something entirely good, entirely noble and entirely loveable.&#8217; &#8211; Stephen Fry Welcome to the life of a junior doctor: 97-hour weeks, life [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-going-to-hurt-secret-diaries-of-a-junior-doctor-adam-kay-abridged/">This is Going to Hurt : Secret Diaries of a Junior Doctor &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now A Major BBC Series Starring Ben Whishaw.    </p>
<p>                    The multi-million copy bestseller and Book of the Year at The National Book Awards.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Painfully funny. The pain and the funniness somehow add up to something entirely good, entirely noble and entirely loveable.&#8217; &#8211; Stephen Fry    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to the life of a junior doctor: 97-hour weeks, life and death decisions, a constant tsunami of bodily fluids, and the hospital parking meter earns more than you.    </p>
<p>                    Scribbled in secret after endless days, sleepless nights and missed weekends, Adam Kay&#8217;s This is Going to Hurt provides a no-holds-barred account of his time on the NHS front line. Hilarious, horrifying and heartbreaking, this diary is everything you wanted to know &#8211; and more than a few things you didn&#8217;t &#8211; about life on and off the hospital ward.    </p>
<p>                    Sunday Times Number One Bestseller for over eight months and winner of a record FOUR National Book Awards: Book of the Year, Non-Fiction Book of the Year, New Writer of the Year and Zoe Ball Book Club Book of the Year.    </p>
<p>                    This edition includes extra diary entries and an afterword by the author.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-going-to-hurt-secret-diaries-of-a-junior-doctor-adam-kay-abridged/">This is Going to Hurt : Secret Diaries of a Junior Doctor &#8211; Adam Kay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
