<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Economic History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/economic-history/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/economic-history/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 15:10:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Economic History Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/economic-history/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hillbilly Elegy : A Memoir of a Family and Culture in Crisis &#8211; J. D. Vance</title>
		<link>/hillbilly-elegy-a-memoir-of-a-family-and-culture-in-crisis-j-d-vance/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Mobility]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hillbilly-elegy-a-memoir-of-a-family-and-culture-in-crisis-j-d-vance/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER Coming November 2020 as a major motion picture from Netflix starring Amy Adams and Glenn Close &#8216;The political book of the year&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;A frank, unsentimental, harrowing memoir &#8230; A superb book&#8217; New York Post &#8216;I bought this to try to better understand Trump&#8217;s appeal &#8230; but the memoir is so [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hillbilly-elegy-a-memoir-of-a-family-and-culture-in-crisis-j-d-vance/">Hillbilly Elegy : A Memoir of a Family and Culture in Crisis &#8211; J. D. Vance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER<br />
Coming November 2020 as a major motion picture from Netflix starring Amy Adams and Glenn Close</p>
<p>&#8216;The political book of the year&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>&#8216;A frank, unsentimental, harrowing memoir &#8230; A superb book&#8217; New York Post</p>
<p>&#8216;I bought this to try to better understand Trump&#8217;s appeal &#8230; but the memoir is so much more than that. A gripping, unputdownable page-turner&#8217; India Knight, Evening Standard</p>
<p>J. D. Vance grew up in the hills of Kentucky. His family and friends were the people most of the world calls rednecks, hillbillies or white trash.</p>
<p>In this deeply moving memoir, Vance tells the story of his family&#8217;s demons and of America &#8216; s problem with generational neglect. How his mother struggled against, but never fully escaped, the legacies of abuse, alcoholism, poverty and trauma. How his grandparents, &#8216;dirt poor and in love&#8217;, gave everything for their children to chase the American dream. How Vance beat the odds to graduate from Yale Law School. And how America came to abandon and then condescend to its white working classes, until they reached breaking point.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hillbilly-elegy-a-memoir-of-a-family-and-culture-in-crisis-j-d-vance/">Hillbilly Elegy : A Memoir of a Family and Culture in Crisis &#8211; J. D. Vance</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Debt : The First 5000 Years &#8211; David Graeber</title>
		<link>/debt-the-first-5000-years-david-graeber/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Laws Of Specific Jurisdictions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/debt-the-first-5000-years-david-graeber/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The groundbreaking international best-seller that turns everything you think about money, debt, and society on its head&#8211;from the &#8220;brilliant, deeply original political thinker&#8221; David Graeber (Rebecca Solnit, author of Men Explain Things to Me) Before there was money, there was debt. For more than 5,000 years, since the beginnings of the first agrarian empires, humans [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/debt-the-first-5000-years-david-graeber/">Debt : The First 5000 Years &#8211; David Graeber</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The groundbreaking international best-seller that turns everything you think about money, debt, and society on its head&#8211;from the &#8220;brilliant, deeply original political thinker&#8221; David Graeber (Rebecca Solnit, author of Men Explain Things to Me) </p>
<p>                    Before there was money, there was debt. For more than 5,000 years, since the beginnings of the first agrarian empires, humans have used elaborate credit systems to buy and sell goods&#8211;that is, long before the invention of coins or cash. It is in this era that we also first encounter a society divided into debtors and creditors&#8211;which lives on in full force to this day. </p>
<p>                     So says anthropologist David Graeber in a stunning reversal of conventional wisdom. He shows that arguments about debt and debt forgiveness have been at the center of political debates from Renaissance Italy to Imperial China, as well as sparking innumerable insurrections. He also brilliantly demonstrates that the language of the ancient works of law and religion (words like &#8220;guilt,&#8221; &#8220;sin,&#8221; and &#8220;redemption&#8221;) derive in large part from ancient debates about debt, and shape even our most basic ideas of right and wrong. </p>
<p>                     We are still fighting these battles today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/debt-the-first-5000-years-david-graeber/">Debt : The First 5000 Years &#8211; David Graeber</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rise and Fall of the Great Powers : Economic Change and Military Conflict from 1500 to 2000 &#8211; Paul Kennedy</title>
		<link>/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-great-powers-economic-change-and-military-conflict-from-1500-to-2000-paul-kennedy/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-great-powers-economic-change-and-military-conflict-from-1500-to-2000-paul-kennedy/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>About national and international power in the &#34;modern&#34; or Post Renaissance period. Explains how the various powers have risen and fallen over the 5 centuries since the formation of the &#34;new monarchies&#34; in W. Europe.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-great-powers-economic-change-and-military-conflict-from-1500-to-2000-paul-kennedy/">The Rise and Fall of the Great Powers : Economic Change and Military Conflict from 1500 to 2000 &#8211; Paul Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>About national and international power in the &quot;modern&quot; or Post Renaissance period. Explains how the various powers have risen and fallen over the 5 centuries since the formation of the &quot;new monarchies&quot; in W. Europe.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-great-powers-economic-change-and-military-conflict-from-1500-to-2000-paul-kennedy/">The Rise and Fall of the Great Powers : Economic Change and Military Conflict from 1500 to 2000 &#8211; Paul Kennedy</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Mistakes : The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments &#8211; Michael Batnick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/big-mistakes-the-best-investors-and-their-worst-investments-michael-batnick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/big-mistakes-the-best-investors-and-their-worst-investments-michael-batnick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Must-Read for Any Investor Looking to Maximize Their Chances of Success Big Mistakes: The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments explores the ways in which the biggest names have failed, and reveals the lessons learned that shaped more successful strategies going forward. Investing can be a rollercoaster of highs and lows, and the investors [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-mistakes-the-best-investors-and-their-worst-investments-michael-batnick-abridged/">Big Mistakes : The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments &#8211; Michael Batnick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Must-Read for Any Investor Looking to Maximize Their Chances of Success Big Mistakes: The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments explores the ways in which the biggest names have failed, and reveals the lessons learned that shaped more successful strategies going forward. Investing can be a rollercoaster of highs and lows, and the investors detailed here show just how low it can go; stories from Warren Buffet, Bill Ackman, Chris Sacca, Jack Bogle, Mark Twain, John Maynard Keynes, and many more illustrate the simple but overlooked concept that investing is really hard, whether you&#8217;re managing a few thousand dollars or a few billion, failures and losses are part of the game. Much more than just anecdotal diversion, these stories set the basis for the book&#8217;s critical focus: learning from mistakes. These investors all recovered from their missteps, and moved forward armed with a wealth of knowledge than can only come from experience. Lessons learned through failure carry a weight that no textbook can convey, and in the case of these legendary investors, informed a set of skills and strategy that propelled them to the top.<br />
                    Research-heavy and grounded in realism, this book is a must-read for any investor looking to maximize their chances of success. * Learn the most common ways even successful investors fail * Learn from the mistakes of the greats to avoid losing ground * Anticipate challenges and obstacles, and develop an advance plan * Exercise caution when warranted, and only take the smart risks While learning from your mistakes is always a valuable experience, learning from the mistakes of others gives you the benefit of wisdom without the consequences of experience. Big Mistakes: The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments provides an incomparable, invaluable resource for investors of all stripes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-mistakes-the-best-investors-and-their-worst-investments-michael-batnick-abridged/">Big Mistakes : The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments &#8211; Michael Batnick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Edge : Inside Information, Dirty Money, and the Quest to Bring Down the Most Wanted Man on Wall Street &#8211; Sheelah Kolhatkar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nominated for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Nominated for the Carnegie Medal for Excellence in Nonfiction Amazon Top 5 Business Books of 2017 &#8216;A prodigious feat of reporting&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell &#8216;Black Edge has the grip of a thriller &#8230; Everyone should read this book&#8217; &#8211; David Grann, New York Times bestselling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/">Black Edge : Inside Information, Dirty Money, and the Quest to Bring Down the Most Wanted Man on Wall Street &#8211; Sheelah Kolhatkar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nominated for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year<br />
                    Nominated for the Carnegie Medal for Excellence in Nonfiction<br />
                    Amazon Top 5 Business Books of 2017    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A prodigious feat of reporting&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Black Edge has the grip of a thriller &#8230; Everyone should read this book&#8217; &#8211; David Grann, New York Times bestselling author of THE LOST CITY OF Z     </p>
<p>                    How do super-rich bankers get away with it?    </p>
<p>                    There is a powerful new class of billionaire financiers in the world, who use their phenomenal wealth to write their own rules and laws.  Chief among them is Steven Cohen, a Wall Street legend, and the basis for Damian Lewis&#8217;s character in BILLIONS, who built his hedge fund into a $15 billion empire on the basis of wizard-like stock trading, and who flies to work by helicopter and owns one of the largest private art collections in the world.  But his iconic status was shattered when his fund became the target of a sprawling FBI investigation into insider trading, charged with using illegal inside information &#8211; or &#8216;black edge&#8217; &#8211; to beat the market.  His firm, SAC Capital, was ultimately indicted and pled guilty to charges of securities and wire fraud, and paid record criminal and civil fines of nearly $2 billion.  But even as the company bearing his name pled guilty, Cohen himself was never charged, and is free to start trading publicly again from January 2018.    </p>
<p>                    Black Edge offers a revelatory look at the grey zone in which so much of Wall Street functions, and a window into the transformation of the worldwide economy. With meticulous reporting and powerful storytelling, this is a riveting, true-life legal thriller that takes readers inside the US government&#8217;s pursuit of Cohen and his employees, and raises urgent questions about the power and wealth of those who sit at the pinnacle of the financial world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/">Black Edge : Inside Information, Dirty Money, and the Quest to Bring Down the Most Wanted Man on Wall Street &#8211; Sheelah Kolhatkar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Haves and the Have-Nots : A Brief and Idiosyncratic History of Global Inequality &#8211; Branko Milanovic (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-haves-and-the-have-nots-a-brief-and-idiosyncratic-history-of-global-inequality-branko-milanovic-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-haves-and-the-have-nots-a-brief-and-idiosyncratic-history-of-global-inequality-branko-milanovic-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Who is the richest person in the world, ever? Does where you were born affect how much money you&#8217;ll earn over a lifetime? How would we know? Why- beyond the idle curiosity- do these questions even matter? In The Haves and the Have-Nots , Branko Milanovic, one of the world&#8217;s leading experts on wealth, poverty, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-haves-and-the-have-nots-a-brief-and-idiosyncratic-history-of-global-inequality-branko-milanovic-abridged/">The Haves and the Have-Nots : A Brief and Idiosyncratic History of Global Inequality &#8211; Branko Milanovic (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Who is the richest person in the world, ever? Does where you were born affect how much money you&#8217;ll earn over a lifetime? How would we know? Why- beyond the idle curiosity- do these questions even matter? In  The Haves and the Have-Nots , Branko Milanovic, one of the world&#8217;s leading experts on wealth, poverty, and the gap that separates them, explains these and other mysteries of how wealth is unevenly spread throughout our world, now and through time. Milanovic uses history, literature and stories straight out of today&#8217;s newspapers, to discuss one of the major divisions in our social lives: between the haves and the have-nots. He reveals just how rich Elizabeth Bennet&#8217;s suitor Mr. Darcy really was how much Anna Karenina gained by falling in love how wealthy ancient Romans compare to today&#8217;s super-rich where in Kenyan income distribution was Obama&#8217;s grandfather how we should think about Marxism in a modern world and how location where one is born determines his wealth. He goes beyond mere entertainment to explain why inequality matters, how it damages our economics prospects, and how it can threaten the foundations of the social order that we take for granted.  Bold, engaging, and illuminating,  The Haves and the Have-Nots  teaches us not only how to think about inequality, but why we should.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-haves-and-the-have-nots-a-brief-and-idiosyncratic-history-of-global-inequality-branko-milanovic-abridged/">The Haves and the Have-Nots : A Brief and Idiosyncratic History of Global Inequality &#8211; Branko Milanovic (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cubed : The Secret History of the Workplace &#8211; Nikil Saval (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cubed-the-secret-history-of-the-workplace-nikil-saval-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Buildings: Civic, Commercial, Industrial, Etc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cubed-the-secret-history-of-the-workplace-nikil-saval-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book &#8211; Daily Beast Best Nonfiction of 2014 &#8211; Inc. Magazine&#8217;s Most Thought-Provoking Books of the Year &#8220;Man is born free, but he is everywhere in cubicles.&#8221; How did we get from Scrooge&#8217;s office to &#8220;Office Space&#8221;? From bookkeepers in dark countinghouses to freelancers in bright cafes? What would the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cubed-the-secret-history-of-the-workplace-nikil-saval-abridged/">Cubed : The Secret History of the Workplace &#8211; Nikil Saval (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book &#8211; Daily Beast Best Nonfiction of 2014 &#8211; Inc. Magazine&#8217;s Most Thought-Provoking Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Man is born free, but he is everywhere in cubicles.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    How did we get from Scrooge&#8217;s office to &#8220;Office Space&#8221;? From bookkeepers in dark countinghouses to freelancers in bright cafes? What would the world be like without the vertical file cabinet? What would the world be like without the office at all? In Cubed, Nikil Saval chronicles the evolution of the office in a fascinating, often funny, and sometimes disturbing anatomy of the white-collar world and how it came to be the way it is. Drawing on the history of architecture and business, as well as a host of pop culture artifacts&#8211;from Mad Men to Dilbert (and, yes, The Office)&#8211;and ranging in time from the earliest clerical houses to the surprisingly utopian origins of the cubicle to the funhouse campuses of Silicon Valley, Cubed is an all-encompassing investigation into the way we work, why we do it the way we do (and often don&#8217;t like it), and how we might do better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cubed-the-secret-history-of-the-workplace-nikil-saval-abridged/">Cubed : The Secret History of the Workplace &#8211; Nikil Saval (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Billion Dollar Whale : the bestselling investigation into the financial fraud of the century &#8211; Tom Wright, Bradley Hope (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hoaxes & Deceptions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A BOOK OF THE YEAR FOR THE FINANCIAL TIMES AND FORTUNE MAGAZINE. The epic story of how a young social climber from Malaysia pulled off one of the biggest financial heists in history. In 2015, rumours began circulating that billions of dollars had been stolen from a Malaysian investment fund. The mastermind of the heist [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/">Billion Dollar Whale : the bestselling investigation into the financial fraud of the century &#8211; Tom Wright, Bradley Hope (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A BOOK OF THE YEAR FOR THE FINANCIAL TIMES AND FORTUNE MAGAZINE.    </p>
<p>                    The epic story of how a young social climber from Malaysia pulled off one of the biggest financial heists in history.    </p>
<p>                    In 2015, rumours began circulating that billions of dollars had been stolen from a Malaysian investment fund. The mastermind of the heist was twenty-seven-year-old Jho Low, a serial fabulist from an upper-middle-class Malaysian family, who had carefully built his reputation as a member of the jet-setting elite by arranging and financing elaborate parties for Wall Street bankers, celebrities, and even royalty.    </p>
<p>                    With the aid of Goldman Sachs and others, Low stole billions of dollars, right under the nose of global financial industry watchdogs. He used the money to finance elections, purchase luxury real estate, throw champagne-drenched parties, and bankroll Hollywood films like The Wolf of Wall Street.     </p>
<p>                    Billion Dollar Whale reveals how this silver-tongued con man, a &#8216;modern Gatsby&#8217;, emerged from obscurity to pull off one of the most audacious financial heists the world has ever seen, and how the financial industry let him. It is a classic harrowing parable of hubris and greed in the financial world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/">Billion Dollar Whale : the bestselling investigation into the financial fraud of the century &#8211; Tom Wright, Bradley Hope (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An absorbing and original narrative history of American capitalism NAMED A BEST BOOK OF 2017 BY THE ECONOMIST From the days of the Mayflower and the Virginia Company, America has been a place for people to dream, invent, build, tinker, and bet the farm in pursuit of a better life. Americana takes us on a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/">Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An absorbing and original narrative history of American capitalism    </p>
<p>                    NAMED A BEST BOOK OF 2017 BY THE ECONOMIST    </p>
<p>                    From the days of the Mayflower and the Virginia Company, America has been a place for people to dream, invent, build, tinker, and bet the farm in pursuit of a better life. Americana takes us on a four-hundred-year journey of this spirit of innovation and ambition through a series of Next Big Things &#8212; the inventions, techniques, and industries that drove American history forward: from the telegraph, the railroad, guns, radio, and banking to flight, suburbia, and sneakers, culminating with the Internet and mobile technology at the turn of the twenty-first century. The result is a thrilling alternative history of modern America that reframes events, trends, and people we thought we knew through the prism of the value that, for better or for worse, this nation holds dearest: capitalism.     </p>
<p>                    In a winning, accessible style, Bhu Srinivasan boldly takes on four centuries of American enterprise, revealing the unexpected connections that link them. We learn how Andrew Carnegie&#8217;s early job as a telegraph messenger boy paved the way for his leadership of the steel empire that would make him one of the nation&#8217;s richest men; how the gunmaker Remington reinvented itself in the postwar years to sell typewriters; how the inner workings of the Mafia mirrored the trend of consolidation and regulation in more traditional business; and how a 1950s infrastructure bill triggered a series of events that produced one of America&#8217;s most enduring brands: KFC. Reliving the heady early days of Silicon Valley, we are reminded that the start-up is an idea as old as America itself.    </p>
<p>                    Entertaining, eye-opening, and sweeping in its reach, Americana is an exhilarating new work of narrative history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americana-a-400-year-history-of-american-capitalism-bhu-srinivasan-abridged/">Americana : A 400-Year History of American Capitalism &#8211; Bhu Srinivasan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Box : How the Shipping Container Made the World Smaller and the World Economy Bigger &#8211; Second Edition with a new chapter by the author &#8211; Marc Levinson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-box-how-the-shipping-container-made-the-world-smaller-and-the-world-economy-bigger-second-edition-with-a-new-chapter-by-the-author-marc-levinson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shipping Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transport Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-box-how-the-shipping-container-made-the-world-smaller-and-the-world-economy-bigger-second-edition-with-a-new-chapter-by-the-author-marc-levinson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In April 1956, a refitted oil tanker carried fifty-eight shipping containers from Newark to Houston. From that modest beginning, container shipping developed into a huge industry that made the boom in global trade possible. The Box tells the dramatic story of the container&#8217;s creation, the decade of struggle before it was widely adopted, and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-box-how-the-shipping-container-made-the-world-smaller-and-the-world-economy-bigger-second-edition-with-a-new-chapter-by-the-author-marc-levinson-abridged/">The Box : How the Shipping Container Made the World Smaller and the World Economy Bigger &#8211; Second Edition with a new chapter by the author &#8211; Marc Levinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In April 1956, a refitted oil tanker carried fifty-eight shipping containers from Newark to Houston. From that modest beginning, container shipping developed into a huge industry that made the boom in global trade possible. The Box tells the dramatic story of the container&#8217;s creation, the decade of struggle before it was widely adopted, and the sweeping economic consequences of the sharp fall in transportation costs that containerization brought about. But the container didn&#8217;t just happen. Its adoption required huge sums of money, both from private investors and from ports that aspired to be on the leading edge of a new technology. It required years of high-stakes bargaining with two of the titans of organized labor, Harry Bridges and Teddy Gleason, as well as delicate negotiations on standards that made it possible for almost any container to travel on any truck or train or ship. Ultimately, it took McLean&#8217;s success in supplying U.S. forces in Vietnam to persuade the world of the container&#8217;s potential.<br />
                    Drawing on previously neglected sources, economist Marc Levinson shows how the container transformed economic geography, devastating traditional ports such as New York and London and fueling the growth of previously obscure ones, such as Oakland. By making shipping so cheap that industry could locate factories far from its customers, the container paved the way for Asia to become the world&#8217;s workshop and brought consumers a previously unimaginable variety of low-cost products from around the globe. Published in hardcover on the fiftieth anniversary of the first container voyage, this is the first comprehensive history of the shipping container. Now with a new chapter, The Box tells the dramatic story of how the drive and imagination of an iconoclastic entrepreneur turned containerization from an impractical idea into a phenomenon that transformed economic geography, slashed transportation costs, and made the boom in global trade possible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-box-how-the-shipping-container-made-the-world-smaller-and-the-world-economy-bigger-second-edition-with-a-new-chapter-by-the-author-marc-levinson-abridged/">The Box : How the Shipping Container Made the World Smaller and the World Economy Bigger &#8211; Second Edition with a new chapter by the author &#8211; Marc Levinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award A New York Times technology and business reporter charts the dramatic rise of Bitcoin and the fascinating personalities who are striving to create a new global money for the Internet age. Digital Gold is New York Times reporter Nathaniel Popper&#8217;s brilliant and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/">Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times and McKinsey Business Book of the Year Award    </p>
<p>                    A New York Times technology and business reporter charts the dramatic rise of Bitcoin and the fascinating personalities who are striving to create a new global money for the Internet age.    </p>
<p>                    Digital Gold is New York Times reporter Nathaniel Popper&#8217;s brilliant and engrossing history of Bitcoin, the landmark digital money and financial technology that has spawned a global social movement.    </p>
<p>                    The notion of a new currency, maintained by the computers of users around the world, has been the butt of many jokes, but that has not stopped it from growing into a technology worth billions of dollars, supported by the hordes of followers who have come to view it as the most important new idea since the creation of the Internet. Believers from Beijing to Buenos Aires see the potential for a financial system free from banks and governments. More than just a tech industry fad, Bitcoin has threatened to decentralize some of society&#8217;s most basic institutions.    </p>
<p>                    An unusual tale of group invention, Digital Gold charts the rise of the Bitcoin technology through the eyes of the movement&#8217;s colorful central characters, including an Argentinian millionaire, a Chinese entrepreneur, Tyler and Cameron Winklevoss, and Bitcoin&#8217;s elusive creator, Satoshi Nakamoto. Already, Bitcoin has led to untold riches for some, and prison terms for others.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/digital-gold-the-untold-story-of-bitcoin-nathaniel-popper-abridged/">Digital Gold : The Untold Story of Bitcoin &#8211; Nathaniel Popper (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The sharing economy&#8217;s unique customer-to-company exchange is possible because of the way in which money has evolved. These transactions have not always been as fluid as they are today, and they are likely to become even more fluid. It is therefore critical that we learn to appreciate money&#8217;s elastic nature as deeply as do Uber, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/">The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The sharing economy&#8217;s unique customer-to-company exchange is possible because of the way in which money has evolved. These transactions have not always been as fluid as they are today, and they are likely to become even more fluid. It is therefore critical that we learn to appreciate money&#8217;s elastic nature as deeply as do Uber, Airbnb, Kickstarter, and other innovators, and that we understand money&#8217;s transition from hard currencies to cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin if we are to access their cooperative potential.  The Evolution of Money illuminates this fascinating reality, focusing on the tension between currency&#8217;s real and abstract properties and advancing a vital theory of money rooted in this dual exchange. It begins with the debt tablets of Mesopotamia and follows with the development of coin money in ancient Greece and Rome, gold-backed currencies in medieval Europe, and monetary economics in Victorian England. The book ends in the digital era, with the cryptocurrencies and service providers that are making the most of money&#8217;s virtual side and that suggest a tectonic shift in what we call money.<br />
                    By building this organic time line, The Evolution of Money helps us anticipate money&#8217;s next, transformative role.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-money-david-orrell-roman-chlupaty-abridged/">The Evolution of Money &#8211; David Orrell, Roman Chlupaty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Fly A Horse : The Secret History of Creation, Invention, and Discovery &#8211; Kevin Ashton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-fly-a-horse-the-secret-history-of-creation-invention-and-discovery-kevin-ashton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inventions & Inventors]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-fly-a-horse-the-secret-history-of-creation-invention-and-discovery-kevin-ashton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE 800-CEO-READ BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR 2015 In the vein of Susan Cain&#8217;s QUIET and Malcolm Gladwell&#8217;s DAVID AND GOLIATH, HOW TO FLY A HORSE is a smart, empowering book that dispels the myths around genius and creativity. There is a myth about how something new comes to be; that geniuses have [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fly-a-horse-the-secret-history-of-creation-invention-and-discovery-kevin-ashton-abridged/">How To Fly A Horse : The Secret History of Creation, Invention, and Discovery &#8211; Kevin Ashton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE 800-CEO-READ BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR 2015    </p>
<p>                    In the vein of Susan Cain&#8217;s QUIET and Malcolm Gladwell&#8217;s DAVID AND GOLIATH, HOW TO FLY A HORSE is a smart, empowering book that dispels the myths around genius and creativity.    </p>
<p>                    There is a myth about how something new comes to be; that geniuses have dramatic moments of insight where great things and thoughts are born whole. Symphonies are composed complete. Science is accomplished with eureka shrieks. Businesses are built by magic touch.    </p>
<p>                    The myth is wrong. Anyone can create.     </p>
<p>                    Acclaimed technology pioneer Kevin Ashton takes us behind the scenes of creation to reveal the true process of discovery and how &#8216;new&#8217; comes to be. From Archimedes to Apple, from Kandinsky to the Coke can, from the Wright brothers &#8211; who set out to &#8216;fly a horse&#8217; &#8211; to Woody Allen, he exposes the seemingly unremarkable individuals, gradual steps, multiple failures and countless ordinary and often uncredited acts that led to our most astounding breakthroughs.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fly-a-horse-the-secret-history-of-creation-invention-and-discovery-kevin-ashton-abridged/">How To Fly A Horse : The Secret History of Creation, Invention, and Discovery &#8211; Kevin Ashton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good Economics for Hard Times : Better Answers to Our Biggest Problems &#8211; Abhijit V. Banerjee, Esther Duflo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FROM THE WINNERS OF THE 2019 NOBEL PRIZE IN ECONOMICS &#8216;Wonderfully refreshing . . . A must read&#8217; Thomas Piketty In this revolutionary book, prize-winning economists Abhijit V. Banerjee and Esther Duflo show how economics, when done right, can help us solve the thorniest social and political problems of our day. From immigration to inequality, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/">Good Economics for Hard Times : Better Answers to Our Biggest Problems &#8211; Abhijit V. Banerjee, Esther Duflo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FROM THE WINNERS OF THE 2019 NOBEL PRIZE IN ECONOMICS    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderfully refreshing . . . A must read&#8217; Thomas Piketty     </p>
<p>                    In this revolutionary book, prize-winning economists Abhijit V. Banerjee and Esther Duflo show how economics, when done right, can help us solve the thorniest social and political problems of our day. From immigration to inequality, slowing growth to accelerating climate change, we have the resources to address the challenges we face but we are so often blinded by ideology.    </p>
<p>                    Original, provocative and urgent, Good Economics for Hard Times offers the new thinking that we need. It builds on cutting-edge research in economics &#8211; and years of exploring the most effective solutions to alleviate extreme poverty &#8211; to make a persuasive case for an intelligent interventionism and a society built on compassion and respect. A much-needed antidote to polarized discourse, this book shines a light to help us appreciate and understand our precariously balanced world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/">Good Economics for Hard Times : Better Answers to Our Biggest Problems &#8211; Abhijit V. Banerjee, Esther Duflo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coined : The Rich Life of Money and How Its History Has Shaped Us &#8211; Kabir Sehgal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/coined-the-rich-life-of-money-and-how-its-history-has-shaped-us-kabir-sehgal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/coined-the-rich-life-of-money-and-how-its-history-has-shaped-us-kabir-sehgal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Money isn&#8217;t just coins, bank notes or clamshells; it is more than a store of value or unit of payment. It&#8217;s an idea, a transformative player in how we view, cope, and harmonise with the world. Money isn&#8217;t just what makes the world go around; it is largely what makes each of us go around. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coined-the-rich-life-of-money-and-how-its-history-has-shaped-us-kabir-sehgal-abridged/">Coined : The Rich Life of Money and How Its History Has Shaped Us &#8211; Kabir Sehgal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Money isn&#8217;t just coins, bank notes or clamshells; it is more than a store of value or unit of payment. It&#8217;s an idea, a transformative player in how we view, cope, and harmonise with the world. Money isn&#8217;t just what makes the world go around; it is largely what makes each of us go around.    </p>
<p>                    In Coined, Kabir Sehgal travels the world while presenting a multidimensional portrait of currency through the ages. He explores the origin of exchange in the Galapagos Islands, searches for hoards of coins from an ancient civilization in Bangladesh, and learns about the art that appears on money from coin collectors in Vietnam. He takes you from the vaults beneath the Federal Reserve in New York to a beehive where pollen can be understood as a natural form of exchange. He details the birth of money, to its place in our culture, to how the obsession for it can lead to death and destruction, all the while mixing engaging and entertaining stories from the front lines of global currency exchange with extensive, thoughtful research. The story of money is rich and varied because it is our story.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coined-the-rich-life-of-money-and-how-its-history-has-shaped-us-kabir-sehgal-abridged/">Coined : The Rich Life of Money and How Its History Has Shaped Us &#8211; Kabir Sehgal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Square and the Tower : Networks, Hierarchies and the Struggle for Global Power &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-square-and-the-tower-networks-hierarchies-and-the-struggle-for-global-power-niall-ferguson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-square-and-the-tower-networks-hierarchies-and-the-struggle-for-global-power-niall-ferguson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Silicon Valley needed a history lesson and Ferguson has provided it&#8217; Eric Schmidt Most history is about the people at the top of the towers of power. But what if the real action is in the social networks down below, in the town squares? Niall Ferguson, the international bestselling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-square-and-the-tower-networks-hierarchies-and-the-struggle-for-global-power-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The Square and the Tower : Networks, Hierarchies and the Struggle for Global Power &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    &#8216;Silicon Valley needed a history lesson and Ferguson has provided it&#8217;  Eric Schmidt    </p>
<p>                    Most history is about the people at the top of the towers of power. But what if the real action is in the social networks down below, in the town squares? Niall Ferguson, the international bestselling author of Empire, The Ascent of Money and Civilization,  brilliantly recasts past and present as an unending contest between hierarchies and networks.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Provocative, snappy, a rare book &#8230; fasten your seatbelts&#8217; Peter Frankopan, Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Immensely stimulating, absorbing, illuminating &#8230; sends ideas blazing all over the place &#8230; one of the best popular historians of our time&#8217; David Goodhart, Prospect    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Powerful, fast-paced &#8230; a pull-yourself-together warning to the present by way of arresting historical precedent&#8217; Andrew Anthony, Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Captivating and compelling&#8217; Jonathan A. Knee, The New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-square-and-the-tower-networks-hierarchies-and-the-struggle-for-global-power-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The Square and the Tower : Networks, Hierarchies and the Struggle for Global Power &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Splendid Exchange : How Trade Shaped the World &#8211; William J Bernstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-splendid-exchange-how-trade-shaped-the-world-william-j-bernstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economic & Trade Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-splendid-exchange-how-trade-shaped-the-world-william-j-bernstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A sweeping narrative history of world trade&#8211;from Sumer in 3000 BC to the firestorm over globalization today&#8211;that brilliantly explores trade&#8217;s colorful and contentious past and provides fresh insights into social, political, cultural, and economic history, as well as a timely assessment of trade&#8217;s future. Adam Smith wrote that man has an intrinsic &#8220;propensity to truck, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-splendid-exchange-how-trade-shaped-the-world-william-j-bernstein-abridged/">A Splendid Exchange : How Trade Shaped the World &#8211; William J Bernstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A sweeping narrative history of world trade&#8211;from Sumer in 3000 BC to the firestorm over globalization today&#8211;that brilliantly explores trade&#8217;s colorful and contentious past and provides fresh insights into social, political, cultural, and economic history, as well as a timely assessment of trade&#8217;s future.    </p>
<p>                    Adam Smith wrote that man has an intrinsic &#8220;propensity to truck, barter, and exchange one thing for another.&#8221; But how did trade evolve to the point where we don&#8217;t think twice about biting into an apple from the other side of the world?    </p>
<p>                    In A Splendid Exchange, William J. Bernstein tells the extraordinary story of global commerce from its prehistoric origins to the myriad controversies surrounding it today. He transports readers from ancient sailing ships that brought the silk trade from China to Rome in the second century to the rise and fall of the Portuguese monopoly in spices in the sixteenth; from the rush for sugar that brought the British to Jamaica in 1655 to the American trade battles of the early twentieth century; from key innovations such as steam, steel, and refrigeration to the modern era of televisions from Taiwan, lettuce from Mexico, and T-shirts from China.    </p>
<p>                    Along the way, Bernstein examines how our age-old dependency on trade has contributed to our planet&#8217;s agricultural bounty, stimulated intellectual progress, and made us both prosperous and vulnerable. Although the impulse to trade often takes a backseat to xenophobia and war, Bernstein concludes that trade is ultimately a force for good among nations, and he argues that societies are far more successful and stable when they are involved in vigorous trade with their neighbors.    </p>
<p>                    Lively, authoritative, and astonishing in scope, A Splendid Exchange is a riveting narrative that views trade and globalization not in political terms, but rather as an evolutionary process as old as war and religion&#8211;a historical constant&#8211;that will continue to foster the growth of intellectual capital, shrink the world, and propel the trajectory of the human species.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-splendid-exchange-how-trade-shaped-the-world-william-j-bernstein-abridged/">A Splendid Exchange : How Trade Shaped the World &#8211; William J Bernstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>False Economy : A Surprising Economic History of the World &#8211; Alan Beattie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/false-economy-a-surprising-economic-history-of-the-world-alan-beattie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/false-economy-a-surprising-economic-history-of-the-world-alan-beattie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER* Why do some countries succeed while others fail? What causes boom or bust? The World Trade Editor of the FT explains how the world really works. &#8216;A thorough examination of economies from the age of empire to the age of the IMF&#8217; The Washington Post Why do oil and diamonds lead [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/false-economy-a-surprising-economic-history-of-the-world-alan-beattie-abridged/">False Economy : A Surprising Economic History of the World &#8211; Alan Beattie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER*    </p>
<p>                    Why do some countries succeed while others fail? What causes boom or bust? The World Trade Editor of the FT explains how the world really works.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A thorough examination of economies from the age of empire to the age of the IMF&#8217; The Washington Post    </p>
<p>                    Why do oil and diamonds lead to economic disaster more often than boom? Why doesn&#8217;t Africa grow cocaine? Why might believing in God be good for your balance-sheet?    </p>
<p>                    Botswana and Sierra Leone are both blessed with abundant diamonds. Why did Botswana became the world&#8217;s fastest-growing economy while Sierra Leone suffered a decade of brutal civil war?    </p>
<p>                    For the past two hundred years Argentina had enjoyed a vista of economic opportunity almost identical to that of the USA but in 2001 Argentina&#8217;s government bankrupted itself. Why did the USA succeed while Argentina stalled?    </p>
<p>                    Time and again, world leaders have failed to learn the lessons of economic history, and their mistakes continue to have surprising and catastrophic consequences.    </p>
<p>                    The path to prosperity is rarely obvious and the sources of success are often unexpected.    </p>
<p>                    In False Economy, Alan Beattie uses extraordinary stories of economic triumph and disaster to explain how some countries went wrong while others went right, and why it&#8217;s so difficult to change course once you&#8217;re on the path to ruin.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/false-economy-a-surprising-economic-history-of-the-world-alan-beattie-abridged/">False Economy : A Surprising Economic History of the World &#8211; Alan Beattie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Capitalism without Capital : The Rise of the Intangible Economy &#8211; Jonathan Haskel, Stian Westlake (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/capitalism-without-capital-the-rise-of-the-intangible-economy-jonathan-haskel-stian-westlake-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/capitalism-without-capital-the-rise-of-the-intangible-economy-jonathan-haskel-stian-westlake-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Early in the twenty-first century, a quiet revolution occurred. For the first time, the major developed economies began to invest more in intangible assets, like design, branding, and software, than in tangible assets, like machinery, buildings, and computers. For all sorts of businesses, the ability to deploy assets that one can neither see nor touch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-without-capital-the-rise-of-the-intangible-economy-jonathan-haskel-stian-westlake-abridged/">Capitalism without Capital : The Rise of the Intangible Economy &#8211; Jonathan Haskel, Stian Westlake (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Early in the twenty-first century, a quiet revolution occurred. For the first time, the major developed economies began to invest more in intangible assets, like design, branding, and software, than in tangible assets, like machinery, buildings, and computers. For all sorts of businesses, the ability to deploy assets that one can neither see nor touch is increasingly the main source of long-term success. But this is not just a familiar story of the so-called new economy. Capitalism without Capital shows that the growing importance of intangible assets has also played a role in some of the larger economic changes of the past decade, including the growth in economic inequality and the stagnation of productivity. Jonathan Haskel and Stian Westlake explore the unusual economic characteristics of intangible investment and discuss how an economy rich in intangibles is fundamentally different from one based on tangibles. Capitalism without Capital concludes by outlining how managers, investors, and policymakers can exploit the characteristics of an intangible age to grow their businesses, portfolios, and economies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-without-capital-the-rise-of-the-intangible-economy-jonathan-haskel-stian-westlake-abridged/">Capitalism without Capital : The Rise of the Intangible Economy &#8211; Jonathan Haskel, Stian Westlake (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The House of Rothschild : Money&#8217;s Prophets 1798-1848 &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his rich and nuanced portrait of the remarkable, elusive Rothschild family, Oxford scholar and bestselling author Niall Ferguson uncovers the secrets behind the family&#8217;s phenomenal economic success. He reveals for the first time the details of the family&#8217;s vast political network, which gave it access to and influence over many of the greatest statesmen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The House of Rothschild : Money&#8217;s Prophets 1798-1848 &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his rich and nuanced portrait of the remarkable, elusive Rothschild  family, Oxford scholar and bestselling author Niall Ferguson uncovers  the secrets behind the family&#8217;s phenomenal economic success. He reveals  for the first time the details of the family&#8217;s vast political network,  which gave it access to and influence over many of the greatest  statesmen of the age. And he tells a family saga, tracing the importance  of unity and the profound role of Judaism in the lives of a dynasty  that rose from the confines of the Frankfurt ghetto and later used its  influence to assist oppressed Jews throughout Europe. A definitive work  of impeccable scholarship with a thoroughly engaging narrative, &#8216;The  House of Rothschild&#8217; is a biography of the rarest kind, in which  mysterious and fascinating historical figures finally spring to life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-house-of-rothschild-moneys-prophets-1798-1848-niall-ferguson-abridged/">The House of Rothschild : Money&#8217;s Prophets 1798-1848 &#8211; Niall Ferguson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Hillbilly Elegy and Strangers in Their Own Land *A New York Post Must-Read Book* *A Newsweek Best New Book* *One of The Week&#8217;s 20 Books to Read in 2017* *One of Bustle&#8217;s 16 Best Nonfiction Books Coming in February 2017* *Best Non-Fiction/2017 Books by the Banks* The Wall Street Journal: A devastating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/">Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For readers of Hillbilly Elegy and Strangers in Their Own Land     </p>
<p>                    *A New York Post Must-Read Book*<br />
                    *A Newsweek Best New Book*<br />
                    *One of The Week&#8217;s 20 Books to Read in 2017*<br />
                    *One of Bustle&#8217;s 16 Best Nonfiction Books Coming in February 2017*<br />
                    *Best Non-Fiction/2017 Books by the Banks*     </p>
<p>                    The Wall Street Journal: A devastating portrait&#8230;For anyone wondering why swing-state America voted against the establishment in 2016, Mr. Alexander supplies plenty of answers.      </p>
<p>                    Laura Miller, Slate: This book hunts bigger game. Reads like an odd&#8211;and oddly satisfying&#8211;fusion of George Packer&#8217;s The Unwinding and one of Michael Lewis&#8217; real-life financial thrillers.     </p>
<p>                    The New Yorker: Does a remarkable job.     </p>
<p>                    Beth Macy, author of Factory Man: This book should be required reading for people trying to understand Trumpism, inequality, and the sad state of a needlessly wrecked rural America. I wish I had written it.      </p>
<p>                    In 1947, Forbes magazine declared Lancaster, Ohio the epitome of the all-American town. Today it is damaged, discouraged, and fighting for its future. In Glass House, journalist Brian Alexander uses the story of one town to show how seeds sown 35 years ago have sprouted to give us Trumpism, inequality, and an eroding national cohesion.     </p>
<p>                    The Anchor Hocking Glass Company, once the world&#8217;s largest maker of glass tableware, was the base on which Lancaster&#8217;s society was built. As Glass House unfolds, bankruptcy looms. With access to the company and its leaders, and Lancaster&#8217;s citizens, Alexander shows how financial engineering took hold in the 1980s, accelerated in the 21st Century, and wrecked the company. We follow CEO Sam Solomon, an African-American leading the nearly all-white town&#8217;s biggest private employer, as he tries to rescue the company from the New York private equity firm that hired him. Meanwhile, Alexander goes behind the scenes, entwined with the lives of residents as they wrestle with heroin, politics, high-interest lenders, low wage jobs, technology, and the new demands of American life: people like Brian Gossett, the fourth generation to work at Anchor Hocking; Joe Piccolo, first-time director of the annual music festival who discovers the town relies on him, and it, for salvation; Jason Roach, who police believed may have been Lancaster&#8217;s biggest drug dealer; and Eric Brown, a local football hero-turned-cop who comes to realize that he can never arrest Lancaster&#8217;s real problems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/glass-house-the-1-economy-and-the-shattering-of-the-all-american-town-brian-alexander-abridged/">Glass House : The 1% Economy and the Shattering of the All-American Town &#8211; Brian Alexander (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of Jobs : Money, Meaning and Freedom Without the 9-to-5 &#8211; Taylor Pearson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-jobs-money-meaning-and-freedom-without-the-9-to-5-taylor-pearson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-jobs-money-meaning-and-freedom-without-the-9-to-5-taylor-pearson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 Amazon Bestseller in Business and Money, Small Business, Entrepreneurship, and International Economics A Top 3 &#8216;Start Your Own Business&#8217; Book -Inc Magazine The rapid development of technology and globalization has changed the leverage points in accumulating wealth: money, meaning and freedom. Those that don&#8217;t adapt are becoming trapped in the downward spiral of a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-jobs-money-meaning-and-freedom-without-the-9-to-5-taylor-pearson-abridged/">The End of Jobs : Money, Meaning and Freedom Without the 9-to-5 &#8211; Taylor Pearson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 Amazon Bestseller in Business and Money, Small Business, Entrepreneurship, and International Economics    </p>
<p>                    A Top 3 &#8216;Start Your Own Business&#8217; Book -Inc Magazine    </p>
<p>                    The rapid development of technology and globalization has changed the leverage points in accumulating wealth: money, meaning and freedom. Those that don&#8217;t adapt are becoming trapped in the downward spiral of a dying middle class &#8211; working harder and earning less. Entrepreneurs that understand the new paradigm, have created unprecedented wealth in their lives and the lives of those they love.    </p>
<p>                    In This Book You&#8217;ll Learn:     </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why the century-long growth in wages came to a halt in 2000.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why MBAs and JDs can&#8217;t get jobs and what that means for the future of work and your job.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why The Theory of Constraints and a shift into the Fourth Economy has made entrepreneurship the highest-leveraged career path for the young and ambitious.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why The Turkey Problem means accounting may be the riskiest profession in the 21st century while entrepreneurship may be the safest.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; How entrepreneurs with second-rate degrees are leveraging the radical democracy of the Long Tail to get rich.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; How the Stair Step Method and return of apprenticeships have transformed the &#8220;entrepreneurial leap&#8221; to make entrepreneurship at large, and small business entrepreneurship in particular, more accessible than ever.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; The scientific research on how giving up balanced living and embracing integrated living leads to more money, more meaning, and more freedom.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why a 20th century world view to career search questions like &#8220;What career is right for me?&#8221; and &#8220;How do I find a career?&#8221; could be the source of your frustration (and a better way to think about it)    </p>
<p>                    Included (Free) Resources:     </p>
<p>                    Get access by visiting http: //taylorpearson.me/eoj    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Full Recorded Interviews with the Ten Entrepreneurs featured in The End of Jobs detailing how they launched their own successful businesses.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Taylor&#8217;s 67 must-read business books and the best entrepreneur books to fuel your entrepreneurial career.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; 49 tools and templates to save you hundreds of hours when launching and growing a business.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; A Ninety-Day goal setting template to translate the book into actionable steps    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Access to a private community to discuss the book and get support from a community of like-minded individuals to inspire, motivate, and assist each other in seeking out apprenticeships, your career search and other elements around &#8220;how to find a career&#8221; and other career guidance questions like &#8220;what career is right for me</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-jobs-money-meaning-and-freedom-without-the-9-to-5-taylor-pearson-abridged/">The End of Jobs : Money, Meaning and Freedom Without the 9-to-5 &#8211; Taylor Pearson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antiques & Collectables: Books, Manuscripts, Ephemera & Printed Matter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On the death of France&#8217;s most glorious king, Louis XIV, in 1715, few people benefited from the shift in power more than the intriguing financial genius from Edinburgh, John Law. Already notorious for killing a man in a duel and for acquiring a huge fortune from gambling, Law had proposed to the English monarch that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/">Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the death of France&#8217;s most glorious king, Louis XIV, in 1715, few people benefited from the shift in power more than the intriguing financial genius from Edinburgh, John Law. Already notorious for killing a man in a duel and for acquiring a huge fortune from gambling, Law had proposed to the English monarch that a bank be established to issue paper money with the credit based on the value of land. But Queen Anne was not about to take advice from a gambler and felon. So, in exile in Paris, he convinced the bankrupt court of Louis XV of the value of his idea.<br />
                     Law soon engineered the revival of the French economy and found himself one of the most powerful men in Europe. In August 1717, he founded the Mississippi Company, and the Court granted him the right to trade in France&#8217;s vast territory in America. The shareholders in his new trading company made such enormous profits that the term millionaire was coined to describe them. Paris was soon in a frenzy of speculation, conspiracies, and insatiable consumption. Before this first boom-and-bust cycle was complete, markets throughout Europe crashed, the mob began calling for Law&#8217;s head, and his visionary ideas about what money could do were abandoned and forgotten.<br />
                     In Millionaire,  Janet Gleeson lucidly reconstructs this epic drama where fortunes were made and lost, paupers grew rich, and lords fell into penury &#8212; and a modern fiscal philosophy was born. Her enthralling tragicomic tale reveals two great characters: John Law, with his complex personality and inscrutable motives, and money itself, whose true nature even to this day remains elusive</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/millionaire-the-philanderer-gambler-and-duelist-who-invented-modern-finance-janet-gleeson-abridged/">Millionaire : The Philanderer, Gambler, and Duelist Who Invented Modern Finance &#8211; Janet Gleeson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Escape : Health, Wealth, and the Origins of Inequality &#8211; Angus Deaton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-great-escape-health-wealth-and-the-origins-of-inequality-angus-deaton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Safety Law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-escape-health-wealth-and-the-origins-of-inequality-angus-deaton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The world is a better place than it used to be. People are healthier, wealthier, and live longer. Yet the escapes from destitution by so many has left gaping inequalities between people and nations. In The Great Escape, Angus Deaton&#8211;one of the foremost experts on economic development and on poverty&#8211;tells the remarkable story of how, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-escape-health-wealth-and-the-origins-of-inequality-angus-deaton-abridged/">The Great Escape : Health, Wealth, and the Origins of Inequality &#8211; Angus Deaton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world is a better place than it used to be. People are healthier, wealthier, and live longer. Yet the escapes from destitution by so many has left gaping inequalities between people and nations. In The Great Escape, Angus Deaton&#8211;one of the foremost experts on economic development and on poverty&#8211;tells the remarkable story of how, beginning 250 years ago, some parts of the world experienced sustained progress, opening up gaps and setting the stage for today&#8217;s disproportionately unequal world. Deaton takes an in-depth look at the historical and ongoing patterns behind the health and wealth of nations, and addresses what needs to be done to help those left behind. Deaton describes vast innovations and wrenching setbacks: the successes of antibiotics, pest control, vaccinations, and clean water on the one hand, and disastrous famines and the HIV/AIDS epidemic on the other. He examines the United States, a nation that has prospered but is today experiencing slower growth and increasing inequality. He also considers how economic growth in India and China has improved the lives of more than a billion people. Deaton argues that international aid has been ineffective and even harmful.<br />
                    He suggests alternative efforts&#8211;including reforming incentives to drug companies and lifting trade restrictions&#8211;that will allow the developing world to bring about its own Great Escape. Demonstrating how changes in health and living standards have transformed our lives, The Great Escape is a powerful guide to addressing the well-being of all nations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-escape-health-wealth-and-the-origins-of-inequality-angus-deaton-abridged/">The Great Escape : Health, Wealth, and the Origins of Inequality &#8211; Angus Deaton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Makers and Takers : How Wall Street Destroyed Main Street &#8211; Rana Foroohar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is Wall Street bad for Main Street America? A well-told exploration of why our current economy is leaving too many behind. &#8211;The New York Times In looking at the forces that shaped the 2016 presidential election, one thing is clear: much of the population believes that our economic system is rigged to enrich the privileged [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/">Makers and Takers : How Wall Street Destroyed Main Street &#8211; Rana Foroohar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is Wall Street bad for Main Street America?     </p>
<p>                    A well-told exploration of why our current economy is leaving too many behind. &#8211;The New York Times     </p>
<p>                     In looking at the forces that shaped the 2016 presidential election, one thing is clear: much of the population believes that our economic system is rigged to enrich the privileged elites at the expense of hard-working Americans. This is a belief held equally on both sides of political spectrum, and it seems only to be gaining momentum.     </p>
<p>                    A key reason, says Financial Times columnist Rana Foroohar, is the fact that Wall Street is no longer supporting Main Street businesses that create the jobs for the middle and working class. She draws on in-depth reporting and interviews at the highest rungs of business and government to show how the &#8220;financialization of America&#8221;&#8211;the phenomenon by which finance and its way of thinking have come to dominate every corner of business&#8211;is threatening the American Dream.     </p>
<p>                     Now updated with new material explaining how our corrupted financial system propelled Donald Trump to power, Makers and Takers explores the confluence of forces that has led American businesses to favor balance-sheet engineering over the actual kind, greed over growth, and short-term profits over putting people to work. From the cozy relationship between Wall Street and Washington, to a tax code designed to benefit wealthy individuals and corporations, to forty years of bad policy decisions, she shows why so many Americans have lost trust in the system, and why it matters urgently to us all.     </p>
<p>                     Through colorful stories of both &#8220;Takers,&#8221; those stifling job creation while lining their own pockets, and &#8220;Makers,&#8221; businesses serving the real economy, Foroohar shows how we can reverse these trends for a better path forward.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/makers-and-takers-how-wall-street-destroyed-main-street-rana-foroohar-abridged/">Makers and Takers : How Wall Street Destroyed Main Street &#8211; Rana Foroohar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Empire of Cotton : A New History of Global Capitalism &#8211; Sven Beckert (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colonialism & Imperialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Textile Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE 2015 BANCROFT PRIZE WINNER OF THE 2015 PHILIP TAFT PRIZE FINALIST FOR THE 2015 PULITZER PRIZE FOR HISTORY SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2015 CUNDHILL PRIZE IN HISTORICAL LITERATURE Economist BOOKS OF THE YEAR 2015 &#8216;Knowledgeable and stunning&#8217; Orhan Pamuk &#8216;A masterpiece of the historian&#8217;s craft&#8217; The Nation For about 900 years, from 1000 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/">Empire of Cotton : A New History of Global Capitalism &#8211; Sven Beckert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE 2015 BANCROFT PRIZE<br />
                    WINNER OF THE 2015 PHILIP TAFT PRIZE<br />
                    FINALIST FOR THE 2015 PULITZER PRIZE FOR HISTORY<br />
                    SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2015 CUNDHILL PRIZE IN HISTORICAL LITERATURE<br />
                    Economist BOOKS OF THE YEAR 2015    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Knowledgeable and stunning&#8217; Orhan Pamuk     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A masterpiece of the historian&#8217;s craft&#8217; The Nation    </p>
<p>                    For about 900 years, from 1000 to 1900, cotton was the world&#8217;s most important manufacturing industry. It remains a vast business &#8211; if all the cotton bales produced in 2013 had been stacked on top of each other they would have made a somewhat unstable tower 40,000 miles high.      </p>
<p>                    Sven Beckert&#8217;s superb new book is a history of the overwhelming role played by cotton in dictating the shape of our world. It is both a gripping narrative and a brilliant case history of how the world works.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-cotton-a-new-history-of-global-capitalism-sven-beckert-abridged/">Empire of Cotton : A New History of Global Capitalism &#8211; Sven Beckert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crashed : How a Decade of Financial Crises Changed the World &#8211; Adam Tooze (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the 2019 Lionel Gelber Prize &#8216;Majestic, informative and often delightful &#8230; insights on every page&#8217; Yanis Varoufakis, Observer The definitive history of the Great Financial Crisis, from the acclaimed author of The Deluge and The Wages of Destruction. In September 2008 the Great Financial Crisis, triggered by the collapse of Lehman brothers, shook [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/">Crashed : How a Decade of Financial Crises Changed the World &#8211; Adam Tooze (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the 2019 Lionel Gelber Prize    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Majestic, informative and often delightful &#8230; insights on every page&#8217; Yanis Varoufakis, Observer    </p>
<p>                    The definitive history of the Great Financial Crisis, from the acclaimed author of The Deluge and The Wages of Destruction.     </p>
<p>                    In September 2008 the Great Financial Crisis, triggered by the collapse of Lehman brothers, shook the world. A decade later its spectre still haunts us. As the appalling scope and scale of the crash was revealed, the financial institutions that had symbolised the West&#8217;s triumph since the end of the Cold War, seemed &#8211; through greed, malice and incompetence &#8211; to be about to bring the entire system to its knees.    </p>
<p>                    Crashed is a brilliantly original and assured analysis of what happened and how we were rescued from something even worse &#8211; but at a price which continues to undermine democracy across Europe and the United States. Gnawing away at our institutions are the many billions of dollars which were conjured up to prevent complete collapse. Over and over again, the end of the crisis has been announced, but it continues to hound us &#8211; whether in Greece or Ukraine, whether through Brexit or Trump. Adam Tooze follows the trail like no previous writer and has written a book compelling as history, as economic analysis and as political horror story.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crashed-how-a-decade-of-financial-crises-changed-the-world-adam-tooze-abridged/">Crashed : How a Decade of Financial Crises Changed the World &#8211; Adam Tooze (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>America&#8217;s Bank : The Epic Struggle to Create the Federal Reserve &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A tour de force of historical reportage, America&#8217;s Bank illuminates the tumultuous era and remarkable personalities that spurred the unlikely birth of America&#8217;s modern central bank, the Federal Reserve. Today, the Fed is the bedrock of the financial landscape, yet the fight to create it was so protracted and divisive that it seems a small [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">America&#8217;s Bank : The Epic Struggle to Create the Federal Reserve &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A tour de force of historical reportage, America&#8217;s Bank illuminates the tumultuous era and remarkable personalities that spurred the unlikely birth of America&#8217;s modern central bank, the Federal Reserve. Today, the Fed is the bedrock of the financial landscape, yet the fight to create it was so protracted and divisive that it seems a small miracle that it was ever established.     </p>
<p>                    For nearly a century, America, alone among developed nations, refused to consider any central or organizing agency in its financial system. Americans&#8217; mistrust of big government and of big banks-a legacy of the country&#8217;s Jeffersonian, small-government traditions-was so widespread that modernizing reform was deemed impossible. Each bank was left to stand on its own, with no central reserve or lender of last resort. The real-world consequences of this chaotic and provincial system were frequent financial panics, bank runs, money shortages, and depressions. By the first decade of the twentieth century, it had become plain that the outmoded banking system was ill equipped to finance America&#8217;s burgeoning industry. But political will for reform was lacking. It took an economic meltdown, a high-level tour of Europe, and-improbably-a conspiratorial effort by vilified captains of Wall Street to overcome popular resistance. Finally, in 1913, Congress conceived a federalist and quintessentially American solution to the conflict that had divided bankers, farmers, populists, and ordinary Americans, and enacted the landmark Federal Reserve Act.    </p>
<p>                    Roger Lowenstein-acclaimed financial journalist and bestselling author of When Genius Failed and The End of Wall Street-tells the drama-laden story of how America created the Federal Reserve, thereby taking its first steps onto the world stage as a global financial power. America&#8217;s Bank showcases Lowenstein at his very finest: illuminating complex financial and political issues with striking clarity, infusing the debates of our past with all the gripping immediacy of today, and painting unforgettable portraits of Gilded Age bankers, presidents, and politicians.    </p>
<p>                    Lowenstein focuses on the four men at the heart of the struggle to create the Federal Reserve. These were Paul Warburg, a refined, German-born financier, recently relocated to New York, who was horrified by the primitive condition of America&#8217;s finances; Rhode Island&#8217;s Nelson W. Aldrich, the reigning power broker in the U.S. Senate and an archetypal Gilded Age legislator; Carter Glass, the ambitious, if then little-known, Virginia congressman who chaired the House Banking Committee at a crucial moment of political transition; and President Woodrow Wilson, the academician-turned-progressive-politician who forced Glass to reconcile his deep-seated differences with bankers and accept the principle (anathema to southern Democrats) of federal control. Weaving together a raucous era in American politics with a storied financial crisis and intrigue at the highest levels of Washington and Wall Street, Lowenstein brings the beginnings of one of the country&#8217;s most crucial institutions to vivid and unforgettable life. Readers of this gripping historical narrative will wonder whether they&#8217;re reading about one hundred years ago or the still-seething conflicts that mark our discussions of banking and politics today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">America&#8217;s Bank : The Epic Struggle to Create the Federal Reserve &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Population & Demography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Are mass violence and catastrophes the only forces that can seriously decrease economic inequality? To judge by thousands of years of history, the answer is yes. Tracing the global history of inequality from the Stone Age to today, Walter Scheidel shows that it never dies peacefully. The Great Leveler is the first book to chart [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/">The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Are mass violence and catastrophes the only forces that can seriously decrease economic inequality? To judge by thousands of years of history, the answer is yes. Tracing the global history of inequality from the Stone Age to today, Walter Scheidel shows that it never dies peacefully. The Great Leveler is the first book to chart the crucial role of violent shocks in reducing inequality over the full sweep of human history around the world. The &#8220;Four Horsemen&#8221; of leveling-mass-mobilization warfare, transformative revolutions, state collapse, and catastrophic plagues-have repeatedly destroyed the fortunes of the rich. Today, the violence that reduced inequality in the past seems to have diminished, and that is a good thing. But it casts serious doubt on the prospects for a more equal future. An essential contribution to the debate about inequality, The Great Leveler provides important new insights about why inequality is so persistent-and why it is unlikely to decline anytime soon.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-leveler-violence-and-the-history-of-inequality-from-the-stone-age-to-the-twenty-first-century-walter-scheidel-abridged/">The Great Leveler : Violence and the History of Inequality from the Stone Age to the Twenty-First Century &#8211; Walter Scheidel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Capitalism and Freedom &#8211; Milton Friedman, Foreword byBinyamin Appelbaum (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/capitalism-and-freedom-milton-friedman-foreword-by-binyamin-appelbaum-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/capitalism-and-freedom-milton-friedman-foreword-by-binyamin-appelbaum-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of TIME magazine&#8217;s All-TIME 100 Best Nonfiction Books One of Times Literary Supplement&#8217;s Hundred Most Influential Books Since the War One of National Review&#8217;s 100 Best Nonfiction Books of the Century One of Intercollegiate Studies Institute&#8217;s 50 Best Books of the 20th Century How can we benefit from the promise of government while avoiding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-and-freedom-milton-friedman-foreword-by-binyamin-appelbaum-abridged/">Capitalism and Freedom &#8211; Milton Friedman, Foreword byBinyamin Appelbaum (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of TIME magazine&#8217;s All-TIME 100 Best Nonfiction Books<br />
                     One of Times Literary Supplement&#8217;s Hundred Most Influential Books Since the War<br />
                     One of National Review&#8217;s 100 Best Nonfiction Books of the Century<br />
                      One of Intercollegiate Studies Institute&#8217;s 50 Best Books of the 20th Century  How can we benefit from the promise of government while avoiding the threat it poses to individual freedom? In this classic book, Milton Friedman provides the definitive statement of an immensely influential economic philosophy&#8211;one in which competitive capitalism serves as both a device for achieving economic freedom and a necessary condition for political freedom.     </p>
<p>                     First published in 1962, Friedman&#8217;s Capitalism and Freedom is one of the most significant works of economic theory ever written. Enduring in its eminence and esteem, it has sold nearly a million copies in English, has been translated into eighteen languages, and continues to inform economic thinking and policymaking around the world. This new edition includes prefaces written by Friedman for both the 1982 and 2002 reissues of the book, as well as a new foreword by Binyamin Appelbaum, lead economics writer for the New York Times editorial board.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-and-freedom-milton-friedman-foreword-by-binyamin-appelbaum-abridged/">Capitalism and Freedom &#8211; Milton Friedman, Foreword byBinyamin Appelbaum (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
