<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cookery By Ingredient Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/cookery-by-ingredient/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/cookery-by-ingredient/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Cookery By Ingredient Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/cookery-by-ingredient/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Heat Salt, Fat, Acid &#8211; Samin Nosrat (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery By Ingredient]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now a Netflix series! New York Times Bestseller and Winner of the 2018 James Beard Award for Best General Cookbook and multiple IACP Cookbook Awards Named one of the Best Books of 2017 by: NPR, BuzzFeed, The Atlantic, The Washington Post, Chicago Tribune, Rachel Ray Every Day, San Francisco Chronicle, Vice Munchies, Elle.com, Glamour, Eater, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/">Heat Salt, Fat, Acid &#8211; Samin Nosrat (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now a Netflix series!     </p>
<p>                     New York Times Bestseller and Winner of the 2018 James Beard Award for Best General Cookbook and multiple IACP Cookbook Awards      </p>
<p>                     Named one of the Best Books of 2017 by: NPR, BuzzFeed, The Atlantic, The Washington Post, Chicago Tribune, Rachel Ray Every Day, San Francisco Chronicle, Vice Munchies, Elle.com, Glamour, Eater, Newsday, Minneapolis Star Tribune,  The Seattle Times, Tampa Bay Times, Tasting Table, Modern Farmer, Publishers Weekly,  and more.     </p>
<p>                     A visionary new master class in cooking that distills decades of professional experience into just four simple elements, from the woman declared &#8220;America&#8217;s next great cooking teacher&#8221; by Alice Waters.     </p>
<p>                    In the tradition of The Joy of Cooking and How to Cook Everything comes Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat, an ambitious new approach to cooking by a major new culinary voice. Chef and writer Samin Nosrat has taught everyone from professional chefs to middle school kids to author Michael Pollan to cook using her revolutionary, yet simple, philosophy. Master the use of just four elements&#8211;Salt, which enhances flavor; Fat, which delivers flavor and generates texture; Acid, which balances flavor; and Heat, which ultimately determines the texture of food&#8211;and anything you cook will be delicious. By explaining the hows and whys of good cooking, Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat will teach and inspire a new generation of cooks how to confidently make better decisions in the kitchen and cook delicious meals with any ingredients, anywhere, at any time.     </p>
<p>                    Echoing Samin&#8217;s own journey from culinary novice to award-winning chef, Salt, Fat Acid, Heat immediately bridges the gap between home and professional kitchens. With charming narrative, illustrated walkthroughs, and a lighthearted approach to kitchen science, Samin demystifies the four elements of good cooking for everyone. Refer to the canon of 100 essential recipes&#8211;and dozens of variations&#8211;to put the lessons into practice and make bright, balanced vinaigrettes, perfectly caramelized roast vegetables, tender braised meats, and light, flaky pastry doughs.     </p>
<p>                    Featuring 150 illustrations and infographics that reveal an atlas to the world of flavor by renowned illustrator Wendy MacNaughton, Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat will be your compass in the kitchen. Destined to be a classic, it just might be the last cookbook you&#8217;ll ever need.     </p>
<p>                    With a foreword by Michael Pollan.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/">Heat Salt, Fat, Acid &#8211; Samin Nosrat (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cod &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cod-mark-kurlansky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aquaculture & Fish-farming: Practice & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery By Ingredient]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sea Life & The Seashore]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Aquatic Creatures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cod-mark-kurlansky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Who would ever think that a book on cod would make a compulsive read? And yet this is precisely what Kurlansky has done&#8217; Express on Sunday The Cod. Wars have been fought over it, revolutions have been triggered by it, national diets have been based on it, economies and livelihoods have depended on it. To [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cod-mark-kurlansky-abridged/">Cod &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Who would ever think that a book on cod would make a compulsive read? And yet this is precisely what Kurlansky has done&#8217; Express on Sunday    </p>
<p>                    The Cod. Wars have been fought over it, revolutions have been triggered by it, national diets have been based on it, economies and livelihoods have depended on it. To the millions it has sustained, it has been a treasure more precious that gold. This book spans 1,000 years and four continents. From the Vikings to Clarence Birdseye, Mark Kurlansky introduces the explorers, merchants, writers, chefs and fisherman, whose lives have been interwoven with this prolific fish. He chronicles the cod wars of the 16th and 20th centuries. He blends in recipes and lore from the Middle Ages to the present. In a story that brings world history and human passions into captivating focus, he shows how the most profitable fish in history is today faced with extinction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cod-mark-kurlansky-abridged/">Cod &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Fat Surprise : why butter, meat, and cheese belong in a healthy diet &#8211; Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery By Ingredient]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking study that reveals how decades of misleading science and policy unjustly demonized the high-fat diet, which might actually be our healthiest option. For the past 60 years we have been told that a low-fat diet can protect against obesity, diabetes, and heart disease. Yet despite many of us taking this advice in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Big Fat Surprise : why butter, meat, and cheese belong in a healthy diet &#8211; Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking study that reveals how decades of misleading science and policy unjustly demonized the high-fat diet, which<br />
                    might actually be our healthiest option.    </p>
<p>                    For the past 60 years we have been told that a low-fat diet can protect against obesity, diabetes, and heart disease. Yet despite<br />
                    many of us taking this advice in the developed West, we are now in the midst of an obesity epidemic that is breeding serious<br />
                    health problems.    </p>
<p>                    Recent more rigorous scientific work has overturned some of the shoddier theories of earlier decades to demonstrate conclusively that we have been needlessly avoiding red meat, cheese, whole milk, and eggs for decades, and that we can now, guilt-free, welcome these delicious foods back into our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-fat-surprise-why-butter-meat-and-cheese-belong-in-a-healthy-diet-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Big Fat Surprise : why butter, meat, and cheese belong in a healthy diet &#8211; Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Pursuit of Garlic : An Intimate Look at the Divinely Odorous Bulb &#8211; Liz Primeau (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-pursuit-of-garlic-an-intimate-look-at-the-divinely-odorous-bulb-liz-primeau-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery By Ingredient]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gardening: Growing Fruit & Vegetables]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gardening: Plants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Homoeopathy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-pursuit-of-garlic-an-intimate-look-at-the-divinely-odorous-bulb-liz-primeau-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Garlic has been used throughout history as a nourishing food and a magical medicine, healing everything from toothaches to dysentery. For much of this past century many dismissed its medicinal qualities as folk remedies more efficiently replaced by modern drugs &#8212; but today garlic is undergoing a renaissance. Not only are more people cooking with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-pursuit-of-garlic-an-intimate-look-at-the-divinely-odorous-bulb-liz-primeau-abridged/">In Pursuit of Garlic : An Intimate Look at the Divinely Odorous Bulb &#8211; Liz Primeau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Garlic has been used throughout history as a nourishing food and a magical medicine, healing everything from toothaches to dysentery. For much of this past century many dismissed its medicinal qualities as folk remedies more efficiently replaced by modern drugs &#8212; but today garlic is undergoing a renaissance. Not only are more people cooking with garlic, they are also growing it in their backyards. And scientists are studying garlic&#8217;s antibiotic, antifungal, and antiparasitic qualities, as well as its potential for cancer treatment. In Pursuit of Garlic tells Liz Primeau&#8217;s story of her love affair with the divinely odorous bulb and leads us on a tour of garlic&#8217;s role in history, art, medicine, and science. Primeau shares her favorite garlic-centered recipes, visits garlic fairs, discusses the many varieties of garlic &#8212; from Russian Red to German Brown to Kettle River Giant &#8212; and gives invaluable tips for growing your own.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-pursuit-of-garlic-an-intimate-look-at-the-divinely-odorous-bulb-liz-primeau-abridged/">In Pursuit of Garlic : An Intimate Look at the Divinely Odorous Bulb &#8211; Liz Primeau (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
