<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Artificial Intelligence Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/artificial-intelligence/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/artificial-intelligence/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Artificial Intelligence Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/artificial-intelligence/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Superintelligence : Paths, Dangers, Strategies &#8211; Nick Bostrom</title>
		<link>/superintelligence-paths-dangers-strategies-nick-bostrom/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Risk Assessment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/superintelligence-paths-dangers-strategies-nick-bostrom/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The human brain has some capabilities that the brains of other animals lack. It is to these distinctive capabilities that our species owes its dominant position. Other animals have stronger muscles or sharper claws, but we have cleverer brains. If machine brains one day come to surpass human brains in general intelligence, then this new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superintelligence-paths-dangers-strategies-nick-bostrom/">Superintelligence : Paths, Dangers, Strategies &#8211; Nick Bostrom</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The human brain has some capabilities that the brains of other animals lack. It is to these distinctive capabilities that our species owes its dominant position. Other animals have stronger muscles or sharper claws, but we have cleverer brains.     </p>
<p>                    If machine brains one day come to surpass human brains in general intelligence, then this new superintelligence could become very powerful. As the fate of the gorillas now depends more on us humans than on the gorillas themselves, so the fate of our species then would come to depend on the actions of the machine superintelligence.     </p>
<p>                    But we have one advantage: we get to make the first move. Will it be possible to construct a seed AI or otherwise to engineer initial conditions so as to make an intelligence explosion survivable? How could one achieve a controlled detonation?     </p>
<p>                    To get closer to an answer to this question, we must make our way through a fascinating landscape of topics and considerations. Read the book and learn about oracles, genies, singletons; about boxing methods, tripwires, and mind crime; about humanity&#8217;s cosmic endowment and differential technological development; indirect normativity, instrumental convergence, whole brain emulation and technology couplings; Malthusian economics and dystopian evolution; artificial intelligence, and biological<br />
                    cognitive enhancement, and collective intelligence.     </p>
<p>                    This profoundly ambitious and original book picks its way carefully through a vast tract of forbiddingly difficult intellectual terrain. Yet the writing is so lucid that it somehow makes it all seem easy. After an utterly engrossing journey that takes us to the frontiers of thinking about the human condition and the future of intelligent life, we find in Nick Bostrom&#8217;s work nothing less than a reconceptualization of the essential task of our time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superintelligence-paths-dangers-strategies-nick-bostrom/">Superintelligence : Paths, Dangers, Strategies &#8211; Nick Bostrom</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Humility Is the New Smart &#8211; Edward D. Hess, Katherine Ludwig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/humility-is-the-new-smart-edward-d-hess-katherine-ludwig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/humility-is-the-new-smart-edward-d-hess-katherine-ludwig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Humility Is the New Smart Your job is at risk&#8211;if not now, then soon. We are on the leading edge of a Smart Machine Age led by artificial intelligence that will be as transformative for us as the Industrial Revolution was for our ancestors. Smart machines will take over millions of jobs in manufacturing, office [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humility-is-the-new-smart-edward-d-hess-katherine-ludwig-abridged/">Humility Is the New Smart &#8211; Edward D. Hess, Katherine Ludwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Humility Is the New Smart     </p>
<p>                     Your job is at risk&#8211;if not now, then soon. We are on the leading edge of a Smart Machine Age led by artificial intelligence that will be as transformative for us as the Industrial Revolution was for our ancestors. Smart machines will take over millions of jobs in manufacturing, office work, the service sector, the professions, you name it. Not only can they know more data and analyze it faster than any mere human, say Edward Hess and Katherine Ludwig, but smart machines are free of the emotional, psychological, and cultural baggage that so often mars human thinking.     </p>
<p>                     So we can&#8217;t beat &#8217;em and we can&#8217;t join &#8217;em. To stay relevant, we have to play a different game. Hess and Ludwig offer us that game plan. We need to excel at critical, creative, and innovative thinking and at genuinely engaging with others&#8211;things machines can&#8217;t do well. The key is to change our definition of what it means to be smart. Hess and Ludwig call it being NewSmart. In this extraordinarily timely book, they offer detailed guidance for developing NewSmart attitudes and four critical behaviors that will help us adapt to the new reality.     </p>
<p>                     The crucial mindset underlying NewSmart is humility&#8211;not self-effacement but an accurate self-appraisal: acknowledging you can&#8217;t have all the answers, remaining open to new ideas, and committing yourself to lifelong learning. Drawing on extensive multidisciplinary research, Hess and Ludwig emphasize that the key to success in this new era is not to be more like the machines but to excel at the best of what makes us human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humility-is-the-new-smart-edward-d-hess-katherine-ludwig-abridged/">Humility Is the New Smart &#8211; Edward D. Hess, Katherine Ludwig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ai Superpowers : China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order &#8211; Kai-Fu Lee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ai-superpowers-china-silicon-valley-and-the-new-world-order-kai-fu-lee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ai-superpowers-china-silicon-valley-and-the-new-world-order-kai-fu-lee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES, USA TODAY, AND WALL STREET JOURNAL BESTSELLER &#8220;Kai-Fu Lee believes China will be the next tech-innovation superpower and in AI Superpowers: China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order, he explains why. Taiwan-born Lee is perfectly positioned for the task.&#8221;-New York Magazine In this thought-provoking book, Lee argues powerfully that because [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ai-superpowers-china-silicon-valley-and-the-new-world-order-kai-fu-lee-abridged/">Ai Superpowers : China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order &#8211; Kai-Fu Lee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES, USA TODAY, AND WALL STREET JOURNAL BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Kai-Fu Lee believes China will be the next tech-innovation superpower and in AI Superpowers: China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order, he explains why. Taiwan-born Lee is perfectly positioned for the task.&#8221;-New York Magazine     </p>
<p>                    In this thought-provoking book, Lee argues powerfully that because of the unprecedented developments in AI, dramatic changes will be happening much sooner than many of us expected. Indeed, as the US-Sino AI competition begins to heat up, Lee urges the US and China to both accept and to embrace the great responsibilities that come with significant technological power.     </p>
<p>                    Most experts already say that AI will have a devastating impact on blue-collar jobs. But Lee predicts that Chinese and American AI will have a strong impact on white-collar jobs as well. Is universal basic income the solution? In Lee&#8217;s opinion, probably not. But he provides a clear description of which jobs will be affected and how soon, which jobs can be enhanced with AI, and most importantly, how we can provide solutions to some of the most profound changes in the future of human history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ai-superpowers-china-silicon-valley-and-the-new-world-order-kai-fu-lee-abridged/">Ai Superpowers : China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order &#8211; Kai-Fu Lee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult Education, Continuous Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employment & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Services & Welfare, Criminology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for ways to handle the transition to a digital economy.Robots, artificial intelligence, and driverless cars are no longer things of the distant future. They are with us today and will become increasingly common in coming years, along with virtual reality and digital personal assistants. As these tools advance deeper into everyday use, they raise [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/">The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Looking for ways to handle the transition to a digital economy.Robots, artificial intelligence, and driverless cars are no longer things of the distant future. They are with us today and will become increasingly common in coming years, along with virtual reality and digital personal assistants.    </p>
<p>                    As these tools advance deeper into everyday use, they raise the question-how will they transform society, the economy, and politics? If companies need fewer workers due to automation and robotics, what happens to those who once held those jobs and don&#8217;t have the skills for new jobs? And since many social benefits are delivered through jobs, how are people outside the workforce for a lengthy period of time going to earn a living and get health care and social benefits?    </p>
<p>                    Looking past today&#8217;s headlines, political scientist and cultural observer Darrell M. West argues that society needs to rethink the concept of jobs, reconfigure the social contract, move toward a system of lifetime learning, and develop a new kind of politics that can deal with economic dislocations. With the U.S. governance system in shambles because of political polarization and hyper-partisanship, dealing creatively with the transition to a fully digital economy will vex political leaders and complicate the adoption of remedies that could ease the transition pain. It is imperative that we make major adjustments in how we think about work and the social contract in order to prevent society from spiraling out of control.    </p>
<p>                    This book presents a number of proposals to help people deal with the transition from an industrial to a digital economy. We must broaden the  concept of employment to include volunteering and parenting and pay greater attention to the opportunities for leisure time. New forms of identity will be possible when the &#8220;job&#8221; no longer defines people&#8217;s sense of personal meaning, and they engage in a broader range of activities. Workers will need help throughout their lifetimes to acquire new skills and develop new job capabilities. Political reforms will be necessary to  reduce polarization and restore civility so there can be open and healthy debate about where responsibility lies for economic well-being.    </p>
<p>                    This book is an important contribution to a discussion about tomorrow-one that needs to take place today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/">The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Autonomy : The Quest to Build the Driverless Car-And How It Will Reshape Our World &#8211; Lawrence D. Burns, Christopher Shulgan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automotive Technology & Trades]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Road Vehicle Manufacturing Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transport Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transportation Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An automotive and tech world insider investigates the quest to develop and perfect the driverless car&#8211;an innovation that promises to be the most disruptive change to our way of life since the smartphone We stand on the brink of a technological revolution. Soon, few of us will own our own automobiles and instead will get [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/">Autonomy : The Quest to Build the Driverless Car-And How It Will Reshape Our World &#8211; Lawrence D. Burns, Christopher Shulgan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An automotive and tech world insider investigates the quest to develop and perfect the driverless car&#8211;an innovation that promises to be the most disruptive change to our way of life since the smartphone    </p>
<p>                    We stand on the brink of a technological revolution. Soon, few of us will own our own automobiles and instead will get around in driverless electric vehicles that we summon with the touch of an app. We will be liberated from driving, prevent over 90% of car crashes, provide freedom of mobility to the elderly and disabled, and decrease our dependence on fossil fuels.     </p>
<p>                    Autonomy is the story of the maverick engineers and computer nerds who are creating the revolution. Longtime advisor to the Google Self-Driving Car team and former GM research and development chief Lawrence D. Burns provides the perfectly-timed history of how we arrived at this point, in a character-driven and heavily reported account of the unlikely thinkers who accomplished what billion-dollar automakers never dared.    </p>
<p>                    Beginning with the way 9/11 spurred the U.S. government to set a million-dollar prize for a series of off-road robot races in the Mojave Desert up to the early 2016 stampede to develop driverless technology, Autonomy is a page-turner that represents a chronicle of the past, diagnosis of the present, and prediction of the future&#8211;the ultimate guide to understanding the driverless car and navigating the revolution it sparks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/autonomy-the-quest-to-build-the-driverless-car-and-how-it-will-reshape-our-world-lawrence-d-burns-christopher-shulgan-abridged/">Autonomy : The Quest to Build the Driverless Car-And How It Will Reshape Our World &#8211; Lawrence D. Burns, Christopher Shulgan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As we approach a great turning point in history when technology is poised to redefine what it means to be human, The Fourth Age offers fascinating insight into AI, robotics, and their extraordinary implications for our species. &#8220;If you only read just one book about the AI revolution, make it this one&#8221; (John Mackey, cofounder [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/">The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As we approach a great turning point in history when technology is poised to redefine what it means to be human, The Fourth Age offers fascinating insight into AI, robotics, and their extraordinary implications for our species. &#8220;If you only read just one book about the AI revolution, make it this one&#8221; (John Mackey, cofounder and CEO, Whole Foods Market).     </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Age, Byron Reese makes the case that technology has reshaped humanity just three times in history: 100,000 years ago, we harnessed fire, which led to language; 10,000 years ago, we developed agriculture, which led to cities and warfare; 5,000 years ago, we invented the wheel and writing, which lead to the nation state.    </p>
<p>                    We are now on the doorstep of a fourth change brought about by two technologies: AI and robotics. &#8220;Timely, highly informative, and certainly optimistic&#8221; (Booklist), The Fourth Age provides an essential background on how we got to this point, and how-rather than what-we should think about the topics we&#8217;ll soon all be facing: machine consciousness, automation, changes in employment, creative computers, radical life extension, artificial life, AI ethics, the future of warfare, superintelligence, and the implications of extreme prosperity.    </p>
<p>                    By asking questions like &#8220;Are you a machine?&#8221; and &#8220;Could a computer feel anything?&#8221;, Reese leads you through a discussion along the cutting edge in robotics and AI, and provides a framework by which we can all understand, discuss, and act on the issues of the Fourth Age and how they&#8217;ll transform humanity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/">The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Book of Why : The New Science of Cause and Effect &#8211; Judea Pearl, Dana Mackenzie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-book-of-why-the-new-science-of-cause-and-effect-judea-pearl-dana-mackenzie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[People & Places]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Methodology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-book-of-why-the-new-science-of-cause-and-effect-judea-pearl-dana-mackenzie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The hugely influential book on how the understanding of causality revolutionized science and the world, by the pioneer of artificial intelligence &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; illuminating and fun to read&#8217; Daniel Kahneman, Nobel Prize-winner and author of Thinking, Fast and Slow &#8216;Correlation does not imply causation.&#8217; For decades, this mantra was invoked by scientists in order to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-why-the-new-science-of-cause-and-effect-judea-pearl-dana-mackenzie-abridged/">The Book of Why : The New Science of Cause and Effect &#8211; Judea Pearl, Dana Mackenzie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The hugely influential book on how the understanding of causality revolutionized science and the world, by the pioneer of artificial intelligence    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; illuminating and fun to read&#8217; Daniel Kahneman, Nobel Prize-winner and author of Thinking, Fast and Slow    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Correlation  does not imply causation.&#8217; For decades, this mantra was invoked by scientists in order to avoid taking positions as to whether one thing  caused another, such as smoking and cancer, or carbon dioxide and global  warming. But today, that taboo is dead. The causal revolution, sparked  by world-renowned computer scientist Judea Pearl and his colleagues, has  cut through a century of confusion and placed cause and effect on a  firm scientific basis. Now, Pearl and science journalist Dana Mackenzie explain causal thinking to general readers for the first time, showing  how it allows us to explore the world that is and the worlds that could  have been. It is the essence of human and artificial intelligence. And  just as Pearl&#8217;s discoveries have enabled machines to think better, The  Book of Why explains how we too can think better.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Pearl&#8217;s accomplishments over the last 30 years have provided the theoretical basis for progress in artificial intelligence and have redefined the term &#8220;thinking machine&#8221;&#8216; Vint Cerf</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-why-the-new-science-of-cause-and-effect-judea-pearl-dana-mackenzie-abridged/">The Book of Why : The New Science of Cause and Effect &#8211; Judea Pearl, Dana Mackenzie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What To Do When Machines Do Everything : How to Get Ahead in a World of AI, Algorithms, Bots, and Big Data &#8211; Malcolm Frank, Paul Roehrig, Ben Pring (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Systems & Equipment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The essential playbook for the future of your business What To Do When Machines Do Everything is a guidebook to succeeding in the next generation of the digital economy. When systems running on Artificial Intelligence can drive our cars, diagnose medical patients, and manage our finances more effectively than humans it raises profound questions on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/">What To Do When Machines Do Everything : How to Get Ahead in a World of AI, Algorithms, Bots, and Big Data &#8211; Malcolm Frank, Paul Roehrig, Ben Pring (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The essential playbook for the future of your business What To Do When Machines Do Everything is a guidebook to succeeding in the next generation of the digital economy. When systems running on Artificial Intelligence can drive our cars, diagnose medical patients, and manage our finances more effectively than humans it raises profound questions on the future of work and how companies compete. Illustrated with real-world cases, data, and insight, the authors provide clear strategic guidance and actionable steps to help you and your organization move ahead in a world where exponentially developing new technologies are changing how value is created. Written by a team of business and technology expert practitioners who also authored Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business this book provides a clear path to the future of your work. The first part of the book examines the once in a generation upheaval most every organization will soon face as systems of intelligence go mainstream.<br />
                    The authors argue that contrary to the doom and gloom that surrounds much of IT and business at the moment, we are in fact on the cusp of the biggest wave of opportunity creation since the Industrial Revolution. Next, the authors detail a clear-cut business model to help leaders take part in this coming boom; the AHEAD model outlines five strategic initiatives Automate, Halos, Enhance, Abundance, and Discovery that are central to competing in the next phase of global business by driving new levels of efficiency, customer intimacy and innovation. Business leaders today have two options: be swallowed up by the ongoing technological evolution, or ride the crest of the wave to new profits and better business. This book shows you how to avoid your own extinction event, and will help you; * Understand the untold full extent of technology&#8217;s impact on the way we work and live.<br />
                    * Find out where we&#8217;re headed, and how soon the future will arrive * Leverage the new emerging paradigm into a sustainable business advantage * Adopt a strategic model for winning in the new economy The digital world is already transforming how we work, live, and shop, how we are governed and entertained, and how we manage our money, health, security, and relationships. Don&#8217;t let your business or your career get left behind. What To Do When Machines Do Everything is your strategic roadmap to a future full of possibility and success. Or peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/">What To Do When Machines Do Everything : How to Get Ahead in a World of AI, Algorithms, Bots, and Big Data &#8211; Malcolm Frank, Paul Roehrig, Ben Pring (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Human/Machine : The Future of our Partnership with Machines &#8211; Daniel Newman, Olivier Blanchard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Will the workplace of the future be overrun by machines and robots? Are the new frontiers of artificial intelligence (AI) on the cusp of dethroning us in efficiency, intelligence and innovative potential? Automation and AI will augment our human world and potential. The winners of the future of work are those that harness the power [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/">Human/Machine : The Future of our Partnership with Machines &#8211; Daniel Newman, Olivier Blanchard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Will the workplace of the future be overrun by machines and robots? Are the new frontiers of artificial intelligence (AI) on the cusp of dethroning us in efficiency, intelligence and innovative potential? Automation and AI will augment our human world and potential.     </p>
<p>                    The winners of the future of work are those that harness the power of machines to their advantage. Human/Machine is the only guide you need to understand the fourth industrial revolution. It sets out a road map to the challenges ahead, but also unlocks the wondrous opportunities that it offers.     </p>
<p>                    Human/Machine explores how we will work symbiotically with machines, detailing how institutions, companies, individuals and education providers will evolve to integrate seamlessly with new technologies. With exclusive case studies, this book offers a glimpse into the future and details how top companies are already thriving on this very special relationship. From gamification in job training to project management teams integrated with bots and predictive technologies that fix problems in the supply chain before they happen, the authors deliver a powerful manifesto for the adoption and celebration of automation and AI. In a much more fluid, skills-based economy, we will all need to prove our worth and future-proof our skills base. This book offers a blueprint to avoid being left behind and unearth the opportunities unique to human-machine partnership ecosystems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/human-machine-the-future-of-our-partnership-with-machines-daniel-newman-olivier-blanchard-abridged/">Human/Machine : The Future of our Partnership with Machines &#8211; Daniel Newman, Olivier Blanchard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the inventor of the most innovative and compelling technology of our era, an international authority on artificial intelligence, and one of our greatest living visionaries. Now he offers a framework for envisioning the twenty-first century&#8211;an age in which the marriage of human sensitivity and artificial intelligence fundamentally alters and improves the way [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the inventor of the most innovative and compelling technology of our era, an international authority on artificial intelligence, and one of our greatest living visionaries. Now he offers a framework for envisioning the twenty-first century&#8211;an age in which the marriage of human sensitivity and artificial intelligence fundamentally alters and improves the way we live. Kurzweil&#8217;s prophetic blueprint for the future takes us through the advances that inexorably result in computers exceeding the memory capacity and computational ability of the human brain by the year 2020 (with human-level capabilities not far behind); in relationships with automated personalities who will be our teachers, companions, and lovers; and in information fed straight into our brains along direct neural pathways. Optimistic and challenging, thought-provoking and engaging, The Age of Spiritual Machines is the ultimate guide on our road into the next century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Algorithms to Live By : The Computer Science of Human Decisions &#8211; Brian Christian, Tom Griffiths (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/algorithms-to-live-by-the-computer-science-of-human-decisions-brian-christian-tom-griffiths-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/algorithms-to-live-by-the-computer-science-of-human-decisions-brian-christian-tom-griffiths-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fascinating exploration of how computer algorithms can be applied to our everyday lives. In this dazzlingly interdisciplinary work, acclaimed author Brian Christian and cognitive scientist Tom Griffiths show us how the simple, precise algorithms used by computers can also untangle very human questions. Modern life is constrained by limited space and time, limits that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/algorithms-to-live-by-the-computer-science-of-human-decisions-brian-christian-tom-griffiths-abridged/">Algorithms to Live By : The Computer Science of Human Decisions &#8211; Brian Christian, Tom Griffiths (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fascinating exploration of how computer algorithms can be applied to our everyday lives.    </p>
<p>                              In this dazzlingly interdisciplinary work, acclaimed author Brian Christian and cognitive scientist Tom Griffiths show us how the simple, precise algorithms used by computers can also untangle very human questions. Modern life is constrained by limited space and time, limits that give rise to a particular set of problems. What should we do, or leave undone, in a day or a lifetime? How much messiness should we accept? The authors explain how to have better hunches and when to leave things to chance, how to deal with overwhelming choices and how best to connect with others.    </p>
<p>                              From finding a spouse to finding a parking spot, from organizing one&#8217;s inbox to understanding the workings of human memory, Algorithms To Live By is full of practical takeaways to help you solve common decision-making problems and illuminate the workings of the human mind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/algorithms-to-live-by-the-computer-science-of-human-decisions-brian-christian-tom-griffiths-abridged/">Algorithms to Live By : The Computer Science of Human Decisions &#8211; Brian Christian, Tom Griffiths (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weapons of Math Destruction : How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy &#8211; Cathy O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A manual for the 21st-century citizen&#8230; accessible, refreshingly critical, relevant and urgent&#8217; &#8211; Financial Times &#8216;Fascinating and deeply disturbing&#8217; &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari, Guardian Books of the Year In this New York Times bestseller, Cathy O&#8217;Neil, one of the first champions of algorithmic accountability, sounds an alarm on the mathematical models that pervade modern life [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/">Weapons of Math Destruction : How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy &#8211; Cathy O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A manual for the 21st-century citizen&#8230; accessible, refreshingly critical, relevant and urgent&#8217; &#8211;  Financial Times     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating and deeply disturbing&#8217; &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari, Guardian Books of the Year     </p>
<p>                    In this New York Times bestseller, Cathy O&#8217;Neil, one of the first champions of algorithmic accountability, sounds an alarm on the mathematical models that pervade modern life &#8212; and threaten to rip apart our social fabric.    </p>
<p>                    We live in the age of the algorithm. Increasingly, the decisions that affect our lives &#8211; where we go to school, whether we get a loan, how much we pay for insurance &#8211; are being made not by humans, but by mathematical models. In theory, this should lead to greater fairness: everyone is judged according to the same rules, and bias is eliminated.     </p>
<p>                    And yet, as Cathy O&#8217;Neil reveals in this urgent and necessary book, the opposite is true. The models being used today are opaque, unregulated, and incontestable, even when they&#8217;re wrong. Most troubling, they reinforce discrimination. Tracing the arc of a person&#8217;s life, O&#8217;Neil exposes the black box models that shape our future, both as individuals and as a society. These &#8220;weapons of math destruction&#8221; score teachers and students, sort CVs, grant or deny loans, evaluate workers, target voters, and monitor our health.     </p>
<p>                    O&#8217;Neil calls on modellers to take more responsibility for their algorithms and on policy makers to regulate their use. But in the end, it&#8217;s up to us to become more savvy about the models that govern our lives. This important book empowers us to ask the tough questions, uncover the truth, and demand change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/">Weapons of Math Destruction : How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy &#8211; Cathy O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Master Algorithm : How the Quest for the Ultimate Learning Machine Will Remake Our World &#8211; Pedro Domingos (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-master-algorithm-how-the-quest-for-the-ultimate-learning-machine-will-remake-our-world-pedro-domingos-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-master-algorithm-how-the-quest-for-the-ultimate-learning-machine-will-remake-our-world-pedro-domingos-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Pedro Domingos demystifies machine learning and shows how wondrous and exciting the future will be&#8217; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs Society is changing, one learning algorithm at a time, from search engines to online dating, personalized medicine to predicting the stock market. But learning algorithms are not just about Big Data &#8211; these algorithms [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-master-algorithm-how-the-quest-for-the-ultimate-learning-machine-will-remake-our-world-pedro-domingos-abridged/">The Master Algorithm : How the Quest for the Ultimate Learning Machine Will Remake Our World &#8211; Pedro Domingos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Pedro Domingos demystifies machine learning and shows how wondrous and exciting the future will be&#8217; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs    </p>
<p>                    Society is changing, one learning algorithm at a time, from search engines to online dating, personalized medicine to predicting the stock market. But learning algorithms are not just about Big Data &#8211; these algorithms take raw data and make it useful by creating more algorithms. This is something new under the sun: a technology that builds itself. In The Master Algorithm, Pedro Domingos reveals how machine learning is remaking business, politics, science and war. And he takes us on an awe-inspiring quest to find &#8216;The Master Algorithm&#8217; &#8211; a universal learner capable of deriving all knowledge from data.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-master-algorithm-how-the-quest-for-the-ultimate-learning-machine-will-remake-our-world-pedro-domingos-abridged/">The Master Algorithm : How the Quest for the Ultimate Learning Machine Will Remake Our World &#8211; Pedro Domingos (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orwell&#8217;s Revenge : The 1984 Palimpsest &#8211; Senior Fellow Peter Huber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/orwells-revenge-the-1984-palimpsest-senior-fellow-peter-huber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orwells-revenge-the-1984-palimpsest-senior-fellow-peter-huber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mark Zuckerberg&#8217;s &#8216;A Year of Books&#8217; Selection George Orwell&#8217;s bleak visions of the future, one in which citizens are monitored through telescreens by an insidious Big Brother, has haunted our imagination long after the publication of 1984. Orwell&#8217;s dystopian image of the telescreen as a repressive instrument of state power has profoundly affected our view [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orwells-revenge-the-1984-palimpsest-senior-fellow-peter-huber-abridged/">Orwell&#8217;s Revenge : The 1984 Palimpsest &#8211; Senior Fellow Peter Huber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mark Zuckerberg&#8217;s &#8216;A Year of Books&#8217; Selection     </p>
<p>                    George Orwell&#8217;s bleak visions of the future, one in which citizens are monitored through telescreens by an insidious Big Brother, has haunted our imagination long after the publication of 1984. Orwell&#8217;s dystopian image of the telescreen as a repressive instrument of state power has profoundly affected our view of technology, posing a stark confrontational question: Who will be master, human or machine? Experience has shown, however, that Orwell&#8217;s vision of the future was profoundly and significantly wrong: The conjunction of the new communications technologies has not produced a master-slave relation between person and computer, but rather exciting possibilities for partnership.     </p>
<p>                    In an extraordinary demonstration of the emerging supermedium&#8217;s potential to engender new forms of creativity, Huber&#8217;s book boldly reimagines 1984 from the computer&#8217;s point of view. After first scanning all of Orwell&#8217;s writings into his personal computer, Huber used the machine to rewrite the book completely, for the most part using Orwell&#8217;s own language. Alternating fiction and non-fiction chapters, Huber advances Orwell&#8217;s plot to a surprising new conclusion while seamlessly interpolating his own explanations and arguments. The result is a fascinating utopian work which envisions a world at our fingertips of ever-increasing information, equal opportunity, and freedom of choice.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orwells-revenge-the-1984-palimpsest-senior-fellow-peter-huber-abridged/">Orwell&#8217;s Revenge : The 1984 Palimpsest &#8211; Senior Fellow Peter Huber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Out of Control  chronicles the dawn of a new era in which the machines and systems that drive our economy are so complex and autonomous as to be indistinguishable from living things.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-control-the-new-biology-of-machines-social-systems-and-the-economic-world-kevin-kelly-abridged/">Out Of Control : The New Biology Of Machines, Social Systems, And The Economic World &#8211; Kevin Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deep Thinking : Where Machine Intelligence Ends and Human Creativity Begins &#8211; Garry Kasparov, Contributions byMig Greengard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybernetics & Systems Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In May 1997, the world watched as Garry Kasparov, the greatest chess player in the world, was defeated for the first time by the IBM supercomputer Deep Blue. It was a watershed moment in the history of technology: machine intelligence had arrived at the point where it could best human intellect. It wasn&#8217;t a coincidence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/">Deep Thinking : Where Machine Intelligence Ends and Human Creativity Begins &#8211; Garry Kasparov, Contributions byMig Greengard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In May 1997, the world watched as Garry Kasparov, the greatest chess player in the world, was defeated for the first time by the IBM supercomputer Deep Blue. It was a watershed moment in the history of technology: machine intelligence had arrived at the point where it could best human intellect.    </p>
<p>                    It wasn&#8217;t a coincidence that Kasparov became the symbol of man&#8217;s fight against the machines. Chess has long been the fulcrum in development of machine intelligence; the hoax automaton &#8216;The Turk&#8217; in the 18th century and Alan Turing&#8217;s first chess program in 1952 were two early examples of the quest for machines to think like humans &#8212; a talent we measured by their ability to beat their creators at chess. As the pre-eminent chessmaster of the 80s and 90s, it was Kasparov&#8217;s blessing and his curse to play against each generation&#8217;s strongest computer champions, contributing to their development and advancing the field.     </p>
<p>                    Like all passionate competitors, Kasparov has taken his defeat and learned from it. He has devoted much energy to devising ways in which humans can partner with machines in order to produce results better than either can achieve alone. During the twenty years since playing Deep Blue, he&#8217;s played both with and against machines, learning a great deal about our vital relationship with our most remarkable creations. Ultimately, he&#8217;s become convinced that by embracing the competition between human and machine intelligence, we can spend less time worrying about being replaced and more thinking of new challenges to conquer.    </p>
<p>                    In this breakthrough book, Kasparov tells his side of the story of Deep Blue for the first time &#8212; what it was like to strategize against an implacable, untiring opponent &#8212; the mistakes he made and the reasons the odds were against him. But more than that, he tells his story of AI more generally, and how he&#8217;s evolved to embrace it, taking part in an urgent debate with philosophers worried about human values, programmers creating self-learning neural networks, and engineers of cutting edge robotics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/">Deep Thinking : Where Machine Intelligence Ends and Human Creativity Begins &#8211; Garry Kasparov, Contributions byMig Greengard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On Intelligence : How a New Understanding of the Brain Will Lead to the Creation of Truly Intelligent Machines &#8211; Hawkins, Jeff, Sandra Blakeslee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-intelligence-how-a-new-understanding-of-the-brain-will-lead-to-the-creation-of-truly-intelligent-machines-hawkins-jeff-sandra-blakeslee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Atomic & Molecular Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-intelligence-how-a-new-understanding-of-the-brain-will-lead-to-the-creation-of-truly-intelligent-machines-hawkins-jeff-sandra-blakeslee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the inventor of the PalmPilot comes a new and compelling theory of intelligence, brain function, and the future of intelligent machines Jeff Hawkins, the man who created the PalmPilot, Treo smart phone, and other handheld devices, has reshaped our relationship to computers. Now he stands ready to revolutionize both neuroscience and computing in one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-intelligence-how-a-new-understanding-of-the-brain-will-lead-to-the-creation-of-truly-intelligent-machines-hawkins-jeff-sandra-blakeslee-abridged/">On Intelligence : How a New Understanding of the Brain Will Lead to the Creation of Truly Intelligent Machines &#8211; Hawkins, Jeff, Sandra Blakeslee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the inventor of the PalmPilot comes a new and compelling theory of intelligence, brain function, and the future of intelligent machines     </p>
<p>                    Jeff Hawkins, the man who created the PalmPilot, Treo smart phone, and other handheld devices, has reshaped our relationship to computers. Now he stands ready to revolutionize both neuroscience and computing in one stroke, with a new understanding of intelligence itself.     </p>
<p>                    Hawkins develops a powerful theory of how the human brain works, explaining why computers are not intelligent and how, based on this new theory, we can finally build intelligent machines.     </p>
<p>                    The brain is not a computer, but a memory system that stores experiences in a way that reflects the true structure of the world, remembering sequences of events and their nested relationships and making predictions based on those memories. It is this memory-prediction system that forms the basis of intelligence, perception, creativity, and even consciousness.     </p>
<p>                    In an engaging style that will captivate audiences from the merely curious to the professional scientist, Hawkins shows how a clear understanding of how the brain works will make it possible for us to build intelligent machines, in silicon, that will exceed our human ability in surprising ways.     </p>
<p>                    Written with acclaimed science writer Sandra Blakeslee, On Intelligence promises to completely transfigure the possibilities of the technology age. It is a landmark book in its scope and clarity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-intelligence-how-a-new-understanding-of-the-brain-will-lead-to-the-creation-of-truly-intelligent-machines-hawkins-jeff-sandra-blakeslee-abridged/">On Intelligence : How a New Understanding of the Brain Will Lead to the Creation of Truly Intelligent Machines &#8211; Hawkins, Jeff, Sandra Blakeslee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employment & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Extraordinary innovations in technology promise to transform the world, but how realistic is the claim that AI will change our lives? In this much needed book the acclaimed economist Roger Bootle responds to the fascinating economic questions posed by the age of the robot, steering a path away from tech jargon and alarmism towards a rational explanation of the ways in which the AI revolution will affect us all. Tackling the implications of Artificial Intelligence on growth, productivity, inflation and the distribution of wealth and power, THE AI ECONOMY also examines coming changes to the the way we educate, work and spend our leisure time.    </p>
<p>                    A fundamentally optimistic view which will help you plan for changing times, this book explains AI and leads you towards a more certain future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ai-economy-work-wealth-and-welfare-in-the-robot-age-roger-bootle-roger-bootle-ltd-abridged/">The AI Economy : Work, Wealth and Welfare in the Robot Age &#8211; Roger Bootle, ROGER BOOTLE LTD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER The creator of the Gaia hypothesis and the greatest environmental thinker of our time has produced an astounding new theory about the future of life on Earth. James Lovelock argues that the anthropocene &#8211; the age in which humans acquired planetary-scale technologies &#8211; is, after three centuries, coming to an end. A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/">Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The creator of the Gaia hypothesis and the greatest environmental thinker of our time has produced an astounding new theory about the future of life on Earth. James Lovelock argues that the anthropocene &#8211; the age in which humans acquired planetary-scale technologies &#8211; is, after three centuries, coming to an end. A new age &#8211; the novacene &#8211; has already begun.    </p>
<p>                    New beings will emerge from existing artificial intelligence systems. They will think 10,000 times faster than we do and will regard us as we now regard plants. The cruel, violent machine takeover imagined by sci-fi writers will not happen: these hyper-intelligent beings will be as dependent on the health of the planet as we are. They will need the planetary cooling system of Gaia to defend from the increasing heat of the sun. Gaia depends on organic life. We will be partners in this project. It is crucial, Lovelock argues, that the intelligence of Earth survives and prospers. We are at present the only beings capable of understanding the cosmos, but he speculates that the novacene could be the beginning of a process that will see intelligence suffusing the entire cosmos. At the age 100, Lovelock has produced the most compelling work of his life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/">Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Creativity Code : How Ai is Learning to Write, Paint and Think &#8211; Marcus du Sautoy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-creativity-code-how-ai-is-learning-to-write-paint-and-think-marcus-du-sautoy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural Language & Machine Translation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-creativity-code-how-ai-is-learning-to-write-paint-and-think-marcus-du-sautoy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Du Sautoy&#8217;s discussion of computer creativity is fascinating&#8217; Observer CAN MACHINES BE CREATIVE? In The Creativity Code, Marcus du Sautoy examines the nature of creativity, asking how much of our emotional response to art is a product of our brains reacting to pattern and structure, and exactly what it is to be creative in mathematics, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-creativity-code-how-ai-is-learning-to-write-paint-and-think-marcus-du-sautoy-abridged/">The Creativity Code : How Ai is Learning to Write, Paint and Think &#8211; Marcus du Sautoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Du Sautoy&#8217;s discussion of computer creativity is fascinating&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                                CAN MACHINES BE CREATIVE?    </p>
<p>                              In The Creativity Code, Marcus du Sautoy examines the nature of creativity, asking how much of our emotional response to art is a product of our brains reacting to pattern and structure, and exactly what it is to be creative in mathematics, art, language and music.    </p>
<p>                              Exploring how long it might be before machines compose a symphony or paint a masterpiece, and whether they might jolt us into being more imaginative in turn, The Creativity Code is a fascinating and very different exploration into the essence of what it means to be human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-creativity-code-how-ai-is-learning-to-write-paint-and-think-marcus-du-sautoy-abridged/">The Creativity Code : How Ai is Learning to Write, Paint and Think &#8211; Marcus du Sautoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Code Book : The Secret History of Codes and Code-Breaking &#8211; Simon Singh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Science of Secrecy from Ancient Egypt to Quantum Cryptography From the best-selling author of Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, The Code Book is a history of man&#8217;s urge to uncover the secrets of codes, from Egyptian puzzles to modern day computer encryptions. As in Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, Simon Singh brings life to an anstonishing story of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/">The Code Book : The Secret History of Codes and Code-Breaking &#8211; Simon Singh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Science of Secrecy from Ancient Egypt to Quantum Cryptography    </p>
<p>                              From the best-selling author of Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, The Code Book is a history of man&#8217;s urge to uncover the secrets of codes, from Egyptian puzzles to modern day computer encryptions.    </p>
<p>                              As in Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, Simon Singh brings life to an anstonishing story of puzzles, codes, languages and riddles that reveals man&#8217;s continual pursuit to disguise and uncover, and to work out the secret languages of others.    </p>
<p>                              Codes have influenced events throughout history, both in the stories of those who make them and those who break them. The betrayal of Mary Queen of Scots and the cracking of the enigma code that helped the Allies in World War II are major episodes in a continuing history of cryptography. In addition to stories of intrigue and warfare, Simon Singh also investigates other codes, the unravelling of genes and the rediscovery of ancient languages and most tantalisingly, the Beale ciphers, an unbroken code that could hold the key to a $20 million treasure.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/">The Code Book : The Secret History of Codes and Code-Breaking &#8211; Simon Singh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
