<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender &amp; Relationships Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/christian-aspects-of-sexuality-gender-relationships/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/christian-aspects-of-sexuality-gender-relationships/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender &amp; Relationships Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/christian-aspects-of-sexuality-gender-relationships/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Wait : A Powerful Practice for Finding the Love of Your Life and the Life You Love &#8211; DeVon Franklin, Meagan Good, With Tim Vandehey</title>
		<link>/the-wait-a-powerful-practice-for-finding-the-love-of-your-life-and-the-life-you-love-devon-franklin-meagan-good-with-tim-vandehey/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wait-a-powerful-practice-for-finding-the-love-of-your-life-and-the-life-you-love-devon-franklin-meagan-good-with-tim-vandehey/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this New York Times bestseller, Hollywood power couple DeVon Franklin and Meagan Good candidly share their courtship and marriage, and the key to their success-waiting. President/CEO of Franklin Entertainment and former Sony Pictures executive DeVon Franklin and award-winning actress Meagan Good have learned firsthand that some people must wait patiently for &#8220;the one&#8221; to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wait-a-powerful-practice-for-finding-the-love-of-your-life-and-the-life-you-love-devon-franklin-meagan-good-with-tim-vandehey/">The Wait : A Powerful Practice for Finding the Love of Your Life and the Life You Love &#8211; DeVon Franklin, Meagan Good, With Tim Vandehey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this New York Times bestseller, Hollywood power couple DeVon Franklin and Meagan Good candidly share their courtship and marriage, and the key to their success-waiting.<br />
                         President/CEO of Franklin Entertainment and former Sony Pictures executive DeVon Franklin and award-winning actress Meagan Good have learned firsthand that some people must wait patiently for &#8220;the one&#8221; to come into their lives. They spent years crossing paths but it wasn&#8217;t until they were thrown together while working on the film Jumping the Broom that their storybook romance began.<br />
                         DeVon and Meagan chose to do something almost unheard of in today&#8217;s society-abstain from sex until they were married. The Wait is filled with candid his-and-hers accounts and practical advice on how waiting for everything-from dating to sex-can transform relationships.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wait-a-powerful-practice-for-finding-the-love-of-your-life-and-the-life-you-love-devon-franklin-meagan-good-with-tim-vandehey/">The Wait : A Powerful Practice for Finding the Love of Your Life and the Life You Love &#8211; DeVon Franklin, Meagan Good, With Tim Vandehey</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Covenant with My Eyes &#8211; Bob Sorge</title>
		<link>/a-covenant-with-my-eyes-bob-sorge/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Men]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-covenant-with-my-eyes-bob-sorge/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This books sounds a bold call to the highest consecration in our sexuality. Get ready for a unique book that is apprehending, prudent, and empowering. Based on Bob&#8217;s own experience with Job 31:1, this book extends an invitation to actually make a covenant vow before God with our eyes. Written for all ages, men and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-covenant-with-my-eyes-bob-sorge/">A Covenant with My Eyes &#8211; Bob Sorge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This books sounds a bold call to the highest consecration in our sexuality. Get ready for a unique book that is apprehending, prudent, and empowering. Based on Bob&#8217;s own experience with Job 31:1, this book extends an invitation to actually make a covenant vow before God with our eyes. Written for all ages, men and women alike, this book excavates from the ancient spirituality of the book of Job the master key to consecration and illuminates its relevance to us today. The careful writing style will make you feel safe recommending this book even to teens.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-covenant-with-my-eyes-bob-sorge/">A Covenant with My Eyes &#8211; Bob Sorge</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bless This Mess : A Modern Guide to Faith and Parenting in a Chaotic World &#8211; Molly Baskette (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A witty, compelling guide to raising open-minded and morally grounded kids in these crazy times, with an approach that&#8217;s rooted in science, psychology, and faith &#8220;Groundbreaking, profound, frank and friendly.&#8221;&#8211;Wendy Mogel, PhD, author of The Blessing of a Skinned Knee NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY LIBRARY JOURNAL When Rev. Molly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/">Bless This Mess : A Modern Guide to Faith and Parenting in a Chaotic World &#8211; Molly Baskette (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A witty, compelling guide to raising open-minded and morally grounded kids in these crazy times, with an approach that&#8217;s rooted in science, psychology, and faith     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Groundbreaking, profound, frank and friendly.&#8221;&#8211;Wendy Mogel, PhD, author of The Blessing of a Skinned Knee     </p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY LIBRARY JOURNAL     </p>
<p>                    When Rev. Molly Baskette and Dr. Ellen O&#8217;Donnell first met, they were both new mothers seeking parenting wisdom. They read a lot of books on the topic, but none of them contained practical suggestions that would help their families psychologically and spiritually while maintaining their progressive values: How do we teach the art of forgiving and serving others? How do we raise kids who are tolerant, curious, and honorable? And what about the sex talk?     </p>
<p>                    Taking matters into their own hands, Baskette and O&#8217;Donnell began creating actionable steps addressing these questions and more. This book is the fruit of their many conversations begun long ago during the daycare carpool, from angsty moments to hallelujahs.     </p>
<p>                    In Bless This Mess, readers will gain constructive tools as they learn how to talk to their children about social justice, money, God, ethics, bullying, disabilities, sexuality, and their bodies. Parents will also glean insights on how to serve others with joy, give generously and gratefully, and&#8211;perhaps most important&#8211;learn how to stop being so afraid all the damn time, even while raising kids in an increasingly chaotic and often scary world. With real-life examples, relatable personal stories, and strategies tailored to the toddler, preteen, or teenager, Bless This Mess guides parents of children at all stages of their development.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bless-this-mess-a-modern-guide-to-faith-and-parenting-in-a-chaotic-world-molly-baskette-abridged/">Bless This Mess : A Modern Guide to Faith and Parenting in a Chaotic World &#8211; Molly Baskette (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get Out of your Head : The One Thought that Can Shift Our Chaotic Minds &#8211; Jennie Allen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/get-out-of-your-head-the-one-thought-that-can-shift-our-chaotic-minds-jennie-allen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Christian Testimony & Popular Inspirational Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/get-out-of-your-head-the-one-thought-that-can-shift-our-chaotic-minds-jennie-allen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; You can choose hope in the midst of chaos. The visionary behind the million-strong IF: Gathering challenges you to exercise your God-given power to shift negative thinking patterns and take back control of your thoughts and emotions. &#8220;A must-have resource for anyone looking to get control of their thoughts.&#8221;&#8211;Lysa TerKeurst, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-out-of-your-head-the-one-thought-that-can-shift-our-chaotic-minds-jennie-allen-abridged/">Get Out of your Head : The One Thought that Can Shift Our Chaotic Minds &#8211; Jennie Allen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; You can choose hope in the midst of chaos. The visionary behind the million-strong IF: Gathering challenges you to exercise your God-given power to shift negative thinking patterns and take back control of your thoughts and emotions.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A must-have resource for anyone looking to get control of their thoughts.&#8221;&#8211;Lysa TerKeurst, #1 New York Times bestselling author and president of Proverbs 31 Ministries     </p>
<p>                    CHRISTIAN BOOK AWARD FINALIST &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY COSMOPOLITAN     </p>
<p>                    Are your thoughts holding you captive? I&#8217;ll never be good enough. Other people have better lives than I do. God couldn&#8217;t really love me. Jennie Allen knows what it&#8217;s like to swirl in a spiral of destructive thoughts, but she also knows we don&#8217;t have to stay stuck in toxic thinking patterns.     </p>
<p>                    As she discovered in her own life, God built a way for us to escape that downward spiral. Freedom comes when we refuse to be victims to our thoughts and realize we have already been equipped with power from God to fight and win the war for our minds.     </p>
<p>                    In Get Out of Your Head,  Jennie inspires and equips us to transform our emotions, our outlook, and even our circumstances by taking control of our thoughts. Our enemy is determined to get in our heads to make us feel helpless, overwhelmed, and incapable of making a difference for the kingdom of God. But when we submit our minds to Christ, the promises and goodness of God flood our lives in remarkable ways.     </p>
<p>                    It starts in your head. And from there, the possibilities are endless.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-out-of-your-head-the-one-thought-that-can-shift-our-chaotic-minds-jennie-allen-abridged/">Get Out of your Head : The One Thought that Can Shift Our Chaotic Minds &#8211; Jennie Allen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Screamfree Parenting : The Revolutionary Approach to Raising your Kids by Keeping your Cool &#8211; Hal Edward Runkel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/screamfree-parenting-the-revolutionary-approach-to-raising-your-kids-by-keeping-your-cool-hal-edward-runkel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/screamfree-parenting-the-revolutionary-approach-to-raising-your-kids-by-keeping-your-cool-hal-edward-runkel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Parents are facing the toughest challenge of their lives. They want to create a loving family environment filled with mutual respect and cooperation&#8230; but they find instead that human nature and the influence of our culture combine to produce an atmosphere of anxiety, exhaustion, and far too much screaming. Perhaps you can relate! Whether you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/screamfree-parenting-the-revolutionary-approach-to-raising-your-kids-by-keeping-your-cool-hal-edward-runkel-abridged/">Screamfree Parenting : The Revolutionary Approach to Raising your Kids by Keeping your Cool &#8211; Hal Edward Runkel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Parents are facing the toughest challenge of their lives. They want to create a loving family environment filled with mutual respect and cooperation&#8230; but they find instead that human nature and the influence of our culture combine to produce an atmosphere of anxiety, exhaustion, and far too much screaming. Perhaps you can relate!     </p>
<p>                    Whether you scream at your children or not, you no doubt feel anxious about them and their choices. You worry how they&#8217;ll turn out. Unfortunately for parents, many of the techniques some experts present only seem to make matters worse. Hal Edward Runkel has discovered why: Parents are spending far too much time orbiting their lives around their children. They need to return the focus to themselves. They need to grow up and calm down.     </p>
<p>                    ScreamFree Parenting is about taming your reactive responses to your deep anxiety. Rather than learning new techniques, you&#8217;ll discover the liberating principles, based on scriptural truths, that are inspiring parents just like you to revolutionize their family life. Principles that will enable you to remain cool, calm, and connected with your children, no matter what.     </p>
<p>                    Learn how to parent less out of your deepest fears and more out of the highest principles in ScreamFree Parenting.     </p>
<p>                    Special edition distributed through Christian booksellers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/screamfree-parenting-the-revolutionary-approach-to-raising-your-kids-by-keeping-your-cool-hal-edward-runkel-abridged/">Screamfree Parenting : The Revolutionary Approach to Raising your Kids by Keeping your Cool &#8211; Hal Edward Runkel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Keep Showing Up : How to Stay Crazy in Love When Your Love Drives You Crazy &#8211; Karen Ehman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/keep-showing-up-how-to-stay-crazy-in-love-when-your-love-drives-you-crazy-karen-ehman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/keep-showing-up-how-to-stay-crazy-in-love-when-your-love-drives-you-crazy-karen-ehman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Discover how your differences can become the strength of your marriage in this real-life guide to both living with and loving your spouse. It is true that opposites attract&#8211;for a while. But often as the years go by in our marriages, opposites may also begin to attack. The habits and characteristics we once found endearing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/keep-showing-up-how-to-stay-crazy-in-love-when-your-love-drives-you-crazy-karen-ehman-abridged/">Keep Showing Up : How to Stay Crazy in Love When Your Love Drives You Crazy &#8211; Karen Ehman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Discover how your differences can become the strength of your marriage in this real-life guide to both living with and loving your spouse.    </p>
<p>                    It is true that opposites attract&#8211;for a while. But often as the years go by in our marriages, opposites may also begin to attack. The habits and characteristics we once found endearing about our significant other are the exact things that drive us crazy years later!    </p>
<p>                    Whether you and your spouse disagree about finances, parenting, or how to load the dishwasher, your differences don&#8217;t need to divide you. They can actually bring you closer together&#8211;and closer to God.    </p>
<p>                    In Keep Showing Up, Karen Ehman shows you . . .    </p>
<p>                    How to play to each other&#8217;s strengths as you work on your own weaknesses<br />
                    The difference between having a soul mate and having a sole mate<br />
                    How to become a faithful forgiver who also forgets<br />
                    Strategies for avoiding the social media comparison trap<br />
                    Why it&#8217;s dangerous to mimic a friend&#8217;s marriage<br />
                    How to unearth the magic in the mundane<br />
                    Why a spouse who drives you crazy can drive you straight to Jesus    </p>
<p>                    Throughout Keep Showing Up, Karen also includes ideas to implement in your marriage right now, such as powerful statements to speak to your spouse, date-night-on-a-shoestring suggestions, and discussion starters.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/keep-showing-up-how-to-stay-crazy-in-love-when-your-love-drives-you-crazy-karen-ehman-abridged/">Keep Showing Up : How to Stay Crazy in Love When Your Love Drives You Crazy &#8211; Karen Ehman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Next Right Thing : A Simple, Soulful Practice for Making Life Decisions &#8211; Emily P. Freeman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-next-right-thing-a-simple-soulful-practice-for-making-life-decisions-emily-p-freeman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-next-right-thing-a-simple-soulful-practice-for-making-life-decisions-emily-p-freeman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nothing gets our attention like an unmade decision: Should I accept the new position? Which schooling choice is best for my kids? How can I support my aging parents? When we have a decision to make and the answer isn&#8217;t clear, what we want more than anything is peace, clarity, and a nudge in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-next-right-thing-a-simple-soulful-practice-for-making-life-decisions-emily-p-freeman-abridged/">The Next Right Thing : A Simple, Soulful Practice for Making Life Decisions &#8211; Emily P. Freeman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nothing gets our attention like an unmade decision: Should I accept the new position? Which schooling choice is best for my kids? How can I support my aging parents? When we have a decision to make and the answer isn&#8217;t clear, what we want more than anything is peace, clarity, and a nudge in the right direction.     </p>
<p>                    If you have trouble making decisions, because of either chronic hesitation you&#8217;ve always lived with or a more recent onset of decision fatigue, Emily P. Freeman offers a fresh way of practicing familiar but often forgotten advice: simply do the next right thing. With this simple, soulful practice, it is possible to clear the decision-making chaos, quiet the fear of choosing wrong, and find the courage to finally decide without regret or second-guessing.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re in the midst of a major life transition or are weary of the low-grade anxiety that daily life can bring, Emily helps create space for your soul to breathe so you can live life with God at a gentle pace and discern your next right thing in love.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-next-right-thing-a-simple-soulful-practice-for-making-life-decisions-emily-p-freeman-abridged/">The Next Right Thing : A Simple, Soulful Practice for Making Life Decisions &#8211; Emily P. Freeman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everybody, Always : Becoming Love in a World Full of Setbacks and Difficult People &#8211; Bob Goff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everybody-always-becoming-love-in-a-world-full-of-setbacks-and-difficult-people-bob-goff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everybody-always-becoming-love-in-a-world-full-of-setbacks-and-difficult-people-bob-goff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What if we stopped avoiding the difficult people in our lives and committed to simply loving everybody? What happens when we give away love like we&#8217;re made of it? In Everybody, Always, Bob Goff&#8217;s joyful New York Times bestselling follow-up to Love Does, you&#8217;ll discover the secret to living without fear, constraint, or worry. Bob [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-always-becoming-love-in-a-world-full-of-setbacks-and-difficult-people-bob-goff-abridged/">Everybody, Always : Becoming Love in a World Full of Setbacks and Difficult People &#8211; Bob Goff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What if we stopped avoiding the difficult people in our lives and committed to simply loving everybody? What happens when we give away love like we&#8217;re made of it? In Everybody, Always, Bob Goff&#8217;s joyful New York Times bestselling follow-up to Love Does, you&#8217;ll discover the secret to living without fear, constraint, or worry.     </p>
<p>                    Bob teaches us that the path toward the outsized, unfettered, liberated existence we all long for is found in one simple truth: love people, even the difficult ones, without distinction and without limits.    </p>
<p>                    In Everybody, Always, Bob shows us the simple truths about life that have the power to shift our mindset forever:    </p>
<p>                    Jesus uses our blind spots to reveal himself to us<br />
                    It&#8217;s easy to love kind, lovely, humble people, but you have to tackle fear in order to love people who are difficult<br />
                    What we do with our love will become the conversations we have with God<br />
                    Dark and scary places are filled with beautiful people who need our unconditional love<br />
                    Extravagant love has extraordinary power to change lives, including our own    </p>
<p>                    Driven by Bob&#8217;s trademark storytelling, this book reveals the wisdom Bob learned&#8211;often the hard way&#8211;about what it means to love without inhibition, insecurity, or restriction. From finding the right friends to discovering the upside of failure, Everybody, Always points the way to embodying love by doing the unexpected, the intimidating, the seemingly impossible.    </p>
<p>                    Whether losing his shoes while skydiving solo or befriending a Ugandan witch doctor, Bob steps into life with a no-limits embrace of others that is as infectious as it is extraordinarily ordinary. Everybody, Always reveals how we can do the same.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-always-becoming-love-in-a-world-full-of-setbacks-and-difficult-people-bob-goff-abridged/">Everybody, Always : Becoming Love in a World Full of Setbacks and Difficult People &#8211; Bob Goff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Girl, Wash Your Face : Stop Believing the Lies About Who You Are so You Can Become Who You Were Meant to Be &#8211; Rachel Hollis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 3 MILLION COPIES SOLD Do you ever suspect that everyone else has life figured out and you don&#8217;t have a clue? If so, Rachel Hollis has something to tell you: that&#8217;s a lie. If you have ever said any of these things to yourself . . . Something [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/">Girl, Wash Your Face : Stop Believing the Lies About Who You Are so You Can Become Who You Were Meant to Be &#8211; Rachel Hollis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; OVER 3 MILLION COPIES SOLD    </p>
<p>                    Do you ever suspect that everyone else has life figured out and you don&#8217;t have a clue? If so, Rachel Hollis has something to tell you: that&#8217;s a lie.    </p>
<p>                    If you have ever said any of these things to yourself . . .    </p>
<p>                    Something else will make me happy.<br />
                    I&#8217;m not a good mom.<br />
                    I will never get past this.<br />
                    I am defined by my weight.<br />
                    I should be further along by now.    </p>
<p>                    . . . then you could benefit from the unflinching faith and rock-hard tenacity Rachel Hollis has in store for you. In this challenging but conversational book, Rachel exposes the twenty lies and misconceptions that too often hold us back from living joyfully and productively, lies we&#8217;ve told ourselves so often we don&#8217;t even hear them anymore.    </p>
<p>                    Rachel is real and talks about real issues. More than that, she reveals the specific practical strategies that helped her move past them. In the process, she encourages, entertains, and even kicks a little butt, all to convince you to do whatever it takes to get real and become the joyous, confident woman you were meant to be. Because you really can live with passion and hustle &#8211; and give yourself grace without giving up.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girl-wash-your-face-stop-believing-the-lies-about-who-you-are-so-you-can-become-who-you-were-meant-to-be-rachel-hollis-abridged/">Girl, Wash Your Face : Stop Believing the Lies About Who You Are so You Can Become Who You Were Meant to Be &#8211; Rachel Hollis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Loving Your Spouse When you Feel Like Walking Away : Real Help for Desperate Hearts in Difficult Marriages &#8211; Gary D. Chapman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/loving-your-spouse-when-you-feel-like-walking-away-real-help-for-desperate-hearts-in-difficult-marriages-gary-d-chapman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/loving-your-spouse-when-you-feel-like-walking-away-real-help-for-desperate-hearts-in-difficult-marriages-gary-d-chapman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What to do when you feel like giving up When you said, &#8220;I do,&#8221; you entered marriage with high hopes, dreaming it would be supremely happy. You never intended it to be miserable. Millions of couples are struggling in desperate marriages. But the story doesn&#8217;t have to end there. Dr. Gary Chapman writes, &#8220;I believe [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/loving-your-spouse-when-you-feel-like-walking-away-real-help-for-desperate-hearts-in-difficult-marriages-gary-d-chapman-abridged/">Loving Your Spouse When you Feel Like Walking Away : Real Help for Desperate Hearts in Difficult Marriages &#8211; Gary D. Chapman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What to do when you feel like giving up    </p>
<p>                    When you said, &#8220;I do,&#8221; you entered marriage with high hopes, dreaming it would be supremely happy.     </p>
<p>                    You never intended it to be miserable.    </p>
<p>                    Millions of couples are struggling in desperate marriages. But the story doesn&#8217;t have to end there. Dr. Gary Chapman writes, &#8220;I believe that in every troubled marriage, one or both partners can take positive steps that have the potential for changing the emotional climate in their marriage.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Loving Your Spouse When You Feel Like Walking Away, the revised and updated edition of the award-winning Desparate Marriages, teaches you how to: Recognize and reject the myths that hold you captiveBetter understand your spouse&#8217;s behaviorTake responsibility for your own thoughts, feelings, and actionsMake choices that can have a lasting, positive impact on you and your spouse    </p>
<p>                    An experienced marriage and family counselor, Gary Chapman speaks to those whose spouse is any of the following: IrresponsibleA workaholicControllingUncommunicativeVerbally abusivePhysically abusiveSexually abusiveUnfaithfulAddicted to alcohol or drugsDepressed    </p>
<p>                    Marriage has the same potential to be miserable as it does to be blissful. Read Loving Your Spouse When You Feel Like Walking Away to learn how you can turn things around.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/loving-your-spouse-when-you-feel-like-walking-away-real-help-for-desperate-hearts-in-difficult-marriages-gary-d-chapman-abridged/">Loving Your Spouse When you Feel Like Walking Away : Real Help for Desperate Hearts in Difficult Marriages &#8211; Gary D. Chapman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
