<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Industrial / Commercial Art &amp; Design Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/industrial-commercial-art-design/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/industrial-commercial-art-design/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Industrial / Commercial Art &amp; Design Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/industrial-commercial-art-design/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Creative Confidence : Unleashing the Creative Potential within Us All &#8211; David Kelley, Tom Kelley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/creative-confidence-unleashing-the-creative-potential-within-us-all-david-kelley-tom-kelley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/creative-confidence-unleashing-the-creative-potential-within-us-all-david-kelley-tom-kelley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A powerful and inspiring book from the founders of IDEO, the award-winning design firm, on unleashing the creativity that lies within each and every one of us. Too often, companies and individuals assume that creativity and innovation are the domain of the &#8216;creative types&#8217;. But two of the foremost experts in innovation, design and creativity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/creative-confidence-unleashing-the-creative-potential-within-us-all-david-kelley-tom-kelley-abridged/">Creative Confidence : Unleashing the Creative Potential within Us All &#8211; David Kelley, Tom Kelley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A powerful and inspiring book from the founders of IDEO, the award-winning design firm, on unleashing the creativity that lies within each and every one of us.    </p>
<p>                              Too often, companies and individuals assume that creativity and innovation are the domain of the &#8216;creative types&#8217;. But two of the foremost experts in innovation, design and creativity on the planet show us that each and every one of us is creative.    </p>
<p>                              In an entertaining and inspiring narrative that draws on countless stories from their work at IDEO, and with many of the world&#8217;s top companies and design firms, David and Tom Kelley identify the principles and strategies that will allow us to tap into our creative potential in our work lives, and in our personal lives, allow us to think outside the box in terms of how we approach and solve problems.    </p>
<p>                              &#8216;Creative Confidence&#8217; is a book that will help each of us be more productive and successful in our lives and in our careers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/creative-confidence-unleashing-the-creative-potential-within-us-all-david-kelley-tom-kelley-abridged/">Creative Confidence : Unleashing the Creative Potential within Us All &#8211; David Kelley, Tom Kelley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lean UX : Creating Great Products with Agile Teams &#8211; Jeff Gothelf, Josh Seiden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Development Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lean UX is synonymous with modern product design and development. By combining human-centric design, agile ways of working, and a strong business sense, designers, product managers, developers, and scrum masters around the world are making Lean UX the leading approach for digital product teams today In the third edition of this award-winning book, authors Jeff [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/">Lean UX : Creating Great Products with Agile Teams &#8211; Jeff Gothelf, Josh Seiden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Lean UX is synonymous with modern product design and development. By combining human-centric design, agile ways of working, and a strong business sense, designers, product managers, developers, and scrum masters around the world are making Lean UX the leading approach for digital product teams today    </p>
<p>                    In the third edition of this award-winning book, authors Jeff Gothelf and Josh Seiden help you focus on the product experience rather than deliverables. You&#8217;ll learn tactics for integrating user experience design, product discovery, agile methods, and product management. And you&#8217;ll discover how to drive your design in short, iterative cycles to assess what works best for businesses and users. Lean UX guides you through this change&#8211;for the better.    </p>
<p>                    Facilitate the Lean UX process with your team with the Lean UX Canvas<br />
                    Ensure every project starts with clear customer-centric success criteria<br />
                    Understand the role of the designer on an agile team<br />
                    Write and contribute design and experiment stories to the backlog<br />
                    Ensure design work takes place in every sprint<br />
                    Build product discovery into the team&#8217;s &#8220;velocity&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lean-ux-creating-great-products-with-agile-teams-jeff-gothelf-josh-seiden-abridged/">Lean UX : Creating Great Products with Agile Teams &#8211; Jeff Gothelf, Josh Seiden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stoned : Jewelry, Obsession, and How Desire Shapes the World &#8211; Aja Raden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stoned-jewelry-obsession-and-how-desire-shapes-the-world-aja-raden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antiques & Collectables: Jewellery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fashion & Textiles: Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewellery & Beadcraft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stoned-jewelry-obsession-and-how-desire-shapes-the-world-aja-raden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As entertaining as it is incisive, Stoned is a raucous journey through the history of human desire for what is rare, and therefore precious. What makes a stone a jewel? What makes a jewel priceless? And why do we covet beautiful things? In this brilliant account of how eight jewels shaped the course of history, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stoned-jewelry-obsession-and-how-desire-shapes-the-world-aja-raden-abridged/">Stoned : Jewelry, Obsession, and How Desire Shapes the World &#8211; Aja Raden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As entertaining as it is incisive, Stoned is a raucous journey through the history of human desire for what is rare, and therefore precious.  What makes a stone a jewel? What makes a jewel priceless? And why do we covet beautiful things? In this brilliant account of how eight jewels shaped the course of history, jeweler and scientist Aja Raden tells an original and often startling story about our unshakeable addiction to beauty and the darker side of human desire.  What moves the world is what moves each of us: desire. Jewelry-which has long served as a stand-in for wealth and power, glamor and success-has birthed cultural movements, launched political dynasties, and started wars. Masterfully weaving together pop science and history, Stoned breaks history into three categories-Want, Take, and Have-and explains what the diamond on your finger has to do with the GI Bill, why green-tinted jewelry has been exalted by so many cultures, why the glass beads that bought Manhattan for the Dutch were initially considered a fair trade, and how the French Revolution started over a coveted necklace.<br />
                    Studded with lively personalities and fascinating details, Stoned tells the remarkable story of our abiding desire for the rare and extraordinary.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stoned-jewelry-obsession-and-how-desire-shapes-the-world-aja-raden-abridged/">Stoned : Jewelry, Obsession, and How Desire Shapes the World &#8211; Aja Raden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>100 Things Every Designer Needs to Know About People &#8211; Susan Weinschenk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Desktop Publishing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Graphics & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Web Programming]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WE DESIGN TO ELICIT RESPONSES from people. We want them to buy something, read more, or take action of some kind. Designing without understanding what makes people act the way they do is like exploring a new city without a map: results will be haphazard, confusing, and inefficient. This book combines real science and research [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/">100 Things Every Designer Needs to Know About People &#8211; Susan Weinschenk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WE DESIGN TO ELICIT RESPONSES from people. We want them to buy something, read more, or take action of some kind. Designing without understanding what makes people act the way they do is like exploring a new city without a map: results will be haphazard, confusing, and inefficient. This book combines real science and research with practical examples to deliver a guide every designer needs. With this book you&#8217;ll design more intuitive and engaging apps, software, websites and products that match the way people think, decide and behave.    </p>
<p>                      INCREASE THE EFFECTIVENESS OF YOUR PRODUCTS.    </p>
<p>                      Apply psychology and behavioral science to your designs.    </p>
<p>                      Here are some of the questions this book will answer:    </p>
<p>                      * What grabs and holds attention.    </p>
<p>                      * What makes memories stick?    </p>
<p>                      * What is more important, peripheral or central vision?    </p>
<p>                      * Can you predict the types of errors people will make?    </p>
<p>                      * What is the limit to someone&#8217;s social circle?    </p>
<p>                      * What line length for text is best?    </p>
<p>                      * Are some fonts better than others?    </p>
<p>                      These are just a few of the questions that the book answers in its deep-dive exploration of what makes people tick.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-things-every-designer-needs-to-know-about-people-susan-weinschenk-abridged/">100 Things Every Designer Needs to Know About People &#8211; Susan Weinschenk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Do Design : Why Beauty is Key to Everything &#8211; Alan Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/do-design-why-beauty-is-key-to-everything-alan-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Epistemology & Theory Of Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/do-design-why-beauty-is-key-to-everything-alan-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>So much goes unnoticed. We multi-task, switch between screens, work faster. When was the last time you paused to consider a beautifully made object or stunning natural landscape? Yet this is when our spirits lift, our soul is restored. Designer Alan Moore invites us to rethink not only what we produce &#8211; whether it&#8217;s a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-design-why-beauty-is-key-to-everything-alan-moore-abridged/">Do Design : Why Beauty is Key to Everything &#8211; Alan Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>So much goes unnoticed. We multi-task, switch between screens, work faster. When was the last time you paused to consider a beautifully made object or stunning natural landscape? Yet this is when our spirits lift, our soul is restored. Designer Alan Moore invites us to rethink not only what we produce &#8211; whether it&#8217;s a website, a handmade chair, or a business &#8211; but how and why. With examples including Pixar, Apple, and Blitz Motorcycles, we are encouraged to ask: Is it useful and considered. Is it a thing of beauty? Do Design will inspire you to:<br />
                    &#8211; Improve your creative process<br />
                    &#8211; Raise the quality and craft of your work<br />
                    &#8211; Consider the experience as much as the product<br />
                    &#8211; Adopt simplicity, utility and honesty as guiding principles We are creative beings. We love to make things. This book will inspire you to create better things, for better reasons. Things that people will love &#8211; for a long time to come. Some say beauty is a luxury. But what if it is key to creating a better world for us all?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/do-design-why-beauty-is-key-to-everything-alan-moore-abridged/">Do Design : Why Beauty is Key to Everything &#8211; Alan Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Box : How the Shipping Container Made the World Smaller and the World Economy Bigger &#8211; Second Edition with a new chapter by the author &#8211; Marc Levinson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-box-how-the-shipping-container-made-the-world-smaller-and-the-world-economy-bigger-second-edition-with-a-new-chapter-by-the-author-marc-levinson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial / Commercial Art & Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shipping Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Transport Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-box-how-the-shipping-container-made-the-world-smaller-and-the-world-economy-bigger-second-edition-with-a-new-chapter-by-the-author-marc-levinson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In April 1956, a refitted oil tanker carried fifty-eight shipping containers from Newark to Houston. From that modest beginning, container shipping developed into a huge industry that made the boom in global trade possible. The Box tells the dramatic story of the container&#8217;s creation, the decade of struggle before it was widely adopted, and the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-box-how-the-shipping-container-made-the-world-smaller-and-the-world-economy-bigger-second-edition-with-a-new-chapter-by-the-author-marc-levinson-abridged/">The Box : How the Shipping Container Made the World Smaller and the World Economy Bigger &#8211; Second Edition with a new chapter by the author &#8211; Marc Levinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In April 1956, a refitted oil tanker carried fifty-eight shipping containers from Newark to Houston. From that modest beginning, container shipping developed into a huge industry that made the boom in global trade possible. The Box tells the dramatic story of the container&#8217;s creation, the decade of struggle before it was widely adopted, and the sweeping economic consequences of the sharp fall in transportation costs that containerization brought about. But the container didn&#8217;t just happen. Its adoption required huge sums of money, both from private investors and from ports that aspired to be on the leading edge of a new technology. It required years of high-stakes bargaining with two of the titans of organized labor, Harry Bridges and Teddy Gleason, as well as delicate negotiations on standards that made it possible for almost any container to travel on any truck or train or ship. Ultimately, it took McLean&#8217;s success in supplying U.S. forces in Vietnam to persuade the world of the container&#8217;s potential.<br />
                    Drawing on previously neglected sources, economist Marc Levinson shows how the container transformed economic geography, devastating traditional ports such as New York and London and fueling the growth of previously obscure ones, such as Oakland. By making shipping so cheap that industry could locate factories far from its customers, the container paved the way for Asia to become the world&#8217;s workshop and brought consumers a previously unimaginable variety of low-cost products from around the globe. Published in hardcover on the fiftieth anniversary of the first container voyage, this is the first comprehensive history of the shipping container. Now with a new chapter, The Box tells the dramatic story of how the drive and imagination of an iconoclastic entrepreneur turned containerization from an impractical idea into a phenomenon that transformed economic geography, slashed transportation costs, and made the boom in global trade possible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-box-how-the-shipping-container-made-the-world-smaller-and-the-world-economy-bigger-second-edition-with-a-new-chapter-by-the-author-marc-levinson-abridged/">The Box : How the Shipping Container Made the World Smaller and the World Economy Bigger &#8211; Second Edition with a new chapter by the author &#8211; Marc Levinson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
