<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Finance &amp; Accounting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/finance-accounting/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/finance-accounting/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Finance &amp; Accounting Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/finance-accounting/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Atomic Habits : the life-changing million-copy #1 bestseller &#8211; James Clear</title>
		<link>/atomic-habits-the-life-changing-million-copy-1-bestseller-james-clear/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early & Medieval]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Classical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/atomic-habits-the-life-changing-million-copy-1-bestseller-james-clear/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE PHENOMENAL INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER: 1 MILLION COPIES SOLD Transform your life with tiny changes in behaviour, starting now. People think that when you want to change your life, you need to think big. But world-renowned habits expert James Clear has discovered another way. He knows that real change comes from the compound effect of hundreds [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/atomic-habits-the-life-changing-million-copy-1-bestseller-james-clear/">Atomic Habits : the life-changing million-copy #1 bestseller &#8211; James Clear</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE PHENOMENAL INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER: 1 MILLION COPIES SOLD</p>
<p>                    Transform your life with tiny changes in behaviour, starting now.</p>
<p>                    People think that when you want to change your life, you need to think big. But world-renowned habits expert James Clear has discovered another way. He knows that real change comes from the compound effect of hundreds of small decisions: doing two push-ups a day, waking up five minutes early, or holding a single short phone call.</p>
<p>                    He calls them atomic habits.</p>
<p>                    In this ground-breaking book, Clears reveals exactly how these minuscule changes can grow into such life-altering outcomes. He uncovers a handful of simple life hacks (the forgotten art of Habit Stacking, the unexpected power of the Two Minute Rule, or the trick to entering the Goldilocks Zone), and delves into cutting-edge psychology and neuroscience to explain why they matter. Along the way, he tells inspiring stories of Olympic gold medalists, leading CEOs, and distinguished scientists who have used the science of tiny habits to stay productive, motivated, and happy. </p>
<p>                    These small changes will have a revolutionary effect on your career, your relationships, and your life.<br />
                    ________________________________<br />
                    A NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A supremely practical and useful book.&#8217; Mark Manson, author of The Subtle Art of Not Giving A F*ck</p>
<p>                    &#8216;James Clear has spent years honing the art and studying the science of habits. This engaging, hands-on book is the guide you need to break bad routines and make good ones.&#8217; Adam Grant, author of Originals</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Atomic Habits is a step-by-step manual for changing routines.&#8217; Books of the Month, Financial Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A special book that will change how you approach your day and live your life.&#8217; Ryan Holiday, author of The Obstacle is the Way</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/atomic-habits-the-life-changing-million-copy-1-bestseller-james-clear/">Atomic Habits : the life-changing million-copy #1 bestseller &#8211; James Clear</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bogleheads&#8217; Guide to Investing &#8211; Mel Lindauer</title>
		<link>/the-bogleheads-guide-to-investing-mel-lindauer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bogleheads-guide-to-investing-mel-lindauer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The irreverent guide to investing, Boglehead style The Boglehead&#8217;s Guide to Investing is a DIY handbook that espouses the sage investment wisdom of John C. Bogle. This witty and wonderful book offers contrarian advice that provides the first step on the road to investment success, illustrating how relying on typical &#8220;common sense&#8221; promoted by Wall [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bogleheads-guide-to-investing-mel-lindauer/">The Bogleheads&#8217; Guide to Investing &#8211; Mel Lindauer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The irreverent guide to investing, Boglehead style The Boglehead&#8217;s Guide to Investing is a DIY handbook that espouses the sage investment wisdom of John C. Bogle. This witty and wonderful book offers contrarian advice that provides the first step on the road to investment success, illustrating how relying on typical &#8220;common sense&#8221; promoted by Wall Street is destined to leave you poorer. This updated edition includes new information on backdoor Roth IRAs and ETFs as mainstream buy and hold investments, estate taxes and gifting, plus changes to the laws regarding Traditional and Roth IRAs, and 401k and 403b retirement plans. With warnings and principles both precisely accurate and grandly counterintuitive, the Boglehead authors show how beating the market is a zero-sum game. Investing can be simple, but it&#8217;s certainly not simplistic. Over the course of twenty years, the followers of John C. Bogle have evolved from a loose association of investors to a major force with the largest and most active non-commercial financial forum on the Internet.<br />
                    The Boglehead&#8217;s Guide to Investing brings that communication to you with comprehensive guidance to the investment prowess on display at Bogleheads.org. You&#8217;ll learn how to craft your own investment strategy using the Bogle-proven methods that have worked for thousands of investors, and how to: * Choose a sound financial lifestyle and diversify your portfolio * Start early, invest regularly, and know what you&#8217;re buying * Preserve your buying power, keeping costs and taxes low * Throw out the &#8220;good&#8221; advice promoted by Wall Street that leads to investment failure Financial markets are essentially closed systems in which one&#8217;s gain garners another&#8217;s loss. Investors looking for a roadmap to successfully navigating these choppy waters long-term will find expert guidance, sound advice, and a little irreverent humor in The Boglehead&#8217;s Guide to Investing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bogleheads-guide-to-investing-mel-lindauer/">The Bogleheads&#8217; Guide to Investing &#8211; Mel Lindauer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Practically Radical : Not-So-Crazy Ways to Transform Your Company, Shake Up Your Industry, and Challenge Yourself &#8211; William C Taylor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The most powerful and instructive change manual you&#8217;ll ever read. It will persuade and inspire you to change your business, your work, and maybe your life.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, bestselling author of A Whole New Mind In Practically Radical, William C. Taylor, the New York Times bestselling co-author of Mavericks at Work offers a refreshing, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/">Practically Radical : Not-So-Crazy Ways to Transform Your Company, Shake Up Your Industry, and Challenge Yourself &#8211; William C Taylor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The most powerful and instructive change manual you&#8217;ll ever read. It will persuade and inspire you to change your business, your work, and maybe your life.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel H. Pink, bestselling author of A Whole New Mind     </p>
<p>                    In Practically Radical, William C. Taylor, the New York Times bestselling co-author of Mavericks at Work offers a refreshing, rigorous new look at pragmatic ways to shake things up and make positive change in difficult times.     </p>
<p>                    Exploring how twenty-five for-profit companies and nonprofit organizations&#8211;including IBM, Zappos, Swatch, the Girl Scouts, and Interpol&#8211;made remarkable strides in tough circumstances, Practically Radical raises (and answers) the make-or-break questions facing today&#8217;s leaders in every field: Do you see opportunities the competition doesn&#8217;t see? The most successful organizations embrace one-of-a-kind ideas in a world filled with me-too thinking.Do you have new ideas about where to look for new ideas? Routine practices in one field can be revolutionary when they migrate to another.Are you the most of anything? In business today, the middle of the road is the road to ruin.Are you getting the best contributions from the most people? Change is not a game best played by loners.    </p>
<p>                    Anything but your typical business book, Practically Radical is a must-own for small business owners and CEOs, for managers at all levels, and innovators and entrepreneurs of every stripe.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/practically-radical-not-so-crazy-ways-to-transform-your-company-shake-up-your-industry-and-challenge-yourself-william-c-taylor-abridged/">Practically Radical : Not-So-Crazy Ways to Transform Your Company, Shake Up Your Industry, and Challenge Yourself &#8211; William C Taylor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Barefoot Investor : The Only Money Guide You&#8217;ll Ever Need &#8211; Scott Pape (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-barefoot-investor-the-only-money-guide-youll-ever-need-scott-pape-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-barefoot-investor-the-only-money-guide-youll-ever-need-scott-pape-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** Reviewed and updated for the 2020-2021 financial year** This is the only money guide you&#8217;ll ever need That&#8217;s a bold claim, given there are already thousands of finance books on the shelves. So what makes this one different? Well, you won&#8217;t be overwhelmed with a bunch of &#8216;tips&#8217; &#8230; or a strict budget (that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-barefoot-investor-the-only-money-guide-youll-ever-need-scott-pape-abridged/">The Barefoot Investor : The Only Money Guide You&#8217;ll Ever Need &#8211; Scott Pape (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** Reviewed and updated for the 2020-2021 financial year**    </p>
<p>                     This is the only money guide you&#8217;ll ever need    </p>
<p>                     That&#8217;s a bold claim, given there are already thousands of finance books on the shelves.    </p>
<p>                     So what makes this one different?    </p>
<p>                     Well, you won&#8217;t be overwhelmed with a bunch of &#8216;tips&#8217; &#8230; or a strict budget (that you won&#8217;t follow).    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll get a step-by-step formula: open this account, then do this; call this person, and say this; invest money here, and not there. All with a glass of wine in your hand.    </p>
<p>                     This book will show you how to create an entire financial plan that is so simple you can sketch it on the back of a serviette &#8230; and you&#8217;ll be able to manage your money in 10 minutes a week.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll also get the skinny on:    </p>
<p>                     Saving up a six-figure house deposit in 20 months    </p>
<p>                     Doubling your income using the &#8216;Trapeze Strategy&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     Saving $78,173 on your mortgage and wiping out 7 years of payments    </p>
<p>                     Finding a financial advisor who won&#8217;t rip you off    </p>
<p>                     Handing your kids (or grandkids) a $140,000 cheque on their 21st birthday    </p>
<p>                     Why you don&#8217;t need $1 million to retire &#8230; with the &#8216;Donald Bradman Retirement Strategy&#8217;    </p>
<p>                     Sound too good to be true? It&#8217;s not.    </p>
<p>                     This book is full of stories from everyday Aussies &#8211; single people, young families, empty nesters, retirees &#8211; who have applied the simple steps in this book and achieved amazing, life-changing results.    </p>
<p>                     And you&#8217;re next.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-barefoot-investor-the-only-money-guide-youll-ever-need-scott-pape-abridged/">The Barefoot Investor : The Only Money Guide You&#8217;ll Ever Need &#8211; Scott Pape (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Mistakes : The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments &#8211; Michael Batnick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/big-mistakes-the-best-investors-and-their-worst-investments-michael-batnick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/big-mistakes-the-best-investors-and-their-worst-investments-michael-batnick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Must-Read for Any Investor Looking to Maximize Their Chances of Success Big Mistakes: The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments explores the ways in which the biggest names have failed, and reveals the lessons learned that shaped more successful strategies going forward. Investing can be a rollercoaster of highs and lows, and the investors [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-mistakes-the-best-investors-and-their-worst-investments-michael-batnick-abridged/">Big Mistakes : The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments &#8211; Michael Batnick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Must-Read for Any Investor Looking to Maximize Their Chances of Success Big Mistakes: The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments explores the ways in which the biggest names have failed, and reveals the lessons learned that shaped more successful strategies going forward. Investing can be a rollercoaster of highs and lows, and the investors detailed here show just how low it can go; stories from Warren Buffet, Bill Ackman, Chris Sacca, Jack Bogle, Mark Twain, John Maynard Keynes, and many more illustrate the simple but overlooked concept that investing is really hard, whether you&#8217;re managing a few thousand dollars or a few billion, failures and losses are part of the game. Much more than just anecdotal diversion, these stories set the basis for the book&#8217;s critical focus: learning from mistakes. These investors all recovered from their missteps, and moved forward armed with a wealth of knowledge than can only come from experience. Lessons learned through failure carry a weight that no textbook can convey, and in the case of these legendary investors, informed a set of skills and strategy that propelled them to the top.<br />
                    Research-heavy and grounded in realism, this book is a must-read for any investor looking to maximize their chances of success. * Learn the most common ways even successful investors fail * Learn from the mistakes of the greats to avoid losing ground * Anticipate challenges and obstacles, and develop an advance plan * Exercise caution when warranted, and only take the smart risks While learning from your mistakes is always a valuable experience, learning from the mistakes of others gives you the benefit of wisdom without the consequences of experience. Big Mistakes: The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments provides an incomparable, invaluable resource for investors of all stripes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-mistakes-the-best-investors-and-their-worst-investments-michael-batnick-abridged/">Big Mistakes : The Best Investors and Their Worst Investments &#8211; Michael Batnick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thou Shall Prosper : Ten Commandments for Making Money &#8211; Rabbi Daniel Lapin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thou-shall-prosper-ten-commandments-for-making-money-rabbi-daniel-lapin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jewish Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Judaism: Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thou-shall-prosper-ten-commandments-for-making-money-rabbi-daniel-lapin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical approach to creating wealth-based on the established principles of ancient Jewish wisdom-made accessible to people of all backgrounds The ups and downs of the economy prove Rabbi Daniel Lapin&#8217;s famous principle that the more things change, the more we need to depend upon the things that never change. There&#8217;s no better source for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thou-shall-prosper-ten-commandments-for-making-money-rabbi-daniel-lapin-abridged/">Thou Shall Prosper : Ten Commandments for Making Money &#8211; Rabbi Daniel Lapin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical approach to creating wealth-based on the established principles of ancient Jewish wisdom-made accessible to people of all backgrounds  The ups and downs of the economy prove Rabbi Daniel Lapin&#8217;s famous principle that the more things change, the more we need to depend upon the things that never change. There&#8217;s no better source for both practical and spiritual financial wisdom than the time-tested knowledge found in the ancient Jewish faith and its culture. In the  Second Edition  of  Thou Shall Prosper,  Lapin offers a practical approach to creating wealth based on the established principles of ancient Jewish wisdom. This book details the ten permanent principles that never change, the ten commandments of making money if you will, and explores the economic and philosophic vision of business that has been part of Jewish culture for centuries. The book&#8217;s focus is on making accessible to individuals of all backgrounds, the timeless truths that Jews have used for centuries to excel in business.<br />
                    Outlines ten fundamental &#8220;commandments&#8221; relating to business and money  Includes insights that will increase your potential for creating wealth, no matter what your faith or background may be  Blends contemporary business stories and Lapin&#8217;s own business experiences with the wisdom of the Torah and Talmudic prescriptions This  Second Edition  provides new examples, especially of Internet related business opportunities. In addition, each chapter highlights specific action steps that can lead to wealth opportunities in both difficult economic times and periods of prosperity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thou-shall-prosper-ten-commandments-for-making-money-rabbi-daniel-lapin-abridged/">Thou Shall Prosper : Ten Commandments for Making Money &#8211; Rabbi Daniel Lapin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Here to Financial Happiness : Enrich Your Life in Just 77 Days &#8211; Jonathan Clements (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/from-here-to-financial-happiness-enrich-your-life-in-just-77-days-jonathan-clements-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/from-here-to-financial-happiness-enrich-your-life-in-just-77-days-jonathan-clements-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Just 77 days to a happier, more prosperous life! From Here to Financial Happiness is the day-by-day guide for anyone dreaming of a better life. Whether you&#8217;re dealing with debt, uncertain about retirement or simply want to get a grip on your finances, this book can put you on the road to happiness with a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/from-here-to-financial-happiness-enrich-your-life-in-just-77-days-jonathan-clements-abridged/">From Here to Financial Happiness : Enrich Your Life in Just 77 Days &#8211; Jonathan Clements (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Just 77 days to a happier, more prosperous life!    </p>
<p>                     From Here to Financial Happiness is the day-by-day guide for anyone dreaming of a better life. Whether you&#8217;re dealing with debt, uncertain about retirement or simply want to get a grip on your finances, this book can put you on the road to happiness with a simple 11-week journey. Just 5-10 minutes a day to think about money, your habits, your goals, and your dreams. What steps can you take today to get your finances on track? What bad habits, bad investments, and misconceptions should you let go of? This book is packed with 77 days&#8217; worth of real, actionable guidance for getting your money right-for good. It&#8217;s not an investment scheme, not extreme couponing, not something else to add to your daily to-do list. Instead, it&#8217;s about changing you-and the way you handle and think about money-so you can start building the life of your dreams.         </p>
<p>                     The next 11 weeks will be a revelation: Some days you&#8217;ll learn about finance, other days you&#8217;ll learn about yourself. Many days, you will be given a concrete list of things to do-right at that moment-to start steering your financial situation onto the right path.    </p>
<p>                    Learn how to stack the financial odds in your favor<br />
                    Amass savings for retirement, the children&#8217;s college or that next financial emergency<br />
                    Change your perspective on money and its role in your life    </p>
<p>                    Get your financial house in order-and keep it that way    </p>
<p>                     A better life is possible. You do have the power to change things for the better. From Here to Financial Happiness is your personal roadmap to financial freedom.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/from-here-to-financial-happiness-enrich-your-life-in-just-77-days-jonathan-clements-abridged/">From Here to Financial Happiness : Enrich Your Life in Just 77 Days &#8211; Jonathan Clements (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The 4 Day Week : How the Flexible Work Revolution Can Increase Productivity, Profitability and Well-being, and Create a Sustainable Future &#8211; Andrew Barnes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE BUSINESS BOOK AWARDS 2021 In The 4 Day Week, entrepreneur and business innovator Andrew Barnes makes the case for the four-day work week as the answer to many of the ills of the 21st-century global economy. Barnes conducted an experiment in his own business, the New Zealand trust company Perpetual Guardian, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/">The 4 Day Week : How the Flexible Work Revolution Can Increase Productivity, Profitability and Well-being, and Create a Sustainable Future &#8211; Andrew Barnes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE BUSINESS BOOK AWARDS 2021    </p>
<p>                    In The 4 Day Week, entrepreneur and business innovator Andrew Barnes makes the case for the four-day work week as the answer to many of the ills of the 21st-century global economy.     </p>
<p>                     Barnes conducted an experiment in his own business, the New Zealand trust company Perpetual Guardian, and asked his staff to design a four-day week that would permit them to meet their existing productivity requirements on the same salary but with a 20% cut in work hours. The outcomes of this trial, which no business leader had previously attempted on these terms, were stunning. People were happier and healthier, more engaged in their personal lives, and more focused and productive in the office.    </p>
<p>                     The world of work has seen a dramatic shift in recent times: the former security and benefits associated with permanent employment are being displaced by the less stable gig economy. Barnes explains the dangers of a focus on flexibility at the expense of hard-won worker protections, and argues that with the four-day week, we can have the best of all worlds: optimal productivity, work-life balance, worker benefits and, at long last, a solution to pervasive economic inequities such as the gender pay gap and lack of diversity in business and governance.     </p>
<p>                     The 4 Day Week is a practical, how-to guide for business leaders and employees alike that is applicable to nearly every industry. Using qualitative and quantitative data from research gathered through the Perpetual Guardian trial and other sources by the University of Auckland and Auckland University of Technology, the book presents a step-by-step approach to preparing businesses for productivity-focused flexibility, from the necessary cultural conditions to the often complex legislative considerations.    </p>
<p>                     The story of Perpetual Guardian&#8217;s unprecedented work experiment has made headlines around the world and stormed social media, reaching a global audience in more than seventy countries. A mix of trenchant analysis, personal observation and actionable advice, The 4 Day Week is an essential guide for leaders and workers seeking to make a change for the better in their work world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-4-day-week-how-the-flexible-work-revolution-can-increase-productivity-profitability-and-well-being-and-create-a-sustainable-future-andrew-barnes-abridged/">The 4 Day Week : How the Flexible Work Revolution Can Increase Productivity, Profitability and Well-being, and Create a Sustainable Future &#8211; Andrew Barnes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Road to Reinvention : How to Drive Disruption and Accelerate Transformation &#8211; Josh Linkner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-road-to-reinvention-how-to-drive-disruption-and-accelerate-transformation-josh-linkner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-road-to-reinvention-how-to-drive-disruption-and-accelerate-transformation-josh-linkner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Companies, communities, and individuals fall for many reasons, but one of the most common and easily avoidable is the failure to reinvent. When people and organizations rest on prior successes rather than driving purposeful transformation, they discover too late that they have lost their market position altogether to competitors and external forces. The most successful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-road-to-reinvention-how-to-drive-disruption-and-accelerate-transformation-josh-linkner-abridged/">The Road to Reinvention : How to Drive Disruption and Accelerate Transformation &#8211; Josh Linkner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Companies, communities, and individuals fall for many reasons, but one of the most common and easily avoidable is the failure to reinvent. When people and organizations rest on prior successes rather than driving purposeful transformation, they discover too late that they have lost their market position altogether to competitors and external forces. The most successful companies, brands, and individuals make reinvention a regular part of their business strategies. Transformation demands an ongoing process of discovery and imagination, and The Road to Reinvention lays out a systematic approach for continually challenging and reinventing yourself and your business. Venture capitalist and serial entrepreneur Josh Linkner identifies six elements in any business that are ripe for reinvention and shares examples, methods, and step-by-step techniques for creating deliberate, productive disruption. Throughout The Road to Reinvention, Linkner also explores the history the great rise, unprecedented fall, and now rebirth of his beloved hometown, Detroit.<br />
                    First rising to greatness as the result of breathtaking innovation, Detroit had generations of booming growth before succumbing to apathy, atrophy, and finally bankruptcy. Now, the city is rising from the ashes and driving sustainable success through an intense focus on reinvention. Linkner brings an insider&#8217;s view of this incredible story of grit, determination, and creativity, sharing his perspective on Detroit&#8217;s successes and setbacks as a profound example of large-scale organizational and personal transformation. Change is inevitable. You need to decide: Will you drive that change, or be driven away by it? Will you disrupt or be disrupted? By choosing to deliberately reimagine your own status quo, you can secure a strong future for both your company and your career.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-road-to-reinvention-how-to-drive-disruption-and-accelerate-transformation-josh-linkner-abridged/">The Road to Reinvention : How to Drive Disruption and Accelerate Transformation &#8211; Josh Linkner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jugaad Innovation : Think Frugal, Be Flexible, Generate Breakthrough Growth &#8211; Navi Radjou, Jaideep Prabhu, Simone Ahuja, Foreword by Kevin Roberts (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/jugaad-innovation-think-frugal-be-flexible-generate-breakthrough-growth-navi-radjou-jaideep-prabhu-simone-ahuja-foreword-by-kevin-roberts-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/jugaad-innovation-think-frugal-be-flexible-generate-breakthrough-growth-navi-radjou-jaideep-prabhu-simone-ahuja-foreword-by-kevin-roberts-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Jugaad Innovation is the most comprehensive book yet to appear on the subject [of frugal innovation].&#8221; The Economist A frugal and flexible approach to innovation for the 21st century Innovation is a key directive at companies worldwide. But in these tough times, we can&#8217;t rely on the old formula that has sustained innovation efforts for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jugaad-innovation-think-frugal-be-flexible-generate-breakthrough-growth-navi-radjou-jaideep-prabhu-simone-ahuja-foreword-by-kevin-roberts-abridged/">Jugaad Innovation : Think Frugal, Be Flexible, Generate Breakthrough Growth &#8211; Navi Radjou, Jaideep Prabhu, Simone Ahuja, Foreword by Kevin Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Jugaad Innovation is the most comprehensive book yet to appear on the subject [of frugal innovation].&#8221; The Economist A frugal and flexible approach to innovation for the 21st century Innovation is a key directive at companies worldwide. But in these tough times, we can&#8217;t rely on the old formula that has sustained innovation efforts for decades expensive R&#038;D projects and highly-structured innovation processes. Jugaad Innovation argues the West must look to places like India, Brazil, and China for a new approach to frugal and flexible innovation. The authors show how in these emerging markets, jugaad (a Hindi word meaning an improvised solution born from ingenuity and cleverness) is leading to dramatic growth and how Western companies can adopt jugaad innovation to succeed in our hypercompetitive world.<br />
                    * Outlines the six principles of jugaad innovation: Seek opportunity in adversity, do more with less, think and act flexibly, keep it simple, include the margin, and follow your heart * Features twenty case studies on large corporations from around the world Google, Facebook, 3M, Apple, Best Buy, GE, IBM, Nokia, Procter &#038; Gamble, PepsiCo, Tata Group, and more that are actively practicing jugaad innovation * The authors blog regularly at Harvard Business Review; their work has been profiled in BusinessWeek, MIT Sloan Management Review, The Financial Times, The Economist, and more * Filled with previously untold and engaging stories of resourceful jugaad innovators and entrepreneurs in emerging markets and the United States This groundbreaking book shows leaders everywhere why the time is right for jugaad to emerge as a powerful business tool in the West and how to bring jugaad practices to their organizations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/jugaad-innovation-think-frugal-be-flexible-generate-breakthrough-growth-navi-radjou-jaideep-prabhu-simone-ahuja-foreword-by-kevin-roberts-abridged/">Jugaad Innovation : Think Frugal, Be Flexible, Generate Breakthrough Growth &#8211; Navi Radjou, Jaideep Prabhu, Simone Ahuja, Foreword by Kevin Roberts (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book That Still Beats the Market &#8211; Joel Greenblatt, Foreword by Andrew Tobias (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-that-still-beats-the-market-joel-greenblatt-foreword-by-andrew-tobias-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-that-still-beats-the-market-joel-greenblatt-foreword-by-andrew-tobias-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2005, Joel Greenblatt published a book that is already considered one of the classics of finance literature. In The Little Book that Beats the Market a New York Times bestseller with 300,000 copies in print Greenblatt explained how investors can outperform the popular market averages by simply and systematically applying a formula that seeks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-that-still-beats-the-market-joel-greenblatt-foreword-by-andrew-tobias-abridged/">The Little Book That Still Beats the Market &#8211; Joel Greenblatt, Foreword by Andrew Tobias (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2005, Joel Greenblatt published a book that is already considered one of the classics of finance literature. In  The Little Book that Beats the Market a  New York Times bestseller with 300,000 copies in print Greenblatt explained how investors can outperform the popular market averages by simply and systematically applying a formula that seeks out good businesses when they are available at bargain prices. Now, with a new Introduction and Afterword for 2010,  The Little Book that Still Beats the Market updates and expands upon the research findings from the original book. Included are data and analysis covering the recent financial crisis and model performance through the end of 2009. In a straightforward and accessible style, the book explores the basic principles of successful stock market investing and then reveals the author s time-tested formula that makes buying above average companies at below average prices automatic. Though the formula has been extensively tested and is a breakthrough in the academic and professional world, Greenblatt explains it using 6 th grade math, plain language and humor.<br />
                    He shows how to use his method to beat both the market and professional managers by a wide margin. You ll also learn why success eludes almost all individual and professional investors, and why the formula will continue to work even after everyone knows it.  While the formula may be simple, understanding why the formula works is the true key to success for investors. The book will take readers on a step-by-step journey so that they can learn the principles of value investing in a way that will provide them with a long term strategy that they can understand and stick with through both good and bad periods for the stock market.  As the Wall Street Journal stated about the original edition, Mr. Greenblatt says his goal was to provide advice that, while sophisticated, could be understood and followed by his five children, ages 6 to 15. They are in luck. His Little Book is one of the best, clearest guides to value investing out there.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-that-still-beats-the-market-joel-greenblatt-foreword-by-andrew-tobias-abridged/">The Little Book That Still Beats the Market &#8211; Joel Greenblatt, Foreword by Andrew Tobias (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Wealth of Common Sense : Why Simplicity Trumps Complexity in Any Investment Plan &#8211; Ben Carlson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A simple guide to a smarter strategy for the individual investor A Wealth of Common Sense sheds a refreshing light on investing, and shows you how a simplicity-based framework can lead to better investment decisions. The financial market is a complex system, but that doesn&#8217;t mean it requires a complex strategy; in fact, this false [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/">A Wealth of Common Sense : Why Simplicity Trumps Complexity in Any Investment Plan &#8211; Ben Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A simple guide to a smarter strategy for the individual investor A Wealth of Common Sense sheds a refreshing light on investing, and shows you how a simplicity-based framework can lead to better investment decisions. The financial market is a complex system, but that doesn&#8217;t mean it requires a complex strategy; in fact, this false premise is the driving force behind many investors&#8217; market &#8220;mistakes.&#8221; Information is important, but understanding and perspective are the keys to better decision-making. This book describes the proper way to view the markets and your portfolio, and show you the simple strategies that make investing more profitable, less confusing, and less time-consuming. Without the burden of short-term performance benchmarks, individual investors have the advantage of focusing on the long view, and the freedom to construct the kind of portfolio that will serve their investment goals best. This book proves how complex strategies essentially waste these advantages, and provides an alternative game plan for those ready to simplify.<br />
                    Complexity is often used as a mechanism for talking investors into unnecessary purchases, when all most need is a deeper understanding of conventional options. This book explains which issues you actually should pay attention to, and which ones are simply used for an illusion of intelligence and control. * Keep up with or beat professional money managers * Exploit stock market volatility to your utmost advantage * Learn where advisors and consultants fit into smart strategy * Build a portfolio that makes sense for your particular situation You don&#8217;t have to outsmart the market if you can simply outperform it. Cut through the confusion and noise and focus on what actually matters. A Wealth of Common Sense clears the air, and gives you the insight you need to become a smarter, more successful investor.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-wealth-of-common-sense-why-simplicity-trumps-complexity-in-any-investment-plan-ben-carlson-abridged/">A Wealth of Common Sense : Why Simplicity Trumps Complexity in Any Investment Plan &#8211; Ben Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fit for Growth : A Guide to Strategic Cost Cutting, Restructuring, and Renewal &#8211; Vinay Couto, John Plansky, Deniz Caglar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fit-for-growth-a-guide-to-strategic-cost-cutting-restructuring-and-renewal-vinay-couto-john-plansky-deniz-caglar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fit-for-growth-a-guide-to-strategic-cost-cutting-restructuring-and-renewal-vinay-couto-john-plansky-deniz-caglar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical approach to business transformation Fit for Growth* is a unique approach to business transformation that explicitly connects growth strategy with cost management and organization restructuring. Drawing on 70-plus years of strategy consulting experience and in-depth research, the experts at PwC s Strategy&#038; lay out a winning framework that helps CEOs and senior executives [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fit-for-growth-a-guide-to-strategic-cost-cutting-restructuring-and-renewal-vinay-couto-john-plansky-deniz-caglar-abridged/">Fit for Growth : A Guide to Strategic Cost Cutting, Restructuring, and Renewal &#8211; Vinay Couto, John Plansky, Deniz Caglar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical approach to business transformation Fit for Growth* is a unique approach to business transformation that explicitly connects growth strategy with cost management and organization restructuring. Drawing on 70-plus years of strategy consulting experience and in-depth research, the experts at PwC s Strategy&#038; lay out a winning framework that helps CEOs and senior executives transform their organizations for sustainable, profitable growth. This approach gives structure to strategy while promoting lasting change. Examples from Strategy&#038; s hundreds of clients illustrate successful transformation on the ground, and illuminate how senior and middle managers are able to take ownership and even thrive during difficult periods of transition. Throughout the Fit for Growth process, the focus is on maintaining consistent high-value performance while enabling fundamental change. Strategy&#038; has helped major clients around the globe achieve significant and sustained results with its research-backed approach to restructuring and cost reduction.<br />
                    This book provides practical guidance for leveraging that expertise to make the choices that allow companies to: * Achieve growth while reducing costs * Manage transformation and transition productively * Create lasting competitive advantage * Deliver reliable, high-value performance Sustainable success is founded on efficiency and high performance. Companies are always looking to do more with less, but their efforts often work against them in the long run. Total business transformation requires total buy-in, and it entails a series of decisions that must not be made lightly. The Fit for Growth approach provides a clear strategy and practical framework for growth-oriented change, with expert guidance on getting it right.  * Fit for Growth is a registered service mark of PwC Strategy&#038; Inc. in the United States</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fit-for-growth-a-guide-to-strategic-cost-cutting-restructuring-and-renewal-vinay-couto-john-plansky-deniz-caglar-abridged/">Fit for Growth : A Guide to Strategic Cost Cutting, Restructuring, and Renewal &#8211; Vinay Couto, John Plansky, Deniz Caglar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trading for a Living : Psychology, Trading Tactics, Money Management &#8211; Alexander Elder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trading-for-a-living-psychology-trading-tactics-money-management-alexander-elder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trading-for-a-living-psychology-trading-tactics-money-management-alexander-elder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Trading for a Living Successful trading is based on three Ma s: Mind, Method, and Money. Trading for a Living helps you master all of those three areas: aeo How to become a cool, calm, and collected trader aeo How to profit from reading the behavior of the market crowd aeo How to use a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trading-for-a-living-psychology-trading-tactics-money-management-alexander-elder-abridged/">Trading for a Living : Psychology, Trading Tactics, Money Management &#8211; Alexander Elder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Trading for a Living Successful trading is based on three Ma s: Mind, Method, and Money. Trading for a Living helps you master all of those three areas: aeo How to become a cool, calm, and collected trader aeo How to profit from reading the behavior of the market crowd aeo How to use a computer to find good trades aeo How to develop a powerful trading system aeo How to find the trades with the best odds of success aeo How to find entry and exit points, set stops, and take profits Trading for a Living helps you discipline your Mind, shows you the Methods for trading the markets, and shows you how to manage Money in your trading accounts so that no string of losses can kick you out of the game. To help you profit even more from the ideas in Trading for a Living, look for the companion volume&#8212;-Study Guide for Trading for a Living. It asks over 200 multiple&#8211;choice questions, with answers and 11 rating scales for sharpening your trading skills.<br />
                    For example: Question Markets rise when aeo there are more buyers than sellers aeo buyers are more aggressive than sellers aeo sellers are afraid and demand a premium aeo more shares or contracts are bought than sold aeo I and II aeo II and III aeo II and IV aeo III and IV Answer B. II and III. Every change in price reflects what happens in the battle between bulls and bears. Markets rise when bulls feel more strongly than bears. They rally when buyers are confident and sellers demand a premium for participating in the game that is going against them. There is a buyer and a seller behind every transaction. The number of stocks or futures bought and sold is equal by definition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trading-for-a-living-psychology-trading-tactics-money-management-alexander-elder-abridged/">Trading for a Living : Psychology, Trading Tactics, Money Management &#8211; Alexander Elder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Breakfast Club for 40-Somethings : A Novel Approach to Unlearning Money and Reinventing Your Life &#8211; Vanessa Stoykov (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-breakfast-club-for-40-somethings-a-novel-approach-to-unlearning-money-and-reinventing-your-life-vanessa-stoykov-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-breakfast-club-for-40-somethings-a-novel-approach-to-unlearning-money-and-reinventing-your-life-vanessa-stoykov-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new way of seeing life and money High school&#8217;s over. We&#8217;re no longer the nerd, the athlete, the princess or the bad boy. Instead, we are the parent, worker, wife, husband, daughter or son. But we all have things in common &#8211; and one of them is money. People have always sought financial freedom, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-breakfast-club-for-40-somethings-a-novel-approach-to-unlearning-money-and-reinventing-your-life-vanessa-stoykov-abridged/">The Breakfast Club for 40-Somethings : A Novel Approach to Unlearning Money and Reinventing Your Life &#8211; Vanessa Stoykov (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new way of seeing life and money    </p>
<p>                    High school&#8217;s over. We&#8217;re no longer the nerd, the athlete, the princess or the bad boy. Instead, we are the parent, worker, wife, husband, daughter or son. But we all have things in common &#8211; and one of them is money.     </p>
<p>                    People have always sought financial freedom, but our influences, from our parents to our community, have made our grounding in money anything but helpful. In fact, that grounding might be the thing that is holding us back. The Breakfast Club for 40-Somethings draws upon the five major lessons you need to unlearn about the way you see your life and money to give you the best chance of getting the future you want.    </p>
<p>                    Written in the form of a novel from the perspective of six unique characters, the book explores how the different financial decisions and behaviours of each character have led to their current situations. Through this entertaining story, this guide presents the invaluable financial and life lessons you need to understand, to build a solid foundation for your life, no matter your situation.    </p>
<p>                    If you don&#8217;t like traditional self-help or finance books, this is for you. The Breakfast Club for 40-Somethings offers a new and entertaining way to change your long-term financial behaviours for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-breakfast-club-for-40-somethings-a-novel-approach-to-unlearning-money-and-reinventing-your-life-vanessa-stoykov-abridged/">The Breakfast Club for 40-Somethings : A Novel Approach to Unlearning Money and Reinventing Your Life &#8211; Vanessa Stoykov (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Innovator&#8217;s Hypothesis : How Cheap Experiments Are Worth More than Good Ideas &#8211; Michael Schrage (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-innovators-hypothesis-how-cheap-experiments-are-worth-more-than-good-ideas-michael-schrage-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Company Secretary: Role & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Knowledge Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-innovators-hypothesis-how-cheap-experiments-are-worth-more-than-good-ideas-michael-schrage-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Achieving faster, better, cheaper, and more creative innovation outcomes with the 5&#215;5 framework: 5 people, 5 days, 5 experiments, $5,000, and 5 weeks. What is the best way for a company to innovate? Advice recommending &#8220;innovation vacations&#8221; and the luxury of failure may be wonderful for organizations with time to spend and money to waste. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innovators-hypothesis-how-cheap-experiments-are-worth-more-than-good-ideas-michael-schrage-abridged/">The Innovator&#8217;s Hypothesis : How Cheap Experiments Are Worth More than Good Ideas &#8211; Michael Schrage (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Achieving faster, better, cheaper, and more creative innovation outcomes with the 5&#215;5 framework: 5 people, 5 days, 5 experiments, $5,000, and 5 weeks.     </p>
<p>                    What is the best way for a company to innovate? Advice recommending &#8220;innovation vacations&#8221; and the luxury of failure may be wonderful for organizations with time to spend and money to waste. The Innovator&#8217;s Hypothesis addresses the innovation priorities of companies that live in the real world of limits. Michael Schrage advocates a cultural and strategic shift: small teams, collaboratively&#8211;and competitively&#8211;crafting business experiments that make top management sit up and take notice. He introduces the 5&#215;5 framework: giving diverse teams of five people up to five days to come up with portfolios of five business experiments costing no more than $5,000 each and taking no longer than five weeks to run. Successful 5x5s, Schrage shows, make people more effective innovators, and more effective innovators mean more effective innovations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innovators-hypothesis-how-cheap-experiments-are-worth-more-than-good-ideas-michael-schrage-abridged/">The Innovator&#8217;s Hypothesis : How Cheap Experiments Are Worth More than Good Ideas &#8211; Michael Schrage (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The best-selling index investing &#8220;bible&#8221; offers new information and is updated to reflect the latest market data The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the classic guide to getting smart about the market. Legendary mutual fund veteran John C. Bogle reveals his key to getting more out of investing: low-cost index funds. Bogle describes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/">The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The best-selling index investing &#8220;bible&#8221; offers new information and is updated to reflect the latest market data The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the classic guide to getting smart about the market. Legendary mutual fund veteran John C. Bogle reveals his key to getting more out of investing: low-cost index funds. Bogle describes the simplest and most effective investment strategy for building wealth over the long term: buy and hold, at very low cost, a mutual fund that tracks the S&#038;P 500 Stock Index. Such an index portfolio is the only investment that guarantees your fair share of stock market returns. This strategy is favored by Warren Buffett, who has endorsed this best selling 10th Anniversary Edition. The book shows you how to make index investing work for you and help you achieve your financial goals, cut through the hype to see what&#8217;s really in your best interest, and analyze the metrics that truly matter. You&#8217;ll gain candid insight from some of the world&#8217;s best financial minds: not only Warren Buffett, but Benjamin Graham, Paul Samuelson, Burton Malkiel, and others.<br />
                    Updated with current data and laced with two new chapters on asset allocation and retirement investing, the new Little Book of Common Sense Investing gives you a solid strategy for building your financial future. * Build a broadly diversified, low-cost portfolio without the risks of individual stocks, manager selection, and sector rotation * Forget the fads and focus on what works in the real world * Emphasize business reality over market expectations * Understand how index investing is the only game that assures your fair share of stock market returns Too many investors trade franticly, turning a winners game into a losers game, while index investing allows you to sit back and let the market do the work for you. Learn how to harness the magic of compounding returns while avoiding the tyranny of compounding costs. Bogle describes his simple method for developing rational expectations for future market returns, and what he sees coming over the next decade.  The Little Book of Common Sense Investing is the guidebook to your financial future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-common-sense-investing-the-only-way-to-guarantee-your-fair-share-of-stock-market-returns-john-c-bogle-abridged/">The Little Book of Common Sense Investing : The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns &#8211; John C. Bogle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits and Other Writings &#8211; Philip A. Fisher, Introduction by Kenneth L. Fisher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits-and-other-writings-philip-a-fisher-introduction-by-kenneth-l-fisher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits-and-other-writings-philip-a-fisher-introduction-by-kenneth-l-fisher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Widely respected and admired, Philip Fisher is among the most influential investors of all time. His investment philosophies, introduced almost forty years ago, are not only studied and applied by today&#8217;s financiers and investors, but are also regarded by many as gospel. This book is invaluable reading and has been since it was first published [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits-and-other-writings-philip-a-fisher-introduction-by-kenneth-l-fisher-abridged/">Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits and Other Writings &#8211; Philip A. Fisher, Introduction by Kenneth L. Fisher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Widely respected and admired, Philip Fisher is among the most influential investors of all time. His investment philosophies, introduced almost forty years ago, are not only studied and applied by today&#8217;s financiers and investors, but are also regarded by many as gospel. This book is invaluable reading and has been since it was first published in 1958. The updated paperback retains the investment wisdom of the original edition and includes the perspectives of the author&#8217;s son Ken Fisher, an investment guru in his own right in an expanded preface and introduction &#8220;I sought out Phil Fisher after reading his Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits&#8230;A thorough understanding of the business, obtained by using Phil&#8217;s techniques&#8230;enables one to make intelligent investment commitments.&#8221; Warren Buffet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-stocks-and-uncommon-profits-and-other-writings-philip-a-fisher-introduction-by-kenneth-l-fisher-abridged/">Common Stocks and Uncommon Profits and Other Writings &#8211; Philip A. Fisher, Introduction by Kenneth L. Fisher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ultimate Sales Machine &#8211; Chet Holmes, Notes by Jay Conrad Levinson, Foreword by Michael Gerber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A classic.-Jay Conrad Levinson, author of Guerrilla Marketing Now in paperback, the bestselling business playbook that introduced a simple framework for turbocharging any organization. What if you could create the finest, most profitable and best-run version of your business without wasting precious dollars on a thousand different strategies? Legendary sales expert Chet Holmes says you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/">Ultimate Sales Machine &#8211; Chet Holmes, Notes by Jay Conrad Levinson, Foreword by Michael Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A classic.-Jay Conrad Levinson, author of Guerrilla Marketing     </p>
<p>                    Now in paperback, the bestselling business playbook that introduced a simple framework for turbocharging any organization.     </p>
<p>                     What if you could create the finest, most profitable and best-run version of your business without wasting precious dollars on a thousand different strategies? Legendary sales expert Chet Holmes says you can. All you need is to focus on twelve key areas of improvement&#8211;and practice them over and over with pigheaded discipline.     </p>
<p>                     The Ultimate Sales Machine is essential reading for anyone who wants to transform their organization into a high-performing, moneymaking force. By spending just an hour per week on crucial aspects of your business&#8211;from sales and marketing to management and hiring&#8211;you can systematically improve how your business operates. With practical tools, real-life examples, and proven strategies presented in Holmes&#8217; signature tell-it-like-it-is style, this book will show you how to:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Teach your team to work smarter, not harder<br />
                     &#8211; Get more bang from your marketing for less<br />
                     &#8211; Perfect every sales interaction by working on sales, not just in sales<br />
                     &#8211; Land your dream clients     </p>
<p>                    For every CEO, manager, and business owner who wants to take their organization to the next level, The Ultimate Sales Machine will put you and your company on the path to success&#8211;and help you stay there!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ultimate-sales-machine-chet-holmes-notes-by-jay-conrad-levinson-foreword-by-michael-gerber-abridged/">Ultimate Sales Machine &#8211; Chet Holmes, Notes by Jay Conrad Levinson, Foreword by Michael Gerber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Only the Paranoid Survive : How to Exploit the Crisis Points That Challenge Every Company &#8211; Andrew S. Grove (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/only-the-paranoid-survive-how-to-exploit-the-crisis-points-that-challenge-every-company-andrew-s-grove-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/only-the-paranoid-survive-how-to-exploit-the-crisis-points-that-challenge-every-company-andrew-s-grove-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Andy Grove, founder and former CEO of Intel shares his strategy for success as he takes the reader deep inside the workings of a major company in Only the Paranoid Survive. Under Andy Grove&#8217;s leadership, Intel became the world&#8217;s largest chip maker and one of the most admired companies in the world. In Only the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/only-the-paranoid-survive-how-to-exploit-the-crisis-points-that-challenge-every-company-andrew-s-grove-abridged/">Only the Paranoid Survive : How to Exploit the Crisis Points That Challenge Every Company &#8211; Andrew S. Grove (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Andy Grove, founder and former CEO of Intel shares his strategy for success as he takes the reader deep inside the workings of a major company in Only the Paranoid Survive.     </p>
<p>                    Under Andy Grove&#8217;s leadership, Intel became the world&#8217;s largest chip maker and one of the most admired companies in the world. In Only the Paranoid Survive, Grove reveals his strategy for measuring the nightmare moment every leader dreads&#8211;when massive change occurs and a company must, virtually overnight, adapt or fall by the wayside&#8211;in a new way.     </p>
<p>                    Grove calls such a moment a Strategic Inflection Point, which can be set off by almost anything: mega-competition, a change in regulations, or a seemingly modest change in technology. When a Strategic Inflection Point hits, the ordinary rules of business go out the window. Yet, managed right, a Strategic Inflection Point can be an opportunity to win in the marketplace and emerge stronger than ever.     </p>
<p>                    Grove underscores his message by examining his own record of success and failure, including how he navigated the events of the Pentium flaw, which threatened Intel&#8217;s reputation in 1994, and how he has dealt with the explosions in growth of the Internet. The work of a lifetime, Only the Paranoid Survive is a classic of managerial and leadership skills.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/only-the-paranoid-survive-how-to-exploit-the-crisis-points-that-challenge-every-company-andrew-s-grove-abridged/">Only the Paranoid Survive : How to Exploit the Crisis Points That Challenge Every Company &#8211; Andrew S. Grove (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Will Teach You To Be Rich (2nd Edition) : No guilt, no excuses &#8211; just a 6-week programme that works &#8211; Ramit Sethi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-will-teach-you-to-be-rich-2nd-edition-no-guilt-no-excuses-just-a-6-week-programme-that-works-ramit-sethi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-will-teach-you-to-be-rich-2nd-edition-no-guilt-no-excuses-just-a-6-week-programme-that-works-ramit-sethi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you think financial health is beyond your reach, think again. I Will Teach You To Be Rich is the modern money classic that has revolutionised the lives of countless people all over the world, teaching them how to effectively manage their finances, demolish their debt, save better and get the most out of their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-will-teach-you-to-be-rich-2nd-edition-no-guilt-no-excuses-just-a-6-week-programme-that-works-ramit-sethi-abridged/">I Will Teach You To Be Rich (2nd Edition) : No guilt, no excuses &#8211; just a 6-week programme that works &#8211; Ramit Sethi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you think financial health is beyond your reach, think again. I Will Teach You To Be Rich is the modern money classic that has revolutionised the lives of countless people all over the world, teaching them how to effectively manage their finances, demolish their debt, save better and get the most out of their bank accounts, credit cards and investments.     </p>
<p>                    Now, Ramit Sethi, who has been described by Forbes as a &#8216;wealth wizard&#8217; and by Fortune as &#8216;the new finance guru&#8217;, is back with a completely revised second edition of I Will Teach You To Be Rich, updating it with new tools and insights on money and psychology, along with fantastic stories of how previous readers have used the book to enrich their lives. From crushing your debt and student loans to talking your way out of late fees, to dead simple investment strategies and negotiating that big raise at work, this is the no-guilt, no-excuses, no-BS 6-week programme that will help you get your finances where you want them to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-will-teach-you-to-be-rich-2nd-edition-no-guilt-no-excuses-just-a-6-week-programme-that-works-ramit-sethi-abridged/">I Will Teach You To Be Rich (2nd Edition) : No guilt, no excuses &#8211; just a 6-week programme that works &#8211; Ramit Sethi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clever Girl Finance : Ditch debt, save money and build real wealth &#8211; Bola Sokunbi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/clever-girl-finance-ditch-debt-save-money-and-build-real-wealth-bola-sokunbi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/clever-girl-finance-ditch-debt-save-money-and-build-real-wealth-bola-sokunbi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Take charge of your finances and achieve financial independence &#8211; the Clever Girl way Join the ranks of thousands of smart and savvy women who have turned to money expert and author Bola Sokunbi for guidance on ditching debt, saving money, and building real wealth. Sokunbi, the force behind the hugely popular Clever Girl Finance [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clever-girl-finance-ditch-debt-save-money-and-build-real-wealth-bola-sokunbi-abridged/">Clever Girl Finance : Ditch debt, save money and build real wealth &#8211; Bola Sokunbi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Take charge of your finances and achieve financial independence &#8211; the Clever Girl way    </p>
<p>                     Join the ranks of thousands of smart and savvy women who have turned to money expert and author Bola Sokunbi for guidance on ditching debt, saving money, and building real wealth. Sokunbi, the force behind the hugely popular Clever Girl Finance website, draws on her personal money mistakes and financial redemption to educate and empower a new generation of women on their journey to financial freedom. Lighthearted and accessible, Clever Girl Finance encourages women to talk about money and financial wellness and shows them how to navigate their own murky financial waters and come out afloat on the other side.    </p>
<p>                    Monitor your expenses, build a budget, and stick with it<br />
                    Make the most of a modest salary and still have money to spare<br />
                    Keep your credit in check and clean up credit card chaos<br />
                    Start and succeed at your side hustle<br />
                    Build a nest egg and invest in your future<br />
                    Transform your money mindset and be accountable for your financial well-being<br />
                    Feel the power of real-world stories from other &#8220;clever girls&#8221;    </p>
<p>                     Put yourself on the path to financial success with the valuable lessons learned from Clever Girl Finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clever-girl-finance-ditch-debt-save-money-and-build-real-wealth-bola-sokunbi-abridged/">Clever Girl Finance : Ditch debt, save money and build real wealth &#8211; Bola Sokunbi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Atomic Habits : the life-changing million-copy #1 bestseller &#8211; James Clear (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/atomic-habits-the-life-changing-million-copy-1-bestseller-james-clear-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Classical, Early & Medieval]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/atomic-habits-the-life-changing-million-copy-1-bestseller-james-clear-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE PHENOMENAL INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER: 1 MILLION COPIES SOLD Transform your life with tiny changes in behaviour, starting now. People think that when you want to change your life, you need to think big. But world-renowned habits expert James Clear has discovered another way. He knows that real change comes from the compound effect of hundreds [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/atomic-habits-the-life-changing-million-copy-1-bestseller-james-clear-abridged/">Atomic Habits : the life-changing million-copy #1 bestseller &#8211; James Clear (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE PHENOMENAL INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER: 1 MILLION COPIES SOLD    </p>
<p>                    Transform your life with tiny changes in behaviour, starting now.    </p>
<p>                    People think that when you want to change your life, you need to think big. But world-renowned habits expert James Clear has discovered another way. He knows that real change comes from the compound effect of hundreds of small decisions: doing two push-ups a day, waking up five minutes early, or holding a single short phone call.    </p>
<p>                    He calls them atomic habits.    </p>
<p>                    In this ground-breaking book, Clears reveals exactly how these minuscule changes can grow into such life-altering outcomes. He uncovers a handful of simple life hacks (the forgotten art of Habit Stacking, the unexpected power of the Two Minute Rule, or the trick to entering the Goldilocks Zone), and delves into cutting-edge psychology and neuroscience to explain why they matter. Along the way, he tells inspiring stories of Olympic gold medalists, leading CEOs, and distinguished scientists who have used the science of tiny habits to stay productive, motivated, and happy.     </p>
<p>                    These small changes will have a revolutionary effect on your career, your relationships, and your life.<br />
                    ________________________________<br />
                    A NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A supremely practical and useful book.&#8217; Mark Manson, author of The Subtle Art of Not Giving A F*ck    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;James Clear has spent years honing the art and studying the science of habits. This engaging, hands-on book is the guide you need to break bad routines and make good ones.&#8217; Adam Grant, author of Originals    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Atomic Habits is a step-by-step manual for changing routines.&#8217; Books of the Month, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A special book that will change how you approach your day and live your life.&#8217; Ryan Holiday, author of The Obstacle is the Way</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/atomic-habits-the-life-changing-million-copy-1-bestseller-james-clear-abridged/">Atomic Habits : the life-changing million-copy #1 bestseller &#8211; James Clear (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cut Costs Not Corners : A Practical Guide to Staying Competitive and Improving Profits &#8211; Colin Barrow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cut-costs-not-corners-a-practical-guide-to-staying-competitive-and-improving-profits-colin-barrow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cut-costs-not-corners-a-practical-guide-to-staying-competitive-and-improving-profits-colin-barrow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cost cutting is an issue for every manager and executive at every level in every company, large or small, public or private sector. Junior managers who are proactively tight on cost are learning good habits for the future, ones that will bring them recognition and advance their climb up the organizational chart. The HR department [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cut-costs-not-corners-a-practical-guide-to-staying-competitive-and-improving-profits-colin-barrow-abridged/">Cut Costs Not Corners : A Practical Guide to Staying Competitive and Improving Profits &#8211; Colin Barrow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cost cutting is an issue for every manager and executive at every level in every company, large or small, public or private sector. Junior managers who are proactively tight on cost are learning good habits for the future, ones that will bring them recognition and advance their climb up the organizational chart. The HR department is now staffed with tough cost managers dealing with the most difficult cost category, people. Marketing departments now focus on how to get higher returns from less spend.    </p>
<p>                    Cut Costs Not Corners has a coherent and structured approach to cost cutting as a permanent activity, combined with guidance on the practical steps to take and powerful international case studies. It covers strategic and tactical cost cutting options such as analysing space needs, buying technology for less, selling off redundant assets, reducing credit risk, reviewing distribution methods, sourcing new suppliers or consolidating existing ones, advertising for less, changing the route to market, travel and utility savings, minimising finance and tax costs, crisis measures &#8211; freezing recruitment, delaying pay rises, sell and lease back assets &#8211; keeping budgets rolling and using a daily cash flow model.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cut-costs-not-corners-a-practical-guide-to-staying-competitive-and-improving-profits-colin-barrow-abridged/">Cut Costs Not Corners : A Practical Guide to Staying Competitive and Improving Profits &#8211; Colin Barrow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
