<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Physics Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/physics-books/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/physics-books/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Physics Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/physics-books/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Something Deeply Hidden : Quantum Worlds and the Emergence of Spacetime &#8211; Sean Carroll</title>
		<link>/something-deeply-hidden-quantum-worlds-and-the-emergence-of-spacetime-sean-carroll/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/something-deeply-hidden-quantum-worlds-and-the-emergence-of-spacetime-sean-carroll/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the Royal Society Winton Prize winner &#8216;An authoritative and beautifully written account of the quest to understand quantum theory and the origin of space and time.&#8217; Professor Brian Cox Quantum physics is not mystifying. The implications are mind-bending, and not yet fully understood, but this revolutionary theory is truly illuminating. It stands as the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/something-deeply-hidden-quantum-worlds-and-the-emergence-of-spacetime-sean-carroll/">Something Deeply Hidden : Quantum Worlds and the Emergence of Spacetime &#8211; Sean Carroll</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the Royal Society Winton Prize winner</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An authoritative and beautifully written account of the quest to understand quantum theory and the origin of space and time.&#8217; Professor Brian Cox </p>
<p>                    Quantum physics is not mystifying. The implications are mind-bending, and not yet fully understood, but this revolutionary theory is truly illuminating. It stands as the best explanation of the fundamental nature of our world.</p>
<p>                    Spanning the history of quantum discoveries, from Einstein and Bohr to the present day, Something Deeply Hidden is the essential guide to the most intriguing subject in science. Acclaimed physicist and writer Sean Carroll debunks the myths, resurrects and reinstates the Many-Worlds interpretation, and presents a new path towards solving the apparent conflict between quantum mechanics and Einstein&#8217;s theory of general relativity. In doing so, he fills a gap in the science that has existed for almost a century.</p>
<p>                    A magisterial tour, Something Deeply Hidden encompasses the cosmological and everyday implications of quantum reality and multiple universes. And &#8211; finally &#8211; it all makes sense.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/something-deeply-hidden-quantum-worlds-and-the-emergence-of-spacetime-sean-carroll/">Something Deeply Hidden : Quantum Worlds and the Emergence of Spacetime &#8211; Sean Carroll</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future of the Mind : The Scientific Quest to Understand, Enhance, and Empower the Mind &#8211; Michio Kaku</title>
		<link>/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michio Kaku, the New York Times bestselling author of Physics of the Impossible and Physics of the Future tackles the most fascinating and complex object in the known universe: the human brain. The Future of the Mind brings a topic that once belonged solely to the province of science fiction into a startling new reality. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/">The Future of the Mind : The Scientific Quest to Understand, Enhance, and Empower the Mind &#8211; Michio Kaku</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michio Kaku, the New York Times bestselling author of Physics of the Impossible and Physics of the Future tackles the most fascinating and complex object in the known universe: the human brain.     </p>
<p>                    The Future of the Mind brings a topic that once belonged solely to the province of science fiction into a startling new reality. This scientific tour de force unveils the astonishing research being done in top laboratories around the world&#8211;all based on the latest advancements in neuroscience and physics&#8211;including recent experiments in telepathy, mind control, avatars, telekinesis, and recording memories and dreams. The Future of the Mind is an extraordinary, mind-boggling exploration of the frontiers of neuroscience. Dr. Kaku looks toward the day when we may achieve the ability to upload the human brain to a computer, neuron for neuron; project thoughts and emotions around the world on a brain-net; take a &#8220;smart pill&#8221; to enhance cognition; send our consciousness across the universe; and push the very limits of immortality.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/">The Future of the Mind : The Scientific Quest to Understand, Enhance, and Empower the Mind &#8211; Michio Kaku</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reality Is Not What It Seems : The Journey to Quantum Gravity &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reality-is-not-what-it-seems-the-journey-to-quantum-gravity-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gravity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relativity Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theoretical & Mathematical Astronomy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reality-is-not-what-it-seems-the-journey-to-quantum-gravity-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The physicist transforming how we see the universe&#8217; (Financial Times) &#8216;An utter joy&#8217; (Adam Rutherford) &#8216;A hugely engaging book&#8230; Rovelli is a charming, thought-provoking tour guide&#8217; (Manjit Kumar Prospect) Do space and time truly exist? What is reality made of? Can we understand its deep texture? Scientist Carlo Rovelli has spent his whole life exploring [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reality-is-not-what-it-seems-the-journey-to-quantum-gravity-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">Reality Is Not What It Seems : The Journey to Quantum Gravity &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The physicist transforming how we see the universe&#8217; (Financial Times)    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An utter joy&#8217; (Adam Rutherford)    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A hugely engaging book&#8230; Rovelli is a charming, thought-provoking tour guide&#8217; (Manjit Kumar Prospect)    </p>
<p>                    Do space and time truly exist? What is reality made of? Can we understand its deep texture?<br />
                    Scientist Carlo Rovelli has spent his whole life exploring these questions and pushing the boundaries of what we know. In this mind-expanding book, he shows how our understanding of reality has changed throughout centuries, from Democritus to loop quantum gravity. Taking us on a wondrous journey, he invites us to imagine a whole new world where black holes are waiting to explode, spacetime is made up of grains, and infinity does not exist &#8212; a vast universe still largely undiscovered.    </p>
<p>                    Translated by Simon Carnell and Erica Segre</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reality-is-not-what-it-seems-the-journey-to-quantum-gravity-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">Reality Is Not What It Seems : The Journey to Quantum Gravity &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Grid : The Fraying Wires Between Americans and Our Energy Future &#8211; Gretchen Bakke (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electricity, Electromagnetism & Magnetism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Power Generation & Distribution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory look at our national power grid&#8211;how it developed, its current flaws, and how it must be completely reimagined for our fast-approaching energy future. America&#8217;s electrical grid, an engineering triumph of the twentieth century, is turning out to be a poor fit for the present. It&#8217;s not just that the grid has grown old [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/">The Grid : The Fraying Wires Between Americans and Our Energy Future &#8211; Gretchen Bakke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory look at our national power grid&#8211;how it developed, its current flaws, and how it must be completely reimagined for our fast-approaching energy future.     </p>
<p>                    America&#8217;s electrical grid, an engineering triumph of the twentieth century, is turning out to be a poor fit for the present. It&#8217;s not just that the grid has grown old and is now in dire need of basic repair. Today, as we invest great hope in new energy sources&#8211;solar, wind, and other alternatives&#8211;the grid is what stands most firmly in the way of a brighter energy future. If we hope to realize this future, we need to reimagine the grid according to twenty-first-century values. It&#8217;s a project which forces visionaries to work with bureaucrats, legislators with storm-flattened communities, moneymen with hippies, and the left with the right. And though it might not yet be obvious, this revolution is already well under way.     </p>
<p>                     Cultural anthropologist Gretchen Bakke unveils the many facets of America&#8217;s energy infrastructure, its most dynamic moments and its most stable ones, and its essential role in personal and national life. The grid, she argues, is an essentially American artifact, one which developed with us: a product of bold expansion, the occasional foolhardy vision, some genius technologies, and constant improvisation. Most of all, her focus is on how Americans are changing the grid right now, sometimes with gumption and big dreams and sometimes with legislation or the brandishing of guns.     </p>
<p>                    The Grid tells&#8211;entertainingly, perceptively&#8211;the story of what has been called the largest machine in the world: its fascinating history, its problematic present, and its potential role in a brighter, cleaner future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-grid-the-fraying-wires-between-americans-and-our-energy-future-gretchen-bakke-abridged/">The Grid : The Fraying Wires Between Americans and Our Energy Future &#8211; Gretchen Bakke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Picture : On the Origins of Life, Meaning, and the Universe Itself &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrophysics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Brian Cox, Mail on Sunday Books of the Year Where are we? Who are we? Do our beliefs, hopes and dreams hold any significance out there in the void? Can human purpose and meaning ever fit into a scientific worldview? Award-winning author Sean Carroll brings his extraordinary intellect to bear on the realms [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Big Picture : On the Origins of Life, Meaning, and the Universe Itself &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Brian Cox, Mail on Sunday Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Where are we? Who are we? Do our beliefs, hopes and dreams hold any significance out there in the void? Can human purpose and meaning ever fit into a scientific worldview?    </p>
<p>                    Award-winning author Sean Carroll brings his extraordinary intellect to bear on the realms of knowledge, the laws of nature and the most profound questions about life, death and our place in it all.    </p>
<p>                    From Darwin and Einstein to the origins of life, consciousness and the universe itself, Carroll combines cosmos-sprawling science and profound thought in a quest to explain our world. Destined to sit alongside the works of our greatest thinkers, The Big Picture demonstrates that while our lives may be forever dwarfed by the immensity of the universe, they can be redeemed by our capacity to comprehend it and give it meaning.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Big Picture : On the Origins of Life, Meaning, and the Universe Itself &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Evolution of Everything : How Small Changes Transform Our World &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If there is one dominant myth about the world, one huge mistake we all make &#8230; it is that we all go around assuming the world is much more of a planned place than it is.&#8217; From the industrial revolution and the rise of China, to urbanisation and the birth of bitcoin, Matt Ridley demolishes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/">The Evolution of Everything : How Small Changes Transform Our World &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If there is one dominant myth about the world, one huge mistake we all make &#8230; it is that we all go around assuming the world is much more of a planned place than it is.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                              From the industrial revolution and the rise of China, to urbanisation and the birth of bitcoin, Matt Ridley demolishes conventional assumptions that the great events and trends of our day are dictated by those on high. On the contrary, our most important achievements develop from the ground up. In this wide-ranging and erudite book, Matt Ridley brilliantly makes the case for evolution as the force that has shaped much of our culture, our minds, and that even now is shaping our future.    </p>
<p>                              As compelling as it is controversial, as authoritative as it is ambitious, Ridley&#8217;s deeply thought-provoking book will change the way we think about the world and how it works.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/">The Evolution of Everything : How Small Changes Transform Our World &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smartest Guys in the Room : The Amazing Rise and Scandalous Fall of Enron &#8211; Peter Elkind, Bethany McLean (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Company Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy Industries & Utilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What went wrong with American business at the end of the 20th century? Until the spring of 2001, Enron epitomized the triumph of the New Economy. Feared by rivals, worshipped by investors, Enron seemingly could do no wrong. Its profits rose every year; its stock price surged ever upward; its leaders were hailed as visionaries. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/">The Smartest Guys in the Room : The Amazing Rise and Scandalous Fall of Enron &#8211; Peter Elkind, Bethany McLean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What went wrong with American business at the end of the 20th century?    </p>
<p>                    Until the spring of 2001, Enron epitomized the triumph of the New Economy. Feared by rivals, worshipped by investors, Enron seemingly could do no wrong. Its profits rose every year; its stock price surged ever upward; its leaders were hailed as visionaries.      </p>
<p>                    Then a young Fortune writer, Bethany McLean, wrote an article posing a simple question &#8211;  how, exactly, does Enron make its money?    </p>
<p>                    Within a year Enron was facing humiliation and bankruptcy, the largest in US history, which caused Americans to lose faith in a system that rewarded top insiders with millions of dollars, while small investors lost everything. It was revealed that Enron was a company whose business was an illusion, an illusion that Wall Street was willing to accept even though they knew what the real truth was.  This book &#8211; fully updated for the paperback &#8211; tells the extraordinary story of Enron&#8217;s fall.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smartest-guys-in-the-room-the-amazing-rise-and-scandalous-fall-of-enron-peter-elkind-bethany-mclean-abridged/">The Smartest Guys in the Room : The Amazing Rise and Scandalous Fall of Enron &#8211; Peter Elkind, Bethany McLean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Tao of Physics : An Exploration of the Parallels between Modern Physics and Eastern Mysticism &#8211; Fritjof Capra (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-tao-of-physics-an-exploration-of-the-parallels-between-modern-physics-and-eastern-mysticism-fritjof-capra-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mysticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-tao-of-physics-an-exploration-of-the-parallels-between-modern-physics-and-eastern-mysticism-fritjof-capra-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A special edition of the &#8220;brilliant&#8221; best-selling classic on the paradoxes of modern physics and their relationship to concepts of Eastern mysticism (New York Magazine) The Tao of Physics brought the mystical implications of subatomic physics to popular consciousness for the very first time. Many books have been written in the ensuing years about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tao-of-physics-an-exploration-of-the-parallels-between-modern-physics-and-eastern-mysticism-fritjof-capra-abridged/">The Tao of Physics : An Exploration of the Parallels between Modern Physics and Eastern Mysticism &#8211; Fritjof Capra (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A special edition of the &#8220;brilliant&#8221; best-selling classic on the paradoxes of modern physics and their relationship to concepts of Eastern mysticism (New York Magazine)    </p>
<p>                    The Tao of Physics brought the mystical implications of subatomic physics to popular consciousness for the very first time. Many books have been written in the ensuing years about the connections between quantum theory and the ideas of Buddhism, Hinduism, and Taoism, but Fritjof Capra&#8217;s text serves as the foundation on which the others have been built&#8211;and its wisdom has stood the test of time. Its publication in more than twenty-three languages stands as testimony to its universal applicability and its enduring significance.     </p>
<p>                    This special edition celebrates the thirty-fifth anniversary of this early Shambhala best seller that has gone on to become a true classic. It includes a fresh cover design and a new preface by the author reflecting on further discoveries and developments in the years since the book&#8217;s original publication.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Physicists do not need mysticism,&#8221; Dr. Capra says, &#8220;and mystics do not need physics, but humanity needs both.&#8221; It is a message of timeless importance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-tao-of-physics-an-exploration-of-the-parallels-between-modern-physics-and-eastern-mysticism-fritjof-capra-abridged/">The Tao of Physics : An Exploration of the Parallels between Modern Physics and Eastern Mysticism &#8211; Fritjof Capra (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Green Illusions : The Dirty Secrets of Clean Energy and the Future of Environmentalism &#8211; Ozzie Zehner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/green-illusions-the-dirty-secrets-of-clean-energy-and-the-future-of-environmentalism-ozzie-zehner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alternative & Renewable Energy Sources & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/green-illusions-the-dirty-secrets-of-clean-energy-and-the-future-of-environmentalism-ozzie-zehner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We don&#8217;t have an energy crisis. We have a consumption crisis. And this book, which takes aim at cherished assumptions regarding energy, offers refreshingly straight talk about what&#8217;s wrong with the way we think and talk about the problem. Though we generally believe we can solve environmental problems with more energy-more solar cells, wind turbines, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/green-illusions-the-dirty-secrets-of-clean-energy-and-the-future-of-environmentalism-ozzie-zehner-abridged/">Green Illusions : The Dirty Secrets of Clean Energy and the Future of Environmentalism &#8211; Ozzie Zehner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We don&#8217;t have an energy crisis. We have a consumption crisis. And this book, which takes aim at cherished assumptions regarding energy, offers refreshingly straight talk about what&#8217;s wrong with the way we think and talk about the problem. Though we generally believe we can solve environmental problems with more energy-more solar cells, wind turbines, and biofuels-alternative technologies come with their own side effects and limitations. How, for instance, do solar cells cause harm? Why can&#8217;t engineers solve wind power&#8217;s biggest obstacle? Why won&#8217;t contraception solve the problem of overpopulation lying at the heart of our concerns about energy, and what will?<br />
                    This practical, environmentally informed, and lucid book persuasively argues for a change of perspective. If consumption is the problem, as Ozzie Zehner suggests, then we need to shift our focus from suspect alternative energies to improving social and political fundamentals: walkable communities, improved consumption, enlightened governance, and, most notably, women&#8217;s rights. The dozens of first steps he offers are surprisingly straightforward. For instance, he introduces a simple sticker that promises a greater impact than all of the nation&#8217;s solar cells. He uncovers why carbon taxes won&#8217;t solve our energy challenges (and presents two taxes that could). Finally, he explores how future environmentalists will focus on similarly fresh alternatives that are affordable, clean, and can actually improve our well-being.<br />
                    Watch a book trailer.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/green-illusions-the-dirty-secrets-of-clean-energy-and-the-future-of-environmentalism-ozzie-zehner-abridged/">Green Illusions : The Dirty Secrets of Clean Energy and the Future of Environmentalism &#8211; Ozzie Zehner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Energy and Civilization : A History &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/energy-and-civilization-a-history-vaclav-smil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/energy-and-civilization-a-history-vaclav-smil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A comprehensive account of how energy has shaped society throughout history, from pre-agricultural foraging societies through today&#8217;s fossil fuel-driven civilization. I wait for new Smil books the way some people wait for the next &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; movie. In his latest book, Energy and Civilization: A History, he goes deep and broad to explain how innovations [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/energy-and-civilization-a-history-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Energy and Civilization : A History &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A comprehensive account of how energy has shaped society throughout history, from pre-agricultural foraging societies through today&#8217;s fossil fuel-driven civilization.    </p>
<p>                    I wait for new Smil books the way some people wait for the next &#8216;Star Wars&#8217; movie. In his latest book, Energy and Civilization: A History, he goes deep and broad to explain how innovations in humans&#8217; ability to turn energy into heat, light, and motion have been a driving force behind our cultural and economic progress over the past 10,000 years.<br />
                    &#8211;Bill Gates, Gates Notes, Best Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Energy is the only universal currency; it is necessary for getting anything done. The conversion of energy on Earth ranges from terra-forming forces of plate tectonics to cumulative erosive effects of raindrops. Life on Earth depends on the photosynthetic conversion of solar energy into plant biomass. Humans have come to rely on many more energy flows&#8211;ranging from fossil fuels to photovoltaic generation of electricity&#8211;for their civilized existence. In this monumental history, Vaclav Smil provides a comprehensive account of how energy has shaped society, from pre-agricultural foraging societies through today&#8217;s fossil fuel-driven civilization.     </p>
<p>                    Humans are the only species that can systematically harness energies outside their bodies, using the power of their intellect and an enormous variety of artifacts&#8211;from the simplest tools to internal combustion engines and nuclear reactors. The epochal transition to fossil fuels affected everything: agriculture, industry, transportation, weapons, communication, economics, urbanization, quality of life, politics, and the environment. Smil describes humanity&#8217;s energy eras in panoramic and interdisciplinary fashion, offering readers a magisterial overview. This book is an extensively updated and expanded version of Smil&#8217;s Energy in World History (1994). Smil has incorporated an enormous amount of new material, reflecting the dramatic developments in energy studies over the last two decades and his own research over that time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/energy-and-civilization-a-history-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Energy and Civilization : A History &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Particle at the End of the Universe : Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-particle-at-the-end-of-the-universe-winner-of-the-royal-society-winton-prize-sean-carroll-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Atomic & Molecular Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Particle & High-energy Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research Methods: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-particle-at-the-end-of-the-universe-winner-of-the-royal-society-winton-prize-sean-carroll-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books A Best Science Book of the Year for the Guardian, Financial Times, and New Scientist It was the universe&#8217;s most elusive particle, the linchpin for everything scientists dreamed up to explain how physics works. It had to be found. But projects as big as CERN&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-particle-at-the-end-of-the-universe-winner-of-the-royal-society-winton-prize-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Particle at the End of the Universe : Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books    </p>
<p>                    A Best Science Book of the Year for the Guardian, Financial Times, and New Scientist    </p>
<p>                    It was the universe&#8217;s most elusive particle, the linchpin for everything scientists dreamed up to explain how physics works. It had to be found. But projects as big as CERN&#8217;s Large Hadron Collider don&#8217;t happen without incredible risks &#8211; or occasional skulduggery. In the definitive account of the greatest science story of our time, acclaimed physicist Sean Carroll reveals the insights, rivalry, and wonder that fuelled the Higgs discovery, and takes us on a riveting and irresistible ride to the very edge of physics today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-particle-at-the-end-of-the-universe-winner-of-the-royal-society-winton-prize-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Particle at the End of the Universe : Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Genius : The Life and Science of Richard Feynman &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/genius-the-life-and-science-of-richard-feynman-james-gleick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nanotechnology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/genius-the-life-and-science-of-richard-feynman-james-gleick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>To his colleagues, Richard Feynman was not so much a genius as he was a full-blown magician: someone who &#8220;does things that nobody else could do and that seem completely unexpected.&#8221; The path he cleared for twentieth-century physics led from the making of the atomic bomb to a Nobel Prize-winning theory of quantam electrodynamics to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genius-the-life-and-science-of-richard-feynman-james-gleick-abridged/">Genius : The Life and Science of Richard Feynman &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To his colleagues, Richard Feynman was not so much a genius as he was a full-blown magician: someone who &#8220;does things that nobody else could do and that seem completely unexpected.&#8221; The path he cleared for twentieth-century physics led from the making of the atomic bomb to a Nobel Prize-winning theory of quantam electrodynamics to his devastating exposé of the Challenger space shuttle disaster. At the same time, the ebullient Feynman established a reputation as an eccentric showman, a master safe cracker and bongo player, and a wizard of seduction.     </p>
<p>                    Now James Gleick, author of the bestselling Chaos, unravels teh dense skein of Feynman&#8217;s thought as well as the paradoxes of his character in a biography&#8211;which was nominated for a National Book Award&#8211;of outstanding lucidity and compassion.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/genius-the-life-and-science-of-richard-feynman-james-gleick-abridged/">Genius : The Life and Science of Richard Feynman &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Laws of Thermodynamics: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Peter Atkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-laws-of-thermodynamics-a-very-short-introduction-peter-atkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thermodynamics & Heat]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-laws-of-thermodynamics-a-very-short-introduction-peter-atkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the sudden expansion of a cloud of gas or the cooling of a hot metal, to the unfolding of a thought in our minds and even the course of life itself, everything is governed by the four Laws of Thermodynamics. These laws specify the nature of &#8216;energy&#8217; and &#8216;temperature&#8217;, and are soon revealed to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-laws-of-thermodynamics-a-very-short-introduction-peter-atkins-abridged/">The Laws of Thermodynamics: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Peter Atkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the sudden expansion of a cloud of gas or the cooling of a hot metal, to the unfolding of a thought in our minds and even the course of life itself, everything is governed by the four Laws of Thermodynamics. These laws specify the nature of &#8216;energy&#8217; and &#8216;temperature&#8217;, and are soon revealed to reach out and define the arrow of time itself: why things change and why death must come.     </p>
<p>                    In this Very Short Introduction Peter Atkins explains the basis and deeper implications of each law, highlighting their relevance in everyday examples. Using the minimum of mathematics, he introduces concepts such as entropy, free energy, and to the brink and beyond of the absolute zero temperature. These are not merely abstract ideas: they govern our lives.     </p>
<p>                    In this concise and compelling introduction Atkins paints a lucid picture of the four elegant laws that, between them, drive the Universe.    </p>
<p>                    ABOUT THE SERIES: The Very Short Introductions series from Oxford University Press contains hundreds of titles in almost every subject area. These pocket-sized books are the perfect way to get ahead in a new subject quickly. Our expert authors combine facts, analysis, perspective, new ideas, and enthusiasm to make interesting and challenging topics highly readable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-laws-of-thermodynamics-a-very-short-introduction-peter-atkins-abridged/">The Laws of Thermodynamics: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Peter Atkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time (chronology), Time Systems & Standards]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR From the acclaimed author of The Information and Chaos, a mind-bending exploration of time travel: its subversive origins, its evolution in literature and science, and its influence on our understanding of time itself. Gleick&#8217;s story begins at the turn of the twentieth century with the young H. G. Wells [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/">Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                              From the acclaimed author of The Information and Chaos, a mind-bending exploration of time travel: its subversive origins, its evolution in literature and science, and its influence on our understanding of time itself.    </p>
<p>                              Gleick&#8217;s story begins at the turn of the twentieth century with the young H. G. Wells writing and rewriting the fantastic tale that became his first book, an international sensation, The Time Machine. A host of forces were converging to transmute the human understanding of time, some philosophical and some technological &#8211; the electric telegraph, the steam railroad, the discovery of buried civilisations, and the perfection of clocks. Gleick tracks the evolution of time travel as an idea in the culture &#8211; from Marcel Proust to Doctor Who, from Woody Allen to Jorge Luis Borges. He explores the inevitable looping paradoxes and examines the porous boundary between pulp fiction and modern physics. Finally, he delves into a temporal shift that is unsettling our own moment: the instantaneous wired world, with its all-consuming present and vanishing future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/">Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Seven Brief Lessons on Physics &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/seven-brief-lessons-on-physics-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrophysics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theoretical & Mathematical Astronomy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/seven-brief-lessons-on-physics-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE PHENOMENAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF HELGOLAND AND THE ORDER OF TIME &#8216;The perfect antidote to the fluff and nonsense around right now. Learn how the world is and how you might just fit in&#8217; Simon Mayo &#8216;By God, it&#8217;s beguiling&#8217; New Statesman These seven short lessons guide us, with simplicity and clarity, through [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/seven-brief-lessons-on-physics-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">Seven Brief Lessons on Physics &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE PHENOMENAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF HELGOLAND AND THE ORDER OF TIME    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The perfect antidote to the fluff and nonsense around right now. Learn how the world is and how you might just fit in&#8217; Simon Mayo    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;By God, it&#8217;s beguiling&#8217; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    These seven short lessons guide us, with simplicity and clarity, through the scientific revolution that shook physics in the twentieth century and still continues to shake us today. In this mind-bending overview of modern physics, Carlo Rovelli explains Einstein&#8217;s theory of general relativity, quantum mechanics, black holes, the complex architecture of the universe, elementary particles, gravity, and the nature of the mind. Not since Richard Feynman&#8217;s celebrated Six Easy Pieces has physics been so vividly, intelligently and entertainingly revealed.    </p>
<p>                    Translated by Simon Carnell and Erica Segre</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/seven-brief-lessons-on-physics-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">Seven Brief Lessons on Physics &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time (chronology), Time Systems & Standards]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER One of TIME&#8217;s Ten Best Nonfiction Books of the Decade &#8216;Captivating, fascinating, profoundly beautiful. . . Rovelli is a wonderfully humane, gentle and witty guide for he is as much philosopher and poet as he is a scientist&#8217; John Banville &#8216;We are time. We are this space, this clearing opened [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    One of TIME&#8217;s Ten Best Nonfiction Books of the Decade    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Captivating, fascinating, profoundly beautiful. . . Rovelli is a wonderfully humane, gentle and witty guide for he is as much philosopher and poet as he is a scientist&#8217; John Banville    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We are time. We are this space, this clearing opened by the traces of memory inside the connections between our neurons. We are memory. We are nostalgia. We are longing for a future that will not come&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Time is a mystery that does not cease to puzzle us. Philosophers, artists and poets have long explored its meaning while scientists have found that its structure is different from the simple intuition we have of it. From Boltzmann to quantum theory, from Einstein to loop quantum gravity, our understanding of time has been undergoing radical transformations. Time flows at a different speed in different places, the past and the future differ far less than we might think, and the very notion of the present evaporates in the vast universe.    </p>
<p>                    With his extraordinary charm and sense of wonder, bringing together science, philosophy and art, Carlo Rovelli unravels this mystery. Enlightening and consoling, The Order of Time shows that to understand ourselves we need to reflect on time &#8212; and to understand time we need to reflect on ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    Translated by Simon Carnell and Erica Segre</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Energy Myths and Realities : Bringing Science to the Energy Policy Debate &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/energy-myths-and-realities-bringing-science-to-the-energy-policy-debate-vaclav-smil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Energy Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/energy-myths-and-realities-bringing-science-to-the-energy-policy-debate-vaclav-smil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are many misconceptions about the future of global energy often presented as fact by the media, politicians, business leaders, activists, and even scientists-wasting time and money and hampering the development of progressive energy policies. Energy Myths and Realities: Bringing Science to the Energy Policy Debate debunks the most common fallacies to make way for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/energy-myths-and-realities-bringing-science-to-the-energy-policy-debate-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Energy Myths and Realities : Bringing Science to the Energy Policy Debate &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are many misconceptions about the future of global energy often presented as fact by the media, politicians, business leaders, activists, and even scientists-wasting time and money and hampering the development of progressive energy policies. Energy Myths and Realities: Bringing Science to the Energy Policy Debate debunks the most common fallacies to make way for a constructive, scientific approach to the global energy challenge.  When will the world run out of oil? Should nuclear energy be adopted on a larger scale? Are ethanol and wind power viable sources of energy for the future? Vaclav Smil advises the public to be wary of exaggerated claims and impossible promises. The global energy transition will be prolonged and expensive-and hinges on the development of an extensive new infrastructure. Established technologies and traditional energy sources are persistent and adaptable enough to see the world through that transition.  Energy Myths and Realities brings a scientific perspective to an issue often dominated by groundless assertions, unfounded claims, and uncritical thinking. Before we can create sound energy policies for the future, we must renounce the popular myths that cloud our judgment and impede true progress.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/energy-myths-and-realities-bringing-science-to-the-energy-policy-debate-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Energy Myths and Realities : Bringing Science to the Energy Policy Debate &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
