<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Autobiography: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/autobiography-general/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/autobiography-general/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Autobiography: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/autobiography-general/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley</title>
		<link>/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay & Lesbian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestselling memoir about identity, love and understanding. Now a major motion picture starring Nicole Kidman, Russell Crowe, and Lucas Hedges, directed by Joel Edgerton. &#8220;Every sentence of the story will stir your soul&#8221; (O Magazine). The son of a Baptist pastor and deeply embedded in church life in small town Arkansas, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley/">Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestselling memoir about identity, love and understanding. Now a major motion picture starring Nicole Kidman, Russell Crowe, and Lucas Hedges, directed by Joel Edgerton. &#8220;Every sentence of the story will stir your soul&#8221; (O Magazine).    </p>
<p>                    The son of a Baptist pastor and deeply embedded in church life in small town Arkansas, as a young man Garrard Conley was terrified and conflicted about his sexuality. When Garrard was a nineteen-year-old college student, he was outed to his parents, and was forced to make a life-changing decision: either agree to attend a church-supported conversion therapy program that promised to cure him of homosexuality; or risk losing family, friends, and the God he had prayed to every day of his life. Through an institutionalized Twelve-Step Program heavy on Bible study, he was supposed to emerge heterosexual, ex-gay, cleansed of impure urges and stronger in his faith in God for his brush with sin. Instead, even when faced with a harrowing and brutal journey, Garrard found the strength and understanding to break out in search of his true self and forgiveness.     </p>
<p>                    By confronting his buried past and the burden of a life lived in shadow, Garrard traces the complex relationships among family, faith, and community. At times heart-breaking, at times triumphant, Boy Erased is a testament to love that survives despite all odds.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley/">Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Just as I Am : A Memoir &#8211; Cicely Tyson</title>
		<link>/just-as-i-am-a-memoir-cicely-tyson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/just-as-i-am-a-memoir-cicely-tyson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In her long and extraordinary career, Cicely Tyson has not only succeeded as an actor, she has shaped the course of history.&#8221; -President Barack Obama, 2016 Presidential Medal of Freedom ceremony &#8220;Just as I Am is my truth. It is me, plain and unvarnished, with the glitter and garland set aside. In these pages, I [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/just-as-i-am-a-memoir-cicely-tyson/">Just as I Am : A Memoir &#8211; Cicely Tyson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In her long and extraordinary career, Cicely Tyson has not only succeeded as an actor, she has shaped the course of history.&#8221; -President Barack Obama, 2016 Presidential Medal of Freedom ceremony    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Just as I Am is my truth. It is me, plain and unvarnished, with the glitter and garland set aside. In these pages, I am indeed Cicely, the actress who has been blessed to grace the stage and screen for six decades. Yet I am also the church girl who once rarely spoke a word. I am the teenager who sought solace in the verses of the old hymn for which this book is named. I am a daughter and a mother, a sister and a friend. I am an observer of human nature and the dreamer of audacious dreams. I am a woman who has hurt as immeasurably as I have loved, a child of God divinely guided by his hand. And here in my ninth decade, I am a woman who, at long last, has something meaningful to say.&#8221; -Cicely Tyson    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/just-as-i-am-a-memoir-cicely-tyson/">Just as I Am : A Memoir &#8211; Cicely Tyson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Out Of My Head (Alt. Version) : Fuzzy memoirs and confused ramblings on stuff I know nothing about &#8211; Clifford James Hayes</title>
		<link>/out-of-my-head-alt-version-fuzzy-memoirs-and-confused-ramblings-on-stuff-i-know-nothing-about-clifford-james-hayes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/out-of-my-head-alt-version-fuzzy-memoirs-and-confused-ramblings-on-stuff-i-know-nothing-about-clifford-james-hayes/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hitler switches &#8211; fairground life &#8211; child labour &#8211; Jamaica &#8211; Florence &#8211; banana addiction &#8211; urban sleepwalks &#8211; flying a 747 &#8211; giant spiders &#8211; beard hatred &#8211; owning half the toys in Hamleys &#8211; brown cars (ugh!) &#8211; Brexit &#8211; migraines and vomit &#8211; &#8216;orlovit&#8217; mantras in the Post Office &#8211; wet wipe [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-my-head-alt-version-fuzzy-memoirs-and-confused-ramblings-on-stuff-i-know-nothing-about-clifford-james-hayes/">Out Of My Head (Alt. Version) : Fuzzy memoirs and confused ramblings on stuff I know nothing about &#8211; Clifford James Hayes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hitler switches &#8211; fairground life &#8211; child labour &#8211; Jamaica &#8211; Florence &#8211; banana addiction &#8211; urban sleepwalks &#8211; flying a 747 &#8211; giant spiders &#8211; beard hatred &#8211; owning half the toys in Hamleys &#8211; brown cars (ugh!) &#8211; Brexit &#8211; migraines and vomit &#8211; &#8216;orlovit&#8217; mantras in the Post Office &#8211; wet wipe joy &#8211; Ladykind &#8211; frog-hurling &#8211; ideas to save the planet &#8211; things I would ban &#8230;    </p>
<p>                    What do all the above have in common? The author of this book, that&#8217;s what. Out of My Head is an autobiographical ramble through Clifford James Hayes&#8217;s life experiences and subsequent skewed views on everything. Discover the true nature of reality and find out why fashion should be banned; understand why the world needs &#8216;splugs&#8217; and learn how to email yourself to distant stars. All this and a great deal more can be found in Out of My Head! Contains some (mild) adult content. If unsure, do not purchase for persons under 16. FULL SELECTION OF BOOKS AT: www.hayesdesign.co.uk/books    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/out-of-my-head-alt-version-fuzzy-memoirs-and-confused-ramblings-on-stuff-i-know-nothing-about-clifford-james-hayes/">Out Of My Head (Alt. Version) : Fuzzy memoirs and confused ramblings on stuff I know nothing about &#8211; Clifford James Hayes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sleepers &#8211; Lorenzo Carcaterra</title>
		<link>/sleepers-lorenzo-carcaterra/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Endurance & Survival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories Of Heroism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sleepers-lorenzo-carcaterra/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An unforgettable true story of friendship, loyalty and revenge, set against the unmistakable backdrop of New York City They were four boys who shared everything &#8211; the laughter and bruises of an impoverished upbringing in New York&#8217;s West Side. Then one of their pranks misfired &#8211; a man nearly died and they were sent away [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sleepers-lorenzo-carcaterra/">Sleepers &#8211; Lorenzo Carcaterra</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An unforgettable true story of friendship, loyalty and revenge, set against the unmistakable backdrop of New York City</p>
<p>                    They  were four boys who shared everything &#8211; the laughter and bruises of an  impoverished upbringing in New York&#8217;s West Side. Then one of their  pranks misfired &#8211; a man nearly died and they were sent away to a  reformatory school. There they suffered the worst abuse the guards could  inflict on them. They were forever scarred by their experiences. Eleven  years later two of them became killers for the mob. They met the  ringleader of the guards who abused them &#8211; and shot him dead in front of  several witnesses. No one thought they would see the outside of a  prison again &#8211; but the four friends banded together once more and in one  last, audacious stand brought their own vengeance to the courtroom.</p>
<p>                    Sleepers was  adapted into an award-winning film, featuring Hollywood stars Dustin  Hoffman, Brad Pitt, Robert de Niro and Kevin Bacon. A moving and  shocking coming-of-age story that is a must read for fans of the cult  film, Stand by Me.</p>
<p>                    Lorenzo Carcaterra was born in New York where he still lives. He was a reporter on the New York Daily News before he wrote A Safe Place. His second book, Sleepers, became a bestseller on both sides of the Atlantic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sleepers-lorenzo-carcaterra/">Sleepers &#8211; Lorenzo Carcaterra</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secrets of My Life &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner</title>
		<link>/the-secrets-of-my-life-caitlyn-jenner/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Transsexuals & Hermaphroditism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nonfiction History Books for Kids]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secrets-of-my-life-caitlyn-jenner/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER In this remarkable memoir &#8211; written with Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Buzz Bissinger during her pivotal first years of rebirth &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner reflects on her past as she looks to her future. With poignancy and humour, Caitlyn writes about her confusion growing up, the temporary triumph of the Olympics as Bruce [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secrets-of-my-life-caitlyn-jenner/">The Secrets of My Life &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    In this remarkable memoir &#8211; written with Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Buzz Bissinger during her pivotal first years of rebirth &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner reflects on her past as she looks to her future.     </p>
<p>                    With poignancy and humour, Caitlyn writes about her confusion growing up, the temporary triumph of the Olympics as Bruce Jenner, and the noose of being endlessly described as the ultimate in manhood. She reveals her sense of shame and deceit she felt as she got older, as she went to great lengths to tell lies to conceal her true self. She also delves into her life in the public eye; her marriages and her troubled relationships with her children; what lead to her decision to becoming Caitlyn, and how the transgender community and the world has embraced her new life. Written with a searing honesty, this books shows you the real and true Caitlyn.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secrets-of-my-life-caitlyn-jenner/">The Secrets of My Life &#8211; Caitlyn Jenner</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Becoming : Mi historia (Spanish Edition) &#8211; Michelle Obama</title>
		<link>/becoming-mi-historia-spanish-edition-michelle-obama/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/becoming-mi-historia-spanish-edition-michelle-obama/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>No te pierdas el documental BECOMING de Michelle Obama en Netflix. Un íntimo, poderoso e inspirador libro de memorias de la ex primera dama de Estados Unidos Protagonista de una vida plena y exitosa, Michelle Obama se ha convertido en una de las mujeres más icónicas y cautivadoras de nuestra era. Como primera dama de [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-mi-historia-spanish-edition-michelle-obama/">Becoming : Mi historia (Spanish Edition) &#8211; Michelle Obama</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No te pierdas el documental BECOMING de Michelle Obama en Netflix. Un íntimo, poderoso e inspirador libro de memorias de la ex primera dama de Estados Unidos</p>
<p>                     Protagonista de una vida plena y exitosa, Michelle Obama se ha convertido en una de las mujeres más icónicas y cautivadoras de nuestra era. Como primera dama de los Estados Unidos de América, y primera afroamericana en desempeñar esa función, contribuyó a que la Casa Blanca alcanzara sus mayores cotas de apertura y pluralidad de la historia; se erigió en destacada defensora de las mujeres y las niñas en Estados Unidos y en el resto del mundo, introdujo cambios drásticos encaminados a promover una vida saludable y activa en las familias, y acompañó a su esposo cuando el país atravesaba algunos de los momentos más desgarradores de su historia. Por el camino nos enseñó pasos de baile, causó furor en Carpool Karaoke y consiguió criar a dos hijas con los pies en la tierra bajo el implacable escrutinio de los medios de comunicación.  En sus memorias, profundamente reflexivas y cautivadoras, Michelle Obama invita al lector a entrar en su mundo relatando las experiencias que han forjado su carácter, desde su infancia en la zona sur de Chicago, hasta los años que vivió en la residencia más famosa del mundo, pasando por su etapa como alta directiva, durante la que tuvo que compaginar la maternidad con la vida profesional. Haciendo gala de una honestidad a toda prueba y de un ingenio vivaz, describe sus logros y decepciones tanto en la esfera pública como en la privada, y narra sin ambages la historia de su vida, con sus propias palabras y en sus propios términos. Cálido, lúcido y revelador, Becoming es un relato excepcionalmente íntimo de una mujer de gran moralidad y valía, que una vez y otra ha superado todas las expectativas y cuya historia nos inspira a seguir su ejemplo.</p>
<p>                    ENGLISH DESCRIPTION Michelle Obama BECOMING Film to Be Released Globally by Netflix. An intimate, powerful, and inspiring memoir by the former First Lady of the United States  In a life filled with meaning and accomplishment, Michelle Obama has emerged as one of the most iconic and compelling women of our era. As First Lady of the United States of America&#8211;the first African-American to serve in that role&#8211;she helped create the most welcoming and inclusive White House in history, while also establishing herself as a powerful advocate for women and girls in the U.S. and around the world, dramatically changing the ways that families pursue healthier and more active lives, and standing with her husband as he led America through some of its most harrowing moments. Along the way, she showed us a few dance moves, crushed Carpool Karaoke, and raised two down-to-earth daughters under an unforgiving media glare.  In her memoir, a work of deep reflection and mesmerizing storytelling, Michelle Obama invites readers into her world, chronicling the experiences that have shaped her&#8211;from her childhood on the South Side of Chicago to her years as an executive balancing the demands of motherhood and work, to her time spent at the world&#8217;s most famous address. With unerring honesty and lively wit, she describes her triumphs and her disappointments, both public and private, telling her full story as she has lived it&#8211;in her own words and on her own terms. Warm, wise, and revelatory, Becoming is the deeply personal reckoning of a woman of soul and substance who has steadily defied expectations&#8211;and whose story inspires us to do the same.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-mi-historia-spanish-edition-michelle-obama/">Becoming : Mi historia (Spanish Edition) &#8211; Michelle Obama</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened : A Mostly True Memoir &#8211; Jenny Lawson</title>
		<link>/lets-pretend-this-never-happened-a-mostly-true-memoir-jenny-lawson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lets-pretend-this-never-happened-a-mostly-true-memoir-jenny-lawson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling (mostly true) memoir from the hilarious author of Furiously Happy. &#8220;Gaspingly funny and wonderfully inappropriate.&#8221;&#8211;O, The Oprah Magazine When Jenny Lawson was little, all she ever wanted was to fit in. That dream was cut short by her fantastically unbalanced father and a morbidly eccentric childhood. It did, however, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lets-pretend-this-never-happened-a-mostly-true-memoir-jenny-lawson/">Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened : A Mostly True Memoir &#8211; Jenny Lawson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling (mostly true) memoir from the hilarious author of Furiously Happy.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Gaspingly funny and wonderfully inappropriate.&#8221;&#8211;O, The Oprah Magazine     </p>
<p>                    When Jenny Lawson was little, all she ever wanted was to fit in. That dream was cut short by her fantastically unbalanced father and a morbidly eccentric childhood. It did, however, open up an opportunity for Lawson to find the humor in the strange shame-spiral that is her life, and we are all the better for it.     </p>
<p>                    In the irreverent Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened, Lawson&#8217;s long-suffering husband and sweet daughter help her uncover the surprising discovery that the most terribly human moments&#8211;the ones we want to pretend never happened&#8211;are the very same moments that make us the people we are today. For every intellectual misfit who thought they were the only ones to think the things that Lawson dares to say out loud, this is a poignant and hysterical look at the dark, disturbing, yet wonderful moments of our lives.     </p>
<p>                    Readers Guide Inside</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lets-pretend-this-never-happened-a-mostly-true-memoir-jenny-lawson/">Let&#8217;s Pretend This Never Happened : A Mostly True Memoir &#8211; Jenny Lawson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Make Trouble : Stand Up, Speak Out, and Find the Courage to Lead &#8211; Cecile Richards, With Lauren Peterson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/make-trouble-stand-up-speak-out-and-find-the-courage-to-lead-cecile-richards-with-lauren-peterson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pressure Groups & Lobbying]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/make-trouble-stand-up-speak-out-and-find-the-courage-to-lead-cecile-richards-with-lauren-peterson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Cecile Richards, the former president of Planned Parenthood for more than a decade, daughter of the late Ann Richards, featured speaker at the Women&#8217;s March on Washington, and &#8220;the heroine of the resistance&#8221; (Vogue), comes &#8220;an enthralling memoir&#8221; (Booklist, starred review) filled with &#8220;practical advice and inspiration for aspiring leaders everywhere&#8221; (Hillary Rodham Clinton). [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-trouble-stand-up-speak-out-and-find-the-courage-to-lead-cecile-richards-with-lauren-peterson-abridged/">Make Trouble : Stand Up, Speak Out, and Find the Courage to Lead &#8211; Cecile Richards, With Lauren Peterson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Cecile Richards, the former president of Planned Parenthood for more than a decade, daughter of the late Ann Richards, featured speaker at the Women&#8217;s March on Washington, and &#8220;the heroine of the resistance&#8221; (Vogue), comes &#8220;an enthralling memoir&#8221; (Booklist, starred review) filled with &#8220;practical advice and inspiration for aspiring leaders everywhere&#8221; (Hillary Rodham Clinton).    </p>
<p>                    Cecile Richards has been an activist since she was taken to the principal&#8217;s office in seventh grade for wearing an armband in protest of the Vietnam War. Richards had an extraordinary childhood in ultra-conservative Texas, where her civil rights attorney father and activist mother taught their kids to be troublemakers. She had a front-row seat to observe the rise of women in American politics and watched her mother, Ann, transform from a housewife to an electrifying force in the Democratic party.    </p>
<p>                    As a young woman, Richards worked as a labor organizer alongside women earning minimum wage, and learned that those in power don&#8217;t give it up without a fight. She experienced first-hand the misogyny, sexism, fake news, and the ever-looming threat of violence that constantly confront women who challenge authority.    </p>
<p>                    Now, after years of advocacy, resistance, and progressive leadership, she shares her &#8220;truly inspiring&#8221; (Redbook) story for the first time-from the joy and heartbreak of activism to the challenges of raising kids, having a life, and making change, all the while garnering a reputation as &#8220;the most badass feminist EVER&#8221; (Teen Vogue).    </p>
<p>                    In the &#8220;powerful and infinitely readable&#8221; (Gloria Steinem) Make Trouble, Richards reflects on the people and lessons that have gotten her through good times and bad, and encourages the rest of us to take risks, make mistakes, and make trouble along the way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-trouble-stand-up-speak-out-and-find-the-courage-to-lead-cecile-richards-with-lauren-peterson-abridged/">Make Trouble : Stand Up, Speak Out, and Find the Courage to Lead &#8211; Cecile Richards, With Lauren Peterson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clay Water Brick : Finding Inspiration from Entrepreneurs Who Do the Most with the Least &#8211; Jessica Jackley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/clay-water-brick-finding-inspiration-from-entrepreneurs-who-do-the-most-with-the-least-jessica-jackley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/clay-water-brick-finding-inspiration-from-entrepreneurs-who-do-the-most-with-the-least-jessica-jackley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Meet Patrick, who had next to nothing and started a thriving business using just the ground beneath his feet &#8230; Blessing, who built her shop right in the middle of the road, refusing to take the chance that her customers might pass her by &#8230; Constance, who cornered the banana market in her African village [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clay-water-brick-finding-inspiration-from-entrepreneurs-who-do-the-most-with-the-least-jessica-jackley-abridged/">Clay Water Brick : Finding Inspiration from Entrepreneurs Who Do the Most with the Least &#8211; Jessica Jackley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meet Patrick, who had next to nothing and started a thriving business using just the ground beneath his feet &#8230; Blessing, who built her shop right in the middle of the road, refusing to take the chance that her customers might pass her by &#8230; Constance, who cornered the banana market in her African village with her big personality and sense of mission.    </p>
<p>                    Patrick, Blessing, Constance and many others are among the poorest of the world&#8217;s poor. And yet they each had crucial lessons to teach Jessica Jackley &#8211; lessons about resilience, creativity, perseverance and, above all, entrepreneurship.    </p>
<p>                    For as long as she could remember, Jackley, the cofounder of the revolutionary microlending site Kiva, had a singular and urgent ambition: to help alleviate global poverty. She believes that many of the most inspiring entrepreneurs in the world are not focused on high-tech ventures or making a lot of money; instead, they wake up every day and build better lives for themselves, their families and their communities, regardless of the things they lack or the obstacles they encounter.     </p>
<p>                    In Clay Water Brick, Jackley challenges listeners to embrace entrepreneurship as a powerful force for change in the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/clay-water-brick-finding-inspiration-from-entrepreneurs-who-do-the-most-with-the-least-jessica-jackley-abridged/">Clay Water Brick : Finding Inspiration from Entrepreneurs Who Do the Most with the Least &#8211; Jessica Jackley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hunger : A Memoir of (My) Body &#8211; Roxane Gay (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hunger-a-memoir-of-my-body-roxane-gay-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hunger-a-memoir-of-my-body-roxane-gay-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I ate and ate and ate in the hopes that if I made myself big, my body would be safe. I buried the girl I was because she ran into all kinds of trouble. I tried to erase every memory of her, but she is still there, somewhere. . . . I was trapped in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hunger-a-memoir-of-my-body-roxane-gay-abridged/">Hunger : A Memoir of (My) Body &#8211; Roxane Gay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I ate and ate and ate in the hopes that if I made myself big, my body would be safe. I buried the girl I was because she ran into all kinds of trouble. I tried to erase every memory of her, but she is still there, somewhere. . . . I was trapped in my body, one that I barely recognized or understood, but at least I was safe.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    New York Times bestselling author Roxane Gay has written with intimacy and sensitivity about food and bodies, using her own emotional and psychological struggles as a means of exploring our shared anxieties over pleasure, consumption, appearance, and health. As a woman who describes her own body as &#8220;wildly undisciplined,&#8221; Roxane understands the tension between desire and denial, between self-comfort and self-care. In Hunger, she casts an insightful and critical eye on her childhood, teens, and twenties-including the devastating act of violence that acted as a turning point in her young life-and brings readers into the present and the realities, pains, and joys of her daily life.    </p>
<p>                    With the bracing candor, vulnerability, and authority that have made her one of the most admired voices of her generation, Roxane explores what it means to be overweight in a time when the bigger you are, the less you are seen. Hunger is a deeply personal memoir from one of our finest writers, and tells a story that hasn&#8217;t yet been told but needs to be.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hunger-a-memoir-of-my-body-roxane-gay-abridged/">Hunger : A Memoir of (My) Body &#8211; Roxane Gay (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Catch Me If You Can : The True Story Of A Real Fake &#8211; Frank Abagnale, Stan Redding (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/catch-me-if-you-can-the-true-story-of-a-real-fake-frank-abagnale-stan-redding-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/catch-me-if-you-can-the-true-story-of-a-real-fake-frank-abagnale-stan-redding-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I stole every nickel and blew it on fine threads, luxurious lodgings, fantastic foxes and other sensual goodies. I partied in every capital in Europe and basked on all the world&#8217;s most famous beaches&#8217;. Frank W Abagnale, alias Frank Williams, Robert Conrad, Frank Adams and Ringo Monjo, was one of the most daring con men, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-me-if-you-can-the-true-story-of-a-real-fake-frank-abagnale-stan-redding-abridged/">Catch Me If You Can : The True Story Of A Real Fake &#8211; Frank Abagnale, Stan Redding (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I stole every nickel and blew it on fine threads, luxurious lodgings, fantastic foxes and other sensual goodies. I partied in every capital in Europe and basked on all the world&#8217;s most famous beaches&#8217;. Frank W Abagnale, alias Frank Williams, Robert Conrad, Frank Adams and Ringo Monjo, was one of the most daring con men, forgers, imposters and escape artists in history. In his brief but notorious career, Abagnale donned a pilot&#8217;s uniform and co-piloted a Pan Am jet, masqueraded as a member of hospital management, practised law without a licence, passed himself off as a college sociology professor, and cashed over $2.5 million in forged checks all before he was twenty-one. Known by the police of twenty-six foreign countries and all fifty states as &#8216;The Skywayman&#8217;, Abagnale lived a sumptuous life on the run &#8211; until the law caught up with him. Now recognised as the nation&#8217;s leading authority on financial foul play, Abagnale is a charming rogue whose hilarious, stranger-than-fiction international escapades and ingenious escapes &#8211; including one from an aeroplane &#8211; make CATCH ME IF YOU CAN an irresistable tale of deceit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-me-if-you-can-the-true-story-of-a-real-fake-frank-abagnale-stan-redding-abridged/">Catch Me If You Can : The True Story Of A Real Fake &#8211; Frank Abagnale, Stan Redding (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An unburdening, a witness statement and a thriller all at the same time &#8230; electrifying.&#8217; The Times I have to assume that there is a very real chance that Putin or members of his regime will have me killed some day. If I&#8217;m killed, you will know who did it. When my enemies read this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/">Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An unburdening, a witness statement and a thriller all at the same time &#8230; electrifying.&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    I have to assume that there is a very real chance that Putin or members of his regime will have me killed some day. If I&#8217;m killed, you will know who did it. When my enemies read this book, they will know that you know.    </p>
<p>                    A Sunday Times and New York Times bestseller. A true-life thriller by one of Putin&#8217;s Most Wanted.    </p>
<p>                    In November 2009, the young lawyer Sergei Magnitsky was beaten to death by eight police officers in a freezing cell in a Moscow prison. His crime? Testifying against Russian officials who were involved in a conspiracy to steal $230 million of taxes.    </p>
<p>                    Red Notice is a searing expose of the whitewash of this imprisonment and murder. The killing hasn&#8217;t been investigated. It hasn&#8217;t been punished. Bill Browder is still campaigning for justice for his late lawyer and friend. This is his explosive journey from the heady world of finance in New York and London in the 1990s, through battles with ruthless oligarchs in turbulent post-Soviet Union Moscow, to the shadowy heart of the Kremlin.    </p>
<p>                    With fraud, bribery, corruption and torture exposed at every turn, Red Notice is a shocking political roller-coaster.<br />
                    __________________    </p>
<p>                    Reads like a classic thriller, with an everyman hero alone and in danger in a hostile foreign city &#8230; but it&#8217;s all true, and it&#8217;s a story that needs to be told.&#8217; Lee Child    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A shocking true-life thriller.&#8217; Tom Stoppard    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A riveting account&#8230; it is a powerful story and Browder tells it skilfully.&#8217; The Washington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/">Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>My Beloved World &#8211; Sonia Sotomayor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/my-beloved-world-sonia-sotomayor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Courts & Procedure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hispanic & Latino Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/my-beloved-world-sonia-sotomayor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A &#8220;searching and emotionally intimate memoir&#8221; (The New York Times) told with a candor never before undertaken by a sitting Justice. This &#8220;powerful defense of empathy&#8221; (The Washington Post) is destined to become a classic of self-invention and self-discovery. The first Hispanic and third woman appointed to the United States Supreme Court, Sonia Sotomayor has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-beloved-world-sonia-sotomayor-abridged/">My Beloved World &#8211; Sonia Sotomayor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A &#8220;searching and emotionally intimate memoir&#8221; (The New York Times) told with a candor never before undertaken by a sitting Justice. This &#8220;powerful defense of empathy&#8221; (The Washington Post) is destined to become a classic of self-invention and self-discovery.     </p>
<p>                    The first Hispanic and third woman appointed to the United States Supreme Court, Sonia Sotomayor has become an instant American icon.     </p>
<p>                    In this story of human triumph that &#8220;hums with hope and exhilaration&#8221; (NPR), she recounts her life from a Bronx housing project to the federal bench, a journey that offers an inspiring testament to her own extraordinary determination and the power of believing in oneself.     </p>
<p>                    Here is the story of a precarious childhood, with an alcoholic father (who would die when she was nine) and a devoted but overburdened mother, and of the refuge a little girl took from the turmoil at home with her passionately spirited paternal grandmother. But it was when she was diagnosed with juvenile diabetes that the precocious Sonia recognized she must ultimately depend on herself. She would learn to give herself the insulin shots she needed to survive and soon imagined a path to a different life.     </p>
<p>                    With only television characters for her professional role models, and little understanding of what was involved, she determined to become a lawyer, a dream that would sustain her on an unlikely course, from valedictorian of her high school class to the highest honors at Princeton, Yale Law School, the New York County District Attorney&#8217;s office, private practice, and appointment to the Federal District Court before the age of forty.     </p>
<p>                    Along the way we see how she was shaped by her invaluable mentors, a failed marriage, and the modern version of extended family she has created from cherished friends and their children. Through her still-astonished eyes, America&#8217;s infinite possibilities are envisioned anew in this warm and honest book.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/my-beloved-world-sonia-sotomayor-abridged/">My Beloved World &#8211; Sonia Sotomayor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tell Me More : Stories About the 12 Hardest Things I&#8217;m Learning to Say &#8211; Kelly Corrigan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tell-me-more-stories-about-the-12-hardest-things-im-learning-to-say-kelly-corrigan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Painting & Art Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prints]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tell-me-more-stories-about-the-12-hardest-things-im-learning-to-say-kelly-corrigan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A story-driven collection of essays on the twelve powerful phrases we use to sustain our relationships, from the bestselling author of Glitter and Glue and The Middle Place &#8220;Kelly Corrigan takes on all the big, difficult questions here, with great warmth and courage.&#8221;&#8211;Glennon Doyle NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tell-me-more-stories-about-the-12-hardest-things-im-learning-to-say-kelly-corrigan-abridged/">Tell Me More : Stories About the 12 Hardest Things I&#8217;m Learning to Say &#8211; Kelly Corrigan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; A story-driven collection of essays on the twelve powerful phrases we use to sustain our relationships, from the bestselling author of Glitter and Glue and The Middle Place  &#8220;Kelly Corrigan takes on all the big, difficult questions here, with great warmth and courage.&#8221;&#8211;Glennon Doyle NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY REAL SIMPLE AND BUSTLE It&#8217;s a crazy idea: trying to name the phrases that make love and connection possible. But that&#8217;s just what Kelly Corrigan has set out to do here. In her New York Times bestselling memoirs,  Corrigan distilled our core relationships to their essences, showcasing a warm, easy storytelling style. Now, in Tell Me More,  she&#8217;s back with a deeply personal, unfailingly honest, and often hilarious examination of the essential phrases that turn the wheel of life.  In &#8220;I Don&#8217;t Know,&#8221; Corrigan wrestles to make peace with uncertainty, whether it&#8217;s over invitations that never came or a friend&#8217;s agonizing infertility. In &#8220;No,&#8221; she admires her mother&#8217;s ability to set boundaries and her liberating willingness to be unpopular. In &#8220;Tell Me More,&#8221; a facialist named Tish teaches her something important about listening. And in &#8220;I Was Wrong,&#8221; she comes clean about her disastrous role in a family fight&#8211;and explains why saying sorry may not be enough. With refreshing candor, a deep well of empathy, and her signature desire to understand &#8220;the thing behind the thing,&#8221; Corrigan swings between meditations on life with a preoccupied husband and two mercurial teenage daughters to profound observations on love and loss.  With the streetwise, ever-relatable voice that defines Corrigan&#8217;s work, Tell Me More is a moving and meaningful take on the power of the right words at the right moment to change everything. Praise for Tell Me More  &#8220;It is such a comfort just knowing that Kelly Corrigan exists: she is somehow both wise and self-deprecating; funny but unafraid of pain; frank but gentle. She is the sister/mother/best friend we all wish we could have&#8211;and because of this big-hearted book, we all get to.&#8221;&#8211;Ariel Levy, author of The Rules Do Not Apply  &#8220;With full-bodied humor and radical sensitivity, Kelly Corrigan transforms the mundane pain of life into a necessary spiritual text of sorts, one that reminds us that we have the right to grieve but the obligation to be grateful. This book will remind you that you are human&#8211;and of the fragile loveliness of being so.&#8221;&#8211;Lena Dunham</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tell-me-more-stories-about-the-12-hardest-things-im-learning-to-say-kelly-corrigan-abridged/">Tell Me More : Stories About the 12 Hardest Things I&#8217;m Learning to Say &#8211; Kelly Corrigan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Writing My Wrongs : Life, Death, and the Redemption in an American Prison &#8211; Shaka Senghor (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/writing-my-wrongs-life-death-and-the-redemption-in-an-american-prison-shaka-senghor-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Penology & Punishment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/writing-my-wrongs-life-death-and-the-redemption-in-an-american-prison-shaka-senghor-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An &#8220;extraordinary, unforgettable&#8221; (Michelle Alexander, author of The New Jim Crow) memoir of redemption and second chances amidst America&#8217;s mass incarceration epidemic, from a member of Oprah&#8217;s SuperSoul 100 Shaka Senghor was raised in a middle-class neighborhood on Detroit&#8217;s east side during the height of the 1980s crack epidemic. An [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/writing-my-wrongs-life-death-and-the-redemption-in-an-american-prison-shaka-senghor-abridged/">Writing My Wrongs : Life, Death, and the Redemption in an American Prison &#8211; Shaka Senghor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An &#8220;extraordinary, unforgettable&#8221; (Michelle Alexander, author of The New Jim Crow) memoir of redemption and second chances amidst America&#8217;s mass incarceration epidemic, from a member of Oprah&#8217;s SuperSoul 100     </p>
<p>                    Shaka Senghor was raised in a middle-class neighborhood on Detroit&#8217;s east side during the height of the 1980s crack epidemic. An honor roll student and a natural leader, he dreamed of becoming a doctor&#8211;but at age eleven, his parents&#8217; marriage began to unravel, and beatings from his mother worsened, which sent him on a downward spiral. He ran away from home, turned to drug dealing to survive, and ended up in prison for murder at the age of nineteen, full of anger and despair.     </p>
<p>                    Writing My Wrongs is the story of what came next. During his nineteen-year incarceration, seven of which were spent in solitary confinement, Senghor discovered literature, meditation, self-examination, and the kindness of others&#8211;tools he used to confront the demons of his past, forgive the people who hurt him, and begin atoning for the wrongs he had committed. Upon his release at age thirty-eight, Senghor became an activist and mentor to young men and women facing circumstances like his. His work in the community and the courage to share his story led him to fellowships at the MIT Media Lab and the Kellogg Foundation and invitations to speak at events like TED and the Aspen Ideas Festival.     </p>
<p>                    In equal turns, Writing My Wrongs is a page-turning portrait of life in the shadow of poverty, violence, and fear; an unforgettable story of redemption; and a compelling witness to our country&#8217;s need for rethinking its approach to crime, prison, and the men and women sent there.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/writing-my-wrongs-life-death-and-the-redemption-in-an-american-prison-shaka-senghor-abridged/">Writing My Wrongs : Life, Death, and the Redemption in an American Prison &#8211; Shaka Senghor (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Full Life : Reflections at Ninety &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-full-life-reflections-at-ninety-jimmy-carter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-full-life-reflections-at-ninety-jimmy-carter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his major New York Times bestseller, Jimmy Carter looks back from ninety years of age and &#8220;reveals private thoughts and recollections over a fascinating career as businessman, politician, evangelist, and humanitarian&#8221; (Booklist). At ninety, Jimmy Carter reflects on his public and private life with a frankness that is disarming. He adds detail and emotion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-full-life-reflections-at-ninety-jimmy-carter-abridged/">A Full Life : Reflections at Ninety &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his major New York Times bestseller, Jimmy Carter looks back from ninety years of age and &#8220;reveals private thoughts and recollections over a fascinating career as businessman, politician, evangelist, and humanitarian&#8221; (Booklist).    </p>
<p>                    At ninety, Jimmy Carter reflects on his public and private life with a frankness that is disarming. He adds detail and emotion about his youth in rural Georgia that he described in his magnificent An Hour Before Daylight. He writes about racism and the isolation of the Carters. He describes the brutality of the hazing regimen at Annapolis, and how he nearly lost his life twice serving on submarines and his amazing interview with Admiral Rickover. He describes the profound influence his mother had on him, and how he admired his father even though he didn&#8217;t emulate him. He admits that he decided to quit the Navy and later enter politics without consulting his wife, Rosalynn, and how appalled he is in retrospect.    </p>
<p>                    In his &#8220;warm and detailed memoir&#8221; (Los Angeles Times), Carter tells what he is proud of and what he might do differently. He discusses his regret at losing his re-election, but how he and Rosalynn pushed on and made a new life and second and third rewarding careers. He is frank about the presidents who have succeeded him, world leaders, and his passions for the causes he cares most about, particularly the condition of women and the deprived people of the developing world.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Always warm and human&#8230;even inspirational&#8221; (Buffalo News), A Full Life is a wise and moving look back from this remarkable man. Jimmy Carter has lived one of our great American lives-from rural obscurity to world fame, universal respect, and contentment. A Full Life is an extraordinary read from a &#8220;force to be reckoned with&#8221; (Christian Science Monitor).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-full-life-reflections-at-ninety-jimmy-carter-abridged/">A Full Life : Reflections at Ninety &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Will Be My Undoing : Living at the Intersection of Black, Female, and Feminist in (White) America &#8211; Morgan Jerkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-will-be-my-undoing-living-at-the-intersection-of-black-female-and-feminist-in-white-america-morgan-jerkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-will-be-my-undoing-living-at-the-intersection-of-black-female-and-feminist-in-white-america-morgan-jerkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;I can&#8217;t wait to read&#8230;This Will Be My Undoing.&#8221;-Roxane Gay One of the sharpest, fiercest, and most eloquent critics writing right now, Morgan Jerkins&#8217;s byline has appeared around the Internet for The New Yorker&#8217;s Page-Turner, Vogue, the New York Times, the Atlantic, Buzzfeed, and more; in this highly anticipated collection of linked essays perfect for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-will-be-my-undoing-living-at-the-intersection-of-black-female-and-feminist-in-white-america-morgan-jerkins-abridged/">This Will Be My Undoing : Living at the Intersection of Black, Female, and Feminist in (White) America &#8211; Morgan Jerkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;I can&#8217;t wait to read&#8230;This Will Be My Undoing.&#8221;-Roxane Gay     </p>
<p>                    One of the sharpest, fiercest, and most eloquent critics writing right now, Morgan Jerkins&#8217;s byline has appeared around the Internet for The New Yorker&#8217;s Page-Turner, Vogue, the New York Times, the Atlantic, Buzzfeed, and more; in this highly anticipated collection of linked essays perfect for fans of Bad Feminist, Rebecca Solnit&#8217;s Men Explain Things to Me, and Chimamanda Ngozie Adichie&#8217;s We Should All Be Feminists, Jerkins interweaves the incisive commentary on pop culture, feminism, black history, misogyny, and racism that she&#8217;s known for with her own experiences to confront the very real challenges of being a black woman today.    </p>
<p>                              &#8220;Growing up as a black woman is different. It prepares you to remember that you have to navigate two worlds. In this predominantly white, male-dominated world, you will never be white or male. Within the black community, belonging to the world of black women demands strength, wit, and aggression, because space for and by ourselves is small. You either assert yourself or learn to do so through humiliation, a constant shedding of respectability necessary to expose who you really are: just another black girl fighting to exist.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                              Morgan Jerkins is only in her twenties, but she has already established herself as an insightful, brutally honest writer who isn&#8217;t afraid of tackling tough, controversial subjects. In This Will Be My Undoing, she takes on perhaps one of the most provocative contemporary topics: What does it mean to &#8220;be&#8221;-to live as, to exist as-a black woman today? This is a book about black women, but it&#8217;s necessary reading for all Americans.     </p>
<p>                              Doubly disenfranchised by race and gender, often deprived of a place within the mostly white mainstream feminist movement, black women are objectified, silenced, and marginalized with devastating consequences, in ways both obvious and subtle, that are rarely acknowledged in our country&#8217;s larger discussion about inequality. In This Will Be My Undoing, Jerkins becomes both narrator and subject to expose the social, cultural, and historical story of black female oppression that influences the black community as well the white, male-dominated world at large.     </p>
<p>                              Whether she&#8217;s writing about Sailor Moon; Rachel Dolezal; the stigma of therapy; her complex relationship with her own physical body; the pain of dating when men say they don&#8217;t &#8220;see color&#8221;; being a black visitor in Russia; the specter of &#8220;the fast-tailed girl&#8221; and the paradox of black female sexuality; or disabled black women in the context of the &#8220;Black Girl Magic&#8221; movement, Jerkins is concise, compelling, and often revelatory.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-will-be-my-undoing-living-at-the-intersection-of-black-female-and-feminist-in-white-america-morgan-jerkins-abridged/">This Will Be My Undoing : Living at the Intersection of Black, Female, and Feminist in (White) America &#8211; Morgan Jerkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Really Good Day : How Microdosing Made a Mega Difference in My Mood, My Marriage and My Life &#8211; Ayelet Waldman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-really-good-day-how-microdosing-made-a-mega-difference-in-my-mood-my-marriage-and-my-life-ayelet-waldman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-really-good-day-how-microdosing-made-a-mega-difference-in-my-mood-my-marriage-and-my-life-ayelet-waldman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ayelet Waldman is fearless&#8217; &#8211; Rebecca Solnit &#8216;Genuinely brave and human&#8217; &#8211; The New York Times &#8216;Wildly brilliant&#8217; &#8211; Elle The true story of how a renowned writer&#8217;s struggle with mood storms led her to try a remedy as drastic as it is forbidden: microdoses of LSD. Her fascinating journey provides a window into one [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-really-good-day-how-microdosing-made-a-mega-difference-in-my-mood-my-marriage-and-my-life-ayelet-waldman-abridged/">A Really Good Day : How Microdosing Made a Mega Difference in My Mood, My Marriage and My Life &#8211; Ayelet Waldman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ayelet Waldman is fearless&#8217; &#8211; Rebecca Solnit    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Genuinely brave and human&#8217; &#8211; The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wildly brilliant&#8217; &#8211; Elle    </p>
<p>                    The true story of how a renowned writer&#8217;s struggle with mood storms led her to try a remedy as drastic as it is forbidden: microdoses of LSD. Her fascinating journey provides a window into one family and the complex world of a once-infamous drug seen through new eyes.    </p>
<p>                    When a small vial arrives in her mailbox from &#8216;Lewis Carroll,&#8217; Ayelet Waldman is at a low point. Her mood storms have become intolerably severe; she has tried nearly every medication possible; her husband and children are suffering with her. So she opens the vial, places two drops on her tongue, and joins the ranks of an underground but increasingly vocal group of scientists and civilians successfully using therapeutic microdoses of LSD. As Waldman charts her experience over the course of a month &#8211; bursts of productivity, sleepless nights, a newfound sense of equanimity &#8211; she also explores the history and mythology of LSD, the cutting-edge research into the drug, and the byzantine policies that control it. Drawing on her experience as a federal public defender, and as the mother of teenagers, and her research into the therapeutic value of psychedelics, Waldman has produced a book that is eye-opening, often hilarious, and utterly enthralling.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-really-good-day-how-microdosing-made-a-mega-difference-in-my-mood-my-marriage-and-my-life-ayelet-waldman-abridged/">A Really Good Day : How Microdosing Made a Mega Difference in My Mood, My Marriage and My Life &#8211; Ayelet Waldman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Unwinding of the Miracle : A Memoir of Life, Death, and Everything That Comes After &#8211; Julie Yip-Williams (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Read with Jenna Book Club Pick as Featured on Today &#8211; As a young mother facing a terminal diagnosis, Julie Yip-Williams began to write her story, a story like no other. What began as the chronicle of an imminent and early death became something much more&#8211;a powerful exhortation to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/">The Unwinding of the Miracle : A Memoir of Life, Death, and Everything That Comes After &#8211; Julie Yip-Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Read with Jenna Book Club Pick as Featured on Today &#8211; As a young mother facing a terminal diagnosis, Julie Yip-Williams began to write her story, a story like no other. What began as the chronicle of an imminent and early death became something much more&#8211;a powerful exhortation to the living.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;An exquisitely moving portrait of the daily stuff of life.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review (Editors&#8217; Choice) NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY The New York Times Book Review &#8211; Time &#8211; Real Simple &#8211; Good Housekeeping  That Julie Yip-Williams survived infancy was a miracle. Born blind in Vietnam, she narrowly escaped euthanasia at the hands of her grandmother, only to flee with her family the political upheaval of her country in the late 1970s. Loaded into a rickety boat with three hundred other refugees, Julie made it to Hong Kong and, ultimately, America, where a surgeon at UCLA gave her partial sight. She would go on to become a Harvard-educated lawyer, with a husband, a family, and a life she had once assumed would be impossible. Then, at age thirty-seven, with two little girls at home, Julie was diagnosed with terminal metastatic colon cancer, and a different journey began.  The Unwinding of the Miracle is the story of a vigorous life refracted through the prism of imminent death. When she was first diagnosed, Julie Yip-Williams sought clarity and guidance through the experience and, finding none, began to write her way through it&#8211;a chronicle that grew beyond her imagining. Motherhood, marriage, the immigrant experience, ambition, love, wanderlust, tennis, fortune-tellers, grief, reincarnation, jealousy, comfort, pain, the marvel of the body in full rebellion&#8211;this book is as sprawling and majestic as the life it records. It is inspiring and instructive, delightful and shattering. It is a book of indelible moments, seared deep&#8211;an incomparable guide to living vividly by facing hard truths consciously.  With humor, bracing honesty, and the cleansing power of well-deployed anger, Julie Yip-Williams set the stage for her lasting legacy and one final miracle: the story of her life. Praise for The Unwinding of the Miracle  &#8220;Everything worth understanding and holding on to is in this book. . . . A miracle indeed.&#8221;&#8211;Kelly Corrigan, New York Times bestselling author &#8220;A beautifully written, moving, and compassionate chronicle that deserves to be read and absorbed widely.&#8221;&#8211;Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/">The Unwinding of the Miracle : A Memoir of Life, Death, and Everything That Comes After &#8211; Julie Yip-Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Year of Yes : How to Dance It Out, Stand In the Sun and Be Your Own Person &#8211; Shonda Rhimes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/year-of-yes-how-to-dance-it-out-stand-in-the-sun-and-be-your-own-person-shonda-rhimes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/year-of-yes-how-to-dance-it-out-stand-in-the-sun-and-be-your-own-person-shonda-rhimes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this poignant, hilarious and deeply intimate call to arms, Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful woman, the mega-talented creator of Grey&#8217;s Anatomy and Scandal and executive producer of Bridgerton, For the People and How to Get Away with Murder , reveals how saying YES changed her life &#8211; and how it can change yours too. With three [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/year-of-yes-how-to-dance-it-out-stand-in-the-sun-and-be-your-own-person-shonda-rhimes-abridged/">Year of Yes : How to Dance It Out, Stand In the Sun and Be Your Own Person &#8211; Shonda Rhimes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this poignant, hilarious and deeply intimate call to arms, Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful woman, the mega-talented creator of Grey&#8217;s Anatomy and Scandal and executive producer of Bridgerton, For the People and How to Get Away with Murder , reveals how saying YES changed her life &#8211; and how it can change yours too.<br />
                     With three hit shows on television and three children at home, Shonda Rhimes had lots of good reasons to say no when invitations arrived. Hollywood party? No. Speaking engagement? No. Media appearances? No.<br />
                     And to an introvert like Shonda, who describes herself as &#8216;hugging the walls&#8217; at social events and experiencing panic attacks before press interviews, there was a particular benefit to saying no: nothing new to fear. Then came Thanksgiving 2013, when Shonda&#8217;s sister Delorse muttered six little words at her: You never say yes to anything.<br />
                     Profound, impassioned and laugh-out-loud funny, in Year of Yes Shonda Rhimes reveals how saying YES changed &#8211; and saved &#8211; her life. And inspires readers everywhere to change their own lives with one little word: Yes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/year-of-yes-how-to-dance-it-out-stand-in-the-sun-and-be-your-own-person-shonda-rhimes-abridged/">Year of Yes : How to Dance It Out, Stand In the Sun and Be Your Own Person &#8211; Shonda Rhimes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay & Lesbian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestselling memoir about identity, love and understanding. Now a major motion picture starring Nicole Kidman, Russell Crowe, and Lucas Hedges, directed by Joel Edgerton. &#8220;Every sentence of the story will stir your soul&#8221; (O Magazine). The son of a Baptist pastor and deeply embedded in church life in small town Arkansas, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley-abridged/">Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestselling memoir about identity, love and understanding. Now a major motion picture starring Nicole Kidman, Russell Crowe, and Lucas Hedges, directed by Joel Edgerton. &#8220;Every sentence of the story will stir your soul&#8221; (O Magazine).    </p>
<p>                    The son of a Baptist pastor and deeply embedded in church life in small town Arkansas, as a young man Garrard Conley was terrified and conflicted about his sexuality. When Garrard was a nineteen-year-old college student, he was outed to his parents, and was forced to make a life-changing decision: either agree to attend a church-supported conversion therapy program that promised to cure him of homosexuality; or risk losing family, friends, and the God he had prayed to every day of his life. Through an institutionalized Twelve-Step Program heavy on Bible study, he was supposed to emerge heterosexual, ex-gay, cleansed of impure urges and stronger in his faith in God for his brush with sin. Instead, even when faced with a harrowing and brutal journey, Garrard found the strength and understanding to break out in search of his true self and forgiveness.     </p>
<p>                    By confronting his buried past and the burden of a life lived in shadow, Garrard traces the complex relationships among family, faith, and community. At times heart-breaking, at times triumphant, Boy Erased is a testament to love that survives despite all odds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley-abridged/">Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Story of My Life &#8211; Helen Keller (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-story-of-my-life-helen-keller-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Disability: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-story-of-my-life-helen-keller-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When she was 19 months old, Helen Keller (1880-1968) suffered a severe illness that left her blind and deaf. Not long after, she also became mute. Her tenacious struggle to overcome these handicaps &#8212; with the help of her inspired teacher, Anne Sullivan &#8212; is one of the great stories of human courage and dedication. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-my-life-helen-keller-abridged/">The Story of My Life &#8211; Helen Keller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When she was 19 months old, Helen Keller (1880-1968) suffered a severe illness that left her blind and deaf. Not long after, she also became mute. Her tenacious struggle to overcome these handicaps &#8212; with the help of her inspired teacher, Anne Sullivan &#8212; is one of the great stories of human courage and dedication. In this classic autobiography, first published in 1903, Miss Keller recounts the first 22 years of her life, including the magical moment at the water pump when, recognizing the connection between the word &#8220;water&#8221; and the cold liquid flowing over her hand, she realized that objects had names. Subsequent experiences were equally noteworthy: her joy at eventually learning to speak, her friendships with Oliver Wendell Holmes, Edward Everett Hale and other notables, her education at Radcliffe (from which she graduated cum laude), and-underlying all-her extraordinary relationship with Miss Sullivan, who showed a remarkable genius for communicating with her eager and quick-to-learn pupil. These and many other aspects of Helen Keller&#8217;s life are presented here in clear, straightforward prose full of wonderful descriptions and imagery that would do credit to a sighted writer. Completely devoid of self-pity, yet full of love and compassion for others, this deeply moving memoir offers an unforgettable portrait of one of the outstanding women of the twentieth century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-my-life-helen-keller-abridged/">The Story of My Life &#8211; Helen Keller (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thirst : A Story of Redemption, Compassion, and a Mission to Bring Clean Water to the World &#8211; Scott Harrison, Contributions by Lisa Sweetingham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drought & Water Supply]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An inspiring personal story of redemption, second chances, and the transformative power within us all, from the founder and CEO of the nonprofit charity: water. At 28 years old, Scott Harrison had it all. A top nightclub promoter in New York City, his life was an endless cycle of drugs, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/">Thirst : A Story of Redemption, Compassion, and a Mission to Bring Clean Water to the World &#8211; Scott Harrison, Contributions by Lisa Sweetingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An inspiring personal story of redemption, second chances, and the transformative power within us all, from the founder and CEO of the nonprofit charity: water.    </p>
<p>                    At 28 years old, Scott Harrison had it all. A top nightclub promoter in New York City, his life was an endless cycle of drugs, booze, models&#8211;repeat. But 10 years in, desperately unhappy and morally bankrupt, he asked himself, What would the exact opposite of my life look like? Walking away from everything, Harrison spent the next 16 months on a hospital ship in West Africa and discovered his true calling. In 2006, with no money and less than no experience, Harrison founded charity: water. Today, his organization has raised over $400 million to bring clean drinking water to more than 10 million people around the globe.     </p>
<p>                    In Thirst, Harrison recounts the twists and turns that built charity: water into one of the most trusted and admired nonprofits in the world. Renowned for its 100% donation model, bold storytelling, imaginative branding, and radical commitment to transparency, charity: water has disrupted how social entrepreneurs work while inspiring millions of people to join its mission of bringing clean water to everyone on the planet within our lifetime.     </p>
<p>                    In the tradition of such bestselling books as Shoe Dog and Mountains Beyond Mountains, Thirst is a riveting account of how to build a better charity, a better business, a better life&#8211;and a gritty tale that proves it&#8217;s never too late to make a change.     </p>
<p>                    100% of the author&#8217;s net proceeds from Thirst will go to fund charity: water projects around the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thirst-a-story-of-redemption-compassion-and-a-mission-to-bring-clean-water-to-the-world-scott-harrison-contributions-by-lisa-sweetingham-abridged/">Thirst : A Story of Redemption, Compassion, and a Mission to Bring Clean Water to the World &#8211; Scott Harrison, Contributions by Lisa Sweetingham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bright Hour : A Memoir of Living and Dying &#8211; Nina Riggs (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bright-hour-a-memoir-of-living-and-dying-nina-riggs-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bright-hour-a-memoir-of-living-and-dying-nina-riggs-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER * &#8220;Stunning&#8230;heartrending&#8230;this year&#8217;s When Breath Becomes Air.&#8221; &#8211;Nora Krug, The Washington Post &#8220;Beautiful and haunting.&#8221; &#8211;Matt McCarthy, MD, USA TODAY &#8220;Deeply affecting&#8230;simultaneously heartbreaking and funny.&#8221; &#8211;People (Book of the Week) &#8220;Vivid, immediate.&#8221; &#8211;Laura Collins-Hughes, The Boston Globe Starred reviews from * Kirkus Reviews * Publishers Weekly * Library Journal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bright-hour-a-memoir-of-living-and-dying-nina-riggs-abridged/">The Bright Hour : A Memoir of Living and Dying &#8211; Nina Riggs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER *      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Stunning&#8230;heartrending&#8230;this year&#8217;s When Breath Becomes Air.&#8221; &#8211;Nora Krug, The Washington Post      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Beautiful and haunting.&#8221; &#8211;Matt McCarthy, MD, USA TODAY      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Deeply affecting&#8230;simultaneously heartbreaking and funny.&#8221; &#8211;People (Book of the Week)      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Vivid, immediate.&#8221; &#8211;Laura Collins-Hughes, The Boston Globe      </p>
<p>                    Starred reviews from * Kirkus Reviews * Publishers Weekly * Library Journal *      </p>
<p>                    Best Books of 2017 Selection by * The Washington Post *      </p>
<p>                    Most Anticipated Summer Reading Selection by * The Washington Post * Entertainment Weekly * Glamour * The Seattle Times * Vulture * InStyle * Bookpage * Bookriot * Real Simple * The Atlanta Journal-Constitution *      </p>
<p>                    The New York Times bestseller by poet Nina Riggs, mother of two young sons and the direct descendant of Ralph Waldo Emerson, is &#8220;a stunning&#8230;heart-rending meditation on life&#8230;It is this year&#8217;s When Breath Becomes Air&#8221; (The Washington Post).     </p>
<p>                    We are breathless but we love the days. They are promises. They are the only way to walk from one night to the other.     </p>
<p>                    Poet and essayist Nina Riggs was just thirty-seven years old when initially diagnosed with breast cancer&#8211;one small spot. Within a year, she received the devastating news that her cancer was terminal.     </p>
<p>                    How does a dying person learn to live each day &#8220;unattached to outcome&#8221;? How does one approach the moments, big and small, with both love and honesty? How does a young mother and wife prepare her two young children and adored husband for a loss that will shape the rest of their lives? How do we want to be remembered?     </p>
<p>                    Exploring motherhood, marriage, friendship, and memory, Nina asks: What makes a meaningful life when one has limited time? &#8220;Profound and poignant&#8221; (O, The Oprah Magazine), The Bright Hour is about how to make the most of all the days, even the painful ones. It&#8217;s about the way literature, especially Nina&#8217;s direct ancestor, Ralph Waldo Emerson, and her other muse, Montaigne, can be a balm and a form of prayer.     </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly written and exceptionally moving, it&#8217;s a &#8220;deeply affecting memoir, a simultaneously heartbreaking and funny account of living with loss and the specter of death. As Riggs lyrically, unflinchingly details her reality, she finds beauty and truth that comfort even amid the crushing sadness&#8221; (People, Book of the Week).     </p>
<p>                    Tender and heartwarming, The Bright Hour &#8220;is a gentle reminder to cherish each day&#8221; (Entertainment Weekly, Best New Books) and offers us this important perspective: &#8220;You can read a multitude books about how to die, but Riggs, a dying woman, will show you how to live&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review, Editor&#8217;s Choice).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bright-hour-a-memoir-of-living-and-dying-nina-riggs-abridged/">The Bright Hour : A Memoir of Living and Dying &#8211; Nina Riggs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Life, on the Line : A Chef&#8217;s Story of Chasing Greatness, Facing Death, and Redefining the Way We Eat &#8211; Grant Achatz, Nick Kokonas (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-on-the-line-a-chefs-story-of-chasing-greatness-facing-death-and-redefining-the-way-we-eat-grant-achatz-nick-kokonas-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hotel & Catering Trades]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-on-the-line-a-chefs-story-of-chasing-greatness-facing-death-and-redefining-the-way-we-eat-grant-achatz-nick-kokonas-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of America&#8217;s great chefs&#8221; (Vogue), Grant Achatz, shares how his drive to cook immaculate food fueled his miraculous triumph over tongue cancer. By 2007 chef Grant Achatz had been named one of the best new chefs in America by Food &#038; Wine, he had received the James Beard Foundation Rising Star Chef of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-on-the-line-a-chefs-story-of-chasing-greatness-facing-death-and-redefining-the-way-we-eat-grant-achatz-nick-kokonas-abridged/">Life, on the Line : A Chef&#8217;s Story of Chasing Greatness, Facing Death, and Redefining the Way We Eat &#8211; Grant Achatz, Nick Kokonas (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of America&#8217;s great chefs&#8221; (Vogue), Grant Achatz, shares how his drive to cook immaculate food fueled his miraculous triumph over tongue cancer.     </p>
<p>                    By 2007 chef Grant Achatz had been named one of the best new chefs in America by Food &#038; Wine, he had received the James Beard Foundation Rising Star Chef of the Year Award, and he and Nick Kokonas had opened the conceptually radical restaurant Alinea, which was named Best Restaurant in America by Gourmet magazine. Then, positioned firmly in the world&#8217;s culinary spotlight, Achatz was diagnosed with stage IV squamous cell carcinoma-tongue cancer.    </p>
<p>                    The prognosis grim, Grant undertook an alternative treatment of aggressive chemotherapy and radiation that ravaged his body and left him without a sense of taste. Tapping into his profound discipline and passion, he trained his chefs to mimic his palate and learned how to cook with his other senses. As Kokonas was able to attest, the food was never better. Five months later, Grant was declared cancer-free and went on to achieve some of the highest honors in the culinary world. Life, on the Line is not only a chef&#8217;s memoir, it is also a book about survival, about nurturing creativity, and about profound friendship.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-on-the-line-a-chefs-story-of-chasing-greatness-facing-death-and-redefining-the-way-we-eat-grant-achatz-nick-kokonas-abridged/">Life, on the Line : A Chef&#8217;s Story of Chasing Greatness, Facing Death, and Redefining the Way We Eat &#8211; Grant Achatz, Nick Kokonas (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hinch Yourself Happy : All The Best Cleaning Tips To Shine Your Sink And Soothe Your Soul &#8211; Mrs Hinch (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hinch-yourself-happy-all-the-best-cleaning-tips-to-shine-your-sink-and-soothe-your-soul-mrs-hinch-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DIY: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Household Hints]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interior Design, Decor & Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hinch-yourself-happy-all-the-best-cleaning-tips-to-shine-your-sink-and-soothe-your-soul-mrs-hinch-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Start the new year with a clean house and a calm mind with Mrs Hinch&#8217;s very best cleaning tips THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER FROM THE INSTAGRAM SENSATION &#8216;Will not only help you transform your home and make it sparkle, but also show you how cleaning can soothe anxiety and stress&#8217; BEST BOOKS TO [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hinch-yourself-happy-all-the-best-cleaning-tips-to-shine-your-sink-and-soothe-your-soul-mrs-hinch-abridged/">Hinch Yourself Happy : All The Best Cleaning Tips To Shine Your Sink And Soothe Your Soul &#8211; Mrs Hinch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Start the new year with a clean house and a calm mind with Mrs Hinch&#8217;s very best cleaning tips    </p>
<p>                    THE NUMBER ONE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER FROM THE INSTAGRAM SENSATION    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Will not only help you transform your home and make it sparkle, but also show you how cleaning can soothe anxiety and stress&#8217; BEST BOOKS TO HELP YOU ORGANISE YOUR HOME IN 2020, MAIL ONLINE<br />
                    _______________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The sensation&#8217; Sun    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We&#8217;re mad about Mrs Hinch&#8217; Vogue<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    Cleaning &#8211; aka hinching &#8211; doesn&#8217;t have to be that job you dread, not when Mrs Hinch is here to show you her sparkly ways.    </p>
<p>                    At over 3 million followers and counting, she has taken the nation by storm with her infectiously addictive charm, clever tidying tips and passionate belief in cleaning. Mrs Hinch invites you into her home and while inside you&#8217;ll discover how a spot of cleaning is the perfect way to cleanse the soul. She&#8217;ll even share the story of Mr and Mrs Hinch and their &#8216;dorgeous&#8217; boy, Henry.    </p>
<p>                    Inside you&#8217;ll find out:    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; How cleaning can soothe anxiety      and stress<br />
                     &#8211; Mrs Hinch&#8217;s must-haves<br />
                     &#8211; Step-by-step guides to hinching      your home<br />
                     &#8211; And so much more!     </p>
<p>                    With the help of her cloth family, Mrs Hinch will help you turn your house into a home. Whether you&#8217;re a daily duster or looking for a monthly makeover, Hinch Yourself Happy shows you how to create not only a cleaner house, but a calmer you.    </p>
<p>                    If you want your kitchen to sparkle like Meghan Markle, then this is the book for you.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Will not only help you transform your home and make it sparkle, but also show you how cleaning can soothe anxiety and stress&#8217; BEST BOOKS TO HELP YOU DECLUTTER, ORGANISE &#038; CLEAN YOUR HOME IN 2020 MAIL ONLINE     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Doing for household chores what Marie Kondo did for tidying. A step-by-step guide to achieving a spotless and immaculately tidy home&#8217; Daily Mirror    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;My new cleaning goddess&#8217; Daily Telegraph</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hinch-yourself-happy-all-the-best-cleaning-tips-to-shine-your-sink-and-soothe-your-soul-mrs-hinch-abridged/">Hinch Yourself Happy : All The Best Cleaning Tips To Shine Your Sink And Soothe Your Soul &#8211; Mrs Hinch (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial and truly unique life. Born in a small Austrian town in 1947, a year of famine, he was the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/">Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial and truly unique life.    </p>
<p>                     Born in a small Austrian town in 1947, a year of famine, he was the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a movie star. By the age of 21, he was living in Los Angeles and had been crowned Mr Universe. Within five years, he had learned English and become the greatest bodybuilder in the world. Within ten years, he had earned his college degree and was a millionaire from his business enterprises in real estate, landscaping and bodybuilding. He was also the winner of a Golden Globe Award for his debut as a dramatic actor in Stay Hungry.    </p>
<p>                     But that was only the beginning. The Terminator spawned numerous sequels and made him one of Hollywood&#8217;s biggest stars, as he had a series of hit films including Predator, Total Recall, True Lies and Twins. He married Maria Shriver, becoming part of the Kennedy clan, while going on to become the Republican governor of California, where he led the state through a budget crisis, natural disasters and political turmoil.     </p>
<p>                    It is the greatest immigrant success story of our time. His story is unique, and uniquely entertaining, and he tells it brilliantly in these pages. Until now, he has never told the full story of his life, in his own voice. Here is Arnold, with total recall.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/">Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Autobiography of Malcolm X &#8211; Alex Haley, Malcolm X, Introduction by Paul Gilroy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-autobiography-of-malcolm-x-alex-haley-malcolm-x-introduction-by-paul-gilroy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-autobiography-of-malcolm-x-alex-haley-malcolm-x-introduction-by-paul-gilroy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Malcolm X&#8217;s The Autobiography of Malcolm X was written in collaboration with Alex Haley, author of Roots, and includes an introduction by Paul Gilroy, author of The Black Atlantic, in Penguin Modern Classics. From hustling, drug addiction and armed violence in America&#8217;s black ghettos Malcolm X turned, in a dramatic prison conversion, to the puritanical [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-autobiography-of-malcolm-x-alex-haley-malcolm-x-introduction-by-paul-gilroy-abridged/">The Autobiography of Malcolm X &#8211; Alex Haley, Malcolm X, Introduction by Paul Gilroy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Malcolm X&#8217;s The Autobiography of Malcolm X was written in collaboration with Alex Haley, author of Roots, and includes an introduction by Paul Gilroy, author of The Black Atlantic, in Penguin Modern Classics.    </p>
<p>                    From hustling, drug addiction and armed violence in America&#8217;s black ghettos Malcolm X turned, in a dramatic prison conversion, to the puritanical fervour of the Black Muslims. As their spokesman he became identified in the white press as a terrifying teacher of race hatred; but to his direct audience, the oppressed American blacks, he brought hope and self-respect. This autobiography (written with Alex Haley) reveals his quick-witted integrity, usually obscured by batteries of frenzied headlines, and the fierce idealism which led him to reject both liberal hypocrisies and black racialism.    </p>
<p>                    Vilified by his critics as an anti-white demagogue, Malcolm X gave a voice to unheard African-Americans, bringing them pride, hope and fearlessness, and remains an inspirational and controversial figure.    </p>
<p>                    Malcolm X (1925-65), born Malcolm Little in Omaha, and also known as El-Hajj Malik El-Shabazz, lost both his parents at a young age. Leaving school early, he soon became part of Harlem&#8217;s underworld, and in 1946 he was sentenced to ten years&#8217; imprisonment. It was in prison that Malcolm X converted to Islam. Paroled in 1952, he became an outspoken defender of Muslim doctrines, formed the Organization of Afro-American Unity in 1963, and had received considerable publicity by the time of his assassination in 1965.    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed The Autobiography of Malcolm X, you might like Nelson Mandela&#8217;s No Easy Walk to Freedom, also available in Penguin Modern Classics.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This extraordinary autobiography is a brilliant, painful, important book&#8217;<br />
                    The New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-autobiography-of-malcolm-x-alex-haley-malcolm-x-introduction-by-paul-gilroy-abridged/">The Autobiography of Malcolm X &#8211; Alex Haley, Malcolm X, Introduction by Paul Gilroy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
