<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Specific Bands &amp; Groups Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/specific-bands-groups/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/specific-bands-groups/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Specific Bands &amp; Groups Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/specific-bands-groups/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Broken Horses : A Memoir &#8211; Brandi Carlile</title>
		<link>/broken-horses-a-memoir-brandi-carlile/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/broken-horses-a-memoir-brandi-carlile/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The critically acclaimed singer-songwriter, producer, and six-time Grammy winner opens up about faith, sexuality, parenthood, and a life shaped by music in &#8220;one of the great memoirs of our time&#8221; (Glennon Doyle, author of Untamed). NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR AND AUTOSTRADDLE &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/broken-horses-a-memoir-brandi-carlile/">Broken Horses : A Memoir &#8211; Brandi Carlile</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The critically acclaimed singer-songwriter, producer, and six-time Grammy winner opens up about faith, sexuality, parenthood, and a life shaped by music in &#8220;one of the great memoirs of our time&#8221; (Glennon Doyle, author of Untamed). </p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR AND AUTOSTRADDLE &#8211; &#8220;The best-written, most engaging rock autobiography since her childhood hero, Elton John, published Me.&#8221;&#8211;Variety </p>
<p>                    Brandi Carlile was born into a musically gifted, impoverished family on the outskirts of Seattle and grew up in a constant state of change, moving from house to house, trailer to trailer, fourteen times in as many years. Though imperfect in every way, her dysfunctional childhood was as beautiful as it was strange, and as nurturing as it was difficult. At the age of five, Brandi contracted bacterial meningitis, which almost took her life, leaving an indelible mark on her formative years and altering her journey into young adulthood. </p>
<p>                    As an openly gay teenager, Brandi grappled with the tension between her sexuality and her faith when her pastor publicly refused to baptize her on the day of the ceremony. Shockingly, her small town rallied around Brandi in support and set her on a path to salvation where the rest of the misfits and rejects find it: through twisted, joyful, weird, and wonderful music. </p>
<p>                    In Broken Horses,  Brandi Carlile takes readers through the events of her life that shaped her very raw art&#8211;from her start at a local singing competition where she performed Elton John&#8217;s &#8220;Honky Cat&#8221; in a bedazzled white polyester suit, to her first break opening for Dave Matthews Band, to many sleepless tours over fifteen years and six studio albums, all while raising two children with her wife, Catherine Shepherd. This hard-won success led her to collaborations with personal heroes like Elton John, Dolly Parton, Mavis Staples, Pearl Jam, Tanya Tucker, and Joni Mitchell, as well as her peers in the supergroup The Highwomen, and ultimately to the Grammy stage, where she converted millions of viewers into instant fans. </p>
<p>                    Evocative and piercingly honest, Broken Horses is at once an examination of faith through the eyes of a person rejected by the church&#8217;s basic tenets and a meditation on the moments and lyrics that have shaped the life of a creative mind, a brilliant artist, and a genuine empath on a mission to give back.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/broken-horses-a-memoir-brandi-carlile/">Broken Horses : A Memoir &#8211; Brandi Carlile</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kiss and Make-Up &#8211; Gene Simmons</title>
		<link>/kiss-and-make-up-gene-simmons/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Heavy Metal Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/kiss-and-make-up-gene-simmons/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>KISS has released thirty-seven records and sold 80 million albums worldwide. Gene Simmons has also acted in films and on television, has written and produced albums for other recording artists, has managed the recording career of, among others, Liza Minelli, and was founder and president of his own recording label, Simmons Records/RCA. He also launched [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/kiss-and-make-up-gene-simmons/">Kiss and Make-Up &#8211; Gene Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>KISS has released thirty-seven records and sold 80 million albums worldwide. Gene Simmons has also acted in films and on television, has written and produced albums for other recording artists, has managed the recording career of, among others, Liza Minelli, and was founder and president of his own recording label, Simmons Records/RCA. He also launched his film and TV producing career with Detroit Rock City for New Line Cinema. Gene Simmons lives in Beverley Hills, California, and was recently the rock star teacher on Channel 4&#8217;s Rock School.    </p>
<p>                    Here for the first time Gene Simmons, the notorious mainman of the explosive rock and roll group KISS, tells his story. Delivered in Gene&#8217;s own honest, outrageous and uncensored voice, he tells of his early beginnings in Israel, of his arrival in New York at the age of eight, his first taste of 1950s pop culture and his developing thirst for fame, fun and girls. Undoubtedly one of the most infamous rock and roll legends alive, Gene tells the never before revealed story of KISS&#8217;s reign as the biggest and most popular band in the world. Finally, the real story of the man behind the make-up.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/kiss-and-make-up-gene-simmons/">Kiss and Make-Up &#8211; Gene Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John</title>
		<link>/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is Me &#8211; the joyously funny, honest and moving story of the most enduringly successful singer/songwriter of all time.<br />
                    ______________</p>
<p>                    Christened Reginald Dwight, he was a shy boy with Buddy Holly glasses who grew up in the London suburb of Pinner and dreamed of becoming a pop star.  By the age of twenty-three, he was performing his first gig in America, facing an astonished audience in his bright yellow dungarees, a star-spangled T-shirt and boots with wings. Elton John had arrived and the music world would never be the same again.</p>
<p>                    His life has been full of drama, from the early rejection of his work with songwriting partner Bernie Taupin to spinning out of control as a chart-topping superstar; from half-heartedly trying to drown himself in his LA swimming pool to disco-dancing with the Queen; from friendships with John Lennon, Freddie Mercury and George Michael to setting up his AIDS Foundation. All the while, Elton was hiding a drug addiction that would grip him for over a decade.</p>
<p>                    In Me Elton also writes powerfully about getting clean and changing his life, about finding love with David Furnish and becoming a father.   In a voice that is warm, humble and open, this is Elton on his music and his relationships, his passions and his mistakes.  This is a story that will stay with you, by a living legend.<br />
                    ______________</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Self-deprecating, funny . . . You cannot help but enjoy his company throughout, temper tantrums and all&#8217; The Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Racy, pacy and crammed with scurrilous anecdotes &#8211; what more could you ask from the rocket man&#8217; Guardian (Book of the Week)</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Chatty, gossipy, amusing and at times brutally candid&#8217; Telegraph</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Face the Music : A Life Exposed &#8211; Paul Stanley</title>
		<link>/face-the-music-a-life-exposed-paul-stanley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/face-the-music-a-life-exposed-paul-stanley/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES and INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER In Face the Music, Paul Stanley-the co-founder and famous &#8220;Starchild&#8221; frontman of KISS-reveals for the first time the incredible highs and equally incredible lows in his life both inside and outside the band. Face the Music is the shocking, funny, smart, inspirational story of one of rock&#8217;s most enduring [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/face-the-music-a-life-exposed-paul-stanley/">Face the Music : A Life Exposed &#8211; Paul Stanley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES and INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER  In Face the Music, Paul Stanley-the co-founder and famous &#8220;Starchild&#8221; frontman of KISS-reveals for the first time the incredible highs and equally incredible lows in his life both inside and outside the band. Face the Music is the shocking, funny, smart, inspirational story of one of rock&#8217;s most enduring icons and the group he helped create, define, and immortalize.  Stanley mixes compelling personal revelations and gripping, gritty war stories that will surprise even the most steadfast member of the KISS Army. He takes us back to his childhood in the 1950s and &#8217;60s, a traumatic time made more painful thanks to a physical deformity. Born with a condition called microtia, he grew up partially deaf, with only one ear. But this instilled in him an inner drive to succeed in the most unlikely of pursuits: music.  With never-before-seen photos and images throughout, Stanley&#8217;s memoir is a fully realized and unflinching portrait of a rock star, a chronicle of the stories behind the famous anthems, the many brawls and betrayals, and all the drama and pyrotechnics on and off the stage.<br />
                    Raw and confessional, Stanley offers candid insights into his personal relationships, and the turbulent dynamics with his bandmates over the past four decades. And no one comes out unscathed-including Stanley himself.  &#8220;People say I was brave to write such a revealing book, but I wrote it because I needed to personally reflect on my own life. I know everyone will see themselves somewhere in this book, and where my story might take them is why I&#8217;m sharing it.&#8221; -Paul Stanley    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/face-the-music-a-life-exposed-paul-stanley/">Face the Music : A Life Exposed &#8211; Paul Stanley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mozart &#8211; Marcia Davenport</title>
		<link>/mozart-marcia-davenport/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Classical Music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mozart-marcia-davenport/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Realistic, moving, engrossing, and positively brilliant, this biography recreates Mozart, the man and his music, against the background of the world he lived in. For Marcia Davenport, the research and writing of Mozart was truly a labor of love, during which she retraced every journey he made, saw every dwelling (then extant) in which he [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mozart-marcia-davenport/">Mozart &#8211; Marcia Davenport</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Realistic, moving, engrossing, and positively brilliant, this biography recreates Mozart, the man and his music, against the background of the world he lived in. For Marcia Davenport, the research and writing of Mozart was truly a labor of love, during which she retraced every journey he made, saw every dwelling (then extant) in which he had ever lived, every theatre where his works were first performed, and every library and museum where his manuscripts were then to be seen. In this eloquent work of historical reconstruction, Davenport lets her characters tell their own stories. She builds from Mozart’s infancy toward the climactic meeting in 1787 of Mozart, Lorenzo Da Ponte, and Casanova in Prague, when Don Giovanni was being written, to Mozart’s tragically early death. The result is a biography of such commanding stature that it has remained unassailable since its publication in 1932.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mozart-marcia-davenport/">Mozart &#8211; Marcia Davenport</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
