<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Corporate Finance Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/corporate-finance/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/corporate-finance/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Corporate Finance Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/corporate-finance/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review</p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.</p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.</p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.</p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Venture Deals : Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist &#8211; Brad Feld, Jason Mendelson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Help take your startup to the next step with the new and revised edition of the popular book on the VC deal process-from the co-founders of the Foundry Group How do venture capital deals come together? This is one of the most frequent questions asked by each generation of new entrepreneurs. Surprisingly, there is little [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/">Venture Deals : Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist &#8211; Brad Feld, Jason Mendelson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Help take your startup to the next step with the new and revised edition of the popular book on the VC deal process-from the co-founders of the Foundry Group    </p>
<p>                     How do venture capital deals come together? This is one of the most frequent questions asked by each generation of new entrepreneurs. Surprisingly, there is little reliable information on the subject. No one understands this better than Brad Feld and Jason Mendelson. The founders and driving force behind the Foundry Group-a venture capital firm focused on investing in early-stage information technology companies-Brad and Jason have been involved in hundreds of venture capital financings. Their investments range from small startups to large Series A venture financing rounds. The new edition of Venture Deals continues to show fledgling entrepreneurs the inner-workings of the VC process, from the venture capital term sheet and effective negotiating strategies to the initial seed and the later stages of development.    </p>
<p>                     Fully updated to reflect the intricacies of startups and entrepreneurship in today&#8217;s dynamic economic environment, this new edition includes revisions and updates to coverage on negotiating, gender issues, ICO&#8217;s, and economic terms. New chapters examine legal and procedural considerations relevant to fundraising, bank debt, equity and convertible debt, how to hire an investment banker to sell a company, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Provides valuable, real-world insights into venture capital structure and strategy<br />
                    Explains and clarifies the VC term sheet and other misunderstood aspects of capital funding<br />
                    Helps to build collaborative and supportive relationships between entrepreneurs and investors<br />
                    Draws from the author&#8217;s years of practical experience in the VC arena<br />
                    Includes extensively revised and updated content throughout to increase readability and currency    </p>
<p>                     Venture Deals: Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist is a must-have resource for Any aspiring entrepreneur, venture capitalist, or lawyer involved in VC deals as well as students and instructors in related areas of study.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/">Venture Deals : Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist &#8211; Brad Feld, Jason Mendelson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>STARTUP WEALTH delivers engaging interviews with early- stage investors in Google, Invisalign, ZipCar, Uber, Twilio, Localytics, and other successful and not so successful companies. Find out how an amazing IPO can result in early investors getting pennies on the dollar&#8211;or a 10x+ return. Josh Maher profiles 23 of the country&#8217;s best investors over the last [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/">Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>STARTUP WEALTH delivers engaging interviews with early- stage investors in Google, Invisalign, ZipCar, Uber, Twilio, Localytics, and other successful and not so successful companies. Find out how an amazing IPO can result in early investors getting pennies on the dollar&#8211;or a 10x+ return.    </p>
<p>                    Josh Maher profiles 23 of the country&#8217;s best investors over the last two decades by way of real-world case studies. Through revealing interviews, readers are introduced to Mark Suster, Catherine Mott, Christopher Mirabile, Brad Feld, Allan May, Joanne Wilson, and many other accomplished angel investors and venture capitalists. In these interviews you&#8217;ll learn:<br />
                     &#8211; How the best investors think about identifying companies, negotiating terms, and partnering with founders and other investors<br />
                     &#8211; How angel investing can involve many different successful approaches<br />
                     &#8211; What the best investors have learned from their largest successes and failures<br />
                     &#8211; How investors design their portfolios and work with companies to achieve the most successful results.    </p>
<p>                    STARTUP WEALTH is an insightful and useful tool for anyone seeking to make better investments, select great investors, or raise early-stage capital for their business.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;There is nothing better when it comes to learning &#8216;best practices&#8217; than hearing from successful people in the trenches. Josh&#8217;s book captures the best of the best, as they reveal both what worked and what didn&#8217;t for them as angel investors and entrepreneurs. Required reading whatever side of the investing fence you&#8217;re on!&#8221;&#8211;Gerry Langeler, Managing Director at OVP Venture Partners. Co-founder of Mentor Graphics (NASDAQ: MENT). Author of The Success Matrix and Take the Money and Run! An Insider&#8217;s Guide to Venture Capital.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/startup-wealth-how-the-best-angel-investors-make-money-in-startups-josh-maher-abridged/">Startup Wealth : How The Best Angel Investors Make Money In Startups &#8211; Josh Maher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Picking up where Liar&#8217;s Poker left off (literally, in the bond dealer&#8217;s desks of Salomon Brothers) the story of Long-Term Capital Management is of a group of elite investors who believed they could beat the market and, like alchemists, create limitless wealth for themselves and their partners. Founded by John Meriweather, a notoriously confident bond [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Picking up where Liar&#8217;s Poker left off (literally, in the bond dealer&#8217;s desks of Salomon Brothers) the story of Long-Term Capital Management is of a group of elite investors who believed they could beat the market and, like alchemists, create limitless wealth for themselves and their partners.    </p>
<p>                              Founded by John Meriweather, a notoriously confident bond dealer, along with two Nobel prize winners and a floor of Wall Street&#8217;s brightest and best, Long-Term Captial Management was from the beginning hailed as a new gold standard in investing. It was to be the hedge fund to end all other hedge funds: a discreet private investment club limited to those rich enough to pony up millions.    </p>
<p>                              It became the banks&#8217; own favourite fund and from its inception achieved a run of dizzyingly spectacular returns. New investors barged each other aside to get their investment money into LTCM&#8217;s hands. But as competitors began to mimic Meriweather&#8217;s fund, he altered strategy to maintain the fund&#8217;s performance, leveraging capital with credit on a scale not fully understood and never seen before.    </p>
<p>                              When the markets in Indonesia, South America and Russia crashed in 1998 LCTM&#8217;s investments crashed with them and mountainous debts accumulated. The fund was in melt-down, and threatening to bring down into its trillion-dollar black hole a host of financial instiutions from New York to Switzerland. It&#8217;s a tale of vivid characters, overwheening ambition, and perilous drama told, in Roger Lowenstein&#8217;s hands, with brilliant style and panache.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/when-genius-failed-the-rise-and-fall-of-long-term-capital-management-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">When Genius Failed : The Rise and Fall of Long Term Capital Management &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Be a Power Connector: The 5+50+100 Rule for Turning Your Business Network into Profits &#8211; Judy Robinett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Create a personal &#8220;power grid&#8221; of influence to spark professional and personal success&#8221;Other people have the answers, deals, money, access, power, and influence you need to get what you want in this world. To achieve any goal, you need other people to help you do it.&#8221; &#8212; JUDY ROBINETT As anyone in business knows, strategic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/">How to Be a Power Connector: The 5+50+100 Rule for Turning Your Business Network into Profits &#8211; Judy Robinett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Create a personal &#8220;power grid&#8221; of influence to spark professional and personal success&#8221;Other people have the answers, deals, money, access, power, and influence you need to get what you want in this world. To achieve any goal, you need other people to help you do it.&#8221; &#8212; JUDY ROBINETT    </p>
<p>                    As anyone in business knows, strategic planning iscritical to achieving long-term success. In How to Be a Power Connector, super-networker Judy Robinett argues that strategic relationship planning should be your top priority.    </p>
<p>                    When you combine your specific skills and talents with a clear, workable path for creating and managing your relationships, nothing will stop you from meeting your goals. With high-value connections, you&#8217;ll tap into a dynamic &#8220;power grid&#8221; of influence guaranteed to accelerate your personal and professional success.    </p>
<p>                    Robinett uses her decades of experience connecting the world&#8217;s highest achievers with one another to help you build high-value relationships. She reveals all the secrets of her trade, including proven ways to:    </p>
<p>                    Find and enter the best network &#8220;ecosystem&#8221; to meet your goalsReach even the most unreachable people quickly and effectivelyGet anyone&#8217;s contact information within 30 secondsCreate a &#8220;3-D connection&#8221; that adds value to multiple people at the same timeAccess key infl uencers through industry and community eventsSubtly seed conversation with information about interests and needsUse social media to your best advantage    </p>
<p>                    Robinett has based her methods on solid researchproving that social groups begin to break up when they become larger than 150 people, and that 50 members is the optimal size for group communication. As such, she has developed what she calls the &#8220;5+50+100&#8243; method: contact your top 5 connections daily, your Key 50 weekly, and your Vital 100 monthly. this is your power grid, and it will work wonders for your career.    </p>
<p>                    Nothing will stop you when you learn How to Be aPower Connector.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR HOW TO BE A POWER CONNECTOR:&#8221;Unlike many books in this genre, this one is written by a woman who has lived it.. . . Judy Robinett offers guidance on how to form authentic relationships thatbring mutual benefits.&#8221; &#8212; ADAM GRANT, Wharton professor and New York Times bestselling author of Give and Take    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;How to Be a Power Connector is like an MBA in networking: an advanced course in finding and developing quality relationships with the people who can make the biggest difference in your professional success.&#8221; &#8212; IVAN MISNER, founder and chairman of BNI    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Talk about power! Follow Judy Robinett&#8217;s logical, straightforward, and helpfully detailed advice, and you can be a &#8216;Power Connector&#8217; yourself! Great ideas, wellpresented, with no &#8216;wasted space&#8217; in her argument!&#8221; &#8212; DON PEPPERS, coauthor of Extreme Trust: Honesty as a Competitive Advantage    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Absolutely brilliant. A step-by-step guide to building a network that will be both invaluable to you and just as valuable to those whose lives you will now have theopportunity to touch. I can&#8217;t imagine a more powerful book for one who truly desires to be a Power Connector.&#8221; &#8212; BOB BURG, coauthor of The Go-Giver and author of Adversaries into Allies    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;In the C-Suite or in your personal life everything comes down to the quality of your relationships. Judy&#8217;s book helps you attract and maintain the relationships that will get you what you want most. Be a super connector now!&#8221; &#8212; JEFFREY HAYZLETT, TV host and bestselling author of Running the Gauntlet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/">How to Be a Power Connector: The 5+50+100 Rule for Turning Your Business Network into Profits &#8211; Judy Robinett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019    </p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review    </p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.    </p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.    </p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.    </p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman-abridged/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Revenue Growth Habit : The Simple Art of Growing Your Business by 15% in 15 Minutes Per Day &#8211; Alex Goldfayn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-revenue-growth-habit-the-simple-art-of-growing-your-business-by-15-in-15-minutes-per-day-alex-goldfayn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-revenue-growth-habit-the-simple-art-of-growing-your-business-by-15-in-15-minutes-per-day-alex-goldfayn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>800-CEO-Read Sales Book Of The Year for 2015 &#124; Forbes 15 Best Business Books of 2015 &#124; The chapters, (46 of them in this 256 page book) are quick and concise, and it is easy to pick it up anywhere and find a nugget of easily actionable advice, but the kicker is that the actions [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-revenue-growth-habit-the-simple-art-of-growing-your-business-by-15-in-15-minutes-per-day-alex-goldfayn-abridged/">The Revenue Growth Habit : The Simple Art of Growing Your Business by 15% in 15 Minutes Per Day &#8211; Alex Goldfayn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>800-CEO-Read Sales Book Of The Year for 2015 | Forbes 15 Best Business Books of 2015 | The chapters, (46 of them in this 256 page book) are quick and concise, and it is easy to pick it up anywhere and find a nugget of easily actionable advice, but the kicker is that the actions he recommends are also quick and concise, so that we can accomplish them in the few bursts of spare time we all have left. 800CEORead.com Follow Goldfayn&#8217;s brilliant advice and you will have an endless supply of customer testimonials, spontaneous referrals, and new business, and it will compel you to buy a beautiful fountain pen and stop obsessing over social media. His advice simply works. Inc.com  Grow your business by 15% with these proven daily growth actions Do you have trouble finding time during your hectic day to grow your business? Is your company stalled because you are too busy reacting to customer problems? Do you lack the funds to jumpstart an effective marketing plan? The Revenue Growth Habit gives business owners, leaders, and all customer facing staff a hands-on resource for increasing revenue that is fast, easy, and requires no financial investment.<br />
                    Alex Goldfayn, CEO of the Evangelist Marketing Institute, shows how to grow your organization by 15% or more in 15 minutes or less per day without spending a penny of your money. Forget about relying on social media. Posting on Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn doesn&#8217;t grow revenue, especially for business-to-business companies. The Revenue Growth Habit shows how to request and collect testimonials and how to communicate these testimonials to grow your business. You will discover how to write powerful case studies, ask for (and get!) referrals, grow your lists, and send a revenue-growing newsletter. Goldfayn also includes information for teaching your customer service people how to inform your current clients about what else they can buy from you. This proven approach revolves around letting your customers tell your story. There is nothing you can say about your products and services that is more effective than what your paying customers say. How does it work? Each day, take one quick, proactive communication action that tells someone about how they&#8217;ll be improved after buying from you. Choose from the 22 actions Goldfayn details in The Revenue Growth Habit.<br />
                    Each technique is fast, simple, and free. It only requires your personal effort to communicate the value of your product or service to someone who can buy from you. Personal communication the key to the 22 action steps will make your company stand head-and-shoulders above the competition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-revenue-growth-habit-the-simple-art-of-growing-your-business-by-15-in-15-minutes-per-day-alex-goldfayn-abridged/">The Revenue Growth Habit : The Simple Art of Growing Your Business by 15% in 15 Minutes Per Day &#8211; Alex Goldfayn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film The Wolf of Wall Street is about the finance industry&#8217;s greediest adults, Kevin Roose&#8217;s Young Money is a look at those wolves as cubs&#8217; Amazon.com &#8216;Best Book of the Month&#8217; Every year, thousands of eager graduates are hired by the world&#8217;s financial giants, where they&#8217;re taught the secrets of making obscene [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/">Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If Martin Scorsese&#8217;s film The Wolf of Wall Street is about the finance industry&#8217;s greediest adults, Kevin Roose&#8217;s Young Money is a look at those wolves as cubs&#8217; Amazon.com &#8216;Best Book of the Month&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Every year, thousands of eager graduates are hired by the world&#8217;s financial giants, where they&#8217;re taught the secrets of making obscene amounts of money &#8212; as well as how to dress, talk, date, drink, and schmooze like real financiers. Young Money is the exclusive, inside story of this well-guarded world.<br />
                    Investigative reporter Kevin Roose shadows eight rookies as they are exposed to the exhausting workloads, huge bonuses, and recreational drugs that have always characterized Wall Street life. But they experience something new, too: an industry forever changed by the massive financial collapse of 2008. And as they get their Wall Street educations, they face hard questions about morality, prestige, and the value of their work.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A great new read that doubles as a post-crash update to Michael Lewis&#8217; Liar&#8217;s Poker &#8211; Mother Jones    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fun fast read that will make you laugh out loud&#8217; Fortune Magazine</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/young-money-inside-the-hidden-world-of-wall-streets-post-crash-recruits-kevin-roose-abridged/">Young Money : Inside the Hidden World of Wall Street&#8217;s Post-Crash Recruits &#8211; Kevin Roose (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Business Adventures : Twelve Classic Tales from the World of Wall Street: The New York Times bestseller Bill Gates calls &#8216;the best business book I&#8217;ve ever read&#8217; &#8211; John Brooks (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/business-adventures-twelve-classic-tales-from-the-world-of-wall-street-the-new-york-times-bestseller-bill-gates-calls-the-best-business-book-ive-ever-read-john-brooks-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/business-adventures-twelve-classic-tales-from-the-world-of-wall-street-the-new-york-times-bestseller-bill-gates-calls-the-best-business-book-ive-ever-read-john-brooks-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The best business book I&#8217;ve ever read.&#8217; Bill Gates, Wall Street Journal&#8217;The Michael Lewis of his day.&#8217; New York TimesWhat do the $350 million Ford Motor Company disaster known as the Edsel, the fast and incredible rise of Xerox, and the unbelievable scandals at General Electric and Texas Gulf Sulphur have in common? Each is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/business-adventures-twelve-classic-tales-from-the-world-of-wall-street-the-new-york-times-bestseller-bill-gates-calls-the-best-business-book-ive-ever-read-john-brooks-abridged/">Business Adventures : Twelve Classic Tales from the World of Wall Street: The New York Times bestseller Bill Gates calls &#8216;the best business book I&#8217;ve ever read&#8217; &#8211; John Brooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The best business book I&#8217;ve ever read.&#8217; Bill Gates, Wall Street Journal&#8217;The Michael Lewis of his day.&#8217; New York TimesWhat do the $350 million Ford Motor Company disaster known as the Edsel, the fast and incredible rise of Xerox, and the unbelievable scandals at General Electric and Texas Gulf Sulphur have in common? Each is an example of how an iconic company was defined by a particular moment of fame or notoriety. These notable and fascinating accounts are as relevant today to understanding the intricacies of corporate life as they were when the events happened.Stories about Wall Street are infused with drama and adventure and reveal the machinations and volatile nature of the world of finance. John Brooks&#8217;s insightful reportage is so full of personality and critical detail that whether he is looking at the astounding market crash of 1962, the collapse of a well-known brokerage firm, or the bold attempt by American bankers to save the British pound, one gets the sense that history really does repeat itself.This business classic written by longtime New Yorker contributor John Brooks is an insightful and engaging look into corporate and financial life in America.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/business-adventures-twelve-classic-tales-from-the-world-of-wall-street-the-new-york-times-bestseller-bill-gates-calls-the-best-business-book-ive-ever-read-john-brooks-abridged/">Business Adventures : Twelve Classic Tales from the World of Wall Street: The New York Times bestseller Bill Gates calls &#8216;the best business book I&#8217;ve ever read&#8217; &#8211; John Brooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Commodities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employee-ownership & Co-operatives]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Jim Paul&#8217;s meteoric rise took him from a small town in Northern Kentucky to governor of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, yet he lost it all-his fortune, his reputation, and his job-in one fatal attack of excessive economic hubris. In this honest, frank analysis, Paul and Brendan Moynihan revisit the events that led to Paul&#8217;s disastrous [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/">What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jim Paul&#8217;s meteoric rise took him from a small town in Northern Kentucky to governor of the Chicago Mercantile Exchange, yet he lost it all-his fortune, his reputation, and his job-in one fatal attack of excessive economic hubris. In this honest, frank analysis, Paul and Brendan Moynihan revisit the events that led to Paul&#8217;s disastrous decision and examine the psychological factors behind bad financial practices in several economic sectors.  This book-winner of a 2014 Axiom Business Book award gold medal-begins with the unbroken string of successes that helped Paul achieve a jet-setting lifestyle and land a key spot with the Chicago Mercantile Exchange. It then describes the circumstances leading up to Paul&#8217;s $1.6 million loss and the essential lessons he learned from it-primarily that, although there are as many ways to make money in the markets as there are people participating in them, all losses come from the same few sources. Investors lose money in the markets either because of errors in their analysis or because of psychological barriers preventing the application of analysis.<br />
                    While all analytical methods have some validity and make allowances for instances in which they do not work, psychological factors can keep an investor in a losing position, causing him to abandon one method for another in order to rationalize the decisions already made. Paul and Moynihan&#8217;s cautionary tale includes strategies for avoiding loss tied to a simple framework for understanding, accepting, and dodging the dangers of investing, trading, and speculating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-i-learned-losing-a-million-dollars-jim-paul-brendan-moynihan-foreword-by-jack-schwager-abridged/">What I Learned Losing a Million Dollars &#8211; Jim Paul, Brendan Moynihan, Foreword by Jack Schwager (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
