<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Biography: Science Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/biography-science/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/biography-science/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Biography: Science Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/biography-science/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Chaos Monkeys : Inside the Silicon Valley Money Machine &#8211; Antonio Garcia Martinez</title>
		<link>/chaos-monkeys-inside-the-silicon-valley-money-machine-antonio-garcia-martinez/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chaos-monkeys-inside-the-silicon-valley-money-machine-antonio-garcia-martinez/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER An adrenaline-fuelled expose of life inside the tech bubble, Chaos Monkeys lays bare the secrets, power plays and lifestyle excesses of the visionaries, grunts, sociopaths, opportunists and money cowboys who are revolutionising our world. Written by startup CEO and industry provocateur Antonio Garcia Martinez, this is Liar&#8217;s Poker meets The Social [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chaos-monkeys-inside-the-silicon-valley-money-machine-antonio-garcia-martinez/">Chaos Monkeys : Inside the Silicon Valley Money Machine &#8211; Antonio Garcia Martinez</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    An adrenaline-fuelled expose of life inside the tech bubble, Chaos Monkeys lays bare the secrets, power plays and lifestyle excesses of the visionaries, grunts, sociopaths, opportunists and money cowboys who are revolutionising our world. Written by startup CEO and industry provocateur Antonio Garcia Martinez, this is Liar&#8217;s Poker meets The Social Network. </p>
<p>                    Computer engineers use &#8216;chaos monkey&#8217; software to wreak havoc and test system robustness. Similarly, tech entrepreneurs like Antonio Garcia Martinez are society&#8217;s chaos monkeys &#8211; their innovations disrupt every aspect of our lives, from transportation (Uber) and holidays (Airbnb) to television (Netflix) and dating (Tinder) &#8211; all in search of the perfect business miracle.  </p>
<p>                    Describing himself as &#8216;high-strung, fast-talking, and wired on a combination of caffeine, fear, and greed at all times&#8217;, Garcia Martinez left Wall Street to make his fortune in Silicon Valley, becoming CEO of his own startup, before bailing and being poached by Facebook&#8217;s nascent advertising team. Here he turned users&#8217; data into profit for COO Sheryl Sandberg and chairman and CEO Mark &#8216;Zuck&#8217; Zuckerberg. Forced out of Facebook in the wake of a bitter internal product war, Garcia Martinez  took his unique brand of entrepreneurial hyperactivity to rivals Twitter. Along the way, he got into a lot of trouble with a lot of people, brewed illegal beer on the Facebook campus (accidentally flooding Zuckerberg&#8217;s desk), lived on a yacht, raced sport cars on the highway, and enthusiastically pursued the lifestyle of an overpaid Silicon Valley mercenary.</p>
<p>                    In Chaos Monkeys he tells you HOW &#8211; and HOW NOT &#8211; to make a fortune through startups and digital marketing.  Highly entertaining and always offering genuine insight, Garcia Martinez  unravels the chaotic evolution of social media and online marketing. From startups and credit derivatives to Big Brother and data tracking, social media monetisation and digital &#8216;privacy&#8217;, he shares both his scathing observations and outrageous antics, taking us on a subversive and very funny tour of the fascinatingly insular and unbelievably wealthy tech industry.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chaos-monkeys-inside-the-silicon-valley-money-machine-antonio-garcia-martinez/">Chaos Monkeys : Inside the Silicon Valley Money Machine &#8211; Antonio Garcia Martinez</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hidden Valley Road &#8211; Robert Kolker</title>
		<link>/hidden-valley-road-robert-kolker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hidden-valley-road-robert-kolker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unforgettable&#8217; The Times &#8216;Grippingly told and brilliantly reported&#8217; Mail on Sunday &#8216;Startlingly intimate&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;Groundbreaking&#8217; Evening Standard &#8216;Exceptional and moving&#8217; Spectator &#8216;Hidden Valley Road contains everything: scientific intrigue, meticulous reporting, startling revelations, and, most of all, a profound sense of humanity. It is that rare book that can be read again [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hidden-valley-road-robert-kolker/">Hidden Valley Road &#8211; Robert Kolker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unforgettable&#8217; The Times &#8216;Grippingly told and brilliantly reported&#8217; Mail on Sunday &#8216;Startlingly intimate&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;Fascinating&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;Groundbreaking&#8217; Evening Standard &#8216;Exceptional and moving&#8217; Spectator &#8216;Hidden Valley Road contains everything: scientific intrigue, meticulous reporting, startling revelations, and, most of all, a profound sense of humanity. It is that rare book that can be read again and again.&#8217; -David Grann, author of Killers of the Flower Moon One of the New York Times&#8217; &#8217;20 most anticipated books of 2020&#8242;: the heartrending story of a mid-century American family with twelve children, six of them diagnosed with schizophrenia, that became science&#8217;s great hope in the quest to understand the disease. &#8216;An extraordinary case study and tour de force of reporting.&#8217; -Sylvia Nasar, author of A Beautiful Mind Don and Mimi Galvin seemed to be living the American dream. After World War II, Don&#8217;s work with the Air Force brought them to Colorado, where their twelve children perfectly spanned the baby boom: the oldest born in 1945, the youngest in 1965. In those years, there was an established script for a family like the Galvins &#8211; aspiration, hard work, upward mobility, domestic harmony &#8211; and they worked hard to play their parts. But behind the scenes was a different story: psychological breakdown, sudden shocking violence, hidden abuse. By the mid-1970s, six of the ten Galvin boys, one after the other, were diagnosed as schizophrenic. How could all this happen to one family? What took place inside the house on Hidden Valley Road was so extraordinary that the Galvins became one of the first families to be studied by the National Institutes of Mental Health. Their story offers a shadow history of the science of schizophrenia, from the era of institutionalization, lobotomy, and the schizophrenogenic mother, to the search for genetic markers for the disease, always amidst profound disagreements about the nature of the illness itself. And unbeknownst to the Galvins, samples of their DNA informed decades of genetic research that continues today, offering paths to treatment, prediction, and even eradication of the disease for future generations. With clarity and compassion, bestselling and award-winning author Robert Kolker uncovers one family&#8217;s unforgettable legacy of suffering, love and hope. &#8216;This book tore my heart out. It is a revelation-about the history of mental health treatment, about trauma, foremost about family-and a more-than-worthy follow-up to Robert Kolker&#8217;s brilliant Lost Girls.&#8217; -Megan Abbott, Edgar Award-winning author of Dare Me and Give Me Your Hand</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hidden-valley-road-robert-kolker/">Hidden Valley Road &#8211; Robert Kolker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Just Breathe : My Journey Through Cancer and Back &#8211; Stephen Graham King</title>
		<link>/just-breathe-my-journey-through-cancer-and-back-stephen-graham-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/just-breathe-my-journey-through-cancer-and-back-stephen-graham-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the year 2000, Stephen Graham King was diagnosed with a rare, aggressive cancer known as synovial sarcoma, beginning a four-year ordeal of radiation, chemotherapy, physiotherapy, and multiple recurrences. After having trouble with his left knee for much of his adult life, King finally saw a doctor following a bump to the leg that almost [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/just-breathe-my-journey-through-cancer-and-back-stephen-graham-king/">Just Breathe : My Journey Through Cancer and Back &#8211; Stephen Graham King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the year 2000, Stephen Graham King was diagnosed with a rare, aggressive cancer known as synovial sarcoma, beginning a four-year ordeal of radiation, chemotherapy, physiotherapy, and multiple recurrences.    </p>
<p>                     After having trouble with his left knee for much of his adult life, King finally saw a doctor following a bump to the leg that almost made him pass out from the excruciating pain. After the diagnosis, he endured five major, invasive surgeries that cost him a large portion of his left leg and half of his left lung, radically changing his body, mind, and self-image forever. And in the end, forcing him to relearn many things: some as basic as re-learning how to walk.    </p>
<p>                     As a gay man who is part of an image-conscious subculture within our image-driven society, he was forced to confront his feelings about his body on the long road back to health.    </p>
<p>                     Now, in Just Breathe, King shares his journey from health to illness and back to health again through prose and journal entries written during the battle. Told with candour and humour, this is the story of his challenging recovery and the love of life, friends, and family that helped him to survive.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/just-breathe-my-journey-through-cancer-and-back-stephen-graham-king/">Just Breathe : My Journey Through Cancer and Back &#8211; Stephen Graham King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Right Stuff &#8211; Tom Wolfe</title>
		<link>/the-right-stuff-tom-wolfe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aerospace & Aviation Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aircraft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Astronomy & Space]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Space Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-right-stuff-tom-wolfe/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A wildly vivid and entertaining chronicle of America&#8217;s manned space program, from the author of The Electric Kool-Aid Acid Test `What is it&#8217; asks Tom Wolfe, `that makes a man willing to sit on top of an enormous Roman Candle&#8230;and wait for someone to light the fuse?&#8217; Arrogance? Stupidity? Bravery? Courage? Or, simply, that quality [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-right-stuff-tom-wolfe/">The Right Stuff &#8211; Tom Wolfe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A wildly vivid and entertaining chronicle of America&#8217;s manned space program, from the author of The Electric Kool-Aid Acid Test    </p>
<p>                    `What is it&#8217; asks Tom Wolfe, `that makes a man willing to sit on top of an enormous Roman Candle&#8230;and wait for someone to light the fuse?&#8217; Arrogance? Stupidity? Bravery? Courage? Or, simply, that quality we call &#8216;the right stuff&#8217;?    </p>
<p>                    A monument to the men who battled to beat the Russians into space, The Right Stuff is a voyage into the mythology of the American space program, and a dizzying dive into the sweat, fear, beauty and danger of being on the white-hot edge of history in the making.    </p>
<p>                    `Tom Wolfe at his very best&#8230; Learned, cheeky, risky, touching, tough, compassionate, nostalgic, worshipful, jingoistic&#8230;The Right Stuff is superb&#8217; &#8211; New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-right-stuff-tom-wolfe/">The Right Stuff &#8211; Tom Wolfe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Soul of a New Machine &#8211; Tracy Kidder</title>
		<link>/the-soul-of-a-new-machine-tracy-kidder/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-soul-of-a-new-machine-tracy-kidder/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tracy Kidder&#8217;s &#8220;riveting&#8221; (Washington Post) story of one company&#8217;s efforts to bring a new microcomputer to market won both the Pulitzer Prize and the National Book Award and has become essential reading for understanding the history of the American tech industry. Computers have changed since 1981, when The Soul of a New Machine first examined [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-soul-of-a-new-machine-tracy-kidder/">The Soul of a New Machine &#8211; Tracy Kidder</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tracy Kidder&#8217;s &#8220;riveting&#8221; (Washington Post) story of one company&#8217;s efforts to bring a new microcomputer to market won both the Pulitzer Prize and the National Book Award and has become essential reading for understanding the history of the American tech industry.  Computers have changed since 1981, when The Soul of a New Machine first examined the culture of the computer revolution. What has not changed is the feverish pace of the high-tech industry, the go-for-broke approach to business that has caused so many computer companies to win big (or go belly up), and the cult of pursuing mind-bending technological innovations.<br />
                    The Soul of a New Machine is an essential chapter in the history of the machine that revolutionized the world in the twentieth century. &#8220;Fascinating&#8230;A surprisingly gripping account of people at work.&#8221; &#8211;Wall Street Journal    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-soul-of-a-new-machine-tracy-kidder/">The Soul of a New Machine &#8211; Tracy Kidder</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</title>
		<link>/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Distributive Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Services Law & Regulation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online Finance & Investing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stocks & Shares]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review Jim Simons is the greatest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES AND SUNDAY TIMES BUSINESS BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                                    &#8216;Reads more like a delicious page-turning novel&#8230;Put it on your holiday gift list for your favourite hedge-fund honcho&#8217; Bloomberg</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling read&#8217; Economist</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Captivating&#8217; New York Times book review</p>
<p>                    Jim Simons is the greatest moneymaker in modern financial history. His record bests those of legendary investors, including Warren Buffett, George Soros and Ray Dalio. Yet Simons and his strategies are shrouded in mystery. The financial industry has long craved a look inside Simons&#8217;s secretive hedge fund, Renaissance Technologies and veteran Wall Street Journal reporter Gregory Zuckerman delivers the goods.</p>
<p>                    After a legendary career as a mathematician and a stint breaking Soviet codes, Simons set out to conquer financial markets with a radical approach. Simons hired physicists, mathematicians and computer scientists &#8211; most of whom knew little about finance &#8211; to amass piles of data and build algorithms hunting for the deeply hidden patterns in global markets. Experts scoffed, but Simons and his colleagues became some of the richest in the world, their strategy of creating mathematical models and crunching data embraced by almost every industry today.</p>
<p>                    As Renaissance became a major player in the financial world, its executives began exerting influence on other areas. Simons became a major force in scientific research, education and Democratic politics, funding Hilary Clinton&#8217;s presidential campaign. While senior executive Robert Mercer is more responsible than anyone else for the Trump presidency &#8211; he placed Steve Bannon in the campaign, funded Trump&#8217;s victorious 2016 effort and backed alt-right publication Breitbart. Mercer also impacted the success of the Brexit campaign as he made significant investments in Cambridge Anatlytica. For all his prescience, Simons failed to anticipate how Mercer&#8217;s activity would impact his firm and the world.</p>
<p>                    In this fast-paced narrative, Zuckerman examines how Simons launched a quantitative revolution on Wall Street, and reveals the impact that Simons, the quiet billionaire king of the quants, has had on worlds well beyond finance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-man-who-solved-the-market-how-jim-simons-launched-the-quant-revolution-shortlisted-for-the-ft-mckinsey-business-book-of-the-year-award-2019-gregory-zuckerman/">The Man Who Solved the Market : How Jim Simons Launched the Quant Revolution SHORTLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 &#8211; Gregory Zuckerman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Change Your Mind : What the New Science of Psychedelics Teaches Us About Consciousness, Dying, Addiction, Depression, and Transcendence &#8211; Michael Pollan</title>
		<link>/how-to-change-your-mind-what-the-new-science-of-psychedelics-teaches-us-about-consciousness-dying-addiction-depression-and-transcendence-michael-pollan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Body]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pain & Pain Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-change-your-mind-what-the-new-science-of-psychedelics-teaches-us-about-consciousness-dying-addiction-depression-and-transcendence-michael-pollan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Pollan keeps you turning the pages . . . cleareyed and assured.&#8221; -New York Times A #1 New York Times Bestseller, New York Times Book Review 10 Best Books of 2018, and New York Times Notable Book A brilliant and brave investigation into the medical and scientific revolution taking place around psychedelic drugs&#8211;and the spellbinding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-change-your-mind-what-the-new-science-of-psychedelics-teaches-us-about-consciousness-dying-addiction-depression-and-transcendence-michael-pollan/">How to Change Your Mind : What the New Science of Psychedelics Teaches Us About Consciousness, Dying, Addiction, Depression, and Transcendence &#8211; Michael Pollan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Pollan keeps you turning the pages . . . cleareyed and assured.&#8221; -New York Times</p>
<p>A #1 New York Times Bestseller, New York Times Book Review 10 Best Books of 2018, and New York Times Notable Book</p>
<p>A brilliant and brave investigation into the medical and scientific revolution taking place around psychedelic drugs&#8211;and the spellbinding story of his own life-changing psychedelic experiences</p>
<p>When Michael Pollan set out to research how LSD and psilocybin (the active ingredient in magic mushrooms) are being used to provide relief to people suffering from difficult-to-treat conditions such as depression, addiction and anxiety, he did not intend to write what is undoubtedly his most personal book. But upon discovering how these remarkable substances are improving the lives not only of the mentally ill but also of healthy people coming to grips with the challenges of everyday life, he decided to explore the landscape of the mind in the first person as well as the third. Thus began a singular adventure into various altered states of consciousness, along with a dive deep into both the latest brain science and the thriving underground community of psychedelic therapists.  Pollan sifts the historical record to separate the truth about these mysterious drugs from the myths that have surrounded them since the 1960s, when a handful of psychedelic evangelists inadvertently catalyzed a powerful backlash against what was then a promising field of research.</p>
<p>A unique and elegant blend of science, memoir, travel writing, history, and medicine, How to Change Your Mind is a triumph of participatory journalism. By turns dazzling and edifying, it is the gripping account of a journey to an exciting and unexpected new frontier in our understanding of the mind, the self, and our place in the world. The true subject of Pollan&#8217;s &#8220;mental travelogue&#8221; is not just psychedelic drugs but also the eternal puzzle of human consciousness and how, in a world that offers us both suffering and joy, we can do our best to be fully present and find meaning in our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-change-your-mind-what-the-new-science-of-psychedelics-teaches-us-about-consciousness-dying-addiction-depression-and-transcendence-michael-pollan/">How to Change Your Mind : What the New Science of Psychedelics Teaches Us About Consciousness, Dying, Addiction, Depression, and Transcendence &#8211; Michael Pollan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
