<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Fiction In Translation Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/fiction-in-translation/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/fiction-in-translation/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Fiction In Translation Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/fiction-in-translation/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Angel&#8217;s Game : The Cemetery of Forgotten Books 2 &#8211; Carlos Ruiz Zafón</title>
		<link>/the-angels-game-the-cemetery-of-forgotten-books-2-carlos-ruiz-zafon/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Antiques & Collectables: Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ephemera & Printed Matter]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction In Translation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historical Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manuscripts]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-angels-game-the-cemetery-of-forgotten-books-2-carlos-ruiz-zafon/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The stunning new novel from the internationally bestselling author of THE SHADOW OF THE WIND. In an abandoned mansion at the heart of Barcelona, a young man &#8211; David Martin &#8211; makes his living by writing sensationalist novels under a pseudonym. The survivor of a troubled childhood, he has taken refuge in the world of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-angels-game-the-cemetery-of-forgotten-books-2-carlos-ruiz-zafon/">The Angel&#8217;s Game : The Cemetery of Forgotten Books 2 &#8211; Carlos Ruiz Zafón</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The stunning new novel from the internationally bestselling author of THE SHADOW OF THE WIND.    </p>
<p>                    In an abandoned mansion at the heart of Barcelona, a young man &#8211; David Martin &#8211; makes his living by writing sensationalist novels under a pseudonym. The survivor of a troubled childhood, he has taken refuge in the world of books, and spends his nights spinning baroque tales about the city&#8217;s underworld. But perhaps his dark imaginings are not as strange as they seem, for in a locked room deep within the house letters hinting at the mysterious death of the previous owner. Like a slow poison, the history of the place seeps into his bones as he struggles with an impossible love.     </p>
<p>                    Then David receives the offer of a lifetime: he is to write a book with the power to change hearts and minds. In return, he will receive a fortune, perhaps more. But as David begins the work, he realises that there is a connection between this haunting book and the shadows that surround his home&#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-angels-game-the-cemetery-of-forgotten-books-2-carlos-ruiz-zafon/">The Angel&#8217;s Game : The Cemetery of Forgotten Books 2 &#8211; Carlos Ruiz Zafón</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Before the Coffee Gets Cold &#8211; Toshikazu Kawaguchi</title>
		<link>/before-the-coffee-gets-cold-toshikazu-kawaguchi/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction In Translation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/before-the-coffee-gets-cold-toshikazu-kawaguchi/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What would you change if you could go back in time? In a small back alley in Tokyo, there is a cafe which has been serving carefully brewed coffee for more than one hundred years. But this coffee shop offers its customers a unique experience: the chance to travel back in time. In Before the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/before-the-coffee-gets-cold-toshikazu-kawaguchi/">Before the Coffee Gets Cold &#8211; Toshikazu Kawaguchi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What would you change if you could go back in time?</p>
<p>                    In a small back alley in Tokyo, there is a cafe which has been serving carefully brewed coffee for more than one hundred years. But this coffee shop offers its customers a unique experience: the chance to travel back in time.</p>
<p>                    In Before the Coffee Gets Cold, we meet four visitors, each of whom is hoping to make use of the cafe&#8217;s time-travelling offer, in order to: confront the man who left them, receive a letter from their husband whose memory has been taken by early onset Alzheimer&#8217;s, to see their sister one last time, and to meet the daughter they never got the chance to know.</p>
<p>                    But the journey into the past does not come without risks: customers must sit in a particular seat, they cannot leave the cafe, and finally, they must return to the present before the coffee gets cold . . .  </p>
<p>                    Toshikazu Kawaguchi&#8217;s beautiful, moving story &#8211; translated from Japanese by Geoffrey Trousselot &#8211; explores the age-old question: what would you change if you could travel back in time? More importantly, who would you want to meet, maybe for one last time?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/before-the-coffee-gets-cold-toshikazu-kawaguchi/">Before the Coffee Gets Cold &#8211; Toshikazu Kawaguchi</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Der Wüstenplanet &#8211; Great Schools of Dune 01. Der Thron des Wüstenplaneten &#8211; Brian Herbert</title>
		<link>/der-wustenplanet-great-schools-of-dune-01-der-thron-des-wustenplaneten-brian-herbert/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction In Translation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/der-wustenplanet-great-schools-of-dune-01-der-thron-des-wustenplaneten-brian-herbert/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Der Aufstieg der Bene Gesserit Vor dreiundachtzig Jahren wurden die Maschinen in der großen Schlacht von Corrin vernichtend geschlagen. Vor dreiundachtzig Jahren ernannte sich Faykan Butler zum Imperator des neuen, Planeten umspannenden Menschenreichs, und vor dreiundachtzig Jahren verschwand der große Kriegsheld Vorian Atreides. Inzwischen sitzt Faykans Nachfahre Salvador Corrin auf dem Thron des Sternenreiches, doch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/der-wustenplanet-great-schools-of-dune-01-der-thron-des-wustenplaneten-brian-herbert/">Der Wüstenplanet &#8211; Great Schools of Dune 01. Der Thron des Wüstenplaneten &#8211; Brian Herbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Der Aufstieg der Bene Gesserit    </p>
<p>                    Vor dreiundachtzig Jahren wurden die Maschinen in der großen Schlacht von Corrin vernichtend geschlagen. Vor dreiundachtzig Jahren ernannte sich Faykan Butler zum Imperator des neuen, Planeten umspannenden Menschenreichs, und vor dreiundachtzig Jahren verschwand der große Kriegsheld Vorian Atreides. Inzwischen sitzt Faykans Nachfahre Salvador Corrin auf dem Thron des Sternenreiches, doch von Frieden kann man noch lange nicht sprechen: Vorians Feinde sind noch immer auf der Suche nach ihm; technologiefeindliche, fanatische Gruppen führen immer wieder Säuberungsaktionen durch und geheimnisvolle Mächte greifen nach der Vorherrschaft in der Galaxis. Eine davon ist der sagenumwobene Orden der Schwesternschaft der Bene Gesserit, die im Schutz des Dschungelplaneten Rossak eine Intrige schmieden, die das Schicksal der gesamten Menschheit für immer verändern könnte &#8230;    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/der-wustenplanet-great-schools-of-dune-01-der-thron-des-wustenplaneten-brian-herbert/">Der Wüstenplanet &#8211; Great Schools of Dune 01. Der Thron des Wüstenplaneten &#8211; Brian Herbert</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truth About the Harry Quebert Affair : The million-copy bestselling sensation &#8211; Joel Dicker</title>
		<link>/the-truth-about-the-harry-quebert-affair-the-million-copy-bestselling-sensation-joel-dicker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction In Translation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truth-about-the-harry-quebert-affair-the-million-copy-bestselling-sensation-joel-dicker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>August 30, 1975. The day of the disappearance. The day Somerset, New Hampshire, lost its innocence. That summer, struggling author Harry Quebert fell in love with fifteen-year-old Nola Kellergan. Thirty-three years later, her body is dug up from his yard, along with a manuscript copy of the novel that made him a household name. Quebert [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-the-harry-quebert-affair-the-million-copy-bestselling-sensation-joel-dicker/">The Truth About the Harry Quebert Affair : The million-copy bestselling sensation &#8211; Joel Dicker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>August 30, 1975. The day of the disappearance. The day Somerset, New Hampshire, lost its innocence.     </p>
<p>                    That summer, struggling author Harry Quebert fell in love with fifteen-year-old Nola Kellergan. Thirty-three years later, her body is dug up from his yard, along with a manuscript copy of the novel that made him a household name. Quebert is the only suspect.     </p>
<p>                    Marcus Goldman &#8211; Quebert&#8217;s most gifted protege &#8211; throws off his writer&#8217;s block to clear his mentor&#8217;s name. Solving the case and penning a new bestseller soon merge into one. As his book begins to take on a life of its own, the nation is gripped by the mystery of &#8216;The Girl Who Touched the Heart of America&#8217;.     </p>
<p>                    But with Nola, in death as in life, nothing is ever as it seems.    </p>
<p>                    The Baltimore Boys, a following up to the bestselling The Truth about the Harry Quebert Affair, is available now.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-about-the-harry-quebert-affair-the-million-copy-bestselling-sensation-joel-dicker/">The Truth About the Harry Quebert Affair : The million-copy bestselling sensation &#8211; Joel Dicker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Three-Body Problem &#8211; Cixin Liu</title>
		<link>/the-three-body-problem-cixin-liu/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fantasy Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction In Translation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-three-body-problem-cixin-liu/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Read the award-winning, critically acclaimed, multi-million-copy-selling science-fiction phenomenon &#8211; soon to be a Netflix Original Series from the creators of Game of Thrones. 1967: Ye Wenjie witnesses Red Guards beat her father to death during China&#8217;s Cultural Revolution. This singular event will shape not only the rest of her life but also the future of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-three-body-problem-cixin-liu/">The Three-Body Problem &#8211; Cixin Liu</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Read the award-winning, critically acclaimed, multi-million-copy-selling science-fiction phenomenon &#8211; soon to be a Netflix Original Series from the creators of Game of Thrones. 1967: Ye Wenjie witnesses Red Guards beat her father to death during China&#8217;s Cultural Revolution. This singular event will shape not only the rest of her life but also the future of mankind.</p>
<p>                    Four decades later, Beijing police ask nanotech engineer Wang Miao to infiltrate a secretive cabal of scientists after a spate of inexplicable suicides. Wang&#8217;s investigation will lead him to a mysterious online game and immerse him in a virtual world ruled by the intractable and unpredictable interaction of its three suns.</p>
<p>                    This is the Three-Body Problem and it is the key to everything: the key to the scientists&#8217; deaths, the key to a conspiracy that spans light-years and the key to the extinction-level threat humanity now faces.</p>
<p>                    Praise for The Three-Body Problem: &#8216;Your next favourite sci-fi novel&#8217; Wired<br />
                    &#8216;Immense&#8217; Barack Obama<br />
                    &#8216;Unique&#8217; George R.R. Martin<br />
                    &#8216;SF in the grand style&#8217; Guardian<br />
                    &#8216;Mind-altering and immersive&#8217; Daily Mail<br />
                    Winner of the Hugo and Galaxy Awards for Best Novel</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-three-body-problem-cixin-liu/">The Three-Body Problem &#8211; Cixin Liu</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Six Four : the bestselling Japanese crime sensation &#8211; Hideo Yokoyama</title>
		<link>/six-four-the-bestselling-japanese-crime-sensation-hideo-yokoyama/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fiction In Translation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thriller Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thrillers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/six-four-the-bestselling-japanese-crime-sensation-hideo-yokoyama/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This novel is a real, out-of-the-blue original. I&#8217;ve never read anything like it&#8217; New York Times Book Review THE MILLION-SELLING JAPANESE CRIME PHENOMENON, NOW A UK BESTSELLER. SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2016 CWA INTERNATIONAL DAGGER. NAMED IN NEW YORK TIMES 100 NOTABLE BOOKS OF 2017. SIX FOUR. THE NIGHTMARE NO PARENT COULD ENDURE. THE CASE NO [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/six-four-the-bestselling-japanese-crime-sensation-hideo-yokoyama/">Six Four : the bestselling Japanese crime sensation &#8211; Hideo Yokoyama</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This novel is a real, out-of-the-blue original. I&#8217;ve never read anything like it&#8217;<br />
New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>THE MILLION-SELLING JAPANESE CRIME PHENOMENON, NOW A UK BESTSELLER.<br />
SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2016 CWA INTERNATIONAL DAGGER.<br />
NAMED IN NEW YORK TIMES 100 NOTABLE BOOKS OF 2017.</p>
<p>SIX FOUR.<br />
THE NIGHTMARE NO PARENT COULD ENDURE.<br />
THE CASE NO DETECTIVE COULD SOLVE.<br />
THE TWIST NO READER COULD PREDICT.</p>
<p>For five days in January 1989, the parents of a seven-year-old Tokyo schoolgirl sat and listened to the demands of their daughter&#8217;s kidnapper. They would never learn his identity. They would never see their daughter again.</p>
<p>For the fourteen years that followed, the Japanese public listened to the police&#8217;s apologies. They would never forget the botched investigation that became known as &#8216;Six Four&#8217;. They would never forgive the authorities their failure.</p>
<p>For one week in late 2002, the press officer attached to the police department in question confronted an anomaly in the case. He could never imagine what he would uncover. He would never have looked if he&#8217;d known what he would find.</p>
<p>Loved Six Four and want more Yokoyama? Then why not try Seventeen or Prefecture D . . .</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/six-four-the-bestselling-japanese-crime-sensation-hideo-yokoyama/">Six Four : the bestselling Japanese crime sensation &#8211; Hideo Yokoyama</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
