<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Food &amp; Drink Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/food-drink/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/food-drink/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Food &amp; Drink Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/food-drink/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History: Specific Events & Topics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Fascinating Tour Through the Evolution of the Human Diet and How We Can Improve Our Health by Understanding Our Complicated History with Food    </p>
<p>                    There are few areas of modern life that are burdened by as much information and advice, often contradictory, as our diet and health: eat a lot of meat, eat no meat; whole grains are healthy, whole grains are a disaster; eat everything in moderation; eat only certain foods&#8212;and on and on. In 100 Million Years of Food, biological anthropologist Stephen Le explains how cuisines of different cultures are a result of centuries of evolution, finely tuned to our biology and surroundings. Today many cultures have strayed from their ancestral diets, relying instead on mass-produced food often made with chemicals that may be contributing to a rise in so-called Western diseases, such as cancer, heart disease, and obesity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/100-million-years-of-food-what-our-ancestors-ate-and-why-it-matters-today-stephen-le-abridged/">100 Million Years of Food : What Our Ancestors Ate and Why it Matters Today &#8211; Stephen Le (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A must-read for anyone interested in food and the future&#8217; Yotam Ottolenghi Based on ten years of surveying farming communities around the world, top New York chef Dan Barber&#8217;s The Third Plate offers a radical new way of thinking about food that will heal the land and taste incredible. The &#8216;first plate&#8217; was a classic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/">The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A must-read for anyone interested in food and the future&#8217; Yotam Ottolenghi    </p>
<p>                    Based on ten years of surveying farming communities around the world, top New York chef Dan Barber&#8217;s The Third Plate offers a radical new way of thinking about food that will heal the land and taste incredible.    </p>
<p>                     The &#8216;first plate&#8217; was a classic meal centred on a large cut of meat with few vegetables. On the &#8216;second plate&#8217;, championed by the farm-to-table movement, meat is free-range and vegetables are locally sourced. It&#8217;s better-tasting, and better for the planet, but the second plate&#8217;s architecture is identical to that of the first. It, too, disrupts ecological balances, causing soil depletion and nutrient loss &#8211; it just isn&#8217;t a sustainable way to farm or eat.    </p>
<p>                     The &#8216;third plate&#8217; offers a solution: an integrated system of vegetable, cereal and livestock production that is fully supported &#8211; in fact, dictated &#8211; by what we choose to cook for dinner. The Third Plate is where good farming and good food intersect.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/">The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Heat Salt, Fat, Acid &#8211; Samin Nosrat (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery By Ingredient]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National & Regional Cuisine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now a Netflix series! New York Times Bestseller and Winner of the 2018 James Beard Award for Best General Cookbook and multiple IACP Cookbook Awards Named one of the Best Books of 2017 by: NPR, BuzzFeed, The Atlantic, The Washington Post, Chicago Tribune, Rachel Ray Every Day, San Francisco Chronicle, Vice Munchies, Elle.com, Glamour, Eater, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/">Heat Salt, Fat, Acid &#8211; Samin Nosrat (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now a Netflix series!     </p>
<p>                     New York Times Bestseller and Winner of the 2018 James Beard Award for Best General Cookbook and multiple IACP Cookbook Awards      </p>
<p>                     Named one of the Best Books of 2017 by: NPR, BuzzFeed, The Atlantic, The Washington Post, Chicago Tribune, Rachel Ray Every Day, San Francisco Chronicle, Vice Munchies, Elle.com, Glamour, Eater, Newsday, Minneapolis Star Tribune,  The Seattle Times, Tampa Bay Times, Tasting Table, Modern Farmer, Publishers Weekly,  and more.     </p>
<p>                     A visionary new master class in cooking that distills decades of professional experience into just four simple elements, from the woman declared &#8220;America&#8217;s next great cooking teacher&#8221; by Alice Waters.     </p>
<p>                    In the tradition of The Joy of Cooking and How to Cook Everything comes Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat, an ambitious new approach to cooking by a major new culinary voice. Chef and writer Samin Nosrat has taught everyone from professional chefs to middle school kids to author Michael Pollan to cook using her revolutionary, yet simple, philosophy. Master the use of just four elements&#8211;Salt, which enhances flavor; Fat, which delivers flavor and generates texture; Acid, which balances flavor; and Heat, which ultimately determines the texture of food&#8211;and anything you cook will be delicious. By explaining the hows and whys of good cooking, Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat will teach and inspire a new generation of cooks how to confidently make better decisions in the kitchen and cook delicious meals with any ingredients, anywhere, at any time.     </p>
<p>                    Echoing Samin&#8217;s own journey from culinary novice to award-winning chef, Salt, Fat Acid, Heat immediately bridges the gap between home and professional kitchens. With charming narrative, illustrated walkthroughs, and a lighthearted approach to kitchen science, Samin demystifies the four elements of good cooking for everyone. Refer to the canon of 100 essential recipes&#8211;and dozens of variations&#8211;to put the lessons into practice and make bright, balanced vinaigrettes, perfectly caramelized roast vegetables, tender braised meats, and light, flaky pastry doughs.     </p>
<p>                    Featuring 150 illustrations and infographics that reveal an atlas to the world of flavor by renowned illustrator Wendy MacNaughton, Salt, Fat, Acid, Heat will be your compass in the kitchen. Destined to be a classic, it just might be the last cookbook you&#8217;ll ever need.     </p>
<p>                    With a foreword by Michael Pollan.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/heat-salt-fat-acid-samin-nosrat-abridged/">Heat Salt, Fat, Acid &#8211; Samin Nosrat (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Way We Eat Now : Strategies for Eating in a World of Change &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-way-we-eat-now-strategies-for-eating-in-a-world-of-change-bee-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-way-we-eat-now-strategies-for-eating-in-a-world-of-change-bee-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We never snacked like this and we never binged like this. We never had so many superfoods, or so many chips. We were never quite so confused about food, and what it actually is. This is a book about the good, the terrible and the avocado toast. A riveting exploration of the hidden forces behind [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-way-we-eat-now-strategies-for-eating-in-a-world-of-change-bee-wilson-abridged/">The Way We Eat Now : Strategies for Eating in a World of Change &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We never snacked like this and we never binged like this. We never had so many superfoods, or so many chips. We were never quite so confused about food, and what it actually is.    </p>
<p>                              This is a book about the good, the terrible and the avocado toast. A riveting exploration of the hidden forces behind what we eat, The Way We Eat Now explains how modern food, in all its complexity, has transformed our lives and our world. To re-establish eating as something that gives us both joy and health, we need to find out where we are right now, how we got here and what it is that we share.    </p>
<p>                              Award-winning food writer Bee Wilson explores everything from meal replacements such as Huel, the disappearing lunch hour, the rise of veganism, the lack of time to cook and prepare food and the rapid increase in food delivery services. And Bee provides her own doable strategies for how we might navigate the many options available to us to have a balanced, happier relationship with the food we eat.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-way-we-eat-now-strategies-for-eating-in-a-world-of-change-bee-wilson-abridged/">The Way We Eat Now : Strategies for Eating in a World of Change &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma : The Search for a Perfect Meal in a Fast-Food World (reissued) &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What shall we have for dinner? Such a simple question has grown to have a very complicated answer. We can eat almost anything nature has to offer, but deciding what we should eat stirs anxiety. Should we choose the organic apple or the conventional? If organic, local or imported? Wild fish or farmed? Low-carb or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/">The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma : The Search for a Perfect Meal in a Fast-Food World (reissued) &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What shall we have for dinner? Such a simple question has grown to have a very complicated answer. We can eat almost anything nature has to offer, but deciding what we should eat stirs anxiety. Should we choose the organic apple or the conventional? If organic, local or imported? Wild fish or farmed? Low-carb or low-cal? As the American culture of fast food and unlimited choice invades the world, Pollan follows his next meal from land to table, tracing the origin of everything consumed and the implications for ourselves and our planet. His astonishing findings will shock all who care about what they put on their plate.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-omnivores-dilemma-the-search-for-a-perfect-meal-in-a-fast-food-world-reissued-michael-pollan-abridged/">The Omnivore&#8217;s Dilemma : The Search for a Perfect Meal in a Fast-Food World (reissued) &#8211; Michael Pollan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cork Dork : A Wine-Fuelled Journey into the Art of Sommeliers and the Science of Taste &#8211; Bianca Bosker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cork-dork-a-wine-fuelled-journey-into-the-art-of-sommeliers-and-the-science-of-taste-bianca-bosker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alcoholic Beverages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Beverages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gardening: Growing Fruit & Vegetables]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wines]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cork-dork-a-wine-fuelled-journey-into-the-art-of-sommeliers-and-the-science-of-taste-bianca-bosker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Professional journalist and amateur drinker Bianca Bosker didn&#8217;t know much about wine &#8211; until she discovered the world of elite sommeliers who dedicate their lives to the pursuit of flavour. Astounded by their fervour and seemingly superhuman sensory powers, she set out to uncover what drove their obsession, and whether she, too, could become a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cork-dork-a-wine-fuelled-journey-into-the-art-of-sommeliers-and-the-science-of-taste-bianca-bosker-abridged/">Cork Dork : A Wine-Fuelled Journey into the Art of Sommeliers and the Science of Taste &#8211; Bianca Bosker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Professional journalist and amateur drinker Bianca Bosker didn&#8217;t know much about wine &#8211; until she discovered the world of elite sommeliers who dedicate their lives to the pursuit of flavour. Astounded by their fervour and seemingly superhuman sensory powers, she set out to uncover what drove their obsession, and whether she, too, could become a &#8216;cork dork.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    With boundless curiosity, humour and a healthy dose of scepticism, Bosker takes the reader inside underground tasting groups, exclusive New York City restaurants, California mass-market wine factories and even a neuroscientist&#8217;s fMRI machine as she attempts to answer the most nagging question of all: what&#8217;s the big deal about wine?     </p>
<p>                    Funny, counterintuitive and compulsively readable, Cork Dork not only illuminates wine production and consumption, but also shows how cultivating our taste buds can have enormous ramifications for both our brains and our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cork-dork-a-wine-fuelled-journey-into-the-art-of-sommeliers-and-the-science-of-taste-bianca-bosker-abridged/">Cork Dork : A Wine-Fuelled Journey into the Art of Sommeliers and the Science of Taste &#8211; Bianca Bosker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Bite : How We Learn to Eat &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cooking For/with Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cooking With Meat & Game]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fortnum &#038; Mason Food Book of the Year 2016 We are not born knowing what to eat; we each have to figure it out for ourselves. From childhood onwards, we learn how big a portion is and how sweet is too sweet. The way we learn to eat holds the key to why food has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/">First Bite : How We Learn to Eat &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fortnum &#038; Mason Food Book of the Year 2016    </p>
<p>                              We are not born knowing what to eat; we each have to figure it out for ourselves. From childhood onwards, we learn how big a portion is and how sweet is too sweet. The way we learn to eat holds the key to why food has gone so disastrously wrong for so many people. But how does this happen? And can we ever change our food habits for the better?    </p>
<p>                              An exploration of the extraordinary and surprising origins of our taste and eating habits, in First Bite award-winning food writer Bee Wilson explains how we can change our palates to lead healthier, happier lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-bite-how-we-learn-to-eat-bee-wilson-abridged/">First Bite : How We Learn to Eat &#8211; Bee Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bourbon Empire : The Past and Future of America&#8217;s Whiskey &#8211; Reid Mitenbuler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bourbon-empire-the-past-and-future-of-americas-whiskey-reid-mitenbuler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alcoholic Beverages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Beverages]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brewing Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Beverage Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bourbon-empire-the-past-and-future-of-americas-whiskey-reid-mitenbuler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Pulls aside the curtain of puffery to show . . . the business of liquor to be every bit as fascinating as the fictions in which the distillers love to swaddle themselves.&#8221; &#8211;Wayne Curtis, The Wall Street Journal Walk into a well-stocked liquor store and you&#8217;ll see countless whiskey brands, each boasting an inspiring story [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bourbon-empire-the-past-and-future-of-americas-whiskey-reid-mitenbuler-abridged/">Bourbon Empire : The Past and Future of America&#8217;s Whiskey &#8211; Reid Mitenbuler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Pulls aside the curtain of puffery to show . . . the business of liquor to be every bit as fascinating as the fictions in which the distillers love to swaddle themselves.&#8221; &#8211;Wayne Curtis, The Wall Street Journal     </p>
<p>                     Walk into a well-stocked liquor store and you&#8217;ll see countless whiskey brands, each boasting an inspiring story of independence and heritage. And yet, more than 95% of the nation&#8217;s whiskey comes from a small handful of giant companies with links to organized crime, political controversy, and a colorful history that is far different than what appears on modern labels. In Bourbon Empire, Reid Mitenbuler shows how bourbon, America&#8217;s most iconic style of whiskey, and the industry surrounding it, really came to be&#8211;a saga of shrewd capitalism as well as dedicated craftsmanship.     </p>
<p>                     Mitenbuler traces the big names&#8211;Jim Beam, Maker&#8217;s Mark, Evan Williams, and more&#8211;back to their origins, exploring bourbon&#8217;s founding myths and great successes against the backdrop of America&#8217;s economic history. Illusion is separated from reality in a tale reaching back to the Whiskey Rebellion of 1794, when the ideologies of Thomas Jefferson and Alexander Hamilton battled to define the soul of American business. That debate continues today, punctuated along the way by Prohibition-era bootleggers, the liquor-fueled origins of NASCAR, intense consolidation driven by savvy lobbying, and a Madison Avenue plot to release five thousand parrots&#8211;trained to screech the name of a popular brand&#8211;into the nation&#8217;s bars.     </p>
<p>                     Today, the whiskey business takes a new turn as a nascent craft distilling movement offers the potential to revolutionize the industry once again. But, as Mitenbuler shows, many take advantage of this excitement while employing questionable business practices, either by masquerading whiskey made elsewhere as their own or by shortcutting the proven production standards that made many historic brands great to begin with.     </p>
<p>                     A tale of innovation, success, downfall, and resurrection, Bourbon Empire is an exploration of the spirit in all its unique forms, creating an indelible portrait of both American whiskey and the people who make it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bourbon-empire-the-past-and-future-of-americas-whiskey-reid-mitenbuler-abridged/">Bourbon Empire : The Past and Future of America&#8217;s Whiskey &#8211; Reid Mitenbuler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lesser Beasts : A Snout-to-Tail History of the Humble Pig &#8211; Mark Essig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/lesser-beasts-a-snout-to-tail-history-of-the-humble-pig-mark-essig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Husbandry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Mammals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology: Mammals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/lesser-beasts-a-snout-to-tail-history-of-the-humble-pig-mark-essig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unlike other barnyard animals, which pull plows, give eggs or milk, or grow wool, a pig produces only one thing: meat. Incredibly efficient at converting almost any organic matter into nourishing, delectable protein, swine are nothing short of a gastronomic godsend,yet their flesh is banned in many cultures, and the animals themselves are maligned as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lesser-beasts-a-snout-to-tail-history-of-the-humble-pig-mark-essig-abridged/">Lesser Beasts : A Snout-to-Tail History of the Humble Pig &#8211; Mark Essig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unlike other barnyard animals, which pull plows, give eggs or milk, or grow wool, a pig produces only one thing: meat. Incredibly efficient at converting almost any organic matter into nourishing, delectable protein, swine are nothing short of a gastronomic godsend,yet their flesh is banned in many cultures, and the animals themselves are maligned as filthy, lazy brutes.As historian Mark Essig reveals in  Lesser Beasts , swine have such a bad reputation for precisely the same reasons they are so valuable as a source of food: they are intelligent, self-sufficient, and omnivorous. What&#8217;s more, he argues, we ignore our historic partnership with these astonishing animals at our peril. Tracing the interplay of pig biology and human culture from Neolithic villages 10,000 years ago to modern industrial farms, Essig blends culinary and natural history to demonstrate the vast importance of the pig and the tragedy of its modern treatment at the hands of humans. Pork, Essig explains, has long been a staple of the human diet, prized in societies from Ancient Rome to dynastic China to the contemporary American South. Yet pigs&#8217; ability to track down and eat a wide range of substances (some of them distinctly unpalatable to humans) and convert them into edible meat has also led people throughout history to demonize the entire species as craven and unclean. Today&#8217;s unconscionable system of factory farming, Essig explains, is only the latest instance of humans taking pigs for granted, and the most recent evidence of how both pigs and people suffer when our symbiotic relationship falls out of balance.An expansive, illuminating history of one of our most vital yet unsung food animals,  Lesser Beasts  turns a spotlight on the humble creature that, perhaps more than any other, has been a mainstay of civilization since its very beginnings,whether we like it or not.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/lesser-beasts-a-snout-to-tail-history-of-the-humble-pig-mark-essig-abridged/">Lesser Beasts : A Snout-to-Tail History of the Humble Pig &#8211; Mark Essig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Salt &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Property & Real Estate]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rocks, Minerals & Fossils]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Homer called it a divine substance. Plato described it as especially dear to the gods. As Mark Kurlansky so brilliantly relates here, salt has shaped civilisation from the beginning, and its story is a glittering, often surprising part of the history of mankind. Wars have been fought over salt and, while salt taxes secured empires [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/">Salt &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Homer called it a divine substance. Plato described it as especially dear to the gods. As Mark Kurlansky so brilliantly relates here, salt has shaped civilisation from the beginning, and its story is a glittering, often surprising part of the history of mankind. Wars have been fought over salt and, while salt taxes secured empires across Europe and Asia, they have also inspired revolution &#8211; Gandhi&#8217;s salt march in 1930 began the overthrow of British rule in India.     </p>
<p>                    From the rural Sichuan province where the last home-made soya sauce is produced to the Cheshire brine springs that supplied salt around the globe, Mark Kurlansky has produced a kaleidoscope of world history, a multi-layered masterpiece that blends political, commercial, scientific, religious and culinary records into a rich and memorable tale.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/salt-mark-kurlansky-abridged/">Salt &#8211; Mark Kurlansky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Since his New York Times op-ed column debuted in 2011, Mark Bittman has emerged as one of our most impassioned and opinionated observers of the food landscape. The Times&#8217; only dedicated opinion columnist covering the food beat, Bittman routinely makes readers think twice about how the food we eat is produced, distributed, and cooked, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/">A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Since his New York Times op-ed column debuted in 2011, Mark Bittman has emerged as one of our most impassioned and opinionated observers of the food landscape. The Times&#8217; only dedicated opinion columnist covering the food beat, Bittman routinely makes readers think twice about how the food we eat is produced, distributed, and cooked, and shines a bright light on the profound impact that diet&#8211;both good and bad&#8211;can have on our health and that of the planet.     </p>
<p>                     In A Bone to Pick, Mark&#8217;s most memorable and thought-provoking columns are compiled into a single volume for the first time. As abundant and safe as the American food supply appears to be, the state of our health reveals the presence of staggering deficiencies in both the system that produces food and the forces that regulate it. Bittman leaves no issue unexamined; agricultural practices, government legislation, fad diets, and corporate greed all come under scrutiny and show that the issues governing what ends up in our market basket and on our tables are both complex and often deliberately confusing. Unabashedly opinionated and invariably thought provoking, Bittman&#8217;s columns have helped readers decipher arcane policy, unpack scientific studies, and deflate affronts to common sense when it comes to determining what &#8220;eating well&#8221; truly means. As urgent as the situation is, Mark contends that we can be optimistic about the future of our food and its impact on our health, as slow-food movements, better school-lunch programs, and even &#8220;healthy fast food&#8221; become part of the norm.     </p>
<p>                     At once inspiring, enraging, and enlightening, A Bone to Pick is an essential resource for every reader eager to understand not only the complexities inherent in the American food system, but also the many opportunities that exist to improve it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-bone-to-pick-the-good-and-bad-news-about-food-with-wisdom-and-advice-on-diets-food-safety-gmos-farming-and-more-mark-bittman-abridged/">A Bone to Pick : The good and bad news about food, with wisdom and advice on diets, food safety, GMOs, farming, and more &#8211; Mark Bittman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book. Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book.     </p>
<p>                    Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. Why suffer from disease and ill health when the right food is proven to keep you healthy, and without the side effects of drugs? We can avoid heart disease, cancer and our other biggest killers if we use food as medicine, and the How Not To Die Cookbook offers a sustainable and delicious guide to preparing and eating the foods that will prevent and reverse fatal diseases.    </p>
<p>                    Featuring over 100 easy-to-follow, beautifully photographed plant-based recipes, with plenty of recipes suitable for vegetarians and vegans, the How Not To Die Cookbook merges cutting-edge science with everyday ingredients from the supermarket to help you and your family eat your way to better health and a longer life.    </p>
<p>                    All recipes in this cookbook have been fully anglicized.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cooking Up a Business : Lessons from Food Lovers Who Turned Their Passion into a Career &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Rachel Hofstetter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food Manufacturing & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Stories and advice for creating a business out of the food you love. Do you have a passion for delicious food and want to create your own business out of it, but have no idea where to start? Cooking Up a Business is essential reading for aspiring entrepreneurs and gives you a real-world, up-close-and-personal preview [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/">Cooking Up a Business : Lessons from Food Lovers Who Turned Their Passion into a Career &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Rachel Hofstetter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Stories and advice for creating a business out of the food you love.      </p>
<p>                    Do you have a passion for delicious food and want to create your own business out of it, but have no idea where to start? Cooking Up a Business is essential reading for aspiring entrepreneurs and gives you a real-world, up-close-and-personal preview of the exciting journey. Through profiles and interviews with nationally known food entrepreneurs from Popchips, Vosges Haut-Chocolat, Hint Water, Mary&#8217;s Gone Crackers, Love Grown Foods, Kopali Organics, Tasty, Evol, Justin&#8217;s Nut Butters, Cameron Hughes Wine, and more, you will gain applicable, practical guidance that teaches you how to succeed today:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; How to create a national brand&#8211;with no connections or experience<br />
                    &#8211; The secret to getting meetings with grocery store buyers<br />
                    &#8211; The number one thing you need to know about food safety regulations<br />
                    &#8211; Why a grassroots budget might actually help you succeed<br />
                    &#8211; Specific advice for gluten-free, organic, wine, and beverage companies<br />
                    &#8211; What every entrepreneur wishes someone had told them at the beginning &#8211; Why doing what you love is always a good idea</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cooking-up-a-business-lessons-from-food-lovers-who-turned-their-passion-into-a-career-and-how-you-can-too-rachel-hofstetter-abridged/">Cooking Up a Business : Lessons from Food Lovers Who Turned Their Passion into a Career &#8211; and How You Can, Too &#8211; Rachel Hofstetter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author). We are in the grip of a food [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author).<br />
                       We are in the grip of a food crisis. Obesity has become a leading cause of preventable death, after only smoking. For nearly half a century we&#8217;ve been trying to pin the blame somewhere, fat, carbs, sugar, wheat, high-fructose corn syrup. But that search has been in vain, because the food problem that&#8217;s killing us is not a nutrient problem. It&#8217;s a behavioural problem, and it&#8217;s caused by the changing flavour of the food we eat.<br />
                       Ever since the 1940s, with the rise of industrialized food production, we have been gradually leeching the taste out of what we grow. Simultaneously, we have taken great leaps forward in technology, creating a flavour industry, worth billions annually; in an attempt to put back the tastes we&#8217;ve engineered out of our food. The result is a cuisine that increasingly resembles the paragon of flavour manipulation: Doritos. As food becomes increasingly bland, we dress it up with calories and flavour chemicals to make it delicious again. We have rewired our palates and our brains, and the results are making us sick and killing us.<br />
                       With in-depth historical and scientific research, The Dorito Effect casts the food crisis in a fascinating new light, weaving an enthralling tale of how we got to this point and where we are headed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Life, on the Line : A Chef&#8217;s Story of Chasing Greatness, Facing Death, and Redefining the Way We Eat &#8211; Grant Achatz, Nick Kokonas (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-on-the-line-a-chefs-story-of-chasing-greatness-facing-death-and-redefining-the-way-we-eat-grant-achatz-nick-kokonas-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hotel & Catering Trades]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-on-the-line-a-chefs-story-of-chasing-greatness-facing-death-and-redefining-the-way-we-eat-grant-achatz-nick-kokonas-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of America&#8217;s great chefs&#8221; (Vogue), Grant Achatz, shares how his drive to cook immaculate food fueled his miraculous triumph over tongue cancer. By 2007 chef Grant Achatz had been named one of the best new chefs in America by Food &#038; Wine, he had received the James Beard Foundation Rising Star Chef of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-on-the-line-a-chefs-story-of-chasing-greatness-facing-death-and-redefining-the-way-we-eat-grant-achatz-nick-kokonas-abridged/">Life, on the Line : A Chef&#8217;s Story of Chasing Greatness, Facing Death, and Redefining the Way We Eat &#8211; Grant Achatz, Nick Kokonas (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;One of America&#8217;s great chefs&#8221; (Vogue), Grant Achatz, shares how his drive to cook immaculate food fueled his miraculous triumph over tongue cancer.     </p>
<p>                    By 2007 chef Grant Achatz had been named one of the best new chefs in America by Food &#038; Wine, he had received the James Beard Foundation Rising Star Chef of the Year Award, and he and Nick Kokonas had opened the conceptually radical restaurant Alinea, which was named Best Restaurant in America by Gourmet magazine. Then, positioned firmly in the world&#8217;s culinary spotlight, Achatz was diagnosed with stage IV squamous cell carcinoma-tongue cancer.    </p>
<p>                    The prognosis grim, Grant undertook an alternative treatment of aggressive chemotherapy and radiation that ravaged his body and left him without a sense of taste. Tapping into his profound discipline and passion, he trained his chefs to mimic his palate and learned how to cook with his other senses. As Kokonas was able to attest, the food was never better. Five months later, Grant was declared cancer-free and went on to achieve some of the highest honors in the culinary world. Life, on the Line is not only a chef&#8217;s memoir, it is also a book about survival, about nurturing creativity, and about profound friendship.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-on-the-line-a-chefs-story-of-chasing-greatness-facing-death-and-redefining-the-way-we-eat-grant-achatz-nick-kokonas-abridged/">Life, on the Line : A Chef&#8217;s Story of Chasing Greatness, Facing Death, and Redefining the Way We Eat &#8211; Grant Achatz, Nick Kokonas (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
