<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Graphic Design Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/graphic-design/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/graphic-design/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Graphic Design Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/graphic-design/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Truth, Lies, and Advertising : The Art of Account Planning &#8211; Jon Steel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/truth-lies-and-advertising-the-art-of-account-planning-jon-steel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/truth-lies-and-advertising-the-art-of-account-planning-jon-steel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Account planning exists for the sole purpose of creating advertising that truly connects with consumers. While many in the industry are still dissecting consumer behavior, extrapolating demographic trends, developing complex behavioral models, and measuring Pavlovian salivary responses, Steel advocates an approach to consumer research that is based on simplicity, common sense, and creativity&#8211;an approach that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/truth-lies-and-advertising-the-art-of-account-planning-jon-steel-abridged/">Truth, Lies, and Advertising : The Art of Account Planning &#8211; Jon Steel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Account planning exists for the sole purpose of creating advertising that truly connects with consumers. While many in the industry are still dissecting consumer behavior, extrapolating demographic trends, developing complex behavioral models, and measuring Pavlovian salivary responses, Steel advocates an approach to consumer research that is based on simplicity, common sense, and creativity&#8211;an approach that gains access to consumers&#8217; hearts and minds, develops ongoing relationships with them, and, most important, embraces them as partners in the process of developing and advertising. A witty, erudite raconteur and teacher, Steel describes how successful account planners work in partnership with clients, consumer, and agency creatives. He criticizes research practices that, far from creating relationships, drive a wedge between agencies and the people they aim to persuade; he suggests new ways of approaching research to cut through the BS and get people to show their true selves; and he shows how the right research, when translated into a motivating and inspiring brief, can be the catalyst for great creative ideas.<br />
                    He draws upon his own experiences and those of colleagues in the United States and abroad to illustrate those points, and includes examples of some of the most successful campaigns in recent years, including Polaroid, Norwegian Cruise Line, Porsche, Isuzu, &#8220;got milk?&#8221; and others. The message of this book is that well-thought-out account planning results in better, more effective marketing and advertising for both agencies and clients. And also makes an evening in front of the television easier to bear for the population at large.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/truth-lies-and-advertising-the-art-of-account-planning-jon-steel-abridged/">Truth, Lies, and Advertising : The Art of Account Planning &#8211; Jon Steel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big : Kind of the Story of My Life &#8211; Scott Adams (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-kind-of-the-story-of-my-life-scott-adams-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Graphic Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-kind-of-the-story-of-my-life-scott-adams-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Blasting clichéd career advice, the contrarian pundit and creator of Dilbert recounts the humorous ups and downs of his career, revealing the outsized role of luck in our lives and how best to play the system. Scott Adams has likely failed at more things than anyone you&#8217;ve ever met or anyone you&#8217;ve even heard of. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-kind-of-the-story-of-my-life-scott-adams-abridged/">How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big : Kind of the Story of My Life &#8211; Scott Adams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Blasting clichéd career advice, the contrarian pundit and creator of Dilbert recounts the humorous ups and downs of his career, revealing the outsized role of luck in our lives and how best to play the system.      </p>
<p>                     Scott Adams has likely failed at more things than anyone you&#8217;ve ever met or anyone you&#8217;ve even heard of. So how did he go from hapless office worker and serial failure to the creator of Dilbert, one of the world&#8217;s most famous syndicated comic strips, in just a few years? In How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big, Adams shares the game plan he&#8217;s followed since he was a teen: invite failure in, embrace it, then pick its pocket.     </p>
<p>                     No career guide can offer advice that works for everyone. As Adams explains, your best bet is to study the ways of others who made it big and try to glean some tricks and strategies that make sense for you. Adams pulls back the covers on his own unusual life and shares how he turned one failure after another&#8211;including his corporate career, his inventions, his investments, and his two restaurants&#8211;into something good and lasting. There&#8217;s a lot to learn from his personal story, and a lot of entertainment along the way. Adams discovered some unlikely truths that helped to propel him forward. For instance:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Goals are for losers. Systems are for winners.<br />
                     &#8211; &#8220;Passion&#8221; is bull. What you need is personal energy.<br />
                     &#8211; A combination of mediocre skills can make you surprisingly valuable.<br />
                     &#8211; You can manage your odds in a way that makes you look lucky to others.     </p>
<p>                     Adams hopes you can laugh at his failures while discovering some unique and helpful ideas on your own path to personal victory. As he writes: &#8220;This is a story of one person&#8217;s unlikely success within the context of scores of embarrassing failures. Was my eventual success primarily a result of talent, luck, hard work, or an accidental just-right balance of each? All I know for sure is that I pursued a conscious strategy of managing my opportunities in a way that would make it easier for luck to find me.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-fail-at-almost-everything-and-still-win-big-kind-of-the-story-of-my-life-scott-adams-abridged/">How to Fail at Almost Everything and Still Win Big : Kind of the Story of My Life &#8211; Scott Adams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
