<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Diseases &amp; Disorders Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/diseases-disorders/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/diseases-disorders/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Diseases &amp; Disorders Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/diseases-disorders/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epidemiology & Medical Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Infectious & Contagious Diseases]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than three hundred infectious diseases have emerged or reemerged in new territory during the past fifty years, and ninety percent of epidemiologists expect that one of them will cause a disruptive, deadly pandemic sometime in the next two generations. To reveal how that might happen, Sonia Shah tracks each stage of cholera&#8217;s dramatic journey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/">Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than three hundred infectious diseases have emerged or reemerged in new territory during the past fifty years, and ninety percent of epidemiologists expect that one of them will cause a disruptive, deadly pandemic sometime in the next two generations. To reveal how that might happen, Sonia Shah tracks each stage of cholera&#8217;s dramatic journey from harmless microbe to world-changing pandemic, from its 1817 emergence in the South Asian hinterlands to its rapid dispersal across the nineteenth-century world and its latest beachhead in Haiti. She reports on the pathogens following in cholera&#8217;s footsteps, from the MRSA bacterium that besieges her own family to the never-before-seen killers emerging from China&#8217;s wet markets, the surgical wards of New Delhi, the slums of Port-au-Prince, and the suburban backyards of the East Coast. A deep-dive into the convoluted science, strange politics, and checkered history of one of the world&#8217;s deadliest diseases, Pandemic reveals what the next epidemic might look like&#8211;and what we can do to prevent it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandemic-tracking-contagions-from-cholera-to-ebola-and-beyond-sonia-shah-abridged/">Pandemic : Tracking Contagions, from Cholera to Ebola and Beyond &#8211; Sonia Shah (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Administration & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Equipment & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nursing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Telemedicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy & Therapeutics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A trip to the doctor is almost a guarantee of misery. You&#8217;ll make an appointment months in advance. You&#8217;ll probably wait for several hours until you hear &#8220;the doctor will see you now&#8221;,but only for fifteen minutes! Then you&#8217;ll wait even longer for lab tests, the results of which you&#8217;ll likely never see, unless they [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/">The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A trip to the doctor is almost a guarantee of misery. You&#8217;ll make an appointment months in advance. You&#8217;ll probably wait for several hours until you hear &#8220;the doctor will see you now&#8221;,but only for fifteen minutes! Then you&#8217;ll wait even longer for lab tests, the results of which you&#8217;ll likely never see, unless they indicate further (and more invasive) tests, most of which will probably prove unnecessary (much like physicals themselves). And your bill will be astronomical.In  The Patient Will See You Now , Eric Topol, one of the nation&#8217;s top physicians, shows why medicine does not have to be that way. Instead, you could use your smartphone to get rapid test results from one drop of blood, monitor your vital signs both day and night, and use an artificially intelligent algorithm to receive a diagnosis without having to see a doctor, all at a small fraction of the cost imposed by our modern healthcare system. The change is powered by what Topol calls medicine&#8217;s &#8220;Gutenberg moment.&#8221; Much as the printing press took learning out of the hands of a priestly class, the mobile internet is doing the same for medicine, giving us unprecedented control over our healthcare. With smartphones in hand, we are no longer beholden to an impersonal and paternalistic system in which &#8220;doctor knows best.&#8221; Medicine has been digitized, Topol argues now it will be democratized. Computers will replace physicians for many diagnostic tasks, citizen science will give rise to citizen medicine, and enormous data sets will give us new means to attack conditions that have long been incurable. Massive, open, online medicine, where diagnostics are done by Facebook-like comparisons of medical profiles, will enable real-time, real-world research on massive populations. There&#8217;s no doubt the path forward will be complicated: the medical establishment will resist these changes, and digitized medicine inevitably raises serious issues surrounding privacy. Nevertheless, the result,better, cheaper, and more human health care,will be worth it.Provocative and engrossing,  The Patient Will See You Now  is essential reading for anyone who thinks they deserve better health care. That is, for all of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/">The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; By the pioneer of lifestyle medicine, a simple, scientifically program proven to often reverse the progression of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level! Long rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report, Dr. Ornish&#8217;s Program is now covered by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/">Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; By the pioneer of lifestyle medicine, a simple, scientifically program proven to often reverse the progression of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level! Long rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report,  Dr. Ornish&#8217;s Program is now covered by Medicare when offered virtually at home.     </p>
<p>                     Dean Ornish, M.D., has directed revolutionary research proving, for the first time, that lifestyle changes can often reverse&#8211;undo!&#8211;the progression of many of the most common and costly chronic diseases and even begin reversing aging at a cellular level.     </p>
<p>                     Medicare and many insurance companies now cover Dr. Ornish&#8217;s lifestyle medicine program for reversing chronic disease because it consistently achieves bigger changes in lifestyle, better clinical outcomes, larger cost savings, and greater adherence than have ever been reported&#8211;based on forty years of research published in the leading peer-reviewed medical and scientific journals.     </p>
<p>                     Now, in this landmark book, he and Anne Ornish present a simple yet powerful new unifying theory explaining why these same lifestyle changes can reverse so many different chronic diseases and how quickly these benefits occur. They describe what it is, why it works, and how you can do it:     </p>
<p>                     &#8211; Eat well a whole foods, plant-based diet naturally low in fat and sugar and high in flavor. The &#8220;Ornish diet&#8221; has been rated &#8220;#1 for Heart Health&#8221; by U.S. News &#038; World Report for eleven years since 2011.<br />
                     &#8211; Move more moderate exercise such as walking<br />
                     &#8211; Stress less including meditation and gentle yoga practices<br />
                     &#8211; Love more how love and intimacy transform loneliness into healing     </p>
<p>                    With seventy recipes, easy-to-follow meal plans, tips for stocking your kitchen and eating out, recommended exercises, stress-reduction advice, and inspiring patient stories of life-transforming benefits&#8211;for example, several people improved so much after only nine weeks they were able to avoid a heart transplant&#8211;Undo It! empowers readers with new hope and new choices.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Undo It!     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The Ornishes&#8217; work is elegant and simple and deserving of a Nobel Prize, since it can change the world!&#8221;&#8211;Richard Carmona, M.D., MPH, FACS, seventeenth Surgeon General of the United States     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;If you want to see what medicine will be like ten years from now, read this book today.&#8221;&#8211;Rita F. Redberg, M.D., editor in chief, JAMA Internal Medicine     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This is one of the most important books on health ever written.&#8221;&#8211;John Mackey, CEO, Whole Foods Market</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/undo-it-how-simple-lifestyle-changes-can-reverse-most-chronic-diseases-dean-ornish-md-abridged/">Undo It! : How Simple Lifestyle Changes Can Reverse Most Chronic Diseases &#8211; Dean Ornish, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Plant Paradox : The Hidden Dangers in &#8220;Healthy&#8221; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dr. Gundry is a true trailblazer, always at the forefront of scientific knowledge. The Plant Paradox shows the world what pioneer thinking is about and is a must-read book for anyone interested in being as healthy as nature has designed them to be.&#8221; -Alejandro Junger MD, New York Times bestselling author of Clean, Clean Gut [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Plant Paradox : The Hidden Dangers in &#8220;Healthy&#8221; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Dr. Gundry is a true trailblazer, always at the forefront of scientific knowledge. The Plant Paradox shows the world what pioneer thinking is about and is a must-read book for anyone interested in being as healthy as nature has designed them to be.&#8221; -Alejandro Junger MD, New York Times bestselling author of Clean, Clean Gut and Clean Eats  &#8220;The Plant Paradox elegantly explains how plants defend themselves from being consumed by humans, and how eating the wrong ones at the wrong times immeasurably hurts our health. An eye-opening read.&#8221; -Mehmet Oz, MD, Professor of Surgery, New York Presbyterian/Columbia University  Most of us have heard of gluten-a protein found in wheat that causes widespread inflammation in the body. Americans spend billions of dollars on gluten-free diets in an effort to protect their health. But what if we&#8217;ve been missing the root of the problem? In The Plant Paradox, renowned cardiologist Dr. Steven Gundry reveals that gluten is just one variety of a common, and highly toxic, plant-based protein called lectin.<br />
                    Lectins are found not only in grains like wheat but also in the &#8220;gluten-free&#8221; foods most of us commonly regard as healthy, including many fruits, vegetables, nuts, beans, and conventional dairy products. These proteins, which are found in the seeds, grains, skins, rinds, and leaves of plants, are designed by nature to protect them from predators (including humans). Once ingested, they incite a kind of chemical warfare in our bodies, causing inflammatory reactions that can lead to weight gain and serious health conditions.  At his waitlist-only clinics in California, Dr. Gundry has successfully treated tens of thousands of patients suffering from autoimmune disorders, diabetes, leaky gut syndrome, heart disease, and neurodegenerative diseases with a protocol that detoxes the cells, repairs the gut, and nourishes the body. Now, in The Plant Paradox, he shares this clinically proven program with readers around the world.  The simple (and daunting) fact is, lectins are everywhere. Thankfully, Dr. Gundry offers simple hacks we easily can employ to avoid them, including: * Peel your veggies.<br />
                    Most of the lectins are contained in the skin and seeds of plants; simply peeling and de-seeding vegetables (like tomatoes and peppers) reduces their lectin content.* Shop for fruit in season. Fruit contain fewer lectins when ripe, so eating apples, berries, and other lectin-containing fruits at the peak of ripeness helps minimize your lectin consumption.* Swap your brown rice for white. Whole grains and seeds with hard outer coatings are designed by nature to cause digestive distress-and are full of lectins. With a full list of lectin-containing foods and simple substitutes for each, a step-by-step detox and eating plan, and delicious lectin-free recipes, The Plant Paradox illuminates the hidden dangers lurking in your salad bowl-and shows you how to eat whole foods in a whole new way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-plant-paradox-the-hidden-dangers-in-healthy-foods-that-cause-disease-and-weight-gain-dr-steven-r-gundry-md-abridged/">The Plant Paradox : The Hidden Dangers in &#8220;Healthy&#8221; Foods That Cause Disease and Weight Gain &#8211; Dr. Steven R Gundry, MD (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Vegetarian Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book. Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the author of the global bestseller How Not To Die comes The How Not To Die Cookbook &#8211; a lavish, beautifully illustrated collection of delicious recipes based on the groundbreaking nutritional science of the original book.     </p>
<p>                    Dr Michael Greger, founder of the wildly popular website NutritionFacts, takes his comprehensive, lifesaving science into the kitchen. Why suffer from disease and ill health when the right food is proven to keep you healthy, and without the side effects of drugs? We can avoid heart disease, cancer and our other biggest killers if we use food as medicine, and the How Not To Die Cookbook offers a sustainable and delicious guide to preparing and eating the foods that will prevent and reverse fatal diseases.    </p>
<p>                    Featuring over 100 easy-to-follow, beautifully photographed plant-based recipes, with plenty of recipes suitable for vegetarians and vegans, the How Not To Die Cookbook merges cutting-edge science with everyday ingredients from the supermarket to help you and your family eat your way to better health and a longer life.    </p>
<p>                    All recipes in this cookbook have been fully anglicized.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-how-not-to-die-cookbook-over-100-recipes-to-help-prevent-and-reverse-disease-michael-greger-with-gene-stone-abridged/">The How Not to Die Cookbook : Over 100 Recipes to Help Prevent and Reverse Disease &#8211; Michael Greger, With Gene Stone (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of Illness &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling work that overturns conventional conceptions of health and illness to offer new methods for increasing vital longevity. CAN WE LIVE ROBUSTLY UNTIL OUR LAST BREATH? Do we have to suffer from debilitating conditions and sickness? Is it possible to add more vibrant years to our lives? In the #1 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/">The End of Illness &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling work that overturns conventional conceptions of health and illness to offer new methods for increasing vital longevity. CAN WE LIVE ROBUSTLY UNTIL OUR LAST BREATH? Do we have to suffer from debilitating conditions and sickness? Is it possible to add more vibrant years to our lives? In the #1 New York Times bestselling The End of Illness, Dr. David Agus tackles these fundamental questions and dismantles misperceptions about what &#8220;health&#8221; really means. Presenting an eye-opening picture of the human body and all the ways it works&#8211;and fails&#8211;Dr. Agus shows us how a new perspective on our individual health will allow us to achieve a long, vigorous life. Offering insights and access to powerful new technologies that promise to transform medicine, Dr. Agus emphasizes his belief that there is no &#8220;right&#8221; answer, no master guide that is &#8220;one size fits all.&#8221; Each one of us must get to know our bodies in uniquely personal ways, and he shows us exactly how to do that. A bold call for all of us to become our own personal health advocates, The End of Illness is a moving departure from orthodox thinking.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/">The End of Illness &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Diabetes Code : Prevent and Reverse Type 2 Diabetes Naturally &#8211; Dr. Jason Fung, Foreword by Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diabetes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FROM NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR DR. JASON FUNG * &#8220;The doctor who invented intermittent fasting.&#8221;-The Daily Mail &#8220;Dr. Fung reveals how [type 2 diabetes] can be prevented and also reversed using natural dietary methods instead of medications &#8230; This is an important and timely book. Highly recommended.&#8221;-Dr. Mark Hyman, author of The Pegan Diet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Diabetes Code : Prevent and Reverse Type 2 Diabetes Naturally &#8211; Dr. Jason Fung, Foreword by Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FROM NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLING AUTHOR DR. JASON FUNG * &#8220;The doctor who invented intermittent fasting.&#8221;-The Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Dr. Fung reveals how [type 2 diabetes] can be prevented and also reversed using natural dietary methods instead of medications &#8230; This is an important and timely book. Highly recommended.&#8221;-Dr. Mark Hyman, author of The Pegan Diet    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Dr. Jason Fung has done it again. &#8230; Get this book!&#8221;-Dr. Steven R. Gundry, author of The Plant Paradox    </p>
<p>                    Everything you believe about treating type 2 diabetes is wrong. Today, most doctors, dietitians, and even diabetes specialists consider type 2 diabetes to be a chronic and progressive disease-a life sentence with no possibility of parole. But the truth, as Dr. Fung reveals in this groundbreaking book, is that type 2 diabetes is reversible.     </p>
<p>                    Writing with clear, persuasive language, Dr. Fung explains why conventional treatments that rely on insulin or other blood-glucose-lowering drugs can actually exacerbate the problem, leading to significant weight gain and even heart disease. The only way to treat type 2 diabetes effectively, he argues, is proper dieting and intermittent fasting-not medication.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The Diabetes Code is unabashedly provocative yet practical &#8230; a clear blueprint for everyone to take control of their blood sugar, their health, and their lives.&#8221;- Dr. Will Cole, author of Intuitive Fasting</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-diabetes-code-prevent-and-reverse-type-2-diabetes-naturally-dr-jason-fung-foreword-by-nina-teicholz-abridged/">The Diabetes Code : Prevent and Reverse Type 2 Diabetes Naturally &#8211; Dr. Jason Fung, Foreword by Nina Teicholz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
