<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Coping With Death &amp; Bereavement Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/coping-with-death-bereavement/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/coping-with-death-bereavement/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Coping With Death &amp; Bereavement Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/coping-with-death-bereavement/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Day John Died &#8211; Richard Poe</title>
		<link>/the-day-john-died-richard-poe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-day-john-died-richard-poe/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;People keep telling me I can be a great man. I&#8217;d rather be a good one.&#8221;-John F. Kennedy, Jr. Where were you the day John died? Like his father&#8217;s assassination and the death of Princess Diana, the tragic plane crash that took the life of JFK Jr. on July 16, 1999, is one of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-day-john-died-richard-poe/">The Day John Died &#8211; Richard Poe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;People keep telling me I can be a great man. I&#8217;d rather be a good one.&#8221;-John F. Kennedy, Jr. </p>
<p>                    Where were you the day John died? Like his father&#8217;s assassination and the death of Princess Diana, the tragic plane crash that took the life of JFK Jr. on July 16, 1999, is one of the defining moments of our lives &#8211; an event that moved us so deeply we will never forget where we were the day we heard the news. With good reason. No other American had lived his entire life in the spotlight &#8211; from his rambunctious toddlerhood in the Kennedy White House and heartbreaking salute to his father&#8217;s coffin to his daredevil Sexiest Man Alive bachelor days and his final years poised on the brink of fatherhood and a brilliant political career. </p>
<p>                    Now, in the manner of his other number one New York Times best seller The Day Diana Died, respected Kennedy family biographer Christopher Andersen makes The Day John Died available for the first time as an ebook. Andersen draws on important sources &#8211; many talking here for the first time &#8211; to recreate in vivid and startling detail the events leading up to that fateful night off the coast of Martha&#8217;s Vineyard. An inspiring, sympathetic, and compelling look at one of the most remarkable young men of our time, The Day John Died is more than just the definitive biography of JFK Jr. It is a bittersweet saga of triumph, love, loss, fate &#8211; and promise unfulfilled. It is the story of America&#8217;s son. </p>
<p>                    About the Author: Christopher Andersen is the critically acclaimed author of 18 New York Times best sellers, including six about the Kennedy family &#8211; Jack and Jackie, Jackie After Jack, The Day John Died, Sweet Caroline, These Few Precious Days, and The Good Son &#8211; as well as the No.1 international best seller The Day Diana Died. A former TIME Magazine contributing editor and senior editor of People, Andersen has also written for The New York Times, Life, Vanity Fair, and countless other publications.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-day-john-died-richard-poe/">The Day John Died &#8211; Richard Poe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Year of Magical Thinking &#8211; Joan Didion (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-year-of-magical-thinking-joan-didion-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-year-of-magical-thinking-joan-didion-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From one of America&#8217;s iconic writers, a portrait of a marriage and a life &#8211; in good times and bad &#8211; that will speak to anyone who has ever loved a husband or wife or child. A stunning book of electric honesty and passion. Several days before Christmas 2003, John Gregory Dunne and Joan Didion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-year-of-magical-thinking-joan-didion-abridged/">The Year of Magical Thinking &#8211; Joan Didion (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From one of America&#8217;s iconic writers, a portrait of a marriage and a life &#8211; in good times and bad &#8211; that will speak to anyone who has ever loved a husband or wife or child. A stunning book of electric honesty and passion.    </p>
<p>                              Several days before Christmas 2003, John Gregory Dunne and Joan Didion saw their only daughter, Quintana, fall ill. At first they thought it was flu, then pneumonia, then complete sceptic shock. She was put into an induced coma and placed on life support. Days later &#8211; the night before New Year&#8217;s Eve -the Dunnes were just sitting down to dinner after visiting the hospital when John suffered a massive and fatal coronary. In a second, this close, symbiotic partnership of 40 years was over. Four weeks later, their daughter pulled through. Two months after that, arriving at LA airport, she collapsed and underwent six hours of brain surgery at UCLA Medical Centre to relieve a massive hematoma.    </p>
<p>                              This powerful book is Didion&#8217;s &#8216;attempt to make sense of the weeks and then months that cut loose any fixed idea I ever had about death, about illness &#8230; about marriage and children and memory &#8230; about the shallowness of sanity, about life itself&#8217;. The result is an exploration of an intensely personal yet universal experience: a portrait of a marriage, and a life, in good times and bad.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-year-of-magical-thinking-joan-didion-abridged/">The Year of Magical Thinking &#8211; Joan Didion (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finding Chika : A heart-breaking and hopeful story about family, adversity and unconditional love &#8211; Mitch Albom (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adoption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth: Natural History General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chika Jeune was born three days before the devastating earthquake that decimated Haiti in 2010. She spent her infancy in extreme poverty, and when her mother died giving birth to a baby brother, Chika was brought to the Have Faith Haiti Orphanage that Mitch and his wife, Janine operate. Chika&#8217;s arrival made a quick impression. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/">Finding Chika : A heart-breaking and hopeful story about family, adversity and unconditional love &#8211; Mitch Albom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chika Jeune was born three days before the devastating earthquake that decimated Haiti in 2010. She spent her infancy in extreme poverty, and when her mother died giving birth to a baby brother, Chika was brought to the Have Faith Haiti Orphanage that Mitch and his wife, Janine operate.    </p>
<p>                    Chika&#8217;s arrival made a quick impression. Brave and self-assured, even as a three-year-old, she delighted the other kids and teachers. But at age five, Chika was suddenly diagnosed with a terminal disease that no doctor in Haiti could help with.    </p>
<p>                    Mitch and Janine took Chika to America, hoping that treatment there would enable her to go back home.  Instead, Chika became a permanent part of their lives, as they embarked on a two-year, around-the-world journey to find a cure. As Chika&#8217;s boundless optimism and humour taught Mitch the joys of caring for a child, he learnt that a relationship built on love, no matter what blows it takes, can never be lost.    </p>
<p>                    This is Mitch Albom at his most poignant, powerful and personal. Chika is a celebration of a girl, her adoptive guardians, and the incredible bond they formed &#8211; a devastatingly beautiful portrait of what it means to be a family, regardless of how it is made.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finding-chika-a-heart-breaking-and-hopeful-story-about-family-adversity-and-unconditional-love-mitch-albom-abridged/">Finding Chika : A heart-breaking and hopeful story about family, adversity and unconditional love &#8211; Mitch Albom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Unwinding of the Miracle : A Memoir of Life, Death, and Everything That Comes After &#8211; Julie Yip-Williams (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Read with Jenna Book Club Pick as Featured on Today &#8211; As a young mother facing a terminal diagnosis, Julie Yip-Williams began to write her story, a story like no other. What began as the chronicle of an imminent and early death became something much more&#8211;a powerful exhortation to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/">The Unwinding of the Miracle : A Memoir of Life, Death, and Everything That Comes After &#8211; Julie Yip-Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Read with Jenna Book Club Pick as Featured on Today &#8211; As a young mother facing a terminal diagnosis, Julie Yip-Williams began to write her story, a story like no other. What began as the chronicle of an imminent and early death became something much more&#8211;a powerful exhortation to the living.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;An exquisitely moving portrait of the daily stuff of life.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review (Editors&#8217; Choice) NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY The New York Times Book Review &#8211; Time &#8211; Real Simple &#8211; Good Housekeeping  That Julie Yip-Williams survived infancy was a miracle. Born blind in Vietnam, she narrowly escaped euthanasia at the hands of her grandmother, only to flee with her family the political upheaval of her country in the late 1970s. Loaded into a rickety boat with three hundred other refugees, Julie made it to Hong Kong and, ultimately, America, where a surgeon at UCLA gave her partial sight. She would go on to become a Harvard-educated lawyer, with a husband, a family, and a life she had once assumed would be impossible. Then, at age thirty-seven, with two little girls at home, Julie was diagnosed with terminal metastatic colon cancer, and a different journey began.  The Unwinding of the Miracle is the story of a vigorous life refracted through the prism of imminent death. When she was first diagnosed, Julie Yip-Williams sought clarity and guidance through the experience and, finding none, began to write her way through it&#8211;a chronicle that grew beyond her imagining. Motherhood, marriage, the immigrant experience, ambition, love, wanderlust, tennis, fortune-tellers, grief, reincarnation, jealousy, comfort, pain, the marvel of the body in full rebellion&#8211;this book is as sprawling and majestic as the life it records. It is inspiring and instructive, delightful and shattering. It is a book of indelible moments, seared deep&#8211;an incomparable guide to living vividly by facing hard truths consciously.  With humor, bracing honesty, and the cleansing power of well-deployed anger, Julie Yip-Williams set the stage for her lasting legacy and one final miracle: the story of her life. Praise for The Unwinding of the Miracle  &#8220;Everything worth understanding and holding on to is in this book. . . . A miracle indeed.&#8221;&#8211;Kelly Corrigan, New York Times bestselling author &#8220;A beautifully written, moving, and compassionate chronicle that deserves to be read and absorbed widely.&#8221;&#8211;Siddhartha Mukherjee, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Emperor of All Maladies</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-unwinding-of-the-miracle-a-memoir-of-life-death-and-everything-that-comes-after-julie-yip-williams-abridged/">The Unwinding of the Miracle : A Memoir of Life, Death, and Everything That Comes After &#8211; Julie Yip-Williams (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Beginner&#8217;s Guide to the End : Practical Advice for Living Life and Facing Death &#8211; Dr Bj Miller, Shoshana Berger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-beginners-guide-to-the-end-practical-advice-for-living-life-and-facing-death-dr-bj-miller-shoshana-berger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Household Hints]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-beginners-guide-to-the-end-practical-advice-for-living-life-and-facing-death-dr-bj-miller-shoshana-berger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gentle, knowledgeable guide to a fate we all share&#8221; (The Washington Post): the first and only all-encompassing action plan for the end of life. &#8220;There is nothing wrong with you for dying,&#8221; hospice physician B.J. Miller and journalist and caregiver Shoshana Berger write in A Beginner&#8217;s Guide to the End. &#8220;Our ultimate purpose here [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-beginners-guide-to-the-end-practical-advice-for-living-life-and-facing-death-dr-bj-miller-shoshana-berger-abridged/">A Beginner&#8217;s Guide to the End : Practical Advice for Living Life and Facing Death &#8211; Dr Bj Miller, Shoshana Berger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gentle, knowledgeable guide to a fate we all share&#8221; (The Washington Post): the first and only all-encompassing action plan for the end of life.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;There is nothing wrong with you for dying,&#8221; hospice physician B.J. Miller and journalist and caregiver Shoshana Berger write in A Beginner&#8217;s Guide to the End. &#8220;Our ultimate purpose here isn&#8217;t so much to help you die as it is to free up as much life as possible until you do.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                    Theirs is a clear-eyed and big-hearted action plan for approaching the end of life, written to help readers feel more in control of an experience that so often seems anything but controllable. Their book offers everything from step-by-step instructions for how to do your paperwork and navigate the healthcare system to answers to questions you might be afraid to ask your doctor, like whether or not sex is still okay when you&#8217;re sick. Get advice for how to break the news to your employer, whether to share old secrets with your family, how to face friends who might not be as empathetic as you&#8217;d hoped, and how to talk to your children about your will. (Don&#8217;t worry: if anyone gets snippy, it&#8217;ll likely be their spouses, not them.) There are also lessons for survivors, like how to shut down a loved one&#8217;s social media accounts, clean out the house, and write a great eulogy.     </p>
<p>                    An honest, surprising, and detail-oriented guide to the most universal of all experiences, A Beginner&#8217;s Guide to the End is &#8220;a book that every family should have, the equivalent of Dr. Spock but for this other phase of life&#8221; (New York Times bestselling author Dr. Abraham Verghese).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-beginners-guide-to-the-end-practical-advice-for-living-life-and-facing-death-dr-bj-miller-shoshana-berger-abridged/">A Beginner&#8217;s Guide to the End : Practical Advice for Living Life and Facing Death &#8211; Dr Bj Miller, Shoshana Berger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>With the End in Mind : How to Live and Die Well &#8211; Kathryn Mannix (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/with-the-end-in-mind-how-to-live-and-die-well-kathryn-mannix-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nursing & Ancillary Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Palliative Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/with-the-end-in-mind-how-to-live-and-die-well-kathryn-mannix-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Impossible to read with dry eyes or an unaltered mindset&#8217; Sunday Times &#8216;Illuminating and beautiful&#8217; Cathy Rentzenbrink What if everything you thought you knew about death was wrong? How should we prepare for the facts of dying and saying our goodbyes? And what if understanding death improved your life? By turns [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/with-the-end-in-mind-how-to-live-and-die-well-kathryn-mannix-abridged/">With the End in Mind : How to Live and Die Well &#8211; Kathryn Mannix (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Impossible to read with dry eyes or an unaltered mindset&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Illuminating and beautiful&#8217; Cathy Rentzenbrink    </p>
<p>                                What if everything you thought you knew about death was wrong?    </p>
<p>                                How should we prepare for the facts of dying and saying our goodbyes?    </p>
<p>                                And what if understanding death improved your life?    </p>
<p>                              By turns touching and tragic, funny and wise, With the End in Mind brings together Kathryn Mannix &#8216; s lifetime of medical experience to tell powerful stories of life and death.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/with-the-end-in-mind-how-to-live-and-die-well-kathryn-mannix-abridged/">With the End in Mind : How to Live and Die Well &#8211; Kathryn Mannix (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Death&#8217;s Summer Coat : What the History of Death and Dying Can Tell Us About Life and Living &#8211; Brandy Schillace (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/deaths-summer-coat-what-the-history-of-death-and-dying-can-tell-us-about-life-and-living-brandy-schillace-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Death & Dying]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deaths-summer-coat-what-the-history-of-death-and-dying-can-tell-us-about-life-and-living-brandy-schillace-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new conversation is starting on this most universal of topics. But to know where we are heading, we need to know where we have come from&#8230;Death is the one subject we will all confront; it touches our families, our homes, our hearts. And yet we have grown used to denying its existence, treating it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deaths-summer-coat-what-the-history-of-death-and-dying-can-tell-us-about-life-and-living-brandy-schillace-abridged/">Death&#8217;s Summer Coat : What the History of Death and Dying Can Tell Us About Life and Living &#8211; Brandy Schillace (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new conversation is starting on this most universal of topics. But to know where we are heading, we need to know where we have come from&#8230;Death is the one subject we will all confront; it touches our families, our homes, our hearts. And yet we have grown used to denying its existence, treating it as an enemy to be beaten back with medical advances. What led us to this point &#8211; what drove us to sanitize death and make it foreign and unfamiliar? In Death&#8217;s Summer Coat Brandy Schillace explores our past to examine what it might mean for our future. From Victorian Britain to contemporary Cambodia, forgotten customs and modern-day rituals, we learn about the incredibly diverse &#8211; and sometimes just incredible &#8211; ways in which humans have dealt with mortality in different times and places. Today, as we begin to talk about mortality, there are difficult questions to face. What does it mean to have a &#8216;good death&#8217;? What should a funeral do? As Schillace shows, talking about death and the rituals associated with it can help to provide answers. It also brings us closer together. And conversation and community are just as important for living as for dying.Some of the stories are strikingly unfamiliar; others are far more familiar than you might suppose.<br />
                    But all reveal a lot about the present &#8211; and about ourselves. It&#8217;s time to meet the new (old) death. As seen reviewed in The Guardian in the article Smoke Gets in Your Eyes by Caitlin Doughty review &#8211; startling stories from the crematorium. If you are keen to learn more, you can listen to the interview with Brandy Schillace on Radio Gorgeous or the interview on BBC Radio 4 Thinking Allowed, both to be aired in May 2015.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deaths-summer-coat-what-the-history-of-death-and-dying-can-tell-us-about-life-and-living-brandy-schillace-abridged/">Death&#8217;s Summer Coat : What the History of Death and Dying Can Tell Us About Life and Living &#8211; Brandy Schillace (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wherever You Go There You are &#8211; Jon Kabat-Zinn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-jon-kabat-zinn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Worship, Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-jon-kabat-zinn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>No matter how busy you are, find quiet reflective moments in your life&#8211;and reduce your stress levels drastically&#8211;with this classic bestselling guide from a mindfulness expert. When Wherever You Go, There You Are was first published in 1994, no one could have predicted that the book would launch itself onto bestseller lists nationwide and sell [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-jon-kabat-zinn-abridged/">Wherever You Go There You are &#8211; Jon Kabat-Zinn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No matter how busy you are, find quiet reflective moments in your life&#8211;and reduce your stress levels drastically&#8211;with this classic bestselling guide from a mindfulness expert. When Wherever You Go, There You Are was first published in 1994, no one could have predicted that the book would launch itself onto bestseller lists nationwide and sell over 750,000 copies to date. Ten years later, the book continues to change lives. In honor of the book&#8217;s 10th anniversary, Hyperion is proud to be releasing the book with a new afterword by the author, and to share this wonderful book with an even larger audience.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wherever-you-go-there-you-are-jon-kabat-zinn-abridged/">Wherever You Go There You are &#8211; Jon Kabat-Zinn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gentle Art of Swedish Death Cleaning : How to Free Yourself and Your Family from a Lifetime of Clutter &#8211; Margareta Magnusson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-gentle-art-of-swedish-death-cleaning-how-to-free-yourself-and-your-family-from-a-lifetime-of-clutter-margareta-magnusson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DIY: House Maintenance Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Household Hints]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gentle-art-of-swedish-death-cleaning-how-to-free-yourself-and-your-family-from-a-lifetime-of-clutter-margareta-magnusson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A charming, practical, and unsentimental approach to putting a home in order while reflecting on the tiny joys that make up a long life. In Sweden there is a kind of decluttering called döstädning, dö meaning &#8220;death&#8221; and städning meaning &#8220;cleaning.&#8221; This surprising and invigorating process of clearing out unnecessary belongings can be undertaken at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gentle-art-of-swedish-death-cleaning-how-to-free-yourself-and-your-family-from-a-lifetime-of-clutter-margareta-magnusson-abridged/">The Gentle Art of Swedish Death Cleaning : How to Free Yourself and Your Family from a Lifetime of Clutter &#8211; Margareta Magnusson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A charming, practical, and unsentimental approach to putting a home in order while reflecting on the tiny joys that make up a long life.     </p>
<p>                    In Sweden there is a kind of decluttering called döstädning, dö meaning &#8220;death&#8221; and städning meaning &#8220;cleaning.&#8221; This surprising and invigorating process of clearing out unnecessary belongings can be undertaken at any age or life stage but should be done sooner than later, before others have to do it for you. In The Gentle Art of Swedish Death Cleaning, artist Margareta Magnusson, with Scandinavian humor and wisdom, instructs readers to embrace minimalism. Her radical and joyous method for putting things in order helps families broach sensitive conversations, and makes the process uplifting rather than overwhelming.     </p>
<p>                    Margareta suggests which possessions you can easily get rid of (unworn clothes, unwanted presents, more plates than you&#8217;d ever use) and which you might want to keep (photographs, love letters, a few of your children&#8217;s art projects). Digging into her late husband&#8217;s tool shed, and her own secret drawer of vices, Margareta introduces an element of fun to a potentially daunting task. Along the way readers get a glimpse into her life in Sweden, and also become more comfortable with the idea of letting go.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gentle-art-of-swedish-death-cleaning-how-to-free-yourself-and-your-family-from-a-lifetime-of-clutter-margareta-magnusson-abridged/">The Gentle Art of Swedish Death Cleaning : How to Free Yourself and Your Family from a Lifetime of Clutter &#8211; Margareta Magnusson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
