<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Meteorology &amp; Climatology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/meteorology-climatology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/meteorology-climatology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Meteorology &amp; Climatology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/meteorology-climatology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Deadly Season &#8211; Analysis of the 2011 Tornado Outbreaks &#8211; Kevin M. Simmons</title>
		<link>/deadly-season-analysis-of-the-2011-tornado-outbreaks-kevin-m-simmons/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meteorology & Climatology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Environmental Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deadly-season-analysis-of-the-2011-tornado-outbreaks-kevin-m-simmons/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2011, despite continued developments in forecasting, tracking, and warning technology, the United States was hit by the deadliest tornado season in decades. More than 1,200 tornadoes touched down, shattering communities and their safety nets and killing more than 500 people &#8211; a death toll unmatched since 1953. Drawing on the unique analysis described in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deadly-season-analysis-of-the-2011-tornado-outbreaks-kevin-m-simmons/">Deadly Season &#8211; Analysis of the 2011 Tornado Outbreaks &#8211; Kevin M. Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2011, despite continued developments in forecasting, tracking, and warning technology, the United States was hit by the deadliest tornado season in decades. More than 1,200 tornadoes touched down, shattering communities and their safety nets and killing more than 500 people &#8211; a death toll unmatched since 1953. Drawing on the unique analysis described in their first book, &#8220;Economic and Societal Impacts of Tornadoes&#8221;, economists Kevin M. Simmons and Daniel Sutter here examine the factors that contributed to the outcomes of such tornadoes as the mid-April outbreak that devastated communities in North Carolina, the &#8220;Super Outbreak&#8221; across the southern and eastern United States in late April, and the single, mile-wide funnel that touched down in Joplin, Missouri in late May. In the course of their study the authors identify patterns and anomalies and reconsider previous assertions about the effectiveness of the Doppler radar and storm warning systems. Their conclusions, as well their assessment of early recovery efforts, are aimed at helping community leaders and policymakers keep vulnerable populations safer in the future.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deadly-season-analysis-of-the-2011-tornado-outbreaks-kevin-m-simmons/">Deadly Season &#8211; Analysis of the 2011 Tornado Outbreaks &#8211; Kevin M. Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A World Without Ice &#8211; Henry Pollack (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-world-without-ice-henry-pollack-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Earth Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hydrology & The Hydrosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meteorology & Climatology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-world-without-ice-henry-pollack-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A clear-eyed explanation of the impact of ice on Earth, its climate, and its residents. Much has been written about global warming, but the crucial relationship between people and ice has received little focus, until now &#8211; and there is a fierce urgency as the problem accelerates. With clarity and insight, geophysicist and a co-winner [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-world-without-ice-henry-pollack-abridged/">A World Without Ice &#8211; Henry Pollack (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A clear-eyed explanation of the impact of ice on Earth, its climate, and its residents.      </p>
<p>                     Much has been written about global warming, but the crucial relationship between people and ice has received little focus, until now &#8211; and there is a fierce urgency as the problem accelerates. With clarity and insight, geophysicist and a co-winner of the 2007 Nobel Peace Prize, Henry Pollack, paints a compelling portrait of the delicate geological balance between Earth and its ice, and shows why the current rapid loss of ice portends serious consequences in our not-so-distant future.     </p>
<p>                     Whether sculpting mountains, regulating temperatures, influencing ocean currents, or defining the limits of human settlement, ice has shaped &#8211; and continues to shape &#8211; the world we live in. This important and increasingly relevant book traces the effect of mountain glaciers on supplies of drinking water and agricultural irrigation, as well as the current results of melting permafrost and shrinking Arctic sea ice &#8211; a situation that has degraded the habitat of numerous animals and sparked an international race for seabed oil and minerals. Catastrophic possibilities loom, including rising sea levels and subsequent flooding of low-lying regions worldwide.     </p>
<p>                     A World Without Ice explains why ice matters, and lays out the urgent actions we can take to restore Earth&#8217;s delicate climate balance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-world-without-ice-henry-pollack-abridged/">A World Without Ice &#8211; Henry Pollack (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmos &#8211; Carl Sagan, Foreword by Neil deGrasse Tyson, Introduction by Ann Druyan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meteorology & Climatology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>RETURNING TO TELEVISION AS AN ALL-NEW MINISERIES ON FOX Cosmos is one of the bestselling science books of all time. In clear-eyed prose, Sagan reveals a jewel-like blue world inhabited by a life form that is just beginning to discover its own identity and to venture into the vast ocean of space. Featuring a new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/">Cosmos &#8211; Carl Sagan, Foreword by Neil deGrasse Tyson, Introduction by Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>RETURNING TO TELEVISION AS AN ALL-NEW MINISERIES ON FOX     </p>
<p>                    Cosmos is one of the bestselling science books of all time. In clear-eyed prose, Sagan reveals a jewel-like blue world inhabited by a life form that is just beginning to discover its own identity and to venture into the vast ocean of space. Featuring a new Introduction by Sagan&#8217;s collaborator, Ann Druyan, full color illustrations, and a new Foreword by astrophysicist Neil deGrasse Tyson, Cosmos retraces the fourteen billion years of cosmic evolution that have transformed matter into consciousness, exploring such topics as the origin of life, the human brain, Egyptian hieroglyphics, spacecraft missions, the death of the Sun, the evolution of galaxies, and the forces and individuals who helped to shape modern science.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Cosmos     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Magnificent . . . With a lyrical literary style, and a range that touches almost all aspects of human knowledge, Cosmos often seems too good to be true.&#8221;&#8211;The Plain Dealer     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Sagan is an astronomer with one eye on the stars, another on history, and a third&#8211;his mind&#8217;s&#8211;on the human condition.&#8221;&#8211;Newsday     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Brilliant in its scope and provocative in its suggestions . . . shimmers with a sense of wonder.&#8221;&#8211;The Miami Herald     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Sagan dazzles the mind with the miracle of our survival, framed by the stately galaxies of space.&#8221;&#8211;Cosmopolitan     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Enticing . . . iridescent . . . imaginatively illustrated.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/">Cosmos &#8211; Carl Sagan, Foreword by Neil deGrasse Tyson, Introduction by Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rain : A Natural and Cultural History &#8211; Cynthia Barnett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rain-a-natural-and-cultural-history-cynthia-barnett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meteorology & Climatology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Weather]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rain-a-natural-and-cultural-history-cynthia-barnett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Rain is elemental, mysterious, precious, destructive. It is the subject of countless poems and paintings; the top of the weather report; the source of the world&#8217;s water. Yet this is the first book to tell the story of rain. Cynthia Barnett&#8217;s Rain begins four billion years ago with the torrents that filled the oceans, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rain-a-natural-and-cultural-history-cynthia-barnett-abridged/">Rain : A Natural and Cultural History &#8211; Cynthia Barnett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rain is elemental, mysterious, precious, destructive.    </p>
<p>                     It is the subject of countless poems and paintings; the top of the weather report; the source of the world&#8217;s water. Yet this is the first book to tell the story of rain.     </p>
<p>                     Cynthia Barnett&#8217;s Rain begins four billion years ago with the torrents that filled the oceans, and builds to the storms of climate change. It weaves together science&#8211;the true shape of a raindrop, the mysteries of frog and fish rains&#8211;with the human story of our ambition to control rain, from ancient rain dances to the 2,203 miles of levees that attempt to straitjacket the Mississippi River. It offers a glimpse of our founding forecaster, Thomas Jefferson, who measured every drizzle long before modern meteorology. Two centuries later, rainy skies would help inspire Morrissey&#8217;s mopes and Kurt Cobain&#8217;s grunge. Rain is also a travelogue, taking readers to Scotland to tell the surprising story of the mackintosh raincoat, and to India, where villagers extract the scent of rain from the monsoon-drenched earth and turn it into perfume.     </p>
<p>                     Now, after thousands of years spent praying for rain or worshiping it; burning witches at the stake to stop rain or sacrificing small children to bring it; mocking rain with irrigated agriculture and cities built in floodplains; even trying to blast rain out of the sky with mortars meant for war, humanity has finally managed to change the rain. Only not in ways we intended. As climate change upends rainfall patterns and unleashes increasingly severe storms and drought, Barnett shows rain to be a unifying force in a fractured world. Too much and not nearly enough, rain is a conversation we share, and this is a book for everyone who has ever experienced it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rain-a-natural-and-cultural-history-cynthia-barnett-abridged/">Rain : A Natural and Cultural History &#8211; Cynthia Barnett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
