<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Agriculture &amp; Related Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/agriculture-related-industries/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/agriculture-related-industries/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Agriculture &amp; Related Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/agriculture-related-industries/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A must-read for anyone interested in food and the future&#8217; Yotam Ottolenghi Based on ten years of surveying farming communities around the world, top New York chef Dan Barber&#8217;s The Third Plate offers a radical new way of thinking about food that will heal the land and taste incredible. The &#8216;first plate&#8217; was a classic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/">The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A must-read for anyone interested in food and the future&#8217; Yotam Ottolenghi    </p>
<p>                    Based on ten years of surveying farming communities around the world, top New York chef Dan Barber&#8217;s The Third Plate offers a radical new way of thinking about food that will heal the land and taste incredible.    </p>
<p>                     The &#8216;first plate&#8217; was a classic meal centred on a large cut of meat with few vegetables. On the &#8216;second plate&#8217;, championed by the farm-to-table movement, meat is free-range and vegetables are locally sourced. It&#8217;s better-tasting, and better for the planet, but the second plate&#8217;s architecture is identical to that of the first. It, too, disrupts ecological balances, causing soil depletion and nutrient loss &#8211; it just isn&#8217;t a sustainable way to farm or eat.    </p>
<p>                     The &#8216;third plate&#8217; offers a solution: an integrated system of vegetable, cereal and livestock production that is fully supported &#8211; in fact, dictated &#8211; by what we choose to cook for dinner. The Third Plate is where good farming and good food intersect.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-plate-field-notes-on-the-future-of-food-dan-barber-abridged/">The Third Plate : Field Notes on the Future of Food &#8211; Dan Barber (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agronomy & Crop Production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Husbandry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animals & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sonia Faruqi, an Ivy League graduate and investment banker, had no idea that the night she arrived at the doorstep of a dairy farm would mark the beginning of a journey that would ultimately wind all the way around the world. Instead of turning away from the animal cruelty she came to witness, Sonia made [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/">Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sonia Faruqi, an Ivy League graduate and investment banker, had no idea that the night she arrived at the doorstep of a dairy farm would mark the beginning of a journey that would ultimately wind all the way around the world. Instead of turning away from the animal cruelty she came to witness, Sonia made the most courageous decision of her life: a commitment to change things.    </p>
<p>                     Driven by impulsive will and searing passion, Sonia left behind everything she knew and loved to search the planet for solutions to benefit animals, human health, and the environment. Over the course of living with farmers, hitchhiking with strangers, and risking her life, she developed surprising insights and solutions-both about the food industry and herself.    </p>
<p>                     Lively and heartfelt, Sonia takes readers on an unforgettable adventure from top-secret egg warehouses in Canada to dairy feedlots in the United States, from farm offices in Mexico to lush pastures in Belize, from flocks of village chickens in Indonesia to factory farms in Malaysia.    </p>
<p>                     Revelatory in scope, Project Animal Farm illuminates a hidden world that plays a part in all of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/">Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Meat Racket : The Secret Takeover of America&#8217;s Food Business &#8211; Christopher Leonard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-meat-racket-the-secret-takeover-of-americas-food-business-christopher-leonard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-meat-racket-the-secret-takeover-of-americas-food-business-christopher-leonard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An investigative journalist takes you inside the corporate meat industry&#8211;a shocking, in-depth report every American should read. How much do you know about the meat on your dinner plate? Journalist Christopher Leonard spent more than a decade covering the country&#8217;s biggest meat companies, including four years as the national agribusiness reporter for the Associated Press. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-meat-racket-the-secret-takeover-of-americas-food-business-christopher-leonard-abridged/">The Meat Racket : The Secret Takeover of America&#8217;s Food Business &#8211; Christopher Leonard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An investigative journalist takes you inside the corporate meat industry&#8211;a shocking, in-depth report every American should read.     </p>
<p>                    How much do you know about the meat on your dinner plate? Journalist Christopher Leonard spent more than a decade covering the country&#8217;s biggest meat companies, including four years as the national agribusiness reporter for the Associated Press. Now he delivers the first comprehensive look inside the industrial meat system, exposing how a handful of companies executed an audacious corporate takeover of the nation&#8217;s meat supply.     </p>
<p>                    Leonard&#8217;s revealing account shines a light on the inner workings of Tyson Foods, a pioneer of the industrial system that dominates the market. You&#8217;ll learn how the food industry got to where it is today, and how companies like Tyson have escaped the scrutiny they deserve. You&#8217;ll discover how these companies are able to raise meat prices for consumers while pushing down the price they pay to farmers. And you&#8217;ll even see how big business and politics have derailed efforts to change the system, from a years-long legal fight in Iowa to the Obama administration&#8217;s recent failed attempt to pass reforms.     </p>
<p>                    Important, timely, and explosive, The Meat Racket is an unvarnished portrait of the food industry that now dominates America&#8217;s heartland.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-meat-racket-the-secret-takeover-of-americas-food-business-christopher-leonard-abridged/">The Meat Racket : The Secret Takeover of America&#8217;s Food Business &#8211; Christopher Leonard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author). We are in the grip of a food [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author).<br />
                       We are in the grip of a food crisis. Obesity has become a leading cause of preventable death, after only smoking. For nearly half a century we&#8217;ve been trying to pin the blame somewhere, fat, carbs, sugar, wheat, high-fructose corn syrup. But that search has been in vain, because the food problem that&#8217;s killing us is not a nutrient problem. It&#8217;s a behavioural problem, and it&#8217;s caused by the changing flavour of the food we eat.<br />
                       Ever since the 1940s, with the rise of industrialized food production, we have been gradually leeching the taste out of what we grow. Simultaneously, we have taken great leaps forward in technology, creating a flavour industry, worth billions annually; in an attempt to put back the tastes we&#8217;ve engineered out of our food. The result is a cuisine that increasingly resembles the paragon of flavour manipulation: Doritos. As food becomes increasingly bland, we dress it up with calories and flavour chemicals to make it delicious again. We have rewired our palates and our brains, and the results are making us sick and killing us.<br />
                       With in-depth historical and scientific research, The Dorito Effect casts the food crisis in a fascinating new light, weaving an enthralling tale of how we got to this point and where we are headed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Weed : An Entrepreneur&#8217;s High-Stakes Adventures in the Budding Legal Marijuana Business &#8211; Christian Hageseth, Joseph D&#8217;Agnese (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/big-weed-an-entrepreneurs-high-stakes-adventures-in-the-budding-legal-marijuana-business-christian-hageseth-joseph-dagnese-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/big-weed-an-entrepreneurs-high-stakes-adventures-in-the-budding-legal-marijuana-business-christian-hageseth-joseph-dagnese-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Marijuana legalization is the hottest story in the US today. 22 states have authorized sales in some form; Denver has more legal marijuana dispensaries than Starbucks franchises. We are witnessing the dawn of a new industry. And like the early days of gourmet coffee chains, the rules and players are being established on the fly. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-weed-an-entrepreneurs-high-stakes-adventures-in-the-budding-legal-marijuana-business-christian-hageseth-joseph-dagnese-abridged/">Big Weed : An Entrepreneur&#8217;s High-Stakes Adventures in the Budding Legal Marijuana Business &#8211; Christian Hageseth, Joseph D&#8217;Agnese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Marijuana legalization is the hottest story in the US today. 22 states have authorized sales in some form; Denver has more legal marijuana dispensaries than Starbucks franchises. We are witnessing the dawn of a new industry. And like the early days of gourmet coffee chains, the rules and players are being established on the fly.     </p>
<p>                    Christian Hageseth is the face of the revolution-an entrepreneur and father of three who worked in the white-collar professional world for 20 years before opening his first dispensary. The Founder and Chairman of Green Man Cannabis, the fastest-growing legalized marijuana company in the country, he&#8217;s the perfect tour guide through the wild frontier, where police hardly know what laws to enforce, or parents what to tell their kids. He paints a colorful picture not only of how he got into the business, but of the big interests that are eager to do the same-namely Philip Morris, Monsanto and a who&#8217;s who of Big Pharma. He predicts a future where the marijuana market splits in two: the high-end, artisanal market, supplied by individual growers and small farms, and the mass market, covered by the cigarette giants and anyone bold enough to compete with them. Much like beer and coffee, your brand of weed will be just one more reflection of your lifestyle. It&#8217;s an entrepreneur&#8217;s dream, and Hageseth invites us along in Big Weed as he pitches skeptical investors, negotiates a shaggy cast of colleagues, and builds the biggest business he can.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/big-weed-an-entrepreneurs-high-stakes-adventures-in-the-budding-legal-marijuana-business-christian-hageseth-joseph-dagnese-abridged/">Big Weed : An Entrepreneur&#8217;s High-Stakes Adventures in the Budding Legal Marijuana Business &#8211; Christian Hageseth, Joseph D&#8217;Agnese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
