<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Cosmetics, Hair &amp; Beauty Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/cosmetics-hair-beauty/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/cosmetics-hair-beauty/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Cosmetics, Hair &amp; Beauty Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/cosmetics-hair-beauty/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>How to be Like Walt : Capturing the Disney Magic Every Day of Your Life &#8211; Pat Williams, Jim Denney (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-like-walt-capturing-the-disney-magic-every-day-of-your-life-pat-williams-jim-denney-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmetics, Hair & Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-like-walt-capturing-the-disney-magic-every-day-of-your-life-pat-williams-jim-denney-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An inspiring biography of one of the most influential and beloved figures of the 21st century, based on more than a thousand interviews. `I&#8217;ve read every book that has ever been written about Walt Disney, going back to some that were published in the 1930s. [How to Be Like Walt] is by far the most [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-like-walt-capturing-the-disney-magic-every-day-of-your-life-pat-williams-jim-denney-abridged/">How to be Like Walt : Capturing the Disney Magic Every Day of Your Life &#8211; Pat Williams, Jim Denney (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An inspiring biography of one of the most influential and beloved figures of the 21st century, based on more than a thousand interviews. `I&#8217;ve read every book that has ever been written about Walt Disney, going back to some that were published in the 1930s. [How to Be Like Walt] is by far the most enjoyable to read of them all!`<br />
                     Tim O&#8217;Day, Disney Scholar<br />
                     `How to Be Like Walt is a fitting tribute to Walt&#8217;s memory and an important contribution to the Disney legacy . . . Now more than ever, we need people with the qualities Walt had: optimism, imagination, creativity, leadership, integrity, courage, boldness, perseverance, commitment to excellence, reverence for the past, hope for tomorrow, and faith in God.`<br />
                     Art Linkletter  How to Be Like is a `character biography` series: biographies that also draw out important lessons from the life of their subjects. In this new book-by far the most exhaustive in the series-Pat Williams tackles one of the most influential people in recent history. While many recent biographies of Walt Disney have reveled in the negative, this book takes an honest but positive look at the man behind the myth. For the first time, the book pulls together all the various strands of Disney&#8217;s life into one straightforward, easy-to-read tale of imagination, perseverance, and optimism. Far from a preachy or oppressive tome, this book scrapes away the minutiae to capture the true magic of a brilliant maverick.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-like-walt-capturing-the-disney-magic-every-day-of-your-life-pat-williams-jim-denney-abridged/">How to be Like Walt : Capturing the Disney Magic Every Day of Your Life &#8211; Pat Williams, Jim Denney (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers -Revised Edition &#8211; M. Sapolsky, M. Sapolsky, Robert, Robert (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-zebras-dont-get-ulcers-revised-edition-m-sapolsky-m-sapolsky-robert-robert-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmetics, Hair & Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-zebras-dont-get-ulcers-revised-edition-m-sapolsky-m-sapolsky-robert-robert-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now in a third edition, Robert M. Sapolsky&#8217;s acclaimed and successful Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers features new chapters on how stress affects sleep and addiction, as well as new insights into anxiety and personality disorder and the impact of spirituality on managing stress. As Sapolsky explains, most of us do not lie awake at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-zebras-dont-get-ulcers-revised-edition-m-sapolsky-m-sapolsky-robert-robert-abridged/">Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers -Revised Edition &#8211; M. Sapolsky, M. Sapolsky, Robert, Robert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now in a third edition, Robert M. Sapolsky&#8217;s acclaimed and successful Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers features new chapters on how stress affects sleep and addiction, as well as new insights into anxiety and personality disorder and the impact of spirituality on managing stress. As Sapolsky explains, most of us do not lie awake at night worrying about whether we have leprosy or malaria. Instead, the diseases we fear &#8211; and the ones that plague us now &#8211; are illnesses brought on by the slow accumulation of damage, such as heart disease and cancer. When we worry or experience stress, our body turns on the same physiological responses that an animal&#8217;s does, but we do not resolve conflict in the same way &#8211; through fighting or fleeing. Over time, this activation of a stress response makes us literally sick. Combining cutting-edge research with a healthy dose of good humour and practical advice, Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers explains how prolonged stress causes or intensifies a range of physical and mental afflictions, including depression, ulcers, colitis, heart disease, and more. It also provides essential guidance to controlling our stress responses.<br />
                    This new edition promises to be the most comprehensive and engaging one yet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-zebras-dont-get-ulcers-revised-edition-m-sapolsky-m-sapolsky-robert-robert-abridged/">Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers -Revised Edition &#8211; M. Sapolsky, M. Sapolsky, Robert, Robert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Survival of the Prettiest : The Science of Beauty &#8211; Nancy Etcoff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/survival-of-the-prettiest-the-science-of-beauty-nancy-etcoff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmetics, Hair & Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/survival-of-the-prettiest-the-science-of-beauty-nancy-etcoff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A provocative and thoroughly researched inquiry into what we find beautiful and why, skewering the myth that the pursuit of beauty is a learned behavior. In Survival of the Prettiest, Nancy Etcoff, a faculty member at Harvard Medical School and a practicing psychologist at Massachusetts General Hospital, argues that beauty is neither a cultural construction, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/survival-of-the-prettiest-the-science-of-beauty-nancy-etcoff-abridged/">Survival of the Prettiest : The Science of Beauty &#8211; Nancy Etcoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A provocative and thoroughly researched inquiry into what we find beautiful and why, skewering the myth that the pursuit of beauty is a learned behavior.     </p>
<p>                     In Survival of the Prettiest, Nancy Etcoff, a faculty member at Harvard Medical School and a practicing psychologist at Massachusetts General Hospital, argues that beauty is neither a cultural construction, an invention of the fashion industry, nor a backlash against feminism&#8211;it&#8217;s in our biology.     </p>
<p>                     Beauty, she explains, is an essential and ineradicable part of human nature that is revered and ferociously pursued in nearly every civilization&#8211;and for good reason. Those features to which we are most attracted are often signals of fertility and fecundity. When seen in the context of a Darwinian struggle for survival, our sometimes extreme attempts to attain beauty&#8211;both to become beautiful ourselves and to acquire an attractive partner&#8211;suddenly become much more understandable. Moreover, if we understand how the desire for beauty is innate, then we can begin to work in our own interests, and not just the interests of our genetic tendencies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/survival-of-the-prettiest-the-science-of-beauty-nancy-etcoff-abridged/">Survival of the Prettiest : The Science of Beauty &#8211; Nancy Etcoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Resilience : Hard-Won Wisdom for Living a Better Life &#8211; Eric Greitens (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/resilience-hard-won-wisdom-for-living-a-better-life-eric-greitens-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmetics, Hair & Beauty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/resilience-hard-won-wisdom-for-living-a-better-life-eric-greitens-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two years ago, Eric Greitens unexpectedly heard from a former SEAL comrade, a brother-in-arms he hadn&#8217;t seen in a decade. Zach Walker had been one of the toughest of the tough. But ever since he returned home from war to his young family in a small logging town, he&#8217;d been struggling. Without a sense of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/resilience-hard-won-wisdom-for-living-a-better-life-eric-greitens-abridged/">Resilience : Hard-Won Wisdom for Living a Better Life &#8211; Eric Greitens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two years ago, Eric Greitens unexpectedly heard from a former SEAL comrade, a brother-in-arms he hadn&#8217;t seen in a decade. Zach Walker had been one of the toughest of the tough. But ever since he returned home from war to his young family in a small logging town, he&#8217;d been struggling. Without a sense of purpose, plagued by PTSD, and masking his pain with heavy drinking, he needed help. Zach and Eric started writing and talking nearly every day, and Eric set down his thoughts on what it takes to build resilience in our lives. Eric&#8217;s letters drawing on both his own experience and wisdom from ancient and modern thinkers are now gathered and edited into a timeless handbook. They explain how we can build purpose, confront the pain in our lives, practice compassion, develop our vocations, find a mentor, create happiness, follow a role model, think about the story of our lives, and much more. Resilience grapples with real hardship. The lessons are deep, yet practical, and the advice leads to clear solutions. This is a profoundly hopeful book: We all face pain, difficulty, and doubt. But with resilience, we can lead vital, flourishing lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/resilience-hard-won-wisdom-for-living-a-better-life-eric-greitens-abridged/">Resilience : Hard-Won Wisdom for Living a Better Life &#8211; Eric Greitens (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
