<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Biography: Literary Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/biography-literary/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/biography-literary/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Biography: Literary Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/biography-literary/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley</title>
		<link>/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay & Lesbian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestselling memoir about identity, love and understanding. Now a major motion picture starring Nicole Kidman, Russell Crowe, and Lucas Hedges, directed by Joel Edgerton. &#8220;Every sentence of the story will stir your soul&#8221; (O Magazine). The son of a Baptist pastor and deeply embedded in church life in small town Arkansas, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley/">Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestselling memoir about identity, love and understanding. Now a major motion picture starring Nicole Kidman, Russell Crowe, and Lucas Hedges, directed by Joel Edgerton. &#8220;Every sentence of the story will stir your soul&#8221; (O Magazine).    </p>
<p>                    The son of a Baptist pastor and deeply embedded in church life in small town Arkansas, as a young man Garrard Conley was terrified and conflicted about his sexuality. When Garrard was a nineteen-year-old college student, he was outed to his parents, and was forced to make a life-changing decision: either agree to attend a church-supported conversion therapy program that promised to cure him of homosexuality; or risk losing family, friends, and the God he had prayed to every day of his life. Through an institutionalized Twelve-Step Program heavy on Bible study, he was supposed to emerge heterosexual, ex-gay, cleansed of impure urges and stronger in his faith in God for his brush with sin. Instead, even when faced with a harrowing and brutal journey, Garrard found the strength and understanding to break out in search of his true self and forgiveness.     </p>
<p>                    By confronting his buried past and the burden of a life lived in shadow, Garrard traces the complex relationships among family, faith, and community. At times heart-breaking, at times triumphant, Boy Erased is a testament to love that survives despite all odds.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley/">Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dry : A Memoir &#8211; Augusten Burroughs</title>
		<link>/dry-a-memoir-augusten-burroughs/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dry-a-memoir-augusten-burroughs/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Tenth Anniversary Edition of the New York Times bestselling book that has sold over half a million copies in paperback. I was addicted to Bewitched as a kid. I worshipped Darren Stevens the First. When he&#8217;d come home from work and Samantha would say, &#8216;Darren, would you like me to fix you a drink?&#8217; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dry-a-memoir-augusten-burroughs/">Dry : A Memoir &#8211; Augusten Burroughs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Tenth Anniversary Edition of the New York Times bestselling book that has sold over half a million copies in paperback. </p>
<p>                    I was addicted to Bewitched as a kid. I worshipped Darren Stevens the First. When he&#8217;d come home from work and Samantha would say, &#8216;Darren, would you like me to fix you a drink?&#8217; He&#8217;d always rest his briefcase on the table below the mirror in the foyer, wipe his forehead with a monogrammed handkerchief and say, &#8216;Better make it a double.&#8217; (from Chapter Two) </p>
<p>                    You may not know it, but you&#8217;ve met Augusten Burroughs. You&#8217;ve seen him on the street, in bars, on the subway, at restaurants: a twentysomething guy, nice suit, works in advertising. Regular. Ordinary. But when the ordinary person had two drinks, Augusten was circling the drain by having twelve; when the ordinary person went home at midnight, Augusten never went home at all. Loud, distracting ties, automated wake-up calls and cologne on the tongue could only hide so much for so long. At the request (well, it wasn&#8217;t really a request) of his employers, Augusten lands in rehab, where his dreams of group therapy with Robert Downey Jr. are immediately dashed by grim reality of fluorescent lighting and paper hospital slippers. But when Augusten is forced to examine himself, something actually starts to click and that&#8217;s when he finds himself in the worst trouble of all. Because when his thirty days are up, he has to return to his same drunken Manhattan life&#8211;and live it sober. What follows is a memoir that&#8217;s as moving as it is funny, as heartbreaking as it is true. Dry is the story of love, loss, and Starbucks as a Higher Power.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dry-a-memoir-augusten-burroughs/">Dry : A Memoir &#8211; Augusten Burroughs</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On Writing : A Memoir of the Craft: Twentieth Anniversary Edition with Contributions from Joe Hill and Owen King &#8211; Stephen King</title>
		<link>/on-writing-a-memoir-of-the-craft-twentieth-anniversary-edition-with-contributions-from-joe-hill-and-owen-king-stephen-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Novelists & Prose Writers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-writing-a-memoir-of-the-craft-twentieth-anniversary-edition-with-contributions-from-joe-hill-and-owen-king-stephen-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Twentieth Anniversary Edition with Contributions from Joe Hill and Owen King Immensely helpful and illuminating to any aspiring writer, this special edition of Stephen King&#8217;s critically lauded, million-copy bestseller shares the experiences, habits, and convictions that have shaped him and his work. Part memoir, part masterclass by one of the bestselling authors of all time, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-writing-a-memoir-of-the-craft-twentieth-anniversary-edition-with-contributions-from-joe-hill-and-owen-king-stephen-king/">On Writing : A Memoir of the Craft: Twentieth Anniversary Edition with Contributions from Joe Hill and Owen King &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Twentieth Anniversary Edition with Contributions from Joe Hill and Owen King </p>
<p>                    Immensely helpful and illuminating to any aspiring writer, this special edition of Stephen King&#8217;s critically lauded, million-copy bestseller shares the experiences, habits, and convictions that have shaped him and his work.</p>
<p>                     Part memoir, part masterclass by one of the bestselling authors of all time, this superb volume is a revealing and practical view of the writer&#8217;s craft, comprising the basic tools of the trade every writer must have. </p>
<p>                    King&#8217;s advice is grounded in his vivid memories from childhood through his emergence as a writer, from his struggling early career to his widely reported, near-fatal accident in 1999 &#8211; and how the inextricable link between writing and living spurred his recovery. </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly structured, friendly and inspiring, On Writing will empower and entertain everyone who reads it &#8211; fans, writers, and anyone who loves a great story well told.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-writing-a-memoir-of-the-craft-twentieth-anniversary-edition-with-contributions-from-joe-hill-and-owen-king-stephen-king/">On Writing : A Memoir of the Craft: Twentieth Anniversary Edition with Contributions from Joe Hill and Owen King &#8211; Stephen King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Russian Journal &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Steinbeck and Capa&#8217;s account of their journey through Cold War Russia is a classic piece of reportage and travel writing. A Penguin Classic Just after the Iron Curtain fell on Eastern Europe, Pulitzer Prize-winning author John Steinbeck and acclaimed war photographer Robert Capa ventured into the Soviet Union to report for the New York Herald [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/">A Russian Journal &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Steinbeck and Capa&#8217;s account of their journey through Cold War Russia is a classic piece of reportage and travel writing. </p>
<p>                    A Penguin Classic </p>
<p>                    Just after the Iron Curtain fell on Eastern Europe, Pulitzer Prize-winning author John Steinbeck and acclaimed war photographer Robert Capa ventured into the Soviet Union to report for the New York Herald Tribune. This rare opportunity took the famous travelers not only to Moscow and Stalingrad &#8211; now Volgograd &#8211; but through the countryside of the Ukraine and the Caucasus. Hailed by the New York Times as superb when it first appeared in 1948, A Russian Journal is the distillation of their journey and remains a remarkable memoir and unique historical document.</p>
<p>                    What they saw and movingly recorded in words and on film was what Steinbeck called the great other side there &#8230; the private life of the Russian people. Unlike other Western reporting about Russia at the time, A Russian Journal is free of ideological obsessions. Rather, Steinbeck and Capa recorded the grim realities of factory workers, government clerks, and peasants, as they emerged from the rubble of World War II&#8211;represented here in Capa&#8217;s stirring photographs alongside Steinbeck&#8217;s masterful prose. Through it all, we are given intimate glimpses of two artists at the height of their powers, answering their need to document human struggle. This edition features an introduction by Steinbeck scholar Susan Shillinglaw.</p>
<p>                     For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-russian-journal-john-steinbeck/">A Russian Journal &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bombs Away : The Story of a Bomber Team &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/bombs-away-the-story-of-a-bomber-team-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bombs-away-the-story-of-a-bomber-team-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A magnificent volume of short novels and an essential World War II report from one of America&#8217;s great twentieth-century writers A Penguin Classic On the heels of the enormous success of his masterwork The Grapes of Wrath and at the height of the American war effort John Steinbeck, one of the most prolific and influential [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bombs-away-the-story-of-a-bomber-team-john-steinbeck/">Bombs Away : The Story of a Bomber Team &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A magnificent volume of short novels and an essential World War II report from one of America&#8217;s great twentieth-century writers </p>
<p>                    A Penguin Classic </p>
<p>                    On the heels of the enormous success of his masterwork The Grapes of Wrath and at the height of the American war effort John Steinbeck, one of the most prolific and influential literary figures of his generation, wrote Bombs Away, a nonfiction account of his experiences with U.S. Army Air Force bomber crews during World War II. Now, for the first time since its original publication in 1942, Penguin Classics presents this exclusive edition of Steinbeck&#8217;s introduction to the then-nascent U.S. Army Air Force and its bomber crew&#8211;the essential core unit behind American air power that Steinbeck described as the greatest team in the world. </p>
<p>                    For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bombs-away-the-story-of-a-bomber-team-john-steinbeck/">Bombs Away : The Story of a Bomber Team &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Travels with Charley in Search of America &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/travels-with-charley-in-search-of-america-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/travels-with-charley-in-search-of-america-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An intimate journey across America, as told by one of its most beloved writers To hear the speech of the real America, to smell the grass and the trees, to see the colors and the light-these were John Steinbeck&#8217;s goals as he set out, at the age of fifty-eight, to rediscover the country he had [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/travels-with-charley-in-search-of-america-john-steinbeck/">Travels with Charley in Search of America &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An intimate journey across America, as told by one of its most beloved writers    </p>
<p>                     To hear the speech of the real America, to smell the grass and the trees, to see the colors and the light-these were John Steinbeck&#8217;s goals as he set out, at the age of fifty-eight, to rediscover the country he had been writing about for so many years.    </p>
<p>                     With Charley, his French poodle, Steinbeck drives the interstates and the country roads, dines with truckers, encounters bears at Yellowstone and old friends in San Francisco. Along the way he reflects on the American character, racial hostility, the particular form of American loneliness he finds almost everywhere, and  the unexpected kindness of strangers.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/travels-with-charley-in-search-of-america-john-steinbeck/">Travels with Charley in Search of America &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>ME Talk Pretty One Day &#8211; David Sedaris</title>
		<link>/me-talk-pretty-one-day-david-sedaris/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/me-talk-pretty-one-day-david-sedaris/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A recent transplant to Paris, humorist David Sedaris, bestselling author of Naked, presents a collection of his strongest work yet, including the title story about his hilarious attempt to learn French. A number one national bestseller now in paperback.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-talk-pretty-one-day-david-sedaris/">ME Talk Pretty One Day &#8211; David Sedaris</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A recent transplant to Paris, humorist David Sedaris, bestselling author of Naked, presents a collection of his strongest work yet, including the title story about his hilarious attempt to learn French. A number one national bestseller now in paperback.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-talk-pretty-one-day-david-sedaris/">ME Talk Pretty One Day &#8211; David Sedaris</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Log from the Sea of Cortez &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marine Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic In the two years after the 1939 publication of Steinbeck&#8217;s masterful The Grapes of Wrath, Steinbeck and his novel increasingly became the center of intense controversy and censorship. In search of a respite from the national stage, Steinbeck and his close friend, biologist Ed Ricketts, embarked on a month long marine specimen-collecting [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/">The Log from the Sea of Cortez &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic     </p>
<p>                    In the two years after the 1939 publication of Steinbeck&#8217;s masterful The Grapes of Wrath, Steinbeck and his novel increasingly became the center of intense controversy and censorship. In search of a respite from the national stage, Steinbeck and his close friend, biologist Ed Ricketts, embarked on a month long marine specimen-collecting expedition in the Gulf of California, which resulted in their collaboration on the Sea of Cortez. In 1951, after Ricketts&#8217; death, Steinbeck reissued his narrative portion of the work in memory of his friend and the inspiration for Cannery Row&#8217;s &#8220;Doc&#8221;. This exciting day-by-day account of their journey together is a rare blend of science, philosophy, and high-spirited adventure. This edition features an introduction by Richard Astro.     </p>
<p>                    For more than seventy years, Penguin has been the leading publisher of classic literature in the English-speaking world. With more than 1,700 titles, Penguin Classics represents a global bookshelf of the best works throughout history and across genres and disciplines. Readers trust the series to provide authoritative texts enhanced by introductions and notes by distinguished scholars and contemporary authors, as well as up-to-date translations by award-winning translators.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-log-from-the-sea-of-cortez-john-steinbeck/">The Log from the Sea of Cortez &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The World Is Not Enough : A Biography of Ian Fleming &#8211; Oliver Buckton</title>
		<link>/the-world-is-not-enough-a-biography-of-ian-fleming-oliver-buckton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Novelists & Prose Writers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-world-is-not-enough-a-biography-of-ian-fleming-oliver-buckton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The definitive history of the flamboyant life of Ian Fleming and his most famous creation, James Bond. This new biography of Ian Fleming presents a fresh and illuminating portrayal of the iconic creator of James Bond. Oliver Buckton provides the first in-depth exploration of the entire process of Ian Fleming&#8217;s writing-from initial conception, through composition, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-world-is-not-enough-a-biography-of-ian-fleming-oliver-buckton/">The World Is Not Enough : A Biography of Ian Fleming &#8211; Oliver Buckton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The definitive history of the flamboyant life of Ian Fleming and his most famous creation, James Bond.    </p>
<p>                    This new biography of Ian Fleming presents a fresh and illuminating portrayal of the iconic creator of James Bond. Oliver Buckton provides the first in-depth exploration of the entire process of Ian Fleming&#8217;s writing-from initial conception, through composition, to his involvement in the innovative publication methods of his books. He also investigates the vital impact of Fleming&#8217;s work in naval intelligence during World War Two on his later writings, especially the wartime operations he planned and executed and how they drove the plots of the James Bond novels. Buckton considers the vital role of wartime deception, disinformation, and propaganda in shaping Fleming&#8217;s later techniques and imaginative creations. Offering a radically new view of Fleming&#8217;s relationships with women, Buckton traces the role of strong, independent, and intelligent women such as Maud Russell, Phyllis Bottome, and his wife, Ann, on Fleming&#8217;s portrayal of female characters. The book concludes with a thorough analysis of the James Bond films from Eon productions, and their influence in promoting, while also distorting, the public&#8217;s recognition of Fleming&#8217;s writing.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-world-is-not-enough-a-biography-of-ian-fleming-oliver-buckton/">The World Is Not Enough : A Biography of Ian Fleming &#8211; Oliver Buckton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Darkness Visible : A Memoir of Madness &#8211; William Styron</title>
		<link>/darkness-visible-a-memoir-of-madness-william-styron/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/darkness-visible-a-memoir-of-madness-william-styron/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A work of great personal courage and a literary tour de force, this bestseller is Styron&#8217;s true account of his descent into a crippling and almost suicidal depression. Styron is perhaps the first writer to convey the full terror of depression&#8217;s psychic landscape, as well as the illuminating path to recovery.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darkness-visible-a-memoir-of-madness-william-styron/">Darkness Visible : A Memoir of Madness &#8211; William Styron</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A work of great personal courage and a literary tour de force, this bestseller is Styron&#8217;s true account of his descent into a crippling and almost suicidal depression. Styron is perhaps the first writer to convey the full terror of depression&#8217;s psychic landscape, as well as the illuminating path to recovery.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darkness-visible-a-memoir-of-madness-william-styron/">Darkness Visible : A Memoir of Madness &#8211; William Styron</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Eating Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A TIME magazine Must-Read Book of the Year Ever wonder what your therapist is thinking? Now you can find out, as therapist and New York Times bestselling author Lori Gottlieb takes us behind the scenes of her practice &#8211; where her patients are looking for answers (and so is she). When a personal crisis causes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/">Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A TIME magazine Must-Read Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Ever wonder what your therapist is thinking? Now you can find out, as therapist and New York Times bestselling author Lori Gottlieb takes us behind the scenes of her practice &#8211; where her patients are looking for answers (and so is she).    </p>
<p>                    When a personal crisis causes her world to come crashing down, Lori Gottlieb &#8211; an experienced therapist with a thriving practice in Los Angeles &#8211; is suddenly adrift. Enter Wendell, himself a veteran therapist with an unconventional style, whose sessions with Gottlieb will prove transformative for her.    </p>
<p>                    As Gottlieb explores the inner chambers of her own patients&#8217; lives &#8211; a self-absorbed Hollywood producer, a young newlywed diagnosed with a terminal illness, a senior citizen who feels she has nothing to live for, and a self-destructive twenty-something who can&#8217;t stop hooking up with the wrong guys &#8211; she finds that the questions they are struggling with are the very questions she is bringing to Wendell.    </p>
<p>                    Taking place over one year, and beginning with the devastating event that lands her in Wendell&#8217;s office, Maybe You Should Talk to Someone offers a rare and candid insight into a profession that is conventionally bound with rules and secrecy. Told with charm and compassion, vulnerability and humour, it&#8217;s also the story of an incredible relationship between two therapists, and a disarmingly funny and illuminating account of our own mysterious inner lives, as well as our power to transform them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/maybe-you-should-talk-to-someone-the-heartfelt-funny-memoir-by-a-new-york-times-bestselling-therapist-lori-gottlieb-abridged/">Maybe You Should Talk to Someone : the heartfelt, funny memoir by a New York Times bestselling therapist &#8211; Lori Gottlieb (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Year of Magical Thinking &#8211; Joan Didion (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-year-of-magical-thinking-joan-didion-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-year-of-magical-thinking-joan-didion-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From one of America&#8217;s iconic writers, a portrait of a marriage and a life &#8211; in good times and bad &#8211; that will speak to anyone who has ever loved a husband or wife or child. A stunning book of electric honesty and passion. Several days before Christmas 2003, John Gregory Dunne and Joan Didion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-year-of-magical-thinking-joan-didion-abridged/">The Year of Magical Thinking &#8211; Joan Didion (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From one of America&#8217;s iconic writers, a portrait of a marriage and a life &#8211; in good times and bad &#8211; that will speak to anyone who has ever loved a husband or wife or child. A stunning book of electric honesty and passion.    </p>
<p>                              Several days before Christmas 2003, John Gregory Dunne and Joan Didion saw their only daughter, Quintana, fall ill. At first they thought it was flu, then pneumonia, then complete sceptic shock. She was put into an induced coma and placed on life support. Days later &#8211; the night before New Year&#8217;s Eve -the Dunnes were just sitting down to dinner after visiting the hospital when John suffered a massive and fatal coronary. In a second, this close, symbiotic partnership of 40 years was over. Four weeks later, their daughter pulled through. Two months after that, arriving at LA airport, she collapsed and underwent six hours of brain surgery at UCLA Medical Centre to relieve a massive hematoma.    </p>
<p>                              This powerful book is Didion&#8217;s &#8216;attempt to make sense of the weeks and then months that cut loose any fixed idea I ever had about death, about illness &#8230; about marriage and children and memory &#8230; about the shallowness of sanity, about life itself&#8217;. The result is an exploration of an intensely personal yet universal experience: a portrait of a marriage, and a life, in good times and bad.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-year-of-magical-thinking-joan-didion-abridged/">The Year of Magical Thinking &#8211; Joan Didion (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas : A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream &#8211; Hunter S. Thompson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>50th Anniversary Edition &#8211; With an introduction by Caity Weaver, acclaimed New York Times journalist This cult classic of gonzo journalism is the best chronicle of drug-soaked, addle-brained, rollicking good times ever committed to the printed page. It is also the tale of a long weekend road trip that has gone down in the annals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/">Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas : A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream &#8211; Hunter S. Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>50th Anniversary Edition &#8211; With an introduction by Caity Weaver, acclaimed New York Times journalist     </p>
<p>                    This cult classic of gonzo journalism is the best chronicle of drug-soaked, addle-brained, rollicking good times ever committed to the printed page. It is also the tale of a long weekend road trip that has gone down in the annals of American pop culture as one of the strangest journeys ever undertaken.     </p>
<p>                    Also a major motion picture directed by Terry Gilliam, starring Johnny Depp and Benicio del Toro.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/">Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas : A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream &#8211; Hunter S. Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay & Lesbian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestselling memoir about identity, love and understanding. Now a major motion picture starring Nicole Kidman, Russell Crowe, and Lucas Hedges, directed by Joel Edgerton. &#8220;Every sentence of the story will stir your soul&#8221; (O Magazine). The son of a Baptist pastor and deeply embedded in church life in small town Arkansas, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley-abridged/">Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestselling memoir about identity, love and understanding. Now a major motion picture starring Nicole Kidman, Russell Crowe, and Lucas Hedges, directed by Joel Edgerton. &#8220;Every sentence of the story will stir your soul&#8221; (O Magazine).    </p>
<p>                    The son of a Baptist pastor and deeply embedded in church life in small town Arkansas, as a young man Garrard Conley was terrified and conflicted about his sexuality. When Garrard was a nineteen-year-old college student, he was outed to his parents, and was forced to make a life-changing decision: either agree to attend a church-supported conversion therapy program that promised to cure him of homosexuality; or risk losing family, friends, and the God he had prayed to every day of his life. Through an institutionalized Twelve-Step Program heavy on Bible study, he was supposed to emerge heterosexual, ex-gay, cleansed of impure urges and stronger in his faith in God for his brush with sin. Instead, even when faced with a harrowing and brutal journey, Garrard found the strength and understanding to break out in search of his true self and forgiveness.     </p>
<p>                    By confronting his buried past and the burden of a life lived in shadow, Garrard traces the complex relationships among family, faith, and community. At times heart-breaking, at times triumphant, Boy Erased is a testament to love that survives despite all odds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boy-erased-a-memoir-of-identity-faith-and-family-garrard-conley-abridged/">Boy Erased : A Memoir of Identity, Faith, and Family &#8211; Garrard Conley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>String Theory: David Foster Wallace On Tennis : A Library of America Special Publication &#8211; David Foster Wallace (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/string-theory-david-foster-wallace-on-tennis-a-library-of-america-special-publication-david-foster-wallace-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tennis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/string-theory-david-foster-wallace-on-tennis-a-library-of-america-special-publication-david-foster-wallace-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An instant classic of American sportswriting&#8211;the tennis essays of David Foster Wallace, &#8220;the best mind of his generation&#8221; (A. O. Scott) and &#8220;the best tennis-writer of all time&#8221; (New York Times) Gathered for the first time in a deluxe collector&#8217;s edition, here are David Foster Wallace&#8217;s legendary writings on tennis, five tour-de-force pieces written with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/string-theory-david-foster-wallace-on-tennis-a-library-of-america-special-publication-david-foster-wallace-abridged/">String Theory: David Foster Wallace On Tennis : A Library of America Special Publication &#8211; David Foster Wallace (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An instant classic of American sportswriting&#8211;the tennis essays of David Foster Wallace, &#8220;the best mind of his generation&#8221; (A. O. Scott) and &#8220;the best tennis-writer of all time&#8221; (New York Times)    </p>
<p>                    Gathered for the first time in a deluxe collector&#8217;s edition, here are David Foster Wallace&#8217;s legendary writings on tennis, five tour-de-force pieces written with a competitor&#8217;s insight and a fan&#8217;s obsessive enthusiasm. Wallace brings his dazzling literary magic to the game he loved as he celebrates the other-worldly genius of Roger Federer; offers a wickedly witty disection of Tracy Austin&#8217;s memoir; considers the artistry of Michael Joyce, a supremely disciplined athlete on the threshold of fame; resists the crush of commerce at the U.S. Open; and recalls his own career as a near-great junior player.     </p>
<p>                    Whiting Award-winning writer John Jeremiah Sullivan provides an introduction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/string-theory-david-foster-wallace-on-tennis-a-library-of-america-special-publication-david-foster-wallace-abridged/">String Theory: David Foster Wallace On Tennis : A Library of America Special Publication &#8211; David Foster Wallace (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Great Thinkers : Simple Tools from 60 Great Thinkers to Improve Your Life Today &#8211; The School of Life (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/great-thinkers-simple-tools-from-60-great-thinkers-to-improve-your-life-today-the-school-of-life-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dictionaries Of Biography (Who's Who)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dictionaries Of Quotations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/great-thinkers-simple-tools-from-60-great-thinkers-to-improve-your-life-today-the-school-of-life-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Great Thinkers is a collection of some of the most important ideas of Eastern and Western culture &#8211; drawn from the works of those philosophers, political theorists, sociologists, artists and novelists whom we believe have the most to offer to us today. We&#8217;ve worked hard to make the thinkers in this book clear, relevant [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/great-thinkers-simple-tools-from-60-great-thinkers-to-improve-your-life-today-the-school-of-life-abridged/">Great Thinkers : Simple Tools from 60 Great Thinkers to Improve Your Life Today &#8211; The School of Life (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Great Thinkers is a collection of some of the most important ideas of Eastern and Western culture &#8211; drawn from the works of those philosophers, political theorists, sociologists, artists and novelists whom we believe have the most to offer to us today.    </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;ve worked hard to make the thinkers in this book clear, relevant and charming, mining the history of knowledge to bring you the ideas we think have the greatest importance to our times.    </p>
<p>                    This 480-page book contains the canon of The School of Life, the gallery of individuals across the millennia who help to frame our intellectual project &#8211; and we have succeeded if, in the days and years ahead, you find yourself turning to our thinkers to illuminate the multiple dilemmas, joys and griefs of daily life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/great-thinkers-simple-tools-from-60-great-thinkers-to-improve-your-life-today-the-school-of-life-abridged/">Great Thinkers : Simple Tools from 60 Great Thinkers to Improve Your Life Today &#8211; The School of Life (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
