<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Globalization Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/globalization/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/globalization/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Globalization Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/globalization/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Winners Take All : The Elite Charade of Changing the World &#8211; Anand Giridharadas</title>
		<link>/winners-take-all-the-elite-charade-of-changing-the-world-anand-giridharadas/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/winners-take-all-the-elite-charade-of-changing-the-world-anand-giridharadas/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*The International Bestseller* &#8216;Superb, hugely enjoyable &#8230; a spirited examination of the hubris and hypocrisy of the super-rich who claim they are helping the world&#8217; Aditya Chakrabortty, Guardian What explains the spreading backlash against the global elite? In this revelatory investigation, Anand Giridharadas takes us into the inner sanctums of a new gilded age, showing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/winners-take-all-the-elite-charade-of-changing-the-world-anand-giridharadas/">Winners Take All : The Elite Charade of Changing the World &#8211; Anand Giridharadas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*The International Bestseller*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Superb, hugely enjoyable &#8230; a spirited examination of the hubris and  hypocrisy of the super-rich who claim they are helping the world&#8217; Aditya  Chakrabortty, Guardian    </p>
<p>                    What explains the spreading backlash against the global elite? In this revelatory investigation, Anand Giridharadas takes us into the inner sanctums of a new gilded age, showing how the elite follow a &#8216;win-win&#8217; logic, fighting for equality and justice any way they can &#8211; except ways that threaten their position at the top.     </p>
<p>                    But why should our gravest problems be solved by consultancies, technology companies and corporate-sponsored charities instead of public institutions and elected officials? Why should we rely on scraps from the winners? Trenchant and gripping, this is an indispensable guide and call to action for elites and citizens alike.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/winners-take-all-the-elite-charade-of-changing-the-world-anand-giridharadas/">Winners Take All : The Elite Charade of Changing the World &#8211; Anand Giridharadas</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>From Silk to Silicon: The Story of Globalization Through Ten Extraordinary Lives : The Story of Globalization Through Ten Extraordinary Lives &#8211; Jeffrey E Garten (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/from-silk-to-silicon-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-jeffrey-e-garten-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/from-silk-to-silicon-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-jeffrey-e-garten-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The story of globalization, the most powerful force in history, as told through the life and times of ten people who changed the world by their singular, spectacular accomplishments. This is the first book to look at the history of globalization through the lens of individuals who did something transformative, as opposed to describing globalization [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/from-silk-to-silicon-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-jeffrey-e-garten-abridged/">From Silk to Silicon: The Story of Globalization Through Ten Extraordinary Lives : The Story of Globalization Through Ten Extraordinary Lives &#8211; Jeffrey E Garten (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The story of globalization, the most powerful force in history, as told through the life and times of ten people who changed the world by their singular, spectacular accomplishments.    </p>
<p>                    This is the first book to look at the history of globalization through the lens of individuals who did something transformative, as opposed to describing globalization through trends, policies, or particular industries. From Silk to Silicon tells the story of who these men and women were, what they did, how they did it and how their achievements continue to shape our world today. They include:    </p>
<p>                    &#8221; Genghis Khan, who united east and west by conquest and by opening new trade routes built on groundbreaking transportation, communications, and management innovations.    </p>
<p>                    &#8221; Mayer Amschel Rothschild, who arose from an oppressive Jewish ghetto to establish the most powerful bank the world has seen, and ushered in an era of global finance.    </p>
<p>                    &#8221; Cyrus Field, who became the father of global communications by leading the effort to build the transatlantic telegraph, the forerunner to global radio, TV, and the worldwide Internet.    </p>
<p>                    &#8221; Margaret Thatcher, whose controversial policies opened the gusher of substantially free markets that linked economies across borders.    </p>
<p>                    &#8221; Andy Grove, a Hungarian refugee from the Nazis who built the company&#8217;Intel&#8217;that figured out how to manufacture complex computer chips on a mass, commercial scale and laid the foundation for Silicon Valley&#8217;s computer revolution.    </p>
<p>                    Through these stories Jeffrey E. Garten finds the common links between these figure and probes critical questions including: How much influence can any one person have in fundamentally changing the world? And how have past trends in globalization affected the present and how will they shape the future? From Silk to Silicon is an essential book to understanding the past&#8217;and the future&#8217;of the most powerful force of our times.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/from-silk-to-silicon-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-the-story-of-globalization-through-ten-extraordinary-lives-jeffrey-e-garten-abridged/">From Silk to Silicon: The Story of Globalization Through Ten Extraordinary Lives : The Story of Globalization Through Ten Extraordinary Lives &#8211; Jeffrey E Garten (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ai Superpowers : China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order &#8211; Kai-Fu Lee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ai-superpowers-china-silicon-valley-and-the-new-world-order-kai-fu-lee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ai-superpowers-china-silicon-valley-and-the-new-world-order-kai-fu-lee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES, USA TODAY, AND WALL STREET JOURNAL BESTSELLER &#8220;Kai-Fu Lee believes China will be the next tech-innovation superpower and in AI Superpowers: China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order, he explains why. Taiwan-born Lee is perfectly positioned for the task.&#8221;-New York Magazine In this thought-provoking book, Lee argues powerfully that because [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ai-superpowers-china-silicon-valley-and-the-new-world-order-kai-fu-lee-abridged/">Ai Superpowers : China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order &#8211; Kai-Fu Lee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES, USA TODAY, AND WALL STREET JOURNAL BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Kai-Fu Lee believes China will be the next tech-innovation superpower and in AI Superpowers: China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order, he explains why. Taiwan-born Lee is perfectly positioned for the task.&#8221;-New York Magazine     </p>
<p>                    In this thought-provoking book, Lee argues powerfully that because of the unprecedented developments in AI, dramatic changes will be happening much sooner than many of us expected. Indeed, as the US-Sino AI competition begins to heat up, Lee urges the US and China to both accept and to embrace the great responsibilities that come with significant technological power.     </p>
<p>                    Most experts already say that AI will have a devastating impact on blue-collar jobs. But Lee predicts that Chinese and American AI will have a strong impact on white-collar jobs as well. Is universal basic income the solution? In Lee&#8217;s opinion, probably not. But he provides a clear description of which jobs will be affected and how soon, which jobs can be enhanced with AI, and most importantly, how we can provide solutions to some of the most profound changes in the future of human history.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ai-superpowers-china-silicon-valley-and-the-new-world-order-kai-fu-lee-abridged/">Ai Superpowers : China, Silicon Valley, and the New World Order &#8211; Kai-Fu Lee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>IAN BREMMER WAS NAMED LINKEDIN&#8217;S #1 TOP INFLUENCER in 2017 &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; &#8216;Required reading to help repair a world in pieces and build a world at peace&#8217; &#8211; Antonio Guterres, United Nations Secretary General &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; &#8216;Ian Bremmer is provocative, controversial, and always intelligent about the state of the world, which he knows so well&#8217; &#8211; Christine [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IAN BREMMER WAS NAMED LINKEDIN&#8217;S #1 TOP INFLUENCER in 2017    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Required reading to help repair a world in pieces and build a world at peace&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Antonio Guterres, United Nations Secretary General     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ian Bremmer is provocative, controversial, and always intelligent about the state of the world, which he knows so well&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Christine Lagarde, Managing Director of the International Monetary Fund     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    From Brexit, to Donald Trump, to extremist parties in Europe and the developing world, populism has dominated recent headlines.     </p>
<p>                    But what explains the rise of leaders who stoke nationalist anger in their countries, from Le Pen to Erdogan? How long will the populist wave last? Who will be the winners and losers in this climate, and how can we defend the values of democracy, free trade and international cooperation?     </p>
<p>                    No one is better suited to explore these questions than Ian Bremmer, the CEO of the Eurasia Group and acclaimed Time magazine columnist. Analysing the social, economic and technological forces fuelling this new wave of populism, Bremmer explains why we&#8217;re witnessing a rejection of the democratic, global, cosmopolitan trends of the late 20th century. Us vs. Them is a definitive guide to navigating the shifting political landscape, for businesses looking to weather and survive the populist storm.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Global politics is a jungle today. Thank goodness Ian Bremmer can be your guide&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; David Miliband, president and CEO of the International Rescue Committee    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A masterful analysis of why global crashed and populism soared&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Adam Grant, author of Give and Take, and Originals and Option B with Sheryl Sandberg</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First as Tragedy, Then as Farce &#8211; Slavoj Zizek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/first-as-tragedy-then-as-farce-slavoj-zizek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Phenomenology & Existentialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/first-as-tragedy-then-as-farce-slavoj-zizek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Billions of dollars were hastily poured into the global banking system in a frantic attempt at financial stabilisation. So why has it not been possible to bring the same forces to bear in addressing world poverty and environmental crisis? In this take-no-prisoners analysis, Slavoj Zizek frames the moral failures of the modern world in terms [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-as-tragedy-then-as-farce-slavoj-zizek-abridged/">First as Tragedy, Then as Farce &#8211; Slavoj Zizek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Billions of dollars were hastily poured into the global banking system in a frantic attempt at financial stabilisation. So why has it not been possible to bring the same forces to bear in addressing world poverty and environmental crisis? In this take-no-prisoners analysis, Slavoj Zizek frames the moral failures of the modern world in terms of the epoch-making events of the first decade of this century. What he finds is the old one-two punch of history: the jab of tragedy, the right hook of farce. In the attacks of 9/11 and the global credit crunch, liberalism dies twice: as a political doctrine and as an economic theory. The election of Donald Trump only confirms the bankruptcy of a liberal order on its last legs. First as Tragedy, Then as Farce is a call for the left to reinvent itself in the light of our desperate historical situation. The time for liberal, moralistic blackmail is over.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-as-tragedy-then-as-farce-slavoj-zizek-abridged/">First as Tragedy, Then as Farce &#8211; Slavoj Zizek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Good Economics for Hard Times : Better Answers to Our Biggest Problems &#8211; Abhijit V. Banerjee, Esther Duflo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>FROM THE WINNERS OF THE 2019 NOBEL PRIZE IN ECONOMICS &#8216;Wonderfully refreshing . . . A must read&#8217; Thomas Piketty In this revolutionary book, prize-winning economists Abhijit V. Banerjee and Esther Duflo show how economics, when done right, can help us solve the thorniest social and political problems of our day. From immigration to inequality, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/">Good Economics for Hard Times : Better Answers to Our Biggest Problems &#8211; Abhijit V. Banerjee, Esther Duflo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>FROM THE WINNERS OF THE 2019 NOBEL PRIZE IN ECONOMICS    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderfully refreshing . . . A must read&#8217; Thomas Piketty     </p>
<p>                    In this revolutionary book, prize-winning economists Abhijit V. Banerjee and Esther Duflo show how economics, when done right, can help us solve the thorniest social and political problems of our day. From immigration to inequality, slowing growth to accelerating climate change, we have the resources to address the challenges we face but we are so often blinded by ideology.    </p>
<p>                    Original, provocative and urgent, Good Economics for Hard Times offers the new thinking that we need. It builds on cutting-edge research in economics &#8211; and years of exploring the most effective solutions to alleviate extreme poverty &#8211; to make a persuasive case for an intelligent interventionism and a society built on compassion and respect. A much-needed antidote to polarized discourse, this book shines a light to help us appreciate and understand our precariously balanced world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/good-economics-for-hard-times-better-answers-to-our-biggest-problems-abhijit-v-banerjee-esther-duflo-abridged/">Good Economics for Hard Times : Better Answers to Our Biggest Problems &#8211; Abhijit V. Banerjee, Esther Duflo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Information: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT    </p>
<p>                    We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need to be late.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A master class &#8230; As a guide for perplexed Westerners, this book is very hard to beat &#8230; an honest, cohesive explanation for why the world is the way it is, without miracle cures or scapegoats&#8217; John Micklethwait, The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; admirably honest &#8230; injects a badly needed dose of optimism into the modern debate&#8217; Gillian Tett, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;His main piece of advice for individuals, corporations, and countries is clear: Take a deep breath and adapt. This world isn&#8217;t going to wait for you&#8217; Fortune    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A humane and empathetic book&#8217; David Henkin, The Washington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brave New War : The Next Stage of Terrorism and the End of Globalization &#8211; John Robb, Foreword by James Fallows (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brave-new-war-the-next-stage-of-terrorism-and-the-end-of-globalization-john-robb-foreword-by-james-fallows-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism, Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brave-new-war-the-next-stage-of-terrorism-and-the-end-of-globalization-john-robb-foreword-by-james-fallows-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For my money, John Robb, a former Air Force officer and tech guru, is the futurists&#8217; futurist. &#8211;Slate The counterterrorism expert John Robb reveals how the same technology that has enabled globalization also allows terrorists and criminals to join forces against larger adversaries with relative ease and to carry out small, inexpensive actions&#8211;like sabotaging an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-war-the-next-stage-of-terrorism-and-the-end-of-globalization-john-robb-foreword-by-james-fallows-abridged/">Brave New War : The Next Stage of Terrorism and the End of Globalization &#8211; John Robb, Foreword by James Fallows (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For my money, John Robb, a former Air Force officer and tech guru, is the futurists&#8217; futurist.<br />
                    &#8211;Slate    </p>
<p>                    The counterterrorism expert John Robb reveals how the same technology that has enabled globalization also allows terrorists and criminals to join forces against larger adversaries with relative ease and to carry out small, inexpensive actions&#8211;like sabotaging an oil pipeline&#8211;that generate a huge return. He shows how combating the shutdown of the world&#8217;s oil, high-tech, and financial markets could cost us the thing we&#8217;ve come to value the most&#8211;worldwide economic and cultural integration&#8211;and what we must do now to safeguard against this new method of warfare.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-war-the-next-stage-of-terrorism-and-the-end-of-globalization-john-robb-foreword-by-james-fallows-abridged/">Brave New War : The Next Stage of Terrorism and the End of Globalization &#8211; John Robb, Foreword by James Fallows (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Splendid Exchange : How Trade Shaped the World &#8211; William J Bernstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-splendid-exchange-how-trade-shaped-the-world-william-j-bernstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economic & Trade Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-splendid-exchange-how-trade-shaped-the-world-william-j-bernstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A sweeping narrative history of world trade&#8211;from Sumer in 3000 BC to the firestorm over globalization today&#8211;that brilliantly explores trade&#8217;s colorful and contentious past and provides fresh insights into social, political, cultural, and economic history, as well as a timely assessment of trade&#8217;s future. Adam Smith wrote that man has an intrinsic &#8220;propensity to truck, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-splendid-exchange-how-trade-shaped-the-world-william-j-bernstein-abridged/">A Splendid Exchange : How Trade Shaped the World &#8211; William J Bernstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A sweeping narrative history of world trade&#8211;from Sumer in 3000 BC to the firestorm over globalization today&#8211;that brilliantly explores trade&#8217;s colorful and contentious past and provides fresh insights into social, political, cultural, and economic history, as well as a timely assessment of trade&#8217;s future.    </p>
<p>                    Adam Smith wrote that man has an intrinsic &#8220;propensity to truck, barter, and exchange one thing for another.&#8221; But how did trade evolve to the point where we don&#8217;t think twice about biting into an apple from the other side of the world?    </p>
<p>                    In A Splendid Exchange, William J. Bernstein tells the extraordinary story of global commerce from its prehistoric origins to the myriad controversies surrounding it today. He transports readers from ancient sailing ships that brought the silk trade from China to Rome in the second century to the rise and fall of the Portuguese monopoly in spices in the sixteenth; from the rush for sugar that brought the British to Jamaica in 1655 to the American trade battles of the early twentieth century; from key innovations such as steam, steel, and refrigeration to the modern era of televisions from Taiwan, lettuce from Mexico, and T-shirts from China.    </p>
<p>                    Along the way, Bernstein examines how our age-old dependency on trade has contributed to our planet&#8217;s agricultural bounty, stimulated intellectual progress, and made us both prosperous and vulnerable. Although the impulse to trade often takes a backseat to xenophobia and war, Bernstein concludes that trade is ultimately a force for good among nations, and he argues that societies are far more successful and stable when they are involved in vigorous trade with their neighbors.    </p>
<p>                    Lively, authoritative, and astonishing in scope, A Splendid Exchange is a riveting narrative that views trade and globalization not in political terms, but rather as an evolutionary process as old as war and religion&#8211;a historical constant&#8211;that will continue to foster the growth of intellectual capital, shrink the world, and propel the trajectory of the human species.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-splendid-exchange-how-trade-shaped-the-world-william-j-bernstein-abridged/">A Splendid Exchange : How Trade Shaped the World &#8211; William J Bernstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Third Pillar : How Markets and the State Leave the Community Behind &#8211; Raghuram Rajan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-third-pillar-how-markets-and-the-state-leave-the-community-behind-raghuram-rajan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-third-pillar-how-markets-and-the-state-leave-the-community-behind-raghuram-rajan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FINANCIAL TIMES AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019 From one of the most important economic thinkers of our time, a brilliant and far-seeing analysis of the current populist backlash against globalization and how revitalising community can save liberal market democracy. Raghuram Rajan, author of the 2010 FT &#038; Goldman-Sachs [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-pillar-how-markets-and-the-state-leave-the-community-behind-raghuram-rajan-abridged/">The Third Pillar : How Markets and the State Leave the Community Behind &#8211; Raghuram Rajan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE FINANCIAL TIMES AND MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD 2019    </p>
<p>                                From one of the most important economic thinkers of our time, a brilliant and far-seeing analysis of the current populist backlash against globalization and how revitalising community can save liberal market democracy.     </p>
<p>                              Raghuram Rajan, author of the 2010 FT &#038; Goldman-Sachs Book of the Year Fault Lines, has an unparalleled vantage point onto the social and economic consequences of globalization and their ultimate effect on politics and society.     </p>
<p>                              In The Third Pillar he offers up a magnificent big-picture framework for understanding how three key forces &#8211; the economy, society, and the state &#8211; interact, why things begin to break down, and how we can find our way back to a more secure and stable plane.    </p>
<p>                              The &#8216;third pillar&#8217; of the title is society. Economists all too often understand their field as the relationship between the market and government, and leave social issues for other people. That&#8217;s not just myopic, Rajan argues; it&#8217;s dangerous. All economics is actually socioeconomics &#8211; all markets are embedded in a web of human relations, values and norms. As he shows, throughout history, technological innovations have ripped the market out of old webs and led to violent backlashes, and to what we now call populism. Eventually, a new equilibrium is reached, but it can be ugly and messy, especially if done wrong.     </p>
<p>                              Right now, we&#8217;re doing it wrong. As markets scale up, government scales up with it, concentrating economic and political power in flourishing central hubs and leaving the periphery to decompose, figuratively and even literally. Instead, Rajan offers a way to rethink the relationship between the market and civil society and argues for a return to strengthening and empowering local communities as an antidote to growing despair and unrest.    </p>
<p>                              The Third Pillar is a masterpiece of explication, a book that will be a classic of its kind for its offering of a wise, authoritative and humane explanation of the forces that have wrought such a sea change in our lives. His ultimate argument that decision-making has to be watered at the grass roots or our democracy will continue to wither is sure to be both provocative and agenda-setting across the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-third-pillar-how-markets-and-the-state-leave-the-community-behind-raghuram-rajan-abridged/">The Third Pillar : How Markets and the State Leave the Community Behind &#8211; Raghuram Rajan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the bestselling tradition of The World Is Flat and The Next 100 Years comes a contrarian and eye-opening assessment of American power. In THE ACCIDENTAL SUPERPOWER, international strategist Peter Zeihan examines how the hard rules of geography are eroding the American commitment to free trade; how much of the planet is aging into a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/">The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the bestselling tradition of The World Is Flat and The Next 100 Years comes a contrarian and eye-opening assessment of American power.    </p>
<p>                    In THE ACCIDENTAL SUPERPOWER, international strategist Peter Zeihan examines how the hard rules of geography are eroding the American commitment to free trade; how much of the planet is aging into a mass retirement that will enervate capital supplies; and how it is the ever-ravenous American economy that is rapidly approaching energy independence. Combined, these factors are overturning the global system and ushering in a new (dis)order. For most, that is a disaster-in-waiting, but not for the Americans. The shale revolution allows Americans to sidestep a dangerous energy market. Only the U.S. boasts a youth population large enough to escape the sucking maw of global aging. Geography will matter more than ever in a de-globalizing world, and America&#8217;s geography is simply sublime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/">The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Great Escape : Health, Wealth, and the Origins of Inequality &#8211; Angus Deaton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-great-escape-health-wealth-and-the-origins-of-inequality-angus-deaton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Safety Law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-great-escape-health-wealth-and-the-origins-of-inequality-angus-deaton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The world is a better place than it used to be. People are healthier, wealthier, and live longer. Yet the escapes from destitution by so many has left gaping inequalities between people and nations. In The Great Escape, Angus Deaton&#8211;one of the foremost experts on economic development and on poverty&#8211;tells the remarkable story of how, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-escape-health-wealth-and-the-origins-of-inequality-angus-deaton-abridged/">The Great Escape : Health, Wealth, and the Origins of Inequality &#8211; Angus Deaton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The world is a better place than it used to be. People are healthier, wealthier, and live longer. Yet the escapes from destitution by so many has left gaping inequalities between people and nations. In The Great Escape, Angus Deaton&#8211;one of the foremost experts on economic development and on poverty&#8211;tells the remarkable story of how, beginning 250 years ago, some parts of the world experienced sustained progress, opening up gaps and setting the stage for today&#8217;s disproportionately unequal world. Deaton takes an in-depth look at the historical and ongoing patterns behind the health and wealth of nations, and addresses what needs to be done to help those left behind. Deaton describes vast innovations and wrenching setbacks: the successes of antibiotics, pest control, vaccinations, and clean water on the one hand, and disastrous famines and the HIV/AIDS epidemic on the other. He examines the United States, a nation that has prospered but is today experiencing slower growth and increasing inequality. He also considers how economic growth in India and China has improved the lives of more than a billion people. Deaton argues that international aid has been ineffective and even harmful.<br />
                    He suggests alternative efforts&#8211;including reforming incentives to drug companies and lifting trade restrictions&#8211;that will allow the developing world to bring about its own Great Escape. Demonstrating how changes in health and living standards have transformed our lives, The Great Escape is a powerful guide to addressing the well-being of all nations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-great-escape-health-wealth-and-the-origins-of-inequality-angus-deaton-abridged/">The Great Escape : Health, Wealth, and the Origins of Inequality &#8211; Angus Deaton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
