<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Political Science &amp; Theory Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/political-science-theory/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/political-science-theory/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Political Science &amp; Theory Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/political-science-theory/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>American Dialogue : The Founders and Us &#8211; Joseph J. Ellis</title>
		<link>/american-dialogue-the-founders-and-us-joseph-j-ellis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rebellions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uprisings]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-dialogue-the-founders-and-us-joseph-j-ellis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The award-winning author of Founding Brothers and The Quartet now gives us a deeply insightful examination of the relevance of the views of George Washington, Thomas Jefferson, James Madison, and John Adams to some of the most divisive issues in America today. The story of history is a ceaseless conversation between past and present, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-dialogue-the-founders-and-us-joseph-j-ellis/">American Dialogue : The Founders and Us &#8211; Joseph J. Ellis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The award-winning author of Founding Brothers and The Quartet now gives us a deeply insightful examination of the relevance of the views of George Washington, Thomas Jefferson, James Madison, and John Adams to some of the most divisive issues in America today.     </p>
<p>                    The story of history is a ceaseless conversation between past and present, and in American Dialogue Joseph J. Ellis focuses the conversation on the often-asked question What would the Founding Fathers think? He examines four of our most seminal historical figures through the prism of particular topics, using the perspective of the present to shed light on their views and, in turn, to make clear how their now centuries-old ideas illuminate the disturbing impasse of today&#8217;s political conflicts. He discusses Jefferson and the issue of racism, Adams and the specter of economic inequality, Washington and American imperialism, Madison and the doctrine of original intent. Through these juxtapositions&#8211;and in his hallmark dramatic and compelling narrative voice&#8211;Ellis illuminates the obstacles and pitfalls paralyzing contemporary discussions of these fundamentally important issues.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-dialogue-the-founders-and-us-joseph-j-ellis/">American Dialogue : The Founders and Us &#8211; Joseph J. Ellis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fifth Risk : Undoing Democracy &#8211; Michael Lewis</title>
		<link>/the-fifth-risk-undoing-democracy-michael-lewis/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fifth-risk-undoing-democracy-michael-lewis/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Will set your hair on end&#8217; Telegraph, Top 50 Books of the Year &#8216;Life is what happens between Michael Lewis books. I forgot to breathe while reading The Fifth Risk&#8217; Michael Hofmann, TLS, Books of the Year The phenomenal new book from the international bestselling author of The Big Short &#8216;The election happened &#8230; And [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fifth-risk-undoing-democracy-michael-lewis/">The Fifth Risk : Undoing Democracy &#8211; Michael Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Will set your hair on end&#8217; Telegraph, Top 50 Books of the Year</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Life is what happens between Michael Lewis books. I forgot to breathe while reading The Fifth Risk&#8217; Michael Hofmann, TLS, Books of the Year</p>
<p>                    The phenomenal new book from the international bestselling author of The Big Short</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The election happened &#8230; And then there was radio silence.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    The   morning after Trump was elected president, the people who ran the US   Department of Energy &#8211; an agency that deals with some of the most   powerful risks facing humanity &#8211; waited to welcome the incoming   administration&#8217;s transition team. Nobody appeared. Across the US   government, the same thing happened: nothing.</p>
<p>                    People don&#8217;t  notice  when stuff goes right. That is the stuff government does. It  manages  everything that underpins our lives from funding free school  meals, to  policing rogue nuclear activity, to predicting extreme  weather events.  It steps in where private investment fears to tread,  innovates and  creates knowledge, assesses extreme long-term risk. </p>
<p>                    And now, government is under attack. By its own leaders.</p>
<p>                    In The Fifth Risk,   Michael Lewis reveals the combustible cocktail of wilful ignorance and   venality that is fuelling the destruction of a country&#8217;s fabric. All  of  this, Lewis shows, exposes America and the world to the biggest risk  of  all. It is what you never learned that might have saved you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fifth-risk-undoing-democracy-michael-lewis/">The Fifth Risk : Undoing Democracy &#8211; Michael Lewis</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>McMindfulness : How Mindfulness Became the New Capitalist Spirituality &#8211; Ronald Purser</title>
		<link>/mcmindfulness-how-mindfulness-became-the-new-capitalist-spirituality-ronald-purser/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Body]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mcmindfulness-how-mindfulness-became-the-new-capitalist-spirituality-ronald-purser/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mindfulness is now all the rage. From celebrity endorsements to monks, neuroscientists and meditation coaches rubbing shoulders with CEOs at the World Economic Forum in Davos, it is clear that mindfulness has gone mainstream. Some have even called it a revolution. But what if, instead of changing the world, mindfulness has become a banal form [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mcmindfulness-how-mindfulness-became-the-new-capitalist-spirituality-ronald-purser/">McMindfulness : How Mindfulness Became the New Capitalist Spirituality &#8211; Ronald Purser</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mindfulness is now all the rage. From celebrity endorsements to monks, neuroscientists and meditation coaches rubbing shoulders with CEOs at the World Economic Forum in Davos, it is clear that mindfulness has gone mainstream. Some have even called it a revolution. But what if, instead of changing the world, mindfulness has become a banal form of capitalist spirituality that mindlessly avoids social and political transformation, reinforcing the neoliberal status quo?</p>
<p>                    In McMindfulness, Ronald Purser debunks the so-called &#8220;mindfulness revolution,&#8221; exposing how corporations, schools, governments and the military have coopted it as a technique for social control and<br />
                    self-pacification. </p>
<p>                    A lively and razor-sharp critique, Purser busts the myths its salesmen rely on, challenging the narrative that stress is self-imposed and mindfulness is the cure-all. If we are to harness the truly revolutionary potential of mindfulness, we have to cast off its neoliberal shackles, liberating mindfulness for a collective awakening.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mcmindfulness-how-mindfulness-became-the-new-capitalist-spirituality-ronald-purser/">McMindfulness : How Mindfulness Became the New Capitalist Spirituality &#8211; Ronald Purser</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rage &#8211; Bob Woodward</title>
		<link>/rage-bob-woodward/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rage-bob-woodward/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BOB WOODWARD&#8217;S NEW BOOK, RAGE, IS AN UNPRECEDENTED AND INTIMATE TOUR DE FORCE OF NEW REPORTING ON THE TRUMP PRESIDENCY FACING A GLOBAL PANDEMIC, ECONOMIC DISASTER AND RACIAL UNREST. Woodward, the No 1 international bestselling author of Fear: Trump in the White House, has uncovered the precise moment the president was warned that the Covid-19 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rage-bob-woodward/">Rage &#8211; Bob Woodward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BOB WOODWARD&#8217;S NEW BOOK, RAGE, IS AN UNPRECEDENTED AND INTIMATE TOUR DE FORCE OF NEW REPORTING ON THE TRUMP PRESIDENCY FACING A GLOBAL PANDEMIC, ECONOMIC DISASTER AND RACIAL UNREST.</p>
<p>                     Woodward, the No 1 international bestselling author of Fear: Trump in the White House, has uncovered the precise moment the president was warned that the Covid-19 epidemic would be the biggest national security threat to his presidency. In dramatic detail, Woodward takes readers into the Oval Office as Trump&#8217;s head pops up when he is told in January 2020 that the pandemic could reach the scale of the 1918 Spanish Flu that killed 675,000 Americans.</p>
<p>                     In 17 on-the-record interviews with Woodward over seven volatile months &#8211; an utterly vivid window into Trump&#8217;s mind &#8211; the president provides a self-portrait that is part denial and part combative interchange mixed with surprising moments of doubt as he glimpses the perils in the presidency and what he calls the &#8216;dynamite behind every door&#8217;. At key decision points, Rage shows how Trump&#8217;s responses to the crises of 2020 were rooted in the instincts, habits and style he developed during his first three years as president.</p>
<p>                     Revisiting the earliest days of the Trump presidency, Rage reveals how Secretary of Defense James Mattis, Secretary of State Rex Tillerson and Director of National Intelligence Dan Coats struggled to keep the country safe as the president dismantled any semblance of collegial national security decision making. Rage draws from hundreds of hours of interviews with first-hand witnesses as well as participants&#8217; notes, emails, diaries, calendars and confidential documents.</p>
<p>                     Woodward obtained 25 never-seen personal letters exchanged between Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un, who describes the bond between the two leaders as out of a &#8216;fantasy film&#8217;. Trump insists to Woodward he will triumph over Covid-19 and the economic calamity. &#8216;Don&#8217;t worry about it, Bob. Okay?&#8217; Trump told the author in July. &#8216;Don&#8217;t worry about it. We&#8217;ll get to do another book. You&#8217;ll find I was right.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rage-bob-woodward/">Rage &#8211; Bob Woodward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</title>
		<link>/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER** In twenty-one bite-sized lessons, Yuval Noah Harari explores what it means to be human in an age of bewilderment. &#8217;21 Lessons is, simply put, a crucial book&#8217; Adam Kay How can we protect ourselves from nuclear war, ecological cataclysms and technological disruptions? What can we do about the epidemic of fake [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/">21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER**</p>
<p>                    In twenty-one bite-sized lessons, Yuval Noah Harari explores what it means to be human in an age of bewilderment. </p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                              &#8217;21 Lessons is, simply put, a crucial book&#8217; Adam Kay</p>
<p>                    How can we protect ourselves from nuclear war, ecological cataclysms and technological disruptions? What can we do about the epidemic of fake news or the threat of terrorism? What should we teach our children? </p>
<p>                    Yuval Noah Harari takes us on a thrilling journey through today&#8217;s most urgent issues. The golden thread running through his exhilarating new book is the challenge of maintaining our collective and individual focus in the face of constant and disorienting change.</p>
<p>                    Are we still capable of understanding the world we have created?</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating&#8230; compelling&#8230; [Harari] has teed up a crucial global conversation about how to take on the problems of the 21st century&#8217; Bill Gates, New York Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Truly mind-expanding&#8230; Ultra-topical&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/21-lessons-for-the-21st-century-yuval-noah-harari/">21 Lessons for the 21st Century &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond</title>
		<link>/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A riveting and illuminating tour of how nations deal with crises &#8211; which might hopefully help humanity as a whole deal with our present global crisis&#8217; YUVAL NOAH HARARI, author of SAPIENS ** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Author of the landmark international bestsellers Guns, Germs and Steel and Collapse, Jared Diamond has transformed our understanding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond/">Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A riveting and illuminating tour of how nations deal with crises &#8211; which might hopefully help humanity as a whole deal with our present global crisis&#8217; YUVAL NOAH HARARI, author of SAPIENS </p>
<p>                    ** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** </p>
<p>                    Author of the landmark international bestsellers Guns, Germs and Steel and Collapse, Jared Diamond has transformed our understanding of what makes civilizations rise and fall. Now, at a time when crises are erupting around the world, heexplores what makes certain nations resilient, and reveals the factors that influence how nations and individuals can respond to enormous challenges. </p>
<p>                    In a riveting journey into the recent past, he traces how six distinctive modern nations &#8211; Finland, Chile, Indonesia, Japan, Germany and Australia &#8211; have survived defining catastrophes, and identifies patterns in their recovery. Looking ahead, he investigates the risk that the United States and other countries, faced by grave threat, are set on a course towards catastrophe. </p>
<p>                    Adding a rich psychological dimension to the in-depth history, geography, biology and anthropology that underpin all of Diamond&#8217;s writing, Upheaval is epic in scope, but also his most personal book yet.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating &#8230; I finished the book even more optimistic about our ability to solve problems than I started&#8217; BILL GATES</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Jared Diamond does it again: another rich, original and fascinating chapter in the human saga &#8211; with vital lessons for our difficult times&#8217; STEVEN PINKER</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond/">Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</title>
		<link>/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019 Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump. The 2016 election was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019</p>
<p>                    Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump.</p>
<p>                    The 2016 election was a watershed for the United States. But, as Tim Alberta explains in American Carnage, to understand Trump&#8217;s victory is to view him not as the creator of this era of polarization and bruising partisanship, but rather as its most manifest consequence.</p>
<p>                    American Carnage is the story of a president&#8217;s rise based on a country&#8217;s evolution and a party&#8217;s collapse. As George W. Bush left office with record-low approval ratings and Barack Obama led a Democratic takeover of Washington, Republicans faced a moment of reckoning: They had no vision, no generation of new leaders, and no energy in the party&#8217;s base. Yet Obama&#8217;s forceful pursuit of his progressive agenda, coupled with the nation&#8217;s rapidly changing cultural and demographic landscape, lit a fire under the right, returning Republicans to power and inviting a bloody struggle for the party&#8217;s identity in the post-Bush era. The factions that emerged-one led by absolutists like Jim Jordan and Ted Cruz, the other led by pragmatists like John Boehner and Mitch McConnell-engaged in a series of devastating internecine clashes and attempted coups for control. With the GOP&#8217;s internal fissures rendering it legislatively impotent, and that impotence fueling a growing resentment toward the political class and its institutions, the stage was set for an outsider to crash the party. When Trump descended a gilded escalator to announce his run in the summer of 2015, the candidate had met the moment.</p>
<p>                    Only by viewing Trump as the culmination of a decade-long civil war inside the Republican Party-and of the parallel sense of cultural, socioeconomic, and technological disruption during that period-can we appreciate how he won the White House and consider the fundamental questions at the center of America&#8217;s current turmoil. How did a party obsessed with the national debt vote for trillion-dollar deficits and record-setting spending increases? How did the party of compassionate conservatism become the party of Muslim bans and walls? How did the party of family values elect a thrice-divorced philanderer? And, most important, how long can such a party survive?</p>
<p>                     Loaded with exclusive reporting and based off hundreds of interviews-including with key players such as President Trump, Paul Ryan, Ted Cruz, John Boehner, Mitch McConnell, Jim DeMint, and Reince Priebus, and many others-American Carnage takes us behind the scenes of this tumultuous period as we&#8217;ve never seen it before and establishes Tim Alberta as the premier chronicler of this political era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</title>
		<link>/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As President Trump&#8217;s National Security Advisor, John Bolton spent many of his 453 days in the room where it happened, and the facts speak for themselves. The result is a White House memoir that is the most comprehensive and substantial account of the Trump Administration, and one of the few to date by a top-level [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/">The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As President Trump&#8217;s National Security Advisor, John Bolton spent many of his 453 days in the room where it happened, and the facts speak for themselves. </p>
<p>                    The result is a White House memoir that is the most comprehensive and substantial account of the Trump Administration, and one of the few to date by a top-level official. With almost daily access to the President, John Bolton has produced a precise rendering of his days in and around the Oval Office. What Bolton saw astonished him: a President for whom getting reelected was the only thing that mattered, even if it meant endangering or weakening the nation. &#8220;I am hard-pressed to identify any significant Trump decision during my tenure that wasn&#8217;t driven by reelection calculations,&#8221; he writes. In fact, he argues that the House committed impeachment malpractice by keeping their prosecution focused narrowly on Ukraine when Trump&#8217;s Ukraine-like transgressions existed across the full range of his foreign policy-and Bolton documents exactly what those were, and attempts by him and others in the Administration to raise alarms about them.</p>
<p>                    He shows a President addicted to chaos, who embraced our enemies and spurned our friends, and was deeply suspicious of his own government. In Bolton&#8217;s telling, all this helped put Trump on the bizarre road to impeachment. &#8220;The differences between this presidency and previous ones I had served were stunning,&#8221; writes Bolton, who worked for Reagan, Bush 41, and Bush 43. He discovered a President who thought foreign policy is like closing a real estate deal-about personal relationships, made-for-TV showmanship, and advancing his own interests. As a result, the US lost an opportunity to confront its deepening threats, and in cases like China, Russia, Iran, and North Korea ended up in a more vulnerable place. </p>
<p>                    Bolton&#8217;s account starts with his long march to the West Wing as Trump and others woo him for the National Security job. The minute he lands, he has to deal with Syria&#8217;s chemical attack on the city of Douma, and the crises after that never stop. As he writes in the opening pages, &#8220;If you don&#8217;t like turmoil, uncertainty, and risk-all the while being constantly overwhelmed with information, decisions to be made, and sheer amount of work-and enlivened by international and domestic personality and ego conflicts beyond description, try something else.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    The turmoil, conflicts, and egos are all there-from the upheaval in Venezuela, to the erratic and manipulative moves of North Korea&#8217;s Kim Jong Un, to the showdowns at the G7 summits, the calculated warmongering by Iran, the crazy plan to bring the Taliban to Camp David, and the placating of an authoritarian China that ultimately exposed the world to its lethal lies. But this seasoned public servant also has a great eye for the Washington inside game, and his story is full of wit and wry humor about how he saw it played.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/">The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On Tyranny : Twenty Lessons from the Twentieth Century &#8211; Timothy Snyder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-tyranny-twenty-lessons-from-the-twentieth-century-timothy-snyder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-tyranny-twenty-lessons-from-the-twentieth-century-timothy-snyder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** &#8216;A sort of survival book, a sort of symptom-diagnosis manual in terms of losing your democracy and what tyranny and authoritarianism look like up close&#8217; Rachel Maddow &#8216;These 128 pages are a brief primer in every important thing we might have learned from the history of the last century, and all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-tyranny-twenty-lessons-from-the-twentieth-century-timothy-snyder-abridged/">On Tyranny : Twenty Lessons from the Twentieth Century &#8211; Timothy Snyder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A sort of survival book, a sort of symptom-diagnosis manual in terms of losing your democracy and what tyranny and authoritarianism look like up close&#8217; Rachel Maddow    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;These 128 pages are a brief primer in every important thing we might have learned from the history of the last century, and all that we appear to have forgotten&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                     History does not repeat, but it does instruct.    </p>
<p>                     In the twentieth century, European democracies collapsed into fascism, Nazism and communism. These were movements in which a leader or a party claimed to give voice to the people, promised to protect them from global existential threats, and rejected reason in favour of myth. European history shows us that societies can break, democracies can fall, ethics can collapse, and ordinary people can find themselves in unimaginable circumstances.    </p>
<p>                     History can familiarise, and it can warn. Today, we are no wiser than the Europeans who saw democracy yield to totalitarianism in the twentieth century. But when the political order seems imperilled, our advantage is that we can learn from their experience to resist the advance of tyranny.    </p>
<p>                     Now is a good time to do so.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-tyranny-twenty-lessons-from-the-twentieth-century-timothy-snyder-abridged/">On Tyranny : Twenty Lessons from the Twentieth Century &#8211; Timothy Snyder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EU & European Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** The Sunday Times #1 Bestseller** &#8216;One of the greatest political memoirs of all time&#8217; Guardian What happens when you take on the European establishment? Read as world-famous, provocative economist, and former Greece finance minister, Yanis Varoufakis, blows the lid on his battle with EU officials over the Greek debt crisis. Varoufakis sparked one of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/">Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** The Sunday Times #1 Bestseller**    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the greatest political memoirs of all time&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    What happens when you take on the European establishment?     </p>
<p>                    Read as world-famous, provocative economist, and former Greece finance minister, Yanis Varoufakis, blows the lid on his battle with EU officials over the Greek debt crisis.     </p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                              Varoufakis sparked one of the most spectacular and controversial battles in recent political history with his attempt to renegotiate Greece&#8217;s relationship with the European Union. Yet despite the mass support of the Greek people, and simple logic of his arguments, he succeeded only in provoking the fury of Europe&#8217;s political, financial and media elite.<br />
                                                                                                                                                                                          Exposing the real business taking place behind the EU&#8217;s closed doors, Varoufakis reveals all in this fearless, personal account. Adults In The Room is an extraordinary tale of brinkmanship, hypocrisy, collusion and betrayal that will shake the European and economic establishment to its foundations.     </p>
<p>                    Varoufakis is sending out an urgent wake-up call to renew European democracy before it is too late.    </p>
<p>                    **ONE OF THE GUARDIAN&#8217;S 100 BEST BOOKS OF THE 21st CENTURY**</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/">Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dark Money : how a secretive group of billionaires is trying to buy political control in the US &#8211; Jane Mayer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A LITHUB BOOK OF THE DECADE. The US is one of the largest democracies in the world &#8211; or is it? America is experiencing an age of profound economic inequality. Employee protections have been decimated, and state welfare is virtually non-existent, while hedge fund billionaires are grossly under-taxed and big businesses make astounding profits at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/">Dark Money : how a secretive group of billionaires is trying to buy political control in the US &#8211; Jane Mayer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A LITHUB BOOK OF THE DECADE.    </p>
<p>                    The US is one of the largest democracies in the world &#8211; or is it?    </p>
<p>                    America is experiencing an age of profound economic inequality. Employee protections have been decimated, and state welfare is virtually non-existent, while hedge fund billionaires are grossly under-taxed and big businesses make astounding profits at the expense of the environment and of their workers.    </p>
<p>                    How did this come about, and who were the driving forces behind it?    </p>
<p>                    In this powerful and meticulously researched work of investigative journalism, New Yorker staff writer Jane Mayer exposes the network of billionaires trying to buy the US electoral system &#8211; and succeeding. Led by libertarian industrialists the Koch brothers, they believe that taxes are a form of tyranny and that government oversight of business is an assault on freedom. Together, they have spent hundreds of millions of dollars influencing politicians and voters, and hijacking American democracy for their own ends.    </p>
<p>                    Dark Money brilliantly illuminates a shady corner of US politics. It is essential reading for anybody interested in the future of democracy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-money-how-a-secretive-group-of-billionaires-is-trying-to-buy-political-control-in-the-us-jane-mayer-abridged/">Dark Money : how a secretive group of billionaires is trying to buy political control in the US &#8211; Jane Mayer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Times book of the year A Guardian book of the year &#8216;Magnificent&#8217;The Times &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; New Statesman &#8216;It filled me with hope&#8217; Zadie Smith What happens to our behaviour when we live most of our lives online? What does it mean to &#8216;always be optimising&#8217;? And what is it about scams and the millennial generation? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/">Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Times book of the year<br />
                              A Guardian book of the year<br />
                              &#8216;Magnificent&#8217;The Times<br />
                              &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; New Statesman<br />
                              &#8216;It filled me with hope&#8217; Zadie Smith<br />
                              What happens to our behaviour when we live most of our lives online? What does it mean to &#8216;always be optimising&#8217;? And what is it about scams and the millennial generation?    </p>
<p>                              Offering nuanced and witty reflections on feminism, reality TV, the internet, drugs, identity and more, Trick Mirror is a multifaceted, thought-provoking and entertaining response to our zeitgeist &#8211; a must-read for anyone interested in the way we live and think today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/">Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Clash Of Civilizations : And The Remaking Of World Order &#8211; Samuel P. Huntington (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-clash-of-civilizations-and-the-remaking-of-world-order-samuel-p-huntington-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defence Strategy, Planning & Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-clash-of-civilizations-and-the-remaking-of-world-order-samuel-p-huntington-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 1993 the esteemed journal FOREIGN AFFAIRS published an article entitled &#8220;The Clash of Civilizations?&#8221; by Samuel P. Huntington. According to the journal&#8217;s editors it went on to generate more discussion than anything they had published since the Second World War. In the article, Huntington posed the question whether conflicts between civilizations would dominate the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-clash-of-civilizations-and-the-remaking-of-world-order-samuel-p-huntington-abridged/">The Clash Of Civilizations : And The Remaking Of World Order &#8211; Samuel P. Huntington (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 1993 the esteemed journal FOREIGN AFFAIRS published an article entitled &#8220;The Clash of Civilizations?&#8221; by Samuel P. Huntington. According to the journal&#8217;s editors it went on to generate more discussion than anything they had published since the Second World War. In the article, Huntington posed the question whether conflicts between civilizations would dominate the future of world politics. In the book, he gives the answer, showing not only how clashes between civilizations are the greatest threat to world peace but also how an international order based on civilizations is the best safeguard against war. Since September 11, his thesis has seemed even more prescient and acute. THE CLASH OF CIVILIZATIONS AND THE REMAKING OF WORLD ORDER is now recognised as a classic study of international relations in an increasingly uncertain world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-clash-of-civilizations-and-the-remaking-of-world-order-samuel-p-huntington-abridged/">The Clash Of Civilizations : And The Remaking Of World Order &#8211; Samuel P. Huntington (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Mumbo-Jumbo Conquered the World : A Short History of Modern Delusions &#8211; Francis Wheen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-mumbo-jumbo-conquered-the-world-a-short-history-of-modern-delusions-francis-wheen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-mumbo-jumbo-conquered-the-world-a-short-history-of-modern-delusions-francis-wheen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 1979 two events occurred that would shape the next twenty-five years. In America and Britain, an era of weary consensus was displaced by the arrival of a political marriage of fiery idealists: Ronald Reagan and Margaret Thatcher transformed politics with a combination of breezy charm and assertive &#8220;Victorian values.&#8221; In Iran, the fundamentalist cleric [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-mumbo-jumbo-conquered-the-world-a-short-history-of-modern-delusions-francis-wheen-abridged/">How Mumbo-Jumbo Conquered the World : A Short History of Modern Delusions &#8211; Francis Wheen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 1979 two events occurred that would shape the next twenty-five years. In America and Britain, an era of weary consensus was displaced by the arrival of a political marriage of fiery idealists: Ronald Reagan and Margaret Thatcher transformed politics with a combination of breezy charm and assertive &#8220;Victorian values.&#8221; In Iran, the fundamentalist cleric Ayatollah Ruhollah Khomeini set out to restore a regime that had last existed almost 1,300 years ago. Between them they succeeded in bringing the twentieth century to a premature close. By 1989, Francis Fukuyama was declaring that we had now reached the End of History. What colonized the space recently vacated by notions of history, progress and reason? Cults, quackery, gurus, irrational panics, moral confusion and an epidemic of idiocy, the proof of which was to be found in every state, every work-place, and every library. In  Idiot Proof , columnist Francis Wheen brilliantly evokes the key personalities of the post-political era,including Princess Diana and Deepak Chopra, Osama bin Laden and Nancy Reagan&#8217;s astrologer,while lamenting the extraordinary rise in superstition, relativism and emotional hysteria over the past quarter of a century. In turn comic, indignant, outraged and just plain baffled by the idiocy of it all,  Idiot Proof  is a masterful depiction of the daftness of our times and a plea that we might just think a little more and believe a little less.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-mumbo-jumbo-conquered-the-world-a-short-history-of-modern-delusions-francis-wheen-abridged/">How Mumbo-Jumbo Conquered the World : A Short History of Modern Delusions &#8211; Francis Wheen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Justice : What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? &#8211; Michael J. Sandel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/justice-whats-the-right-thing-to-do-michael-j-sandel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/justice-whats-the-right-thing-to-do-michael-j-sandel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Sandel&#8217;s Justice: What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? invites readers of all ages and political persuasions on a journey of moral reflection, and shows how reasoned debate can illuminate our lives. Is it always wrong to lie? Should there be limits to personal freedom? Can killing sometimes be justified? Is the free market fair? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/justice-whats-the-right-thing-to-do-michael-j-sandel-abridged/">Justice : What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? &#8211; Michael J. Sandel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Sandel&#8217;s Justice: What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? invites readers of all ages and political persuasions on a journey of moral reflection, and shows how reasoned debate can illuminate our lives.    </p>
<p>                    Is it always wrong to lie?<br />
                    Should there be limits to personal freedom?<br />
                    Can killing sometimes be justified?<br />
                    Is the free market fair?<br />
                    What is the right thing to do?    </p>
<p>                    Questions like these are at the heart of our lives. In this acclaimed book Michael Sandel &#8211; BBC Reith Lecturer and the Harvard professor whose &#8216;Justice&#8217; course has become world famous &#8211; gives us a lively and accessible introduction to the intersection of politics and philosophy. He helps us think our way through such hotly contested issues as equal rights, democracy, euthanasia, abortion and same-sex marriage, as well as the ethical dilemmas we face every day.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the most popular teachers in the world&#8217; &#8211; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Enormously refreshing &#8230; Michael Sandel transforms moral philosophy by putting it at the heart of civic debate&#8217; &#8211; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the world&#8217;s most interesting political philosophers&#8217; &#8211; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Spellbinding&#8217; &#8211; The Nation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/justice-whats-the-right-thing-to-do-michael-j-sandel-abridged/">Justice : What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? &#8211; Michael J. Sandel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Presidents of War &#8211; Michael Beschloss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; From a preeminent presidential historian comes a &#8220;superb and important&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) saga of America&#8217;s wartime chief executives &#8220;Fascinating and heartbreaking . . . timely . . . Beschloss&#8217;s broad scope lets you draw important crosscutting lessons about presidential leadership.&#8221;&#8211;Bill Gates Widely acclaimed and ten years [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/">Presidents of War &#8211; Michael Beschloss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; From a preeminent presidential historian comes a &#8220;superb and important&#8221; (The New York Times Book Review) saga of America&#8217;s wartime chief executives    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Fascinating and heartbreaking . . . timely . . . Beschloss&#8217;s broad scope lets you draw important crosscutting lessons about presidential leadership.&#8221;&#8211;Bill Gates     </p>
<p>                    Widely acclaimed and ten years in the making, Michael Beschloss&#8217;s Presidents of War is an intimate and irresistibly readable chronicle of the Chief Executives who took the United States into conflict and mobilized it for victory. From the War of 1812 to Vietnam, we see these leaders considering the difficult decision to send hundreds of thousands of Americans to their deaths; struggling with Congress, the courts, the press, and antiwar protesters; seeking comfort from their spouses and friends; and dropping to their knees in prayer. Through Beschloss&#8217;s interviews with surviving participants and findings in original letters and once-classified national security documents, we come to understand how these Presidents were able to withstand the pressures of war&#8211;or were broken by them.     </p>
<p>                    Presidents of War combines this sense of immediacy with the overarching context of two centuries of American history, traveling from the time of our Founders, who tried to constrain presidential power, to our modern day, when a single leader has the potential to launch nuclear weapons that can destroy much of the human race.    </p>
<p>                    Praise for Presidents of War     </p>
<p>                    A marvelous narrative. . . . As Beschloss explains, the greatest wartime presidents successfully leaven military action with moral concerns. . . . Beschloss&#8217;s writing is clean and concise, and he admirably draws upon new documents. Some of the more titillating tidbits in the book are in the footnotes. . . . There are fascinating nuggets on virtually every page of Presidents of War. It is a superb and important book, superbly rendered.&#8221;&#8211;Jay Winik, The New York Times Book Review     </p>
<p>                    Sparkle and bite. . . . Valuable and engrossing study of how our chief executives have discharged the most significant of all their duties. . . . Excellent. . . . A fluent narrative that covers two centuries of national conflict.&#8221; &#8211;Richard Snow,  The Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/presidents-of-war-michael-beschloss-abridged/">Presidents of War &#8211; Michael Beschloss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>#NeverAgain : A New Generation Draws the Line &#8211; David Hogg, Lauren Hogg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/neveragain-a-new-generation-draws-the-line-david-hogg-lauren-hogg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Students & Student Organisations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/neveragain-a-new-generation-draws-the-line-david-hogg-lauren-hogg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; From two survivors of the Parkland, Florida, shooting comes a declaration for our times, and an in-depth look at the making of the #NeverAgain movement. On February 14, 2018, seventeen-year-old David Hogg and his fourteen-year-old sister, Lauren, went to school at Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School, like any normal Wednesday. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/neveragain-a-new-generation-draws-the-line-david-hogg-lauren-hogg-abridged/">#NeverAgain : A New Generation Draws the Line &#8211; David Hogg, Lauren Hogg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; From two survivors of the Parkland, Florida, shooting comes a declaration for our times, and an in-depth look at the making of the #NeverAgain movement. On February 14, 2018, seventeen-year-old David Hogg and his fourteen-year-old sister, Lauren, went to school at Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School, like any normal Wednesday. That day, of course, the world changed. By the next morning, with seventeen classmates and faculty dead, they had joined the leadership of a movement to save their own lives, and the lives of all other young people in America. It&#8217;s a leadership position they did not seek, and did not want&#8211;but events gave them no choice. The morning after the massacre, David Hogg told CNN: We&#8217;re children. You guys are the adults. You need to take some action and play a role. Work together. Get over your politics and get something done. This book is a manifesto for the movement begun that day, one that has already changed America&#8211;with voices of a new generation that are speaking truth to power, and are determined to succeed where their elders have failed. With moral force and clarity, a new generation has made it clear that problems previously deemed unsolvable due to powerful lobbies and political cowardice will be theirs to solve. Born just after Columbine and raised amid seemingly endless war and routine active shooter drills, this generation now says, Enough. This book is their statement of purpose, and the story of their lives. It is the essential guide to the #NeverAgain movement.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/neveragain-a-new-generation-draws-the-line-david-hogg-lauren-hogg-abridged/">#NeverAgain : A New Generation Draws the Line &#8211; David Hogg, Lauren Hogg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Of course, everything [D&#8217;Souza] says here is accurate&#8230; But it&#8217;s not going to sit well with people on the American left who, of course, are portraying themselves as the exact opposite of all of this. &#8211;RUSH LIMBAUGH The explosive new book from Dinesh D&#8217;Souza, author of the #1 New York Times bestsellers Hillary&#8217;s America, America, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/">The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Of course, everything [D&#8217;Souza] says here is accurate&#8230; But it&#8217;s not going to sit well with people on the American left who, of course, are portraying themselves as the exact opposite of all of this. &#8211;RUSH LIMBAUGH     </p>
<p>                    The explosive new book from Dinesh D&#8217;Souza, author of the #1 New York Times bestsellers Hillary&#8217;s America, America, and Obama&#8217;s America.      </p>
<p>                     What is the big lie of the Democratic Party? That conservatives&#8211;and President Donald Trump in particular&#8211;are fascists. Nazis, even. In a typical comment, MSNBC host Rachel Maddow says the Trump era is reminiscent of what it was like when Hitler first became chancellor.     </p>
<p>                     But in fact, this audacious lie is a complete inversion of the truth. Yes, there is a fascist threat in America&#8211;but that threat is from the Left and the Democratic Party. The Democratic left has an ideology virtually identical with fascism and routinely borrows tactics of intimidation and political terror from the Nazi Brownshirts.     </p>
<p>                     To cover up their insidious fascist agenda, Democrats loudly accuse President Trump and other Republicans of being Nazis&#8211;an obvious lie, considering the GOP has been fighting the Democrats over slavery, genocide, racism and fascism from the beginning.     </p>
<p>                     Now, finally, Dinesh D&#8217;Souza explodes the Left&#8217;s big lie. He expertly exonerates President Trump and his supporters, then uncovers the Democratic Left&#8217;s long, cozy relationship with Nazism: how the racist and genocidal acts of early Democrats inspired Adolf Hitler&#8217;s campaign of death; how fascist philosophers influenced the great 20th century lions of the American Left; and how today&#8217;s anti-free speech, anti-capitalist, anti-religious liberty, pro-violence Democratic Party is a frightening simulacrum of the Nazi Party.     </p>
<p>                     Hitler coined the term the big lie to describe a lie that the great masses of the people will fall for precisely because of how bold and monstrous the lie is. In The Big Lie, D&#8217;Souza shows that the Democratic Left&#8217;s orchestrated campaign to paint President Trump and conservatives as Nazis to cover up its own fascism is, in fact, the biggest lie of all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/">The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Them : Why We Hate Each Other&#8211;and How to Heal &#8211; Ben Sasse (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Something is wrong. We all know it. American life expectancy is declining for a third straight year. Birth rates are dropping. Nearly half of us think the other political party isn&#8217;t just wrong; they&#8217;re evil. We&#8217;re the richest country in history, but we&#8217;ve never been more pessimistic. What&#8217;s causing the despair? In Them, bestselling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/">Them : Why We Hate Each Other&#8211;and How to Heal &#8211; Ben Sasse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Something is wrong. We all know it. American life expectancy is declining for a third straight year. Birth rates are dropping. Nearly half of us think the other political party isn&#8217;t just wrong; they&#8217;re evil. We&#8217;re the richest country in history, but we&#8217;ve never been more pessimistic. What&#8217;s causing the despair?    </p>
<p>                    In Them, bestselling author and U.S. senator Ben Sasse argues that our crisis isn&#8217;t really about politics. It&#8217;s that we&#8217;re so lonely we can&#8217;t see straight &#8211; and it bubbles out as anger. Local communities are collapsing. Across the nation, little leagues are disappearing, Rotary clubs are dwindling, and in all likelihood, we don&#8217;t know the neighbour two doors down. Work isn&#8217;t what we&#8217;d hoped: less certainty, few lifelong coworkers, shallow purpose. Stable families and enduring friendships &#8211; life&#8217;s fundamental pillars &#8211; are in statistical freefall.    </p>
<p>                    As traditional tribes of place evaporate, we rally against common enemies so we can feel part of a team. No institutions command widespread public trust, enabling foreign intelligence agencies to use technology to pick the scabs on our toxic divisions. We&#8217;re in danger of half of us believing different facts than the other half, and the digital revolution throws gas on the fire.    </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s a path forward &#8211; but reversing our decline requires something radical: a rediscovery of real places and human-to-human relationships. Even as technology nudges us to become rootless, Sasse shows how only a recovery of rootedness can heal our lonely souls. America wants you to be happy, but more urgently, America needs you to love your neighbour and connect with your community. Fixing what&#8217;s wrong with the country depends on it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/">Them : Why We Hate Each Other&#8211;and How to Heal &#8211; Ben Sasse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Imagined Communities : Reflections on the Origin and Spread of Nationalism &#8211; Benedict Anderson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/imagined-communities-reflections-on-the-origin-and-spread-of-nationalism-benedict-anderson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nationalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/imagined-communities-reflections-on-the-origin-and-spread-of-nationalism-benedict-anderson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What are the imagined communities that compel men to kill or to die for an idea of a nation? This notion of nationhood had its origins in the founding of the Americas, but was then adopted and transformed by populist movements in nineteenth-century Europe. It became the rallying cry for anti-Imperialism as well as the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/imagined-communities-reflections-on-the-origin-and-spread-of-nationalism-benedict-anderson-abridged/">Imagined Communities : Reflections on the Origin and Spread of Nationalism &#8211; Benedict Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What are the imagined communities that compel men to kill or to die for an idea of a nation? This notion of nationhood had its origins in the founding of the Americas, but was then adopted and transformed by populist movements in nineteenth-century Europe. It became the rallying cry for anti-Imperialism as well as the abiding explanation for colonialism. In this scintillating, groundbreaking work of intellectual history Anderson explores how ideas are formed and reformulated at every level, from high politics to popular culture, and the way that they can make people do extraordinary things. In the twenty-first century, these debates on the nature of the nation state are even more urgent. As new nations rise, vying for influence, and old empires decline, we must understand who we are as a community in the face of history, and change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/imagined-communities-reflections-on-the-origin-and-spread-of-nationalism-benedict-anderson-abridged/">Imagined Communities : Reflections on the Origin and Spread of Nationalism &#8211; Benedict Anderson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A First-Rate Madness : Uncovering the Links Between Leadership and Mental Illness &#8211; Nassir Ghaemi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-first-rate-madness-uncovering-the-links-between-leadership-and-mental-illness-nassir-ghaemi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-first-rate-madness-uncovering-the-links-between-leadership-and-mental-illness-nassir-ghaemi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestseller is a myth-shattering exploration of the powerful connections between mental illness and leadership. Historians have long puzzled over the apparent mental instability of great and terrible leaders alike: Napoleon, Lincoln, Churchill, Hitler, and others. In A First-Rate Madness, Nassir Ghaemi, director of the Mood Disorders Programme at Tufts Medical Center, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-first-rate-madness-uncovering-the-links-between-leadership-and-mental-illness-nassir-ghaemi-abridged/">A First-Rate Madness : Uncovering the Links Between Leadership and Mental Illness &#8211; Nassir Ghaemi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestseller is a myth-shattering exploration of the powerful connections between mental illness and leadership.    </p>
<p>                    Historians have long puzzled over the apparent mental instability of great and terrible leaders alike: Napoleon, Lincoln, Churchill, Hitler, and others. In A First-Rate Madness, Nassir Ghaemi, director of the Mood Disorders Programme at Tufts Medical Center, offers and sets forth a controversial, compelling thesis: the very qualities that mark those with mood disorders also make for the best leaders in times of crisis.     </p>
<p>                    From the importance of Lincoln&#8217;s &#8220;depressive realism&#8221; to the lacklustre leadership of exceedingly sane men as Neville Chamberlain, A First-Rate Madness overturns many of our most cherished perceptions about greatness and the mind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-first-rate-madness-uncovering-the-links-between-leadership-and-mental-illness-nassir-ghaemi-abridged/">A First-Rate Madness : Uncovering the Links Between Leadership and Mental Illness &#8211; Nassir Ghaemi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fight to Vote &#8211; Michael Waldman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fight-to-vote-michael-waldman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fight-to-vote-michael-waldman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Praised by the late John Lewis, this is the seminal book about the long and ongoing struggle to win voting rights for all citizens by the president of The Brennan Center, the leading organization on voter rights and election security, now newly revised to describe today&#8217;s intense fights over voting. As Rep. Lewis said, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fight-to-vote-michael-waldman-abridged/">The Fight to Vote &#8211; Michael Waldman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Praised by the late John Lewis, this is the seminal book about the long and ongoing struggle to win voting rights for all citizens by the president of The Brennan Center, the leading organization on voter rights and election security, now newly revised to describe today&#8217;s intense fights over voting.     </p>
<p>                    As Rep. Lewis said, and recent events in state legislatures across the country demonstrate, the struggle for the right to vote is not over. In this &#8220;important and powerful&#8221; (Linda Greenhouse, former New York Times Supreme Court correspondent) book Michael Waldman describes the long struggle to extend the right to vote to all Americans. From the writing of the Constitution, and at every step along the way, as disenfranchised Americans sought this right, others have fought to stop them. Waldman traces this history from the Founders&#8217; debates to today&#8217;s many restrictions: gerrymandering; voter ID laws; the flood of dark money released by conservative organizations; and the concerted effort in many state legislatures after the 2020 election to enact new limitations on voting.     </p>
<p>                    Despite the pandemic, the 2020 election had the highest turnout since 1900. In this updated edition, Waldman describes the nationwide effort that made this possible. He offers new insights into how Donald Trump&#8217;s false claims of fraud&#8211;&#8220;the Big Lie&#8221;&#8211;led to the January 6 insurrection and the fights over voting laws that followed one of the most dramatic chapters in the story of American democracy.     </p>
<p>                    As Waldman shows, this fight, sometimes vicious, has always been at the center of American politics because it determines the outcome of the struggle for power. The Fight to Vote is &#8220;an engaging, concise history&#8230;offering many useful reforms that advocates on both sides of the aisle should consider&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fight-to-vote-michael-waldman-abridged/">The Fight to Vote &#8211; Michael Waldman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Progress : Ten Reasons to Look Forward to the Future &#8211; Johan Norberg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Customs & Traditions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Book of the Year for The Economist and the Observer Our world seems to be collapsing. The daily news cycle reports the deterioration: divisive politics across the Western world, racism, poverty, war, inequality, hunger. While politicians, journalists and activists from all sides talk about the damage done, Johan Norberg offers an illuminating and heartening [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/">Progress : Ten Reasons to Look Forward to the Future &#8211; Johan Norberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Book of the Year for The Economist and the Observer    </p>
<p>                    Our world seems to be collapsing. The daily news cycle reports the deterioration: divisive politics across the Western world, racism, poverty, war, inequality, hunger. While politicians, journalists and activists from all sides talk about the damage done, Johan Norberg offers an illuminating and heartening analysis of just how far we have come in tackling the greatest problems facing humanity. In the face of fear-mongering, darkness and division, the facts are unequivocal: the golden age is now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/progress-ten-reasons-to-look-forward-to-the-future-johan-norberg-abridged/">Progress : Ten Reasons to Look Forward to the Future &#8211; Johan Norberg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man, the State, and War : A Theoretical Analysis &#8211; Kenneth Waltz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What are the causes of war? To answer this question, Professor Waltz examines the ideas of major thinkers throughout the history of Western civilization. He explores works both by classic political philosophers, such as St. Augustine, Hobbes, Kant, and Rousseau, and by modern psychologists and anthropologists to discover ideas intended to explain war among states [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/">Man, the State, and War : A Theoretical Analysis &#8211; Kenneth Waltz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What are the causes of war? To answer this question, Professor Waltz examines the ideas of major thinkers throughout the history of Western civilization. He explores works both by classic political philosophers, such as St. Augustine, Hobbes, Kant, and Rousseau, and by modern psychologists and anthropologists to discover ideas intended to explain war among states and related prescriptions for peace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/">Man, the State, and War : A Theoretical Analysis &#8211; Kenneth Waltz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anarchism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Colin Ward (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/anarchism-a-very-short-introduction-colin-ward-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anarchism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/anarchism-a-very-short-introduction-colin-ward-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The word &#8216;anarchism&#8217; tends to conjure up images of aggressive protest against government, and &#8211; recently &#8211; of angry demonstrations against bodies such as the World Bank and the International Monetary Fund. But is anarchism inevitably linked with violent disorder? Do anarchists adhere to a coherent ideology? What exactly is anarchism? In this Very Short [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anarchism-a-very-short-introduction-colin-ward-abridged/">Anarchism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Colin Ward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The word &#8216;anarchism&#8217; tends to conjure up images of aggressive protest against government, and &#8211; recently &#8211; of angry demonstrations against bodies such as the World Bank and the International Monetary Fund. But is anarchism inevitably linked with violent disorder? Do anarchists adhere to a coherent ideology? What exactly is anarchism?    </p>
<p>                    In this Very Short Introduction, Colin Ward considers anarchism from a variety of perspectives: theoretical, historical, and international, and by exploring key anarchist thinkers from Kropotkin to Chomsky. He looks critically at anarchism by evaluating key ideas within it, such as its blanket opposition to incarceration, and policy of &#8216;no compromise&#8217; with the apparatus of political decision-making. Among the questions he ponders are: can anarchy ever function effectively as a political force?<br />
                    Is it more &#8216;organized&#8217; and &#8216;reasonable&#8217; than is currently perceived? Whatever the politics of the reader, Ward&#8217;s argument ensures that anarchism will be much better understood after reading this book.    </p>
<p>                    ABOUT THE SERIES: The Very Short Introductions series from Oxford University Press contains hundreds of titles in almost every subject area. These pocket-sized books are the perfect way to get ahead in a new subject quickly. Our expert authors combine facts, analysis, perspective, new ideas, and enthusiasm to make interesting and challenging topics highly readable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anarchism-a-very-short-introduction-colin-ward-abridged/">Anarchism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Colin Ward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Education Of Brett Kavanaugh &#8211; Robin Pogrebin, Kate Kelly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-education-of-brett-kavanaugh-robin-pogrebin-kate-kelly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-education-of-brett-kavanaugh-robin-pogrebin-kate-kelly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A remarkable work of slowed-down journalism&#8230;They are doing their jobs as journalists and writing the first draft of history. &#8211;Jill Filipovic, The Washington Post &#8230;Generous but also damning. &#8211;Hanna Rosin, The New York Times From two New York Times reporters, a deeper look at the formative years of Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh and his [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-brett-kavanaugh-robin-pogrebin-kate-kelly-abridged/">The Education Of Brett Kavanaugh &#8211; Robin Pogrebin, Kate Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A remarkable work of slowed-down journalism&#8230;They are doing their jobs as journalists and writing the first draft of history. &#8211;Jill Filipovic, The Washington Post &#8230;Generous but also damning. &#8211;Hanna Rosin, The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    From two New York Times reporters, a deeper look at the formative years of Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh and his confirmation. In September 2018, the F.B.I. was given only a week to investigate allegations of sexual misconduct against Brett Kavanaugh, President Trump&#8217;s Supreme Court nominee. But even as Kavanaugh was sworn in to his lifetime position, many questions remained unanswered, leaving millions of Americans unsettled. During the Senate confirmation hearings that preceded the bureau&#8217;s brief probe, New York Times reporters Robin Pogrebin and Kate Kelly broke critical stories about Kavanaugh&#8217;s past, including the Renate Alumni yearbook story. They were inundated with tips from former classmates, friends, and associates that couldn&#8217;t be fully investigated before the confirmation process closed. Now, their book fills in the blanks and explores the essential question: Who is Brett Kavanaugh? The Education of Brett Kavanaugh paints a picture of the prep-school and Ivy-League worlds that formed our newest Supreme Court Justice. By offering commentary from key players from his confirmation process who haven&#8217;t yet spoken publicly and pursuing lines of inquiry that were left hanging, it will be essential reading for anyone who wants to understand our political system and Kavanaugh&#8217;s unexpectedly emblematic role in it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-education-of-brett-kavanaugh-robin-pogrebin-kate-kelly-abridged/">The Education Of Brett Kavanaugh &#8211; Robin Pogrebin, Kate Kelly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Success and Luck : Good Fortune and the Myth of Meritocracy &#8211; Robert H. Frank (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/success-and-luck-good-fortune-and-the-myth-of-meritocracy-robert-h-frank-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/success-and-luck-good-fortune-and-the-myth-of-meritocracy-robert-h-frank-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times bestselling author and economics columnist Robert Frank, a compelling book that explains why the rich underestimate the importance of luck in their success, why that hurts everyone, and what we can do about it How important is luck in economic success? No question more reliably divides conservatives from liberals. As conservatives [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/success-and-luck-good-fortune-and-the-myth-of-meritocracy-robert-h-frank-abridged/">Success and Luck : Good Fortune and the Myth of Meritocracy &#8211; Robert H. Frank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times bestselling author and economics columnist Robert Frank, a compelling book that explains why the rich underestimate the importance of luck in their success, why that hurts everyone, and what we can do about it  How important is luck in economic success? No question more reliably divides conservatives from liberals. As conservatives correctly observe, people who amass great fortunes are almost always talented and hardworking. But liberals are also correct to note that countless others have those same qualities yet never earn much. In recent years, social scientists have discovered that chance plays a much larger role in important life outcomes than most people imagine. In Success and Luck, bestselling author and New York Times economics columnist Robert Frank explores the surprising implications of those findings to show why the rich underestimate the importance of luck in success&#8211;and why that hurts everyone, even the wealthy.<br />
                    Frank describes how, in a world increasingly dominated by winner-take-all markets, chance opportunities and trivial initial advantages often translate into much larger ones&#8211;and enormous income differences&#8211;over time; how false beliefs about luck persist, despite compelling evidence against them; and how myths about personal success and luck shape individual and political choices in harmful ways.  But, Frank argues, we could decrease the inequality driven by sheer luck by adopting simple, unintrusive policies that would free up trillions of dollars each year&#8211;more than enough to fix our crumbling infrastructure, expand healthcare coverage, fight global warming, and reduce poverty, all without requiring painful sacrifices from anyone. If this sounds implausible, you&#8217;ll be surprised to discover that the solution requires only a few, noncontroversial steps.  Compellingly readable, Success and Luck shows how a more accurate understanding of the role of chance in life could lead to better, richer, and fairer economies and societies.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/success-and-luck-good-fortune-and-the-myth-of-meritocracy-robert-h-frank-abridged/">Success and Luck : Good Fortune and the Myth of Meritocracy &#8211; Robert H. Frank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>IAN BREMMER WAS NAMED LINKEDIN&#8217;S #1 TOP INFLUENCER in 2017 &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; &#8216;Required reading to help repair a world in pieces and build a world at peace&#8217; &#8211; Antonio Guterres, United Nations Secretary General &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; &#8216;Ian Bremmer is provocative, controversial, and always intelligent about the state of the world, which he knows so well&#8217; &#8211; Christine [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IAN BREMMER WAS NAMED LINKEDIN&#8217;S #1 TOP INFLUENCER in 2017    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Required reading to help repair a world in pieces and build a world at peace&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Antonio Guterres, United Nations Secretary General     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ian Bremmer is provocative, controversial, and always intelligent about the state of the world, which he knows so well&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Christine Lagarde, Managing Director of the International Monetary Fund     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    From Brexit, to Donald Trump, to extremist parties in Europe and the developing world, populism has dominated recent headlines.     </p>
<p>                    But what explains the rise of leaders who stoke nationalist anger in their countries, from Le Pen to Erdogan? How long will the populist wave last? Who will be the winners and losers in this climate, and how can we defend the values of democracy, free trade and international cooperation?     </p>
<p>                    No one is better suited to explore these questions than Ian Bremmer, the CEO of the Eurasia Group and acclaimed Time magazine columnist. Analysing the social, economic and technological forces fuelling this new wave of populism, Bremmer explains why we&#8217;re witnessing a rejection of the democratic, global, cosmopolitan trends of the late 20th century. Us vs. Them is a definitive guide to navigating the shifting political landscape, for businesses looking to weather and survive the populist storm.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Global politics is a jungle today. Thank goodness Ian Bremmer can be your guide&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; David Miliband, president and CEO of the International Rescue Committee    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A masterful analysis of why global crashed and populism soared&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Adam Grant, author of Give and Take, and Originals and Option B with Sheryl Sandberg</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Accidental Presidents : Eight Men Who Changed America &#8211; Jared Cohen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestselling &#8220;deep dive into the terms of eight former presidents is chock-full of political hijinks-and deja vu&#8221; (Vanity Fair) and provides a fascinating look at the men who came to the office without being elected to it, showing how each affected the nation and world. The strength and prestige of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/">Accidental Presidents : Eight Men Who Changed America &#8211; Jared Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This New York Times bestselling &#8220;deep dive into the terms of eight former presidents is chock-full of political hijinks-and deja vu&#8221; (Vanity Fair) and provides a fascinating look at the men who came to the office without being elected to it, showing how each affected the nation and world.    </p>
<p>                    The strength and prestige of the American presidency has waxed and waned since George Washington. Eight men have succeeded to the presidency when the incumbent died in office. In one way or another they vastly changed our history. Only Theodore Roosevelt would have been elected in his own right. Only TR, Truman, Coolidge, and LBJ were re-elected.    </p>
<p>                    John Tyler succeeded William Henry Harrison who died 30 days into his term. He was kicked out of his party and became the first president threatened with impeachment. Millard Fillmore succeeded esteemed General Zachary Taylor. He immediately sacked the entire cabinet and delayed an inevitable Civil War by standing with Henry Clay&#8217;s compromise of 1850. Andrew Johnson, who succeeded our greatest president, sided with remnants of the Confederacy in Reconstruction. Chester Arthur, the embodiment of the spoils system, was so reviled as James Garfield&#8217;s successor that he had to defend himself against plotting Garfield&#8217;s assassination; but he reformed the civil service. Theodore Roosevelt broke up the trusts. Calvin Coolidge silently cooled down the Harding scandals and preserved the White House for the Republican Herbert Hoover and the Great Depression. Harry Truman surprised everybody when he succeeded the great FDR and proved an able and accomplished president. Lyndon B. Johnson was named to deliver Texas electorally. He led the nation forward on Civil Rights but failed on Vietnam.    </p>
<p>                    Accidental Presidents shows that &#8220;history unfolds in death as well as in life&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal) and adds immeasurably to our understanding of the power and limits of the American presidency in critical times.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accidental-presidents-eight-men-who-changed-america-jared-cohen-abridged/">Accidental Presidents : Eight Men Who Changed America &#8211; Jared Cohen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Defence of Selfishness : Why the Code of Self-Sacrifice is Unjust and Destructive &#8211; Peter Schwartz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-defence-of-selfishness-why-the-code-of-self-sacrifice-is-unjust-and-destructive-peter-schwartz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-defence-of-selfishness-why-the-code-of-self-sacrifice-is-unjust-and-destructive-peter-schwartz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From childhood, we&#8217;re taught one central, non-controversial idea about morality: self-sacrifice is a virtue. It is universally accepted that serving the needs of others, rather than our own, is the essence of morality. To be ethical &#8211; it is believed &#8211; is to be altruistic. Questioning this belief is regarded as tantamount to questioning the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defence-of-selfishness-why-the-code-of-self-sacrifice-is-unjust-and-destructive-peter-schwartz-abridged/">In Defence of Selfishness : Why the Code of Self-Sacrifice is Unjust and Destructive &#8211; Peter Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From childhood, we&#8217;re taught one central, non-controversial idea about morality: self-sacrifice is a virtue. It is universally accepted that serving the needs of others, rather than our own, is the essence of morality. To be ethical &#8211; it is believed &#8211; is to be altruistic. Questioning this belief is regarded as tantamount to questioning the self-evident. Here, Peter Schwartz questions it. In Defense of Selfishness refutes widespread misconceptions about the meaning of selfishness and of altruism. Basing his arguments on Ayn Rand&#8217;s ethics of rational self-interest, Schwartz demonstrates that genuine selfishness is not exemplified by the brutal plundering of an Attila the Hun or the conniving duplicity of a Bernard Madoff. To the contrary, such people are acting against their actual, long-range interests. The truly selfish individual is committed to moral principles and lives an honest, productive, self-respecting life. He does not feed parasitically off other people. Instead, he renounces the unearned, and deals with others &#8211; in both the material and spiritual realms &#8211; by offering value for value, to mutual benefit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defence-of-selfishness-why-the-code-of-self-sacrifice-is-unjust-and-destructive-peter-schwartz-abridged/">In Defence of Selfishness : Why the Code of Self-Sacrifice is Unjust and Destructive &#8211; Peter Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Short History of Brexit : From Brentry to Backstop &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Rourke (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EU & European Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crisp, clear and quietly devastating&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Excellent, authoritative, highly readable&#8217; Irish Times A succinct, expert guide to how we got to Brexit After all the debates, manoeuvrings, recriminations and exaltations, Brexit is upon us. But, as Kevin O&#8217;Rourke writes, Brexit did not emerge out of nowhere: it is the culmination of events that have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/">A Short History of Brexit : From Brentry to Backstop &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Rourke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crisp, clear and quietly devastating&#8217; Guardian<br />
                    &#8216;Excellent, authoritative, highly readable&#8217; Irish Times    </p>
<p>                    A succinct, expert guide to how we got to Brexit    </p>
<p>                    After all the debates, manoeuvrings, recriminations and exaltations,  Brexit is upon us. But, as Kevin O&#8217;Rourke writes, Brexit did not emerge  out of nowhere: it is the culmination of events  that have been under  way for decades and have historical roots stretching back well beyond  that. Brexit has a history.    </p>
<p>                    O&#8217;Rourke, one of the leading economic  historians of his generation, explains not only how British attitudes  to Europe have evolved, but also how the EU&#8217;s history explains why it  operates as it does today &#8211; and how that history has shaped the ways in  which it has responded to Brexit. Why are the economics, the politics  and the history so tightly woven together? Crucially, he also explains  why the question of the Irish border is not just one of customs and  trade, but for the EU goes to the heart of what it is about.  The way in  which British, Irish and European histories continue to interact with  each other will shape the future of Brexit &#8211; and of the continent.    </p>
<p>                    Calm and lucid, A Short History of Brexit  rises above the usual fray of discussions to provide fresh perspectives  and understanding of the most momentous political and economic change  in Britain and the EU for decades.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/">A Short History of Brexit : From Brentry to Backstop &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Rourke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research & Information: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER FROM THE AUTHOR OF THE WORLD IS FLAT    </p>
<p>                    We all sense it: something big is going on. Life is speeding up, and it is dizzying. Here Thomas L. Friedman reveals the tectonic movements that are reshaping our world, how to adapt to this new age and why, sometimes, we all need to be late.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A master class &#8230; As a guide for perplexed Westerners, this book is very hard to beat &#8230; an honest, cohesive explanation for why the world is the way it is, without miracle cures or scapegoats&#8217; John Micklethwait, The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Wonderful &#8230; admirably honest &#8230; injects a badly needed dose of optimism into the modern debate&#8217; Gillian Tett, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;His main piece of advice for individuals, corporations, and countries is clear: Take a deep breath and adapt. This world isn&#8217;t going to wait for you&#8217; Fortune    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A humane and empathetic book&#8217; David Henkin, The Washington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thank-you-for-being-late-an-optimists-guide-to-thriving-in-the-age-of-accelerations-thomas-l-friedman-abridged/">Thank You for Being Late : An Optimist&#8217;s Guide to Thriving in the Age of Accelerations &#8211; Thomas L. Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Common Good &#8211; Robert B. Reich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-common-good-robert-b-reich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-common-good-robert-b-reich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Robert B. Reich makes a powerful case for the expansion of America&#8217;s moral imagination. Rooting his argument in common sense and everyday reality, he demonstrates that a common good constitutes the very essence of any society or nation. Societies, he says, undergo virtuous cycles that reinforce the common good as well as vicious cycles that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-common-good-robert-b-reich-abridged/">The Common Good &#8211; Robert B. Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Robert B. Reich makes a powerful case for the expansion of America&#8217;s moral imagination. Rooting his argument in common sense and everyday reality, he demonstrates that a common good constitutes the very essence of any society or nation. Societies, he says, undergo virtuous cycles that reinforce the common good as well as vicious cycles that undermine it, one of which America has been experiencing for the past five decades. This process can and must be reversed. But first we need to weigh the moral obligations of citizenship and carefully consider how we relate to honor, shame, patriotism, truth, and the meaning of leadership.     </p>
<p>                     Powerful, urgent, and utterly vital, this is a heartfelt missive from one of our foremost political thinkers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-common-good-robert-b-reich-abridged/">The Common Good &#8211; Robert B. Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Will to Change : Men, Masculinity, and Love &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Men]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everyone needs to love and be loved-even men. But to know love, men must be able to look at the ways that patriarchal culture keeps them from knowing themselves, from being in touch with their feelings, from loving. In The Will to Change, bell hooks gets to the heart of the matter and shows men [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/">The Will to Change : Men, Masculinity, and Love &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everyone needs to love and be loved-even men. But to know love, men must be able to look at the ways that patriarchal culture keeps them from knowing themselves, from being in touch with their feelings, from loving.    </p>
<p>                    In The Will to Change, bell hooks gets to the heart of the matter and shows men how to express the emotions that are a fundamental part of who they are-whatever their age, marital status, ethnicity, or sexual orientation. But toxic masculinity punishes those fundamental emotions, and it&#8217;s so deeply ingrained in our society that it&#8217;s hard for men to not comply-but hooks wants to help change that.    </p>
<p>                    With trademark candor and fierce intelligence, hooks addresses the most common concerns of men, such as fear of intimacy and loss of their patriarchal place in society, in new and challenging ways. She believes men can find the way to spiritual unity by getting back in touch with the emotionally open part of themselves-and lay claim to the rich and rewarding inner lives that have historically been the exclusive province of women. A brave and astonishing work, The Will to Change is designed to help men reclaim the best part of themselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/">The Will to Change : Men, Masculinity, and Love &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Words Like Loaded Pistols &#8211; Sam Leith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/words-like-loaded-pistols-sam-leith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semantics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/words-like-loaded-pistols-sam-leith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Words Like Loaded Pistols, Sam Leith traces the art of persuasion, beginning in ancient Syracuse and taking us on detours as varied and fascinating as Elizabethan England, Milton&#8217;s Satanic realm, the Springfield of Abraham Lincoln and the Springfield of Homer Simpson. He explains how language has been used by the great heroes of rhetoric [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/words-like-loaded-pistols-sam-leith-abridged/">Words Like Loaded Pistols &#8211; Sam Leith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Words Like Loaded Pistols, Sam Leith traces the art of persuasion, beginning in ancient Syracuse and taking us on detours as varied and fascinating as Elizabethan England, Milton&#8217;s Satanic realm, the Springfield of Abraham Lincoln and the Springfield of Homer Simpson. He explains how language has been used by the great heroes of rhetoric (such as Cicero and Martin Luther King Jr.), as well as some villains (like Adolf Hitler and Richard Nixon.) Words Like Loaded Pistols is a primer to rhetoric&#8217;s key techniques; you&#8217;ll find out how to build your own memory-palace; you&#8217;ll be introduced to the Three Musketeers: Ethos, Pathos and Logos; and you&#8217;ll learn how to use chiasmus with confidence and occultation without thinking about it. Most importantly of all, you will discover that rhetoric is useful, relevant &#8212; and absolutely nothing to be afraid of.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/words-like-loaded-pistols-sam-leith-abridged/">Words Like Loaded Pistols &#8211; Sam Leith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Full Life : Reflections at Ninety &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-full-life-reflections-at-ninety-jimmy-carter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-full-life-reflections-at-ninety-jimmy-carter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his major New York Times bestseller, Jimmy Carter looks back from ninety years of age and &#8220;reveals private thoughts and recollections over a fascinating career as businessman, politician, evangelist, and humanitarian&#8221; (Booklist). At ninety, Jimmy Carter reflects on his public and private life with a frankness that is disarming. He adds detail and emotion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-full-life-reflections-at-ninety-jimmy-carter-abridged/">A Full Life : Reflections at Ninety &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his major New York Times bestseller, Jimmy Carter looks back from ninety years of age and &#8220;reveals private thoughts and recollections over a fascinating career as businessman, politician, evangelist, and humanitarian&#8221; (Booklist).    </p>
<p>                    At ninety, Jimmy Carter reflects on his public and private life with a frankness that is disarming. He adds detail and emotion about his youth in rural Georgia that he described in his magnificent An Hour Before Daylight. He writes about racism and the isolation of the Carters. He describes the brutality of the hazing regimen at Annapolis, and how he nearly lost his life twice serving on submarines and his amazing interview with Admiral Rickover. He describes the profound influence his mother had on him, and how he admired his father even though he didn&#8217;t emulate him. He admits that he decided to quit the Navy and later enter politics without consulting his wife, Rosalynn, and how appalled he is in retrospect.    </p>
<p>                    In his &#8220;warm and detailed memoir&#8221; (Los Angeles Times), Carter tells what he is proud of and what he might do differently. He discusses his regret at losing his re-election, but how he and Rosalynn pushed on and made a new life and second and third rewarding careers. He is frank about the presidents who have succeeded him, world leaders, and his passions for the causes he cares most about, particularly the condition of women and the deprived people of the developing world.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Always warm and human&#8230;even inspirational&#8221; (Buffalo News), A Full Life is a wise and moving look back from this remarkable man. Jimmy Carter has lived one of our great American lives-from rural obscurity to world fame, universal respect, and contentment. A Full Life is an extraordinary read from a &#8220;force to be reckoned with&#8221; (Christian Science Monitor).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-full-life-reflections-at-ninety-jimmy-carter-abridged/">A Full Life : Reflections at Ninety &#8211; Jimmy Carter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Populism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Cas Mudde, Cristbal Rovira Kaltwasser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/populism-a-very-short-introduction-cas-mudde-cristobal-rovira-kaltwasser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/populism-a-very-short-introduction-cas-mudde-cristobal-rovira-kaltwasser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Populism is a central concept in the current media debates about politics and elections. However, like most political buzzwords, the term often floats from one meaning to another, and both social scientists and journalists use it to denote diverse phenomena. What is populism really? Who are the populist leaders? And what is the relationship between [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/populism-a-very-short-introduction-cas-mudde-cristobal-rovira-kaltwasser-abridged/">Populism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Cas Mudde, Cristbal Rovira Kaltwasser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Populism is a central concept in the current media debates about politics and elections. However, like most political buzzwords, the term often floats from one meaning to another, and both social scientists and journalists use it to denote diverse phenomena. What is populism really? Who are the populist leaders? And what is the relationship between populism and democracy? This book answers these questions in a simple and persuasive way, offering a swift guide to<br />
                    populism in theory and practice.    </p>
<p>                    Cas Mudde and Cristobal Rovera Kaltwasser present populism as an ideology that divides society into two antagonistic camps, the &#8220;pure people&#8221; versus the &#8220;corrupt elite,&#8221; and that privileges the general will of the people above all else. They illustrate the practical power of this ideology through a survey of representative populist movements of the modern era: European right-wing parties, left-wing presidents in Latin America, and the Tea Party movement in the United States. The authors<br />
                    delve into the ambivalent personalities of charismatic populist leaders such as Juan Domingo Peron, H. Ross Perot, Jean-Marie le Pen, Silvio Berlusconi, and Hugo Chavez. If the strong male leader embodies the mainstream form of populism, many resolute women, such as Eva Peron, Pauline Hanson, and Sarah<br />
                    Palin, have also succeeded in building a populist status, often by exploiting gendered notions of society.    </p>
<p>                    Although populism is ultimately part of democracy, populist movements constitute an increasing challenge to democratic politics. Comparing political trends across different countries, this compelling book debates what the long-term consequences of this challenge could be, as it turns the spotlight on the bewildering effect of populism on today&#8217;s political and social life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/populism-a-very-short-introduction-cas-mudde-cristobal-rovira-kaltwasser-abridged/">Populism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Cas Mudde, Cristbal Rovira Kaltwasser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Six-time New York Times bestselling author, FOX News star, and radio host Mark R. Levin &#8220;trounces the news media&#8221; (The Washington Times) in this timely and groundbreaking book demonstrating how the great tradition of American free press has degenerated into a standardless profession that has squandered the faith and trust of the public. Unfreedom of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/">Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Six-time New York Times bestselling author, FOX News star, and radio host Mark R. Levin &#8220;trounces the news media&#8221; (The Washington Times) in this timely and groundbreaking book demonstrating how the great tradition of American free press has degenerated into a standardless profession that has squandered the faith and trust of the public.     </p>
<p>                    Unfreedom of the Press is not just another book about the press. In &#8220;Levin&#8217;s finest work&#8221; (Breitbart), he shows how those entrusted with news reporting today are destroying freedom of the press from within-not through actions of government officials, but with its own abandonment of reportorial integrity and objective journalism.    </p>
<p>                    With the depth of historical background for which his books are renowned, Levin takes you on a journey through the early American patriot press, which proudly promoted the principles set forth in the Declaration of Independence and the Constitution. This is followed by the early decades of the Republic during which newspapers around the young country were open and transparent about their fierce allegiance to one political party or another.    </p>
<p>                    It was only at the start of the Progressive Era and the 20th century that the supposed &#8220;objectivity of the press&#8221; first surfaced, leaving us where we are today: with a partisan party-press overwhelmingly aligned with a political ideology but hypocritically engaged in a massive untruth as to its real nature.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/">Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Prime Ministers We Never Had : Success and Failure from Butler to Corbyn &#8211; Steve Richards (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-prime-ministers-we-never-had-success-and-failure-from-butler-to-corbyn-steve-richards-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-prime-ministers-we-never-had-success-and-failure-from-butler-to-corbyn-steve-richards-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BOOK OF THE YEAR, The Times, Guardian and Prospect Was Harold Wilson a bigger figure than Denis Healey? Was John Major more &#8216;prime ministerial&#8217; than Michael Heseltine? Would David Miliband have become prime minister if it were not for his brother Ed? Would Ed have become prime minister if it were not for David? How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-prime-ministers-we-never-had-success-and-failure-from-butler-to-corbyn-steve-richards-abridged/">The Prime Ministers We Never Had : Success and Failure from Butler to Corbyn &#8211; Steve Richards (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BOOK OF THE YEAR, The Times, Guardian and Prospect    </p>
<p>                    Was Harold Wilson a bigger figure than Denis Healey? Was John Major more &#8216;prime ministerial&#8217; than Michael Heseltine? Would David Miliband have become prime minister if it were not for his brother Ed? Would Ed have become prime minister if it were not for David? How close did Jeremy Corbyn come to being prime minister?     </p>
<p>                    In this piercing and original study, journalist and commentator Steve Richards looks at eleven prime ministers we never had, examining what made each of these illustrious figures unique and why they failed to make the final leap to the very top. Combining astute insights into the demands of leadership with compelling historical analysis, this fascinating exploration of failure and success sheds new light on some of the most compelling characters in British public life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-prime-ministers-we-never-had-success-and-failure-from-butler-to-corbyn-steve-richards-abridged/">The Prime Ministers We Never Had : Success and Failure from Butler to Corbyn &#8211; Steve Richards (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aristotle&#8217;s &#8220;Politics&#8221; : Second Edition &#8211; Aristotle, Translated byCarnes Lord (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/aristotles-politics-second-edition-aristotle-translated-by-carnes-lord-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Ancient, To C 500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/aristotles-politics-second-edition-aristotle-translated-by-carnes-lord-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the fundamental works of Western political thought, Aristotle&#8217;s masterwork is the first systematic treatise on the science of politics. For almost three decades, Carnes Lord&#8217;s justly acclaimed translation has served as the standard English edition. Widely regarded as the most faithful to both the original Greek and Aristotle&#8217;s distinctive style, it is also [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/aristotles-politics-second-edition-aristotle-translated-by-carnes-lord-abridged/">Aristotle&#8217;s &#8220;Politics&#8221; : Second Edition &#8211; Aristotle, Translated byCarnes Lord (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the fundamental works of Western political thought, Aristotle&#8217;s masterwork is the first systematic treatise on the science of politics. For almost three decades, Carnes Lord&#8217;s justly acclaimed translation has served as the standard English edition. Widely regarded as the most faithful to both the original Greek and Aristotle&#8217;s distinctive style, it is also written in clear, contemporary English. This new edition of the Politics retains and adds to Lord&#8217;s already extensive notes, clarifying the flow of Aristotle&#8217;s argument and identifying literary and historical references. A glossary defines key terms in Aristotle&#8217;s philosophical-political vocabulary. Lord has made revisions to problematic passages throughout the translation in order to enhance both its accuracy and its readability. He has also substantially revised his introduction for the new edition, presenting an account of Aristotle&#8217;s life in relation to political events of his time; the character and history of his writings and of the Politics in particular; his overall conception of political science; and his impact on subsequent political thought from antiquity to the present.<br />
                    Further enhancing this new edition is an up-to-date selected bibliography.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/aristotles-politics-second-edition-aristotle-translated-by-carnes-lord-abridged/">Aristotle&#8217;s &#8220;Politics&#8221; : Second Edition &#8211; Aristotle, Translated byCarnes Lord (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal: to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221; major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal:  to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221;  major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair way.     </p>
<p>                    Breitbart burst on to the national media scene thanks to his coverage of  the ACORN controversy, where a local ACORN community group leader was videotaped giving business advice to a &#8220;gentleman&#8221; who ran a prostitution ring. When the major news media at first tried to bury the story, Breitbart used his extraordinary marketing savvy to make sure the story got full national attention.     </p>
<p>                    More recently, Congressman Anthony Weiner took on Breitbart, claiming that scurrilous photos of Weiner were being sent on the internet by the conservative right. In a new chapter in RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart details how &#8220;Weinergate&#8221; was entirely the personal fault of Congressman Weiner, and how Weiner derailed his own promising career by trying to implicate Breitbart and conservative journalists.    </p>
<p>                    In short, RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart talks about the key issues that Americans face, how he has aligned himself with the Tea Party, and how one needs to deal with the liberal news world head on. Along the way, he details his early years, working with Matt Drudge, the Huffington Post, and so on, and how Breitbart developed his unique style of launching key websites to help get the word out to conservatives all over.     </p>
<p>                    A rollicking and controversial read, Breitbart will certainly raise your blood pressure, one way or another.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Plato: &#8216;The Republic&#8217; &#8211; Plato, Translated byTom Griffith, Edited byG. R. F. Ferrari (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/plato-the-republic-plato-translated-by-tom-griffith-edited-by-g-r-f-ferrari-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Ancient, To C 500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/plato-the-republic-plato-translated-by-tom-griffith-edited-by-g-r-f-ferrari-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>First published in 2000, this translation of one of the great works of Western political thought is based on the assumption that when Plato chose the dialogue form for his writing, he intended these dialogues to sound like conversations &#8211; although conversations of a philosophical sort. In addition to a vivid, dignified and accurate rendition [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/plato-the-republic-plato-translated-by-tom-griffith-edited-by-g-r-f-ferrari-abridged/">Plato: &#8216;The Republic&#8217; &#8211; Plato, Translated byTom Griffith, Edited byG. R. F. Ferrari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First published in 2000, this translation of one of the great works of Western political thought is based on the assumption that when Plato chose the dialogue form for his writing, he intended these dialogues to sound like conversations &#8211; although conversations of a philosophical sort. In addition to a vivid, dignified and accurate rendition of Plato&#8217;s text, the student and general reader will find many aids to comprehension in this volume: an introduction that assesses the cultural background to the Republic, its place within political philosophy, and its general argument; succinct notes in the body of the text; an analytical summary of the work&#8217;s content; a full glossary of proper names; a chronology of important events; and a guide to further reading. The result is an accomplished and accessible edition of this seminal work, suitable for philosophers and classicists as well as historians of political thought at all levels.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/plato-the-republic-plato-translated-by-tom-griffith-edited-by-g-r-f-ferrari-abridged/">Plato: &#8216;The Republic&#8217; &#8211; Plato, Translated byTom Griffith, Edited byG. R. F. Ferrari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Red Team : How to Succeed By Thinking Like the Enemy &#8211; Micah Zenko (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/red-team-how-to-succeed-by-thinking-like-the-enemy-micah-zenko-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[War & Defence Operations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/red-team-how-to-succeed-by-thinking-like-the-enemy-micah-zenko-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Red teaming. It is a practice as old as the Devil&#8217;s Advocate, the eleventh-century Vatican official charged with discrediting candidates for sainthood. Today, red teams,comprised primarily of fearless skeptics and those assuming the role of saboteurs who seek to better understand the interests, intentions, and capabilities of institutions or potential competitors,are used widely in both [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-team-how-to-succeed-by-thinking-like-the-enemy-micah-zenko-abridged/">Red Team : How to Succeed By Thinking Like the Enemy &#8211; Micah Zenko (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Red teaming. It is a practice as old as the Devil&#8217;s Advocate, the eleventh-century Vatican official charged with discrediting candidates for sainthood. Today, red teams,comprised primarily of fearless skeptics and those assuming the role of saboteurs who seek to better understand the interests, intentions, and capabilities of institutions or potential competitors,are used widely in both the public and private sector. Red teaming, including simulations, vulnerability probes, and alternative analyses, helps institutions in competitive environments to identify vulnerabilities and weaknesses, challenge assumptions, and anticipate potential threats ahead of the next special operations raid, malicious cyberattack, or corporate merger. But not all red teams are created equal indeed, some cause more damage than they prevent. In  Red Team , national security expert Micah Zenko provides an in-depth investigation into the work of red teams, revealing the best practices, most common pitfalls, and most effective applications of these modern-day Devil&#8217;s Advocates. The best practices of red teaming can be applied to the CIA, NYPD, or a pharmaceutical company, and executed correctly they can yield impressive results: red teams give businesses an edge over their competition, poke holes in vital intelligence estimates, and troubleshoot dangerous military missions long before boots are on the ground. But red teams are only as good as leaders allow them to be, and Zenko shows not only how to create and empower red teams, but also what to do with the information they produce.Essential reading for business leaders and policymakers alike,  Red Team  will revolutionize the way organizations think about, exploit, compensate for, and correct their institutional strengths and weaknesses. Drawing on little-known case studies and unprecedented access to elite red teamers in the United States and abroad, Zenko shows how any group,from military units to friendly hackers,can win by thinking like the enemy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-team-how-to-succeed-by-thinking-like-the-enemy-micah-zenko-abridged/">Red Team : How to Succeed By Thinking Like the Enemy &#8211; Micah Zenko (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Logic]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why do Internet, financial service, and beer commercials dominate Super Bowl advertising? How do political ceremonies establish authority? Why does repetition characterize anthems and ritual speech? Why were circular forms favored for public festivals during the French Revolution? This book answers these questions using a single concept: common knowledge. Game theory shows that in order [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/">Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why do Internet, financial service, and beer commercials dominate Super Bowl advertising? How do political ceremonies establish authority? Why does repetition characterize anthems and ritual speech? Why were circular forms favored for public festivals during the French Revolution? This book answers these questions using a single concept: common knowledge. Game theory shows that in order to coordinate its actions, a group of people must form &#8220;common knowledge.&#8221; Each person wants to participate only if others also participate. Members must have knowledge of each other, knowledge of that knowledge, knowledge of the knowledge of that knowledge, and so on. Michael Chwe applies this insight, with striking erudition, to analyze a range of rituals across history and cultures. He shows that public ceremonies are powerful not simply because they transmit meaning from a central source to each audience member but because they let audience members know what other members know. For instance, people watching the Super Bowl know that many others are seeing precisely what they see and that those people know in turn that many others are also watching.<br />
                    This creates common knowledge, and advertisers selling products that depend on consensus are willing to pay large sums to gain access to it. Remarkably, a great variety of rituals and ceremonies, such as formal inaugurations, work in much the same way. By using a rational-choice argument to explain diverse cultural practices, Chwe argues for a close reciprocal relationship between the perspectives of rationality and culture. He illustrates how game theory can be applied to an unexpectedly broad spectrum of problems, while showing in an admirably clear way what game theory might hold for scholars in the social sciences and humanities who are not yet acquainted with it. In a new afterword, Chwe delves into new applications of common knowledge, both in the real world and in experiments, and considers how generating common knowledge has become easier in the digital age.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rational-ritual-culture-coordination-and-common-knowledge-michael-suk-young-chwe-abridged/">Rational Ritual : Culture, Coordination, and Common Knowledge &#8211; Michael Suk-Young Chwe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blood Feud : The Clintons vs. the Obamas &#8211; Lars Mikaelson, Edward Klein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this highly anticipated follow-up to his blockbuster New York Times bestseller The Amateur, former New York Times Magazine editor-in-chief Edward Klein delves into the rocky relationship between the Obamas and the Clintons. An old-school reporter with incredible insider contacts, Klein reveals just how deep the rivalry between the Obamas and the Clintons runs, with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/">Blood Feud : The Clintons vs. the Obamas &#8211; Lars Mikaelson, Edward Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this highly anticipated follow-up to his blockbuster New York Times bestseller The Amateur, former New York Times Magazine editor-in-chief Edward Klein delves into the rocky relationship between the Obamas and the Clintons. An old-school reporter with incredible insider contacts, Klein reveals just how deep the rivalry between the Obamas and the Clintons runs, with details on closed-door meetings buttressed by hundreds of interviews. Blood Feud is a stunning expose of the animosity, jealousy, and competition between America&#8217;s two most powerful political couples.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/blood-feud-the-clintons-vs-the-obamas-lars-mikaelson-edward-klein-abridged/">Blood Feud : The Clintons vs. the Obamas &#8211; Lars Mikaelson, Edward Klein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inventing the Future : Postcapitalism and a World Without Work &#8211; Nick Srnicek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Neoliberalism isn&#8217;t working. Austerity is forcing millions into poverty and many more into precarious work, while the left remains trapped in stagnant political practices that offer no respite. Inventing the Future is a bold new manifesto for life after capitalism. Against the confused understanding of our high-tech world by both the right and the left, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/">Inventing the Future : Postcapitalism and a World Without Work &#8211; Nick Srnicek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Neoliberalism isn&#8217;t working. Austerity is forcing millions into poverty and many more into precarious work, while the left remains trapped in stagnant political practices that offer no respite. Inventing the Future is a bold new manifesto for life after capitalism. Against the confused understanding of our high-tech world by both the right and the left, this book claims that the emancipatory and future-oriented possibilities of our society can be reclaimed. Instead of running from a complex future, Nick Srnicek and Alex Williams demand a postcapitalist economy capable of advancing standards, liberating humanity from work and developing technologies that expand our freedoms. This new edition includes a new chapter where they respond to their various critics.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/">Inventing the Future : Postcapitalism and a World Without Work &#8211; Nick Srnicek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Wellness Syndrome &#8211; Carl Cederstroem, Andre Spicer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-wellness-syndrome-carl-cederstroem-andre-spicer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance, C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wellness-syndrome-carl-cederstroem-andre-spicer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not exercising as much as you should? Counting your calories in your sleep? Feeling ashamed for not being happier? You may be a victim of the wellness syndrome. In this ground-breaking new book, Carl Cederstrom and Andre Spicer argue that the ever-present pressure to maximize our wellness has started to work against us, making us [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wellness-syndrome-carl-cederstroem-andre-spicer-abridged/">The Wellness Syndrome &#8211; Carl Cederstroem, Andre Spicer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not exercising as much as you should? Counting your calories in your sleep? Feeling ashamed for not being happier? You may be a victim of the wellness syndrome. In this ground-breaking new book, Carl Cederstrom and Andre Spicer argue that the ever-present pressure to maximize our wellness has started to work against us, making us feel worse and provoking us to withdraw into ourselves. The Wellness Syndrome follows health freaks who go to extremes to find the perfect diet, corporate athletes who start the day with a dance party, and the self-trackers who monitor everything, including their own toilet habits. This is a world where feeling good has become indistinguishable from being good. Visions of social change have been reduced to dreams of individual transformation, political debate has been replaced by insipid moralising, and scientific evidence has been traded for new-age delusions. A lively and humorous diagnosis of the cult of wellness, this book is an indispensable guide for everyone suspicious of our relentless quest to be happier and healthier.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wellness-syndrome-carl-cederstroem-andre-spicer-abridged/">The Wellness Syndrome &#8211; Carl Cederstroem, Andre Spicer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fantasyland : How America Went Haywire: A 500-Year History &#8211; Kurt Andersen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re entitled to your own opinion but not your own facts Fantasy is the USA&#8217;s primary product. From the Pilgrim Fathers onward America has been a place where renegades and freaks came in search of freedom to create their own realities with little objectively regulated truth standing in their way. The freedom to invent and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/">Fantasyland : How America Went Haywire: A 500-Year History &#8211; Kurt Andersen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re entitled to your own opinion but not your own facts    </p>
<p>                    Fantasy is the USA&#8217;s primary product. From the Pilgrim Fathers onward America has been a place where renegades and freaks came in search of freedom to create their own realities with little objectively regulated truth standing in their way. The freedom to invent and believe whatever the hell you like is, in some ways, an unwritten constitutional right. But, this do-your-own-thing freedom also is the driving credo of America&#8217;s current transformation where the difference between opinion and fact is rapidly crumbling.     </p>
<p>                    So how did we get to this weird pseudo-reality, where science and objective facts are dismissed in favour of opinions and wild speculation, or indeed, fantasies? The post truth, fake news, free-for-all mentality isn&#8217;t exactly a new phenomenon. If you want to understand Trump&#8217;s America, how the lines between reality and illusion have become dangerously blurred, you have to go back to the very beginning and take a dizzying road trip across five centuries of crackpot delusion and make-believe from Salem to Scientology.    </p>
<p>                    Fantasyland is a journey that connects the dots between crazed franchises of true believers &#8211; a rich freak show tapestry from Mormons to Flat-Earthers and satanic panic, new age quacks to anti-vaxxers, conspiracy theorists of every stripe, creationists to climate change deniers, UFO-obsessives to gun-toting libertarians, showmen hucksters from P T Barnum to Trump himself, all topped off with a dangerous dose of anti-government paranoia and pseudoscience. Along the way, New York Times bestselling author Kurt Andersen has created a unique and raucous history of America and a new paradigm for understanding our post-factual world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/">Fantasyland : How America Went Haywire: A 500-Year History &#8211; Kurt Andersen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Back Channel to Cuba : The Hidden History of Negotiations between Washington and Havana, Updated Edition &#8211; William M. Leogrande, Peter Kornbluh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/back-channel-to-cuba-the-hidden-history-of-negotiations-between-washington-and-havana-updated-edition-william-m-leogrande-peter-kornbluh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/back-channel-to-cuba-the-hidden-history-of-negotiations-between-washington-and-havana-updated-edition-william-m-leogrande-peter-kornbluh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>History is being made in U.S.-Cuban relations. Now updated to tell the story behind the stunning December 17, 2014, announcement by President Obama and President Castro of their move to restore full diplomatic relations, this powerful book is essential to understanding ongoing efforts towards normalization. Challenging the conventional wisdom of perpetual conflict and aggression between [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/back-channel-to-cuba-the-hidden-history-of-negotiations-between-washington-and-havana-updated-edition-william-m-leogrande-peter-kornbluh-abridged/">Back Channel to Cuba : The Hidden History of Negotiations between Washington and Havana, Updated Edition &#8211; William M. Leogrande, Peter Kornbluh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>History is being made in U.S.-Cuban relations. Now updated to tell the story behind the stunning December 17, 2014, announcement by President Obama and President Castro of their move to restore full diplomatic relations, this powerful book is essential to understanding ongoing efforts towards normalization. Challenging the conventional wisdom of perpetual conflict and aggression between the United States and Cuba since 1959, Back Channel to Cuba chronicles a surprising, untold history of bilateral efforts toward rapprochement and reconciliation. William M. LeoGrande and Peter Kornbluh here present a remarkably new and relevant account, describing how, despite the intense political clamor surrounding efforts to improve relations with Havana, negotiations have been conducted by every presidential administration since Eisenhower&#8217;s through secret, back-channel diplomacy. From John F. Kennedy&#8217;s offering of an olive branch to Fidel Castro after the missile crisis, to Henry Kissinger&#8217;s top secret quest for normalization, to Barack Obama&#8217;s promise of a new approach, LeoGrande and Kornbluh uncovered hundreds of formerly secret U.S. documents and conducted interviews with dozens of negotiators, intermediaries, and policy makers, including Fidel Castro and Jimmy Carter. They reveal a fifty-year record of dialogue and negotiations, both open and furtive, that provides the historical foundation for the dramatic breakthrough in U.S.-Cuba ties.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/back-channel-to-cuba-the-hidden-history-of-negotiations-between-washington-and-havana-updated-edition-william-m-leogrande-peter-kornbluh-abridged/">Back Channel to Cuba : The Hidden History of Negotiations between Washington and Havana, Updated Edition &#8211; William M. Leogrande, Peter Kornbluh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nationalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From Rick Wilson-longtime Republican strategist, political commentator, Daily Beast contributor-the #1 New York Times bestseller about the disease that is destroying the conservative movement and burning down the GOP: Trumpism. Includes an all-new chapter analyzing Trump&#8217;s impact on the 2018 elections. In the #1 New York Times bestselling Everything Trump Touches Dies, political campaign strategist [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/">Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From Rick Wilson-longtime Republican strategist, political commentator, Daily Beast contributor-the #1 New York Times bestseller about the disease that is destroying the conservative movement and burning down the GOP: Trumpism.    </p>
<p>                    Includes an all-new chapter analyzing Trump&#8217;s impact on the 2018 elections.    </p>
<p>                    In the #1 New York Times bestselling Everything Trump Touches Dies, political campaign strategist and commentator Rick Wilson delivers &#8220;a searingly honest, bitingly funny, comprehensive answer to the question we find ourselves asking most mornings: &#8216;What the hell is going on?&#8217; (Chicago Tribune). The Guardian hails Everything Trump Touches Dies, saying it gives, &#8220;more unvarnished truths about Donald Trump than anyone else in the American political establishment has offered. Wilson never holds back.&#8221; Rick mercilessly exposes the damage Trump has done to the country, to the Republican Party, and to the conservative movement that has abandoned its principles for the worst President in American history.    </p>
<p>                    Wilson unblinkingly dismantles Trump&#8217;s deceptions and the illusions to which his supporters cling, shedding light on the guilty parties who empower and enable Trump in Washington and in the media. He calls out the race-war dead-enders who hitched a ride with Trump, the alt-right basement dwellers who worship him, and the social conservatives who looked the other way. Publishers Weekly calls it, &#8220;a scathing, profane, unflinching, and laugh-out-loud funny rebuke of Donald Trump and his presidency.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    No left-winger, Wilson is a lifelong conservative who delivers his withering critique of Trump from the right. A leader of the Never Trump movement, he warned from the start that Trump would destroy the lives and reputations of everyone in his orbit, and Everything Trump Touches Dies is a deft chronicle the tragicomic political story of our time. From the early campaign days through the shock of election night, to the inconceivable train-wreck of Trump&#8217;s first year. Rick Wilson provides not only an insightful analysis of the Trump administration, but also an optimistic path forward for the GOP, the conservative movement, and the country.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Hilarious, smartly written, and usually spot-on&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews), Everything Trump Touches Dies is perfect for those on either side of the aisle who need a dose of unvarnished reality, a good laugh, a strong cocktail, and a return to sanity in American politics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everything-trump-touches-dies-a-republican-strategist-gets-real-about-the-worst-president-ever-rick-wilson-abridged/">Everything Trump Touches Dies : A Republican Strategist Gets Real About the Worst President Ever &#8211; Rick Wilson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Blood of Emmett Till &#8211; Timothy B. Tyson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-blood-of-emmett-till-timothy-b-tyson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-blood-of-emmett-till-timothy-b-tyson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* Longlisted for the National Book Award * Winner of the Robert F. Kennedy Book Award * A New York Times Notable Book * A Washington Post Notable Book * An NPR Best Book of 2017 * A Los Angeles Times Best Book of 2017 * An Atlanta Journal-Constitution Best Southern Book of 2017 * [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-blood-of-emmett-till-timothy-b-tyson-abridged/">The Blood of Emmett Till &#8211; Timothy B. Tyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* Longlisted for the National Book Award * Winner of the Robert F. Kennedy Book Award * A New York Times Notable Book * A Washington Post Notable Book * An NPR Best Book of 2017 * A Los Angeles Times Best Book of 2017 * An Atlanta Journal-Constitution Best Southern Book of 2017 *    </p>
<p>                     This extraordinary New York Times bestseller reexamines a pivotal event of the civil rights movement-the 1955 lynching of Emmett Till-&#8220;and demands that we do the one vital thing we aren&#8217;t often enough asked to do with history: learn from it&#8221; (The Atlantic).    </p>
<p>                    In 1955, white men in the Mississippi Delta lynched a fourteen-year-old from Chicago named Emmett Till. His murder was part of a wave of white terrorism in the wake of the 1954 Supreme Court decision that declared public school segregation unconstitutional. Only weeks later, Rosa Parks thought about young Emmett as she refused to move to the back of a city bus in Montgomery, Alabama. Five years later, Black students who called themselves &#8220;the Emmett Till generation&#8221; launched sit-in campaigns that turned the struggle for civil rights into a mass movement. Till&#8217;s lynching became the most notorious hate crime in American history.    </p>
<p>                    But what actually happened to Emmett Till-not the icon of injustice, but the flesh-and-blood boy? Part detective story, part political history, The Blood of Emmett Till &#8220;unfolds like a movie&#8221; (The Atlanta Journal-Constitution), drawing on a wealth of new evidence, including a shocking admission of Till&#8217;s innocence from the woman in whose name he was killed. &#8220;Jolting and powerful&#8221; (The Washington Post), the book &#8220;provides fresh insight into the way race has informed and deformed our democratic institutions&#8221; (Diane McWhorter, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of Carry Me Home) and &#8220;calls us to the cause of justice today&#8221; (Rev. Dr. William J. Barber, II, president of the North Carolina NAACP).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-blood-of-emmett-till-timothy-b-tyson-abridged/">The Blood of Emmett Till &#8211; Timothy B. Tyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Communist Manifesto &#8211; Karl Marx (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/communist-manifesto-karl-marx-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/communist-manifesto-karl-marx-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Manifesto of the Communist Party (German: Manifest der Kommunistischen Partei), often referred to as The Communist Manifesto, was published on February 21, 1848, and is one of the world&#8217;s most influential political manuscripts. Commissioned by the Communist League and written by communist theorists Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels, it laid out the League&#8217;s purposes and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/communist-manifesto-karl-marx-abridged/">Communist Manifesto &#8211; Karl Marx (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Manifesto of the Communist Party (German: Manifest der Kommunistischen Partei), often referred to as The Communist Manifesto, was published on February 21, 1848, and is one of the world&#8217;s most influential political manuscripts. Commissioned by the Communist League and written by communist theorists Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels, it laid out the League&#8217;s purposes and program. It presents an analytical approach to the class struggle (historical and present) and the problems of capitalism, rather than a prediction of communism&#8217;s potential future forms.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/communist-manifesto-karl-marx-abridged/">Communist Manifesto &#8211; Karl Marx (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>American Lion : Andrew Jackson in the White House &#8211; Jon Meacham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/american-lion-andrew-jackson-in-the-white-house-jon-meacham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-lion-andrew-jackson-in-the-white-house-jon-meacham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The definitive biography of a larger-than-life president who defied norms, divided a nation, and changed Washington forever Andrew Jackson, his intimate circle of friends, and his tumultuous times are at the heart of this remarkable book about the man who rose from nothing to create the modern presidency. Beloved and hated, venerated and reviled, Andrew [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-lion-andrew-jackson-in-the-white-house-jon-meacham-abridged/">American Lion : Andrew Jackson in the White House &#8211; Jon Meacham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The definitive biography of a larger-than-life president who defied norms, divided a nation, and changed Washington forever Andrew Jackson, his intimate circle of friends, and his tumultuous times are at the heart of this remarkable book about the man who rose from nothing to create the modern presidency. Beloved and hated, venerated and reviled, Andrew Jackson was an orphan who fought his way to the pinnacle of power, bending the nation to his will in the cause of democracy. Jackson&#8217;s election in 1828 ushered in a new and lasting era in which the people, not distant elites, were the guiding force in American politics. Democracy made its stand in the Jackson years, and he gave voice to the hopes and the fears of a restless, changing nation facing challenging times at home and threats abroad. To tell the saga of Jackson&#8217;s presidency, acclaimed author Jon Meacham goes inside the Jackson White House. Drawing on newly discovered family letters and papers, he details the human drama-the family, the women, and the inner circle of advisers- that shaped Jackson&#8217;s private world through years of storm and victory.  One of our most significant yet dimly recalled presidents, Jackson was a battle-hardened warrior, the founder of the Democratic Party, and the architect of the presidency as we know it. His story is one of violence, sex, courage, and tragedy. With his powerful persona, his evident bravery, and his mystical connection to the people, Jackson moved the White House from the periphery of government to the center of national action, articulating a vision of change that challenged entrenched interests to heed the popular will- or face his formidable wrath. The greatest of the presidents who have followed Jackson in the White House-from Lincoln to Theodore Roosevelt to FDR to Truman-have found inspiration in his example, and virtue in his vision.  Jackson was the most contradictory of men. The architect of the removal of Indians from their native lands, he was warmly sentimental and risked everything to give more power to ordinary citizens. He was, in short, a lot like his country: alternately kind and vicious, brilliant and blind; and a man who fought a lifelong war to keep the republic safe-no matter what it took.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-lion-andrew-jackson-in-the-white-house-jon-meacham-abridged/">American Lion : Andrew Jackson in the White House &#8211; Jon Meacham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Travel as a Political Act (Third Edition) &#8211; Rick Steves (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/travel-as-a-political-act-third-edition-rick-steves-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/travel-as-a-political-act-third-edition-rick-steves-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the world through travel is a vital way to shape our political views and our social awareness. These days, it&#8217;s more important than ever to engage in travel as an activist. In this fully revised edition of his award-winning book Travel as a Political Act, acclaimed author and activist Rick Steves explains how to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/travel-as-a-political-act-third-edition-rick-steves-abridged/">Travel as a Political Act (Third Edition) &#8211; Rick Steves (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Exploring the world through travel is a vital way to shape our political views and our social awareness. These days, it&#8217;s more important than ever to engage in travel as an activist.    </p>
<p>                    In this fully revised edition of his award-winning book Travel as a Political Act, acclaimed author and activist Rick Steves explains how to travel thoughtfully and honestly, and to come home with a better understanding of how our nation fits into a universal puzzle. In Rick&#8217;s own words, travel connects us with nature, with culture, and most importantly, with people. When we experience the rest of the world, instead of fearing its diversity, we can learn to celebrate it.    </p>
<p>                    With entirely new chapters focused on the far-reaching impact of global events such as Brexit, Trump, and so much more, Rick shows readers how to travel with intention and an open mind. In times of political and cultural turmoil, his ardent philosophy rings truer than ever: beyond new experiences, great art, and tasty cuisine, travel emboldens us to become better citizens of this planet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/travel-as-a-political-act-third-edition-rick-steves-abridged/">Travel as a Political Act (Third Edition) &#8211; Rick Steves (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The American Spirit : Who We Are and What We Stand For &#8211; David McCullough (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-american-spirit-who-we-are-and-what-we-stand-for-david-mccullough-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-american-spirit-who-we-are-and-what-we-stand-for-david-mccullough-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Bestseller A timely collection of speeches by David McCullough, the most honored historian in the United States-winner of two Pulitzer Prizes, two National Book Awards, and the Presidential Medal of Freedom, among many others-that reminds us of fundamental American principles. Over the course of his distinguished career, David McCullough has spoken [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-american-spirit-who-we-are-and-what-we-stand-for-david-mccullough-abridged/">The American Spirit : Who We Are and What We Stand For &#8211; David McCullough (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                     A timely collection of speeches by David McCullough, the most honored historian in the United States-winner of two Pulitzer Prizes, two National Book Awards, and the Presidential Medal of Freedom, among many others-that reminds us of fundamental American principles.    </p>
<p>                    Over the course of his distinguished career, David McCullough has spoken before Congress, the White House, colleges and universities, historical societies, and other esteemed institutions. Now, at a time of self-reflection in America following a bitter election campaign that has left the country divided, McCullough has collected some of his most important speeches in a brief volume designed to identify important principles and characteristics that are particularly American. The American Spirit reminds us of core American values to which we all subscribe, regardless of which region we live in, which political party we identify with, or our ethnic background. This is a book about America for all Americans that reminds us who we are and helps to guide us as we find our way forward.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-american-spirit-who-we-are-and-what-we-stand-for-david-mccullough-abridged/">The American Spirit : Who We Are and What We Stand For &#8211; David McCullough (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Common Sense &#8211; Thomas Paine (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Among the most influential authors and reformers of his age, Thomas Paine (1737-1809) was born in England but went on to play an important role in both the American and French Revolutions. In 1774, he emigrated to America where, for a time, he helped to edit the Pennsylvania Magazine. On January 10, 1776, he published [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/">Common Sense &#8211; Thomas Paine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Among the most influential authors and reformers of his age, Thomas Paine (1737-1809) was born in England but went on to play an important role in both the American and French Revolutions. In 1774, he emigrated to America where, for a time, he helped to edit the Pennsylvania Magazine. On January 10, 1776, he published his pamphlet Common Sense,  a persuasive argument for the colonies&#8217; political and economic separation from Britain.<br />
                    Common Sense cites the evils of monarchy, accuses the British government of inflicting economic and social injustices upon the colonies, and points to the absurdity of an island attempting to rule a continent. Credited by George Washington as having changed the minds of many of his countrymen, the document sold over 500,000 copies within a few months.<br />
                    Today, Common Sense remains a landmark document in the struggle for freedom, distinguished not only by Paine&#8217;s ideas but also by its clear and passionate presentation. Designed to ignite public opinion against autocratic rule, the pamphlet offered a careful balance between imagination and judgment, and appropriate language and expression to fit the subject. It immediately found a receptive audience, heartened Washington&#8217;s despondent army, and foreshadowed much of the phrasing and substance of the Declaration of Independence.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/">Common Sense &#8211; Thomas Paine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classical History / Classical Civilisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A riveting and illuminating tour of how nations deal with crises &#8211; which might hopefully help humanity as a whole deal with our present global crisis&#8217; YUVAL NOAH HARARI, author of SAPIENS ** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Author of the landmark international bestsellers Guns, Germs and Steel and Collapse, Jared Diamond has transformed our understanding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond-abridged/">Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A riveting and illuminating tour of how nations deal with crises &#8211; which might hopefully help humanity as a whole deal with our present global crisis&#8217; YUVAL NOAH HARARI, author of SAPIENS     </p>
<p>                    ** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**     </p>
<p>                    Author of the landmark international bestsellers Guns, Germs and Steel and Collapse, Jared Diamond has transformed our understanding of what makes civilizations rise and fall. Now, at a time when crises are erupting around the world, heexplores what makes certain nations resilient, and reveals the factors that influence how nations and individuals can respond to enormous challenges.     </p>
<p>                    In a riveting journey into the recent past, he traces how six distinctive modern nations &#8211; Finland, Chile, Indonesia, Japan, Germany and Australia &#8211; have survived defining catastrophes, and identifies patterns in their recovery. Looking ahead, he investigates the risk that the United States and other countries, faced by grave threat, are set on a course towards catastrophe.     </p>
<p>                    Adding a rich psychological dimension to the in-depth history, geography, biology and anthropology that underpin all of Diamond&#8217;s writing, Upheaval is epic in scope, but also his most personal book yet.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating &#8230; I finished the book even more optimistic about our ability to solve problems than I started&#8217; BILL GATES    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Jared Diamond does it again: another rich, original and fascinating chapter in the human saga &#8211; with vital lessons for our difficult times&#8217; STEVEN PINKER</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/upheaval-how-nations-cope-with-crisis-and-change-jared-diamond-abridged/">Upheaval : How Nations Cope with Crisis and Change &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the 2018 Waterstones Book of the Year Winner at the 2018 Parliamentary Book Awards Longlisted for the Orwell Prize, 2019 ____________ &#8220;A really good book&#8230; Well-structured and well-written.&#8221; Observer &#8220;Well written and incisive.&#8221; The Times &#8220;Vital and compelling.&#8221; New Statesman In an era when politicians are responsible for the Brexit logjam and embroiled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/">Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the 2018 Waterstones Book of the Year<br />
                    Winner at the 2018 Parliamentary Book Awards<br />
                    Longlisted for the Orwell Prize, 2019<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A really good book&#8230;  Well-structured and well-written.&#8221; Observer<br />
                    &#8220;Well written and incisive.&#8221; The Times<br />
                    &#8220;Vital and compelling.&#8221; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    In an era when politicians are responsible for the Brexit logjam and embroiled in sexual-harassment and expenses scandals, it&#8217;s no wonder we&#8217;ve lost our faith in government. Every year, they introduce new legislation that doesn&#8217;t do what it sets out to achieve &#8211; often with terrible financial and human costs. But, with some notable exceptions, they are decent, hard-working people, doing a hugely difficult and demanding job. In this searching examination of our political class, award-winning journalist Isabel Hardman investigates the strange and demanding world of Westminster, and asks why we end up with representatives we no longer trust &#8211; and how might faith be restored.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/">Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019 Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump. The 2016 election was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times&#8217; Top Books of 2019    </p>
<p>                    Politico Magazine&#8217;s chief political correspondent provides a rollicking insider&#8217;s look at the making of the modern Republican Party-how a decade of cultural upheaval, populist outrage, and ideological warfare made the GOP vulnerable to a hostile takeover from the unlikeliest of insurgents: Donald J. Trump.    </p>
<p>                    The 2016 election was a watershed for the United States. But, as Tim Alberta explains in American Carnage, to understand Trump&#8217;s victory is to view him not as the creator of this era of polarization and bruising partisanship, but rather as its most manifest consequence.    </p>
<p>                    American Carnage is the story of a president&#8217;s rise based on a country&#8217;s evolution and a party&#8217;s collapse. As George W. Bush left office with record-low approval ratings and Barack Obama led a Democratic takeover of Washington, Republicans faced a moment of reckoning: They had no vision, no generation of new leaders, and no energy in the party&#8217;s base. Yet Obama&#8217;s forceful pursuit of his progressive agenda, coupled with the nation&#8217;s rapidly changing cultural and demographic landscape, lit a fire under the right, returning Republicans to power and inviting a bloody struggle for the party&#8217;s identity in the post-Bush era. The factions that emerged-one led by absolutists like Jim Jordan and Ted Cruz, the other led by pragmatists like John Boehner and Mitch McConnell-engaged in a series of devastating internecine clashes and attempted coups for control. With the GOP&#8217;s internal fissures rendering it legislatively impotent, and that impotence fueling a growing resentment toward the political class and its institutions, the stage was set for an outsider to crash the party. When Trump descended a gilded escalator to announce his run in the summer of 2015, the candidate had met the moment.    </p>
<p>                    Only by viewing Trump as the culmination of a decade-long civil war inside the Republican Party-and of the parallel sense of cultural, socioeconomic, and technological disruption during that period-can we appreciate how he won the White House and consider the fundamental questions at the center of America&#8217;s current turmoil. How did a party obsessed with the national debt vote for trillion-dollar deficits and record-setting spending increases? How did the party of compassionate conservatism become the party of Muslim bans and walls? How did the party of family values elect a thrice-divorced philanderer? And, most important, how long can such a party survive?    </p>
<p>                     Loaded with exclusive reporting and based off hundreds of interviews-including with key players such as President Trump, Paul Ryan, Ted Cruz, John Boehner, Mitch McConnell, Jim DeMint, and Reince Priebus, and many others-American Carnage takes us behind the scenes of this tumultuous period as we&#8217;ve never seen it before and establishes Tim Alberta as the premier chronicler of this political era.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/american-carnage-on-the-front-lines-of-the-republican-civil-war-and-the-rise-of-president-trump-tim-alberta-abridged/">American Carnage : On the Front Lines of the Republican Civil War and the Rise of President Trump &#8211; Tim Alberta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crippled : Austerity and the Demonization of Disabled People &#8211; Frances Ryan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crippled-austerity-and-the-demonization-of-disabled-people-frances-ryan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Disability: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crippled-austerity-and-the-demonization-of-disabled-people-frances-ryan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In austerity Britain, disabled people have become the favourite target. From social care to the benefits system, politicians and media alike have made the case Britain&#8217;s 12 million disabled people are a drain on the public purse. In Crippled, leading commentator Frances Ryan exposes the disturbing reality, telling the story of those most affected by [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crippled-austerity-and-the-demonization-of-disabled-people-frances-ryan-abridged/">Crippled : Austerity and the Demonization of Disabled People &#8211; Frances Ryan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In austerity Britain, disabled people have become the favourite target. From social care to the benefits system, politicians and media alike have made the case Britain&#8217;s 12 million disabled people are a drain on the public purse. In Crippled, leading commentator Frances Ryan exposes the disturbing reality, telling the story of those most affected by this devastating regime. This includes a paralyzed man forced to crawl down the stairs because the council wouldn&#8217;t provide accessible housing; the malnourished woman sleeping in her wheelchair; and the young girl with bipolar forced to turn to sex work to survive.     </p>
<p>                    Through these personal stories, Ryan charts how in recent years the public attitude towards disabled people has transformed from compassion to contempt: from society&#8217;s `most vulnerable&#8217; to benefit cheats. Crippled is a damning indictment of a safety net gone wrong, and a passionate demand for an end to austerity measures hitting those most in need.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crippled-austerity-and-the-demonization-of-disabled-people-frances-ryan-abridged/">Crippled : Austerity and the Demonization of Disabled People &#8211; Frances Ryan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>America&#8217;s Bank : The Epic Struggle to Create the Federal Reserve &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A tour de force of historical reportage, America&#8217;s Bank illuminates the tumultuous era and remarkable personalities that spurred the unlikely birth of America&#8217;s modern central bank, the Federal Reserve. Today, the Fed is the bedrock of the financial landscape, yet the fight to create it was so protracted and divisive that it seems a small [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">America&#8217;s Bank : The Epic Struggle to Create the Federal Reserve &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A tour de force of historical reportage, America&#8217;s Bank illuminates the tumultuous era and remarkable personalities that spurred the unlikely birth of America&#8217;s modern central bank, the Federal Reserve. Today, the Fed is the bedrock of the financial landscape, yet the fight to create it was so protracted and divisive that it seems a small miracle that it was ever established.     </p>
<p>                    For nearly a century, America, alone among developed nations, refused to consider any central or organizing agency in its financial system. Americans&#8217; mistrust of big government and of big banks-a legacy of the country&#8217;s Jeffersonian, small-government traditions-was so widespread that modernizing reform was deemed impossible. Each bank was left to stand on its own, with no central reserve or lender of last resort. The real-world consequences of this chaotic and provincial system were frequent financial panics, bank runs, money shortages, and depressions. By the first decade of the twentieth century, it had become plain that the outmoded banking system was ill equipped to finance America&#8217;s burgeoning industry. But political will for reform was lacking. It took an economic meltdown, a high-level tour of Europe, and-improbably-a conspiratorial effort by vilified captains of Wall Street to overcome popular resistance. Finally, in 1913, Congress conceived a federalist and quintessentially American solution to the conflict that had divided bankers, farmers, populists, and ordinary Americans, and enacted the landmark Federal Reserve Act.    </p>
<p>                    Roger Lowenstein-acclaimed financial journalist and bestselling author of When Genius Failed and The End of Wall Street-tells the drama-laden story of how America created the Federal Reserve, thereby taking its first steps onto the world stage as a global financial power. America&#8217;s Bank showcases Lowenstein at his very finest: illuminating complex financial and political issues with striking clarity, infusing the debates of our past with all the gripping immediacy of today, and painting unforgettable portraits of Gilded Age bankers, presidents, and politicians.    </p>
<p>                    Lowenstein focuses on the four men at the heart of the struggle to create the Federal Reserve. These were Paul Warburg, a refined, German-born financier, recently relocated to New York, who was horrified by the primitive condition of America&#8217;s finances; Rhode Island&#8217;s Nelson W. Aldrich, the reigning power broker in the U.S. Senate and an archetypal Gilded Age legislator; Carter Glass, the ambitious, if then little-known, Virginia congressman who chaired the House Banking Committee at a crucial moment of political transition; and President Woodrow Wilson, the academician-turned-progressive-politician who forced Glass to reconcile his deep-seated differences with bankers and accept the principle (anathema to southern Democrats) of federal control. Weaving together a raucous era in American politics with a storied financial crisis and intrigue at the highest levels of Washington and Wall Street, Lowenstein brings the beginnings of one of the country&#8217;s most crucial institutions to vivid and unforgettable life. Readers of this gripping historical narrative will wonder whether they&#8217;re reading about one hundred years ago or the still-seething conflicts that mark our discussions of banking and politics today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/americas-bank-the-epic-struggle-to-create-the-federal-reserve-roger-lowenstein-abridged/">America&#8217;s Bank : The Epic Struggle to Create the Federal Reserve &#8211; Roger Lowenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
