<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Theory Of Warfare &amp; Military Science Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/theory-of-warfare-military-science/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/theory-of-warfare-military-science/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Theory Of Warfare &amp; Military Science Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/theory-of-warfare-military-science/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Accessory to War : The Unspoken Alliance Between Astrophysics and the Military &#8211; Neil deGrasse Tyson</title>
		<link>/accessory-to-war-the-unspoken-alliance-between-astrophysics-and-the-military-neil-degrasse-tyson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrophysics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Space Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/accessory-to-war-the-unspoken-alliance-between-astrophysics-and-the-military-neil-degrasse-tyson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this fascinating foray into the millennia-long relationship between science and military power, acclaimed astrophysicist and &#8220;the world&#8217;s best science communicator&#8221; (Times Literary Supplement) Neil deGrasse Tyson and writer-researcher Avis Lang examine how the methods and tools of astrophysics have been enlisted in the service of war. &#8220;The overlap is strong, and the knowledge flows [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accessory-to-war-the-unspoken-alliance-between-astrophysics-and-the-military-neil-degrasse-tyson/">Accessory to War : The Unspoken Alliance Between Astrophysics and the Military &#8211; Neil deGrasse Tyson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this fascinating foray into the millennia-long relationship between science and military power, acclaimed astrophysicist and &#8220;the world&#8217;s best science communicator&#8221; (Times Literary Supplement) Neil deGrasse Tyson and writer-researcher Avis Lang examine how the methods and tools of astrophysics have been enlisted in the service of war. &#8220;The overlap is strong, and the knowledge flows in both directions&#8221;, say the authors, because astrophysicists and military planners care about many of the same things: multi-spectral detection, ranging, tracking, imaging, high ground, nuclear fusion and access to space. Tyson and Lang call it a &#8220;curiously complicit&#8221; alliance. &#8220;The universe is both the ultimate frontier and the highest of high grounds&#8221;, they write. &#8220;Shared by both space scientists and space warriors, it&#8217;s a laboratory for one and a battlefield for the other. The explorer wants to understand it; the soldier wants to dominate it. But without the right technology-which is more or less the same technology for both parties-nobody can get to it, operate in it, scrutinise it, dominate it or use it to their advantage and someone else&#8217;s disadvantage.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                     Spanning early celestial navigation to satellite-enabled warfare, Accessory to War is a richly researched and provocative examination of the intersection of science, technology, industry and power that will introduce Tyson&#8217;s millions of fans to yet another dimension of how the universe has shaped our lives and our world.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accessory-to-war-the-unspoken-alliance-between-astrophysics-and-the-military-neil-degrasse-tyson/">Accessory to War : The Unspoken Alliance Between Astrophysics and the Military &#8211; Neil deGrasse Tyson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Team of Teams : New Rules of Engagement for a Complex World &#8211; General Stanley McChrystal, David Silverman, Tantum Collins, Chris Fussell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/team-of-teams-new-rules-of-engagement-for-a-complex-world-general-stanley-mcchrystal-david-silverman-tantum-collins-chris-fussell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arbitration, Mediation & Alternative Dispute Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Negotiation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Life & Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Tactics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Administration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/team-of-teams-new-rules-of-engagement-for-a-complex-world-general-stanley-mcchrystal-david-silverman-tantum-collins-chris-fussell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What if you could combine the agility, adaptability, and cohesion of a small team with the power and resources of a giant organization? When General Stanley McChrystal took command of the Joint Special Operations Task Force in Iraq in 2003, he quickly realized that conventional military tactics were failing. The allied forces had a huge [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/team-of-teams-new-rules-of-engagement-for-a-complex-world-general-stanley-mcchrystal-david-silverman-tantum-collins-chris-fussell-abridged/">Team of Teams : New Rules of Engagement for a Complex World &#8211; General Stanley McChrystal, David Silverman, Tantum Collins, Chris Fussell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What if you could combine the agility, adaptability, and cohesion of a small team with the power and resources of a giant organization?    </p>
<p>                    When General Stanley McChrystal took command of the Joint Special Operations Task Force in Iraq in 2003, he quickly realized that conventional military tactics were failing. The allied forces had a huge advantage in numbers, equipment and training &#8211; but none of the enemy&#8217;s speed and flexibility.    </p>
<p>                    McChrystal and his colleagues discarded a century of conventional wisdom to create a &#8216;team of teams&#8217; that combined extremely transparent communication with decentralized decision-making authority.     </p>
<p>                    Faster, flatter and more flexible, the task force beat back al-Qaeda.    </p>
<p>                    In this powerful book, McChrystal and his colleagues show how the challenges they faced in Iraq can be relevant to any leader. Through compelling examples, the authors demonstrate that the &#8216;team of teams&#8217; strategy has worked everywhere from hospital emergency rooms to NASA and has the potential to transform organizations large and small.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A bold argument that leaders can help teams become greater than the sum of their parts&#8217; Charles Duhigg, author of The Power of Habit    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An indispensable guide to organizational change&#8217; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/team-of-teams-new-rules-of-engagement-for-a-complex-world-general-stanley-mcchrystal-david-silverman-tantum-collins-chris-fussell-abridged/">Team of Teams : New Rules of Engagement for a Complex World &#8211; General Stanley McChrystal, David Silverman, Tantum Collins, Chris Fussell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Viruses, Trojans & Worms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As cyber-attacks dominate front-page news, as hackers displace terrorists on the list of global threats, and as top generals warn of a coming cyber war, few books are more timely and enlightening than Dark Territory: The Secret History of Cyber War, by Slate columnist and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Fred Kaplan. Kaplan probes the inner corridors [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/">Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As cyber-attacks dominate front-page news, as hackers displace terrorists on the list of global threats, and as top generals warn of a coming cyber war, few books are more timely and enlightening than Dark Territory: The Secret History of Cyber War, by Slate columnist and Pulitzer Prize-winning journalist Fred Kaplan.    </p>
<p>                     Kaplan probes the inner corridors of the National Security Agency, the beyond-top-secret cyber units in the Pentagon, the &#8220;information warfare&#8221; squads of the military services, and the national security debates in the White House, to tell this never-before-told story of the officers, policymakers, scientists, and spies who devised this new form of warfare and who have been planning and (more often than people know) fighting these wars for decades.    </p>
<p>                     From the 1991 Gulf War to conflicts in Haiti, Serbia, Syria, the former Soviet republics, Iraq, and Iran, where cyber warfare played a significant role, Dark Territory chronicles, in fascinating detail, a little-known past that shines an unsettling light on our future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-territory-the-secret-history-of-cyber-war-fred-kaplan-abridged/">Dark Territory : The Secret History of Cyber War &#8211; Fred Kaplan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Red Team : How to Succeed By Thinking Like the Enemy &#8211; Micah Zenko (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/red-team-how-to-succeed-by-thinking-like-the-enemy-micah-zenko-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[War & Defence Operations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/red-team-how-to-succeed-by-thinking-like-the-enemy-micah-zenko-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Red teaming. It is a practice as old as the Devil&#8217;s Advocate, the eleventh-century Vatican official charged with discrediting candidates for sainthood. Today, red teams,comprised primarily of fearless skeptics and those assuming the role of saboteurs who seek to better understand the interests, intentions, and capabilities of institutions or potential competitors,are used widely in both [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-team-how-to-succeed-by-thinking-like-the-enemy-micah-zenko-abridged/">Red Team : How to Succeed By Thinking Like the Enemy &#8211; Micah Zenko (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Red teaming. It is a practice as old as the Devil&#8217;s Advocate, the eleventh-century Vatican official charged with discrediting candidates for sainthood. Today, red teams,comprised primarily of fearless skeptics and those assuming the role of saboteurs who seek to better understand the interests, intentions, and capabilities of institutions or potential competitors,are used widely in both the public and private sector. Red teaming, including simulations, vulnerability probes, and alternative analyses, helps institutions in competitive environments to identify vulnerabilities and weaknesses, challenge assumptions, and anticipate potential threats ahead of the next special operations raid, malicious cyberattack, or corporate merger. But not all red teams are created equal indeed, some cause more damage than they prevent. In  Red Team , national security expert Micah Zenko provides an in-depth investigation into the work of red teams, revealing the best practices, most common pitfalls, and most effective applications of these modern-day Devil&#8217;s Advocates. The best practices of red teaming can be applied to the CIA, NYPD, or a pharmaceutical company, and executed correctly they can yield impressive results: red teams give businesses an edge over their competition, poke holes in vital intelligence estimates, and troubleshoot dangerous military missions long before boots are on the ground. But red teams are only as good as leaders allow them to be, and Zenko shows not only how to create and empower red teams, but also what to do with the information they produce.Essential reading for business leaders and policymakers alike,  Red Team  will revolutionize the way organizations think about, exploit, compensate for, and correct their institutional strengths and weaknesses. Drawing on little-known case studies and unprecedented access to elite red teamers in the United States and abroad, Zenko shows how any group,from military units to friendly hackers,can win by thinking like the enemy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-team-how-to-succeed-by-thinking-like-the-enemy-micah-zenko-abridged/">Red Team : How to Succeed By Thinking Like the Enemy &#8211; Micah Zenko (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
