<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Ethical &amp; Social Aspects Of Computing Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/ethical-social-aspects-of-computing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/ethical-social-aspects-of-computing/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Ethical &amp; Social Aspects Of Computing Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/ethical-social-aspects-of-computing/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Augmented : Life in the Smart Lane &#8211; Brett King</title>
		<link>/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Internet and smartphone are just the latest in a 250 year long cycle of disruption that has continuously changed the way we live, the way we work and the way we interact. The coming Augmented Age, however, promises a level of disruption, behavioral shifts and changes that are unparalleled. While consumers today are camping [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/">Augmented : Life in the Smart Lane &#8211; Brett King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Internet and smartphone are just the latest in a 250 year long cycle of disruption that has continuously changed the way we live, the way we work and the way we interact. The coming Augmented Age, however, promises a level of disruption, behavioral shifts and changes that are unparalleled. While consumers today are camping outside of an Apple store waiting to be one of the first to score a new Apple Watch or iPhone, the next generation of wearables will be able to predict if we&#8217;re likely to have a heart attack and recommend a course of action. We watch news of Google&#8217;s self-driving cars, but don&#8217;t likely realize this means progressive cities will have to ban human drives in the next decade because us humans are too risky.  Following on from the Industrial or Machine Age, the Space Age and the Digital Age, the Augmented Age will be based on four key disruptive themes &#8211; Artificial Intelligence, Experience Design, Smart Infrastructure, and Health Tech. Historically the previous &#8216;ages&#8217; brought significant disruption and changes, but on a net basis jobs were created, wealth was enhanced, and the health and security of society improved. What will the Augmented Age bring?<br />
                    Will robots take our jobs, and AI&#8217;s subsume us as inferior intelligences, or will this usher in a new age of abundance?  Augmented is a book on future history, but more than that, it is a story about how you will live your life in a world that will change more in the next 20 years than it has in the last 250 years. Are you ready to adapt? Because if history proves anything, you don&#8217;t have much of a choice.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/augmented-life-in-the-smart-lane-brett-king/">Augmented : Life in the Smart Lane &#8211; Brett King</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Seventh Sense : Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks &#8211; Joshua Cooper Ramo (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER WASHINGTON POST BESTSELLER Winner of the getAbstract 17th International Book Award &#8220;The Seventh Sense is a concept every businessman, diplomat, or student should aspire to master&#8211;a powerful idea, backed by stories and figures that will be impossible to forget.&#8221; &#8212; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs and Leonardo da Vinci Endless [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/">The Seventh Sense : Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks &#8211; Joshua Cooper Ramo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    WASHINGTON POST BESTSELLER Winner of the getAbstract 17th International Book Award &#8220;The Seventh Sense is a concept every businessman, diplomat, or student should aspire to master&#8211;a powerful idea, backed by stories and figures that will be impossible to forget.&#8221; &#8212; Walter Isaacson, author of Steve Jobs and Leonardo da Vinci Endless terror. Refugee waves. An unfixable global economy. Surprising election results. New billion-dollar fortunes. Miracle medical advances. What if they were all connected? What if you could understand why?  The Seventh Sense is the story of what all of today&#8217;s successful figures see and feel: the forces that are invisible to most of us but explain everything from explosive technological change to uneasy political ripples. The secret to power now is understanding our new age of networks. Not merely the Internet, but also webs of trade, finance, and even DNA. Based on his years of advising generals, CEOs, and politicians, Ramo takes us into the opaque heart of our world&#8217;s rapidly connected systems and teaches us what the losers are not yet seeing&#8211;and what the victors of this age already know.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seventh-sense-power-fortune-and-survival-in-the-age-of-networks-joshua-cooper-ramo-abridged/">The Seventh Sense : Power, Fortune, and Survival in the Age of Networks &#8211; Joshua Cooper Ramo (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Them : Why We Hate Each Other&#8211;and How to Heal &#8211; Ben Sasse (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Something is wrong. We all know it. American life expectancy is declining for a third straight year. Birth rates are dropping. Nearly half of us think the other political party isn&#8217;t just wrong; they&#8217;re evil. We&#8217;re the richest country in history, but we&#8217;ve never been more pessimistic. What&#8217;s causing the despair? In Them, bestselling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/">Them : Why We Hate Each Other&#8211;and How to Heal &#8211; Ben Sasse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Something is wrong. We all know it. American life expectancy is declining for a third straight year. Birth rates are dropping. Nearly half of us think the other political party isn&#8217;t just wrong; they&#8217;re evil. We&#8217;re the richest country in history, but we&#8217;ve never been more pessimistic. What&#8217;s causing the despair?    </p>
<p>                    In Them, bestselling author and U.S. senator Ben Sasse argues that our crisis isn&#8217;t really about politics. It&#8217;s that we&#8217;re so lonely we can&#8217;t see straight &#8211; and it bubbles out as anger. Local communities are collapsing. Across the nation, little leagues are disappearing, Rotary clubs are dwindling, and in all likelihood, we don&#8217;t know the neighbour two doors down. Work isn&#8217;t what we&#8217;d hoped: less certainty, few lifelong coworkers, shallow purpose. Stable families and enduring friendships &#8211; life&#8217;s fundamental pillars &#8211; are in statistical freefall.    </p>
<p>                    As traditional tribes of place evaporate, we rally against common enemies so we can feel part of a team. No institutions command widespread public trust, enabling foreign intelligence agencies to use technology to pick the scabs on our toxic divisions. We&#8217;re in danger of half of us believing different facts than the other half, and the digital revolution throws gas on the fire.    </p>
<p>                    There&#8217;s a path forward &#8211; but reversing our decline requires something radical: a rediscovery of real places and human-to-human relationships. Even as technology nudges us to become rootless, Sasse shows how only a recovery of rootedness can heal our lonely souls. America wants you to be happy, but more urgently, America needs you to love your neighbour and connect with your community. Fixing what&#8217;s wrong with the country depends on it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/them-why-we-hate-each-other-and-how-to-heal-ben-sasse-abridged/">Them : Why We Hate Each Other&#8211;and How to Heal &#8211; Ben Sasse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Children]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Nonfiction Pick; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly Best Book of the Year Clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair takes an in-depth look at how the Internet and the digital revolution are profoundly changing childhood and family dynamics, and offers solutions parents can use to successfully shepherd their children through the technological wilderness. As the focus of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/">The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Nonfiction Pick; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly Best Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair takes an in-depth look at how the Internet and the digital revolution are profoundly changing childhood and family dynamics, and offers solutions parents can use to successfully shepherd their children through the technological wilderness.    </p>
<p>                    As the focus of the family has turned to the glow of the screen&#8211;children constantly texting their friends or going online to do homework; parents working online around the clock&#8211;everyday life is undergoing a massive transformation. Easy access to the Internet and social media has erased the boundaries that protect children from damaging exposure to excessive marketing and the unsavory aspects of adult culture. Parents often feel they are losing a meaningful connection with their children. Children are feeling lonely and alienated. The digital world is here to stay, but what are families losing with technology&#8217;s gain?    </p>
<p>                    As renowned clinical psychologist Catherine Steiner-Adair explains, families are in crisis as they face this issue, and even more so than they realize. Not only do chronic tech distractions have deep and lasting effects but children also desperately need parents to provide what tech cannot: close, significant interactions with the adults in their lives. Drawing on real-life stories from her clinical work with children and parents and her consulting work with educators and experts across the country, Steiner-Adair offers insights and advice that can help parents achieve greater understanding, authority, and confidence as they engage with the tech revolution unfolding in their living rooms.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-disconnect-protecting-childhood-and-family-relationships-in-the-digital-age-dr-catherine-steiner-adair-teresa-h-barker-abridged/">The Big Disconnect : Protecting Childhood and Family Relationships in the Digital Age &#8211; Dr Catherine Steiner-Adair, Teresa H Barker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Propaganda]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Does &#8216;fake news&#8217; really exist? Find out from the ultimate insider. After years of working as a respected journalist, Nick Davies, in this shocking expose, reveals what really goes on behind the scenes of this contentious industry. From a prestigious newspaper that allowed intelligence agencies to plant fiction in its columns, to the newsroom that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/">Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Does &#8216;fake news&#8217; really exist? Find out from the ultimate insider.    </p>
<p>                    After years of working as a respected journalist, Nick Davies, in this shocking expose, reveals what really goes on behind the scenes of this contentious industry.     </p>
<p>                    From a prestigious newspaper that allowed intelligence agencies to plant fiction in its columns, to the newsroom that routinely rejected stories due to racial bias, to the number of papers that accepted cash bribes. Gripping, thought-provoking and revelatory, this is an insider&#8217;s look at one of the most tainted professions.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Meticulous, fair-minded and utterly gripping&#8217; Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Powerful and timely&#8230;his analysis is fair, meticulously researched and fascinating&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/">Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fabricated : The New World of 3D Printing &#8211; Hod Lipson, Melba Kurman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[3D Graphics & Modelling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Chemistry & Manufacturing Technologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fabricated tells the story of 3D printers, humble manufacturing machines that are bursting out of the factory and into schools, kitchens, hospitals, even onto the fashion catwalk. Fabricated describes our emerging world of printable products, where people design and 3D print their own creations as easily as they edit an online document. A 3D printer [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/">Fabricated : The New World of 3D Printing &#8211; Hod Lipson, Melba Kurman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fabricated tells the story of 3D printers, humble manufacturing machines that are bursting out of the factory and into schools, kitchens, hospitals, even onto the fashion catwalk. Fabricated describes our emerging world of printable products, where people design and 3D print their own creations as easily as they edit an online document. A 3D printer transforms digital information into a physical object by carrying out instructions from an electronic design file, or &#8216;blueprint.&#8217; Guided by a design file, a 3D printer lays down layer after layer of a raw material to &#8216;print&#8217; out an object. That&#8217;s not the whole story, however. The magic happens when you plug a 3D printer into today s mind-boggling digital technologies. Add to that the Internet, tiny, low cost electronic circuitry, radical advances in materials science and biotech and voila! The result is an explosion of technological and social innovation. Fabricated takes the reader onto a rich and fulfilling journey that explores how 3D printing is poised to impact nearly every part of our lives.<br />
                    Aimed at people who enjoy books on business strategy, popular science and novel technology, Fabricated will provide readers with practical and imaginative insights to the question &#8216;how will this technology change my life?&#8217; Based on hundreds of hours of research and dozens of interviews with experts from a broad range of industries, Fabricated offers readers an informative, engaging and fast-paced introduction to 3D printing now and in the future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fabricated-the-new-world-of-3d-printing-hod-lipson-melba-kurman-abridged/">Fabricated : The New World of 3D Printing &#8211; Hod Lipson, Melba Kurman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Do Nothing : Resisting the Attention Economy &#8211; Jenny Odell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-do-nothing-resisting-the-attention-economy-jenny-odell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Art & Photography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronic & Video Art]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-do-nothing-resisting-the-attention-economy-jenny-odell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** A New York Times Bestseller ** NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY: Time &#8211; The New Yorker &#8211; NPR &#8211; GQ &#8211; Elle &#8211; Vulture &#8211; Fortune &#8211; Boing Boing &#8211; The Irish Times &#8211; The New York Public Library &#8211; The Brooklyn Public Library A complex, smart and ambitious [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-do-nothing-resisting-the-attention-economy-jenny-odell-abridged/">How To Do Nothing : Resisting the Attention Economy &#8211; Jenny Odell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** A New York Times Bestseller **     </p>
<p>                    NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY: Time &#8211; The New Yorker &#8211; NPR &#8211; GQ &#8211; Elle &#8211; Vulture &#8211; Fortune &#8211; Boing Boing &#8211; The Irish Times &#8211; The New York Public Library &#8211; The Brooklyn Public Library     </p>
<p>                    A complex, smart and ambitious book that at first reads like a self-help manual, then blossoms into a wide-ranging political manifesto.&#8211;Jonah Engel Bromwich, The New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    One of President Barack Obama&#8217;s Favorite Books of 2019<br />
                    Porchlight&#8217;s Personal Development &#038; Human Behavior Book of the Year     </p>
<p>                    In a world where addictive technology is designed to buy and sell our attention, and our value is determined by our 24/7 data productivity, it can seem impossible to escape. But in this inspiring field guide to dropping out of the attention economy, artist and critic Jenny Odell shows us how we can still win back our lives.     </p>
<p>                     Odell sees our attention as the most precious&#8211;and overdrawn&#8211;resource we have. And we must actively and continuously choose how we use it. We might not spend it on things that capitalism has deemed important &#8230; but once we can start paying a new kind of attention, she writes, we can undertake bolder forms of political action, reimagine humankind&#8217;s role in the environment, and arrive at more meaningful understandings of happiness and progress.     </p>
<p>                     Far from the simple anti-technology screed, or the back-to-nature meditation we read so often, How to do Nothing is an action plan for thinking outside of capitalist narratives of efficiency and techno-determinism. Provocative, timely, and utterly persuasive, this book will change how you see your place in our world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-do-nothing-resisting-the-attention-economy-jenny-odell-abridged/">How To Do Nothing : Resisting the Attention Economy &#8211; Jenny Odell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adult Education, Continuous Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Employment & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Services & Welfare, Criminology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Looking for ways to handle the transition to a digital economy.Robots, artificial intelligence, and driverless cars are no longer things of the distant future. They are with us today and will become increasingly common in coming years, along with virtual reality and digital personal assistants. As these tools advance deeper into everyday use, they raise [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/">The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Looking for ways to handle the transition to a digital economy.Robots, artificial intelligence, and driverless cars are no longer things of the distant future. They are with us today and will become increasingly common in coming years, along with virtual reality and digital personal assistants.    </p>
<p>                    As these tools advance deeper into everyday use, they raise the question-how will they transform society, the economy, and politics? If companies need fewer workers due to automation and robotics, what happens to those who once held those jobs and don&#8217;t have the skills for new jobs? And since many social benefits are delivered through jobs, how are people outside the workforce for a lengthy period of time going to earn a living and get health care and social benefits?    </p>
<p>                    Looking past today&#8217;s headlines, political scientist and cultural observer Darrell M. West argues that society needs to rethink the concept of jobs, reconfigure the social contract, move toward a system of lifetime learning, and develop a new kind of politics that can deal with economic dislocations. With the U.S. governance system in shambles because of political polarization and hyper-partisanship, dealing creatively with the transition to a fully digital economy will vex political leaders and complicate the adoption of remedies that could ease the transition pain. It is imperative that we make major adjustments in how we think about work and the social contract in order to prevent society from spiraling out of control.    </p>
<p>                    This book presents a number of proposals to help people deal with the transition from an industrial to a digital economy. We must broaden the  concept of employment to include volunteering and parenting and pay greater attention to the opportunities for leisure time. New forms of identity will be possible when the &#8220;job&#8221; no longer defines people&#8217;s sense of personal meaning, and they engage in a broader range of activities. Workers will need help throughout their lifetimes to acquire new skills and develop new job capabilities. Political reforms will be necessary to  reduce polarization and restore civility so there can be open and healthy debate about where responsibility lies for economic well-being.    </p>
<p>                    This book is an important contribution to a discussion about tomorrow-one that needs to take place today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-work-robots-ai-and-automation-darrell-m-west-abridged/">The Future of Work : Robots, AI, and Automation &#8211; Darrell M. West (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Heffernan &#8220;melds the personal with the increasingly universal in a highly informative analysis of what the Internet is-and can be. A thoroughly engrossing examination of the Internet&#8217;s past, present, and future&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review) from one of the best living writers of English prose. This book makes a bold claim: The Internet is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/">Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Heffernan &#8220;melds the personal with the increasingly universal in a highly informative analysis of what the Internet is-and can be. A thoroughly engrossing examination of the Internet&#8217;s past, present, and future&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review) from one of the best living writers of English prose.    </p>
<p>                    This book makes a bold claim: The Internet is among mankind&#8217;s great masterpieces-a massive work of art. As an idea, it rivals monotheism. But its cultural potential and its societal impact often elude us. In this deep and thoughtful book, Virginia Heffernan reveals the logic and aesthetics behind the Internet, just as Susan Sontag did for photography and Marshall McLuhan did for television.    </p>
<p>                    Life online, in the highly visual, social, portable, and global incarnation rewards certain virtues. The new medium favors speed, accuracy, wit, prolificacy, and versatility, and its form and functions are changing how we perceive, experience, and understand the world. In &#8220;sumptuous writing, saturated with observations that are simultaneously personal, cultural, and strikingly original&#8221; (The New Republic), Heffernan presents &#8220;a revealing look at how the Internet continues to reshape our lives emotionally, visually, and culturally&#8221; (The Smithsonian Magazine). &#8220;Magic and Loss is an illuminating guide to the Internet&#8230;it is impossible to come away from this book without sharing some of Heffernan&#8217;s awe for this brave new world&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/">Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uncanny Valley : Seduction and Disillusionment in San Francisco&#8217;s Startup Scene &#8211; Anna Wiener (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/uncanny-valley-seduction-and-disillusionment-in-san-franciscos-startup-scene-anna-wiener-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/uncanny-valley-seduction-and-disillusionment-in-san-franciscos-startup-scene-anna-wiener-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Joan Didion at a startup&#8217; Rebecca Solnit &#8216;Impossibly pleasurable&#8217; Jia Tolentino &#8216;This is essential reading&#8217; Stylist At twenty-five years old, Anna Wiener was beginning to tire of her assistant job in New York publishing. There was no room to grow, and the voyeuristic thrill of answering someone else&#8217;s phone had worn thin. Within a year [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/uncanny-valley-seduction-and-disillusionment-in-san-franciscos-startup-scene-anna-wiener-abridged/">Uncanny Valley : Seduction and Disillusionment in San Francisco&#8217;s Startup Scene &#8211; Anna Wiener (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Joan Didion at a startup&#8217; Rebecca Solnit    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Impossibly pleasurable&#8217; Jia Tolentino    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;This is essential reading&#8217; Stylist    </p>
<p>                              At twenty-five years old, Anna Wiener was beginning to tire of her assistant job in New York publishing. There was no room to grow, and the voyeuristic thrill of answering someone else&#8217;s phone had worn thin.    </p>
<p>                              Within a year she had moved to Silicon Valley to take up a job at a data analytics startup in San Francisco. Leaving her business casual skirts and shirts in the wardrobe, she began working in company-branded T-shirts. She had a healthy income for the first time in her life. She felt like part of the future.    </p>
<p>                              But a tide was beginning to turn. People were speaking of tech startups as surveillance companies. Out of sixty employees, only eight of her colleagues were women. Casual sexism was rife. Sexual harassment cases were proliferating. And soon, like everyone else, she was addicted to the internet, refreshing the news, refreshing social media, scrolling and scrolling and scrolling. Slowly, she began to realise that her blind faith in ambitious, arrogant young men from America&#8217;s soft suburbs wasn&#8217;t just her own personal pathology. It had become a global affliction.    </p>
<p>                              Uncanny Valley is a coming of age story set against the backdrop of our generation&#8217;s very own gold rush. It&#8217;s a story about the tension between old and new, between art and tech, between the quest for money and the quest for meaning &#8211; about how our world is changing forever.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/uncanny-valley-seduction-and-disillusionment-in-san-franciscos-startup-scene-anna-wiener-abridged/">Uncanny Valley : Seduction and Disillusionment in San Francisco&#8217;s Startup Scene &#8211; Anna Wiener (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Labour Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Robotics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As we approach a great turning point in history when technology is poised to redefine what it means to be human, The Fourth Age offers fascinating insight into AI, robotics, and their extraordinary implications for our species. &#8220;If you only read just one book about the AI revolution, make it this one&#8221; (John Mackey, cofounder [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/">The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As we approach a great turning point in history when technology is poised to redefine what it means to be human, The Fourth Age offers fascinating insight into AI, robotics, and their extraordinary implications for our species. &#8220;If you only read just one book about the AI revolution, make it this one&#8221; (John Mackey, cofounder and CEO, Whole Foods Market).     </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Age, Byron Reese makes the case that technology has reshaped humanity just three times in history: 100,000 years ago, we harnessed fire, which led to language; 10,000 years ago, we developed agriculture, which led to cities and warfare; 5,000 years ago, we invented the wheel and writing, which lead to the nation state.    </p>
<p>                    We are now on the doorstep of a fourth change brought about by two technologies: AI and robotics. &#8220;Timely, highly informative, and certainly optimistic&#8221; (Booklist), The Fourth Age provides an essential background on how we got to this point, and how-rather than what-we should think about the topics we&#8217;ll soon all be facing: machine consciousness, automation, changes in employment, creative computers, radical life extension, artificial life, AI ethics, the future of warfare, superintelligence, and the implications of extreme prosperity.    </p>
<p>                    By asking questions like &#8220;Are you a machine?&#8221; and &#8220;Could a computer feel anything?&#8221;, Reese leads you through a discussion along the cutting edge in robotics and AI, and provides a framework by which we can all understand, discuss, and act on the issues of the Fourth Age and how they&#8217;ll transform humanity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-age-smart-robots-conscious-computers-and-the-future-of-humanity-byron-reese-abridged/">The Fourth Age : Smart Robots, Conscious Computers, and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Byron Reese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Speak Machine : Computational Thinking for the Rest of Us &#8211; John Maeda (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-speak-machine-computational-thinking-for-the-rest-of-us-john-maeda-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Programming / Software Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-speak-machine-computational-thinking-for-the-rest-of-us-john-maeda-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Visionary designer and technologist John Maeda defines the fundamental laws of how computers think, and why you should care even if you aren&#8217;t a programmer. &#8220;Maeda is to design what Warren Buffett is to finance.&#8221; &#8211;Wired John Maeda is one of the world&#8217;s preeminent interdisciplinary thinkers on technology and design. In How to Speak Machine, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-speak-machine-computational-thinking-for-the-rest-of-us-john-maeda-abridged/">How to Speak Machine : Computational Thinking for the Rest of Us &#8211; John Maeda (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Visionary designer and technologist John Maeda defines the fundamental laws of how computers think, and why you should care even if you aren&#8217;t a programmer.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Maeda is to design what Warren Buffett is to finance.&#8221; &#8211;Wired    </p>
<p>                    John Maeda is one of the world&#8217;s preeminent interdisciplinary thinkers on technology and design. In How to Speak Machine, he offers a set of simple laws that govern not only the computers of today, but the unimaginable machines of the future.     </p>
<p>                    Technology is already more powerful than we can comprehend, and getting more powerful at an exponential pace. Once set in motion, algorithms never tire. And when a program&#8217;s size, speed, and tirelessness combine with its ability to learn and transform itself, the outcome can be unpredictable and dangerous. Take the seemingly instant transformation of Microsoft&#8217;s chatbot Tay into a hate-spewing racist, or how crime-predicting algorithms reinforce racial bias.    </p>
<p>                    How to Speak Machine provides a coherent framework for today&#8217;s product designers, business leaders, and policymakers to grasp this brave new world. Drawing on his wide-ranging experience from engineering to computer science to design, Maeda shows how businesses and individuals can identify opportunities afforded by technology to make world-changing and inclusive products&#8211;while avoiding the pitfalls inherent to the medium.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-speak-machine-computational-thinking-for-the-rest-of-us-john-maeda-abridged/">How to Speak Machine : Computational Thinking for the Rest of Us &#8211; John Maeda (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What To Do When Machines Do Everything : How to Get Ahead in a World of AI, Algorithms, Bots, and Big Data &#8211; Malcolm Frank, Paul Roehrig, Ben Pring (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Automatic Control Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office Systems & Equipment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The essential playbook for the future of your business What To Do When Machines Do Everything is a guidebook to succeeding in the next generation of the digital economy. When systems running on Artificial Intelligence can drive our cars, diagnose medical patients, and manage our finances more effectively than humans it raises profound questions on [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/">What To Do When Machines Do Everything : How to Get Ahead in a World of AI, Algorithms, Bots, and Big Data &#8211; Malcolm Frank, Paul Roehrig, Ben Pring (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The essential playbook for the future of your business What To Do When Machines Do Everything is a guidebook to succeeding in the next generation of the digital economy. When systems running on Artificial Intelligence can drive our cars, diagnose medical patients, and manage our finances more effectively than humans it raises profound questions on the future of work and how companies compete. Illustrated with real-world cases, data, and insight, the authors provide clear strategic guidance and actionable steps to help you and your organization move ahead in a world where exponentially developing new technologies are changing how value is created. Written by a team of business and technology expert practitioners who also authored Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business this book provides a clear path to the future of your work. The first part of the book examines the once in a generation upheaval most every organization will soon face as systems of intelligence go mainstream.<br />
                    The authors argue that contrary to the doom and gloom that surrounds much of IT and business at the moment, we are in fact on the cusp of the biggest wave of opportunity creation since the Industrial Revolution. Next, the authors detail a clear-cut business model to help leaders take part in this coming boom; the AHEAD model outlines five strategic initiatives Automate, Halos, Enhance, Abundance, and Discovery that are central to competing in the next phase of global business by driving new levels of efficiency, customer intimacy and innovation. Business leaders today have two options: be swallowed up by the ongoing technological evolution, or ride the crest of the wave to new profits and better business. This book shows you how to avoid your own extinction event, and will help you; * Understand the untold full extent of technology&#8217;s impact on the way we work and live.<br />
                    * Find out where we&#8217;re headed, and how soon the future will arrive * Leverage the new emerging paradigm into a sustainable business advantage * Adopt a strategic model for winning in the new economy The digital world is already transforming how we work, live, and shop, how we are governed and entertained, and how we manage our money, health, security, and relationships. Don&#8217;t let your business or your career get left behind. What To Do When Machines Do Everything is your strategic roadmap to a future full of possibility and success. Or peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/what-to-do-when-machines-do-everything-how-to-get-ahead-in-a-world-of-ai-algorithms-bots-and-big-data-malcolm-frank-paul-roehrig-ben-pring-abridged/">What To Do When Machines Do Everything : How to Get Ahead in a World of AI, Algorithms, Bots, and Big Data &#8211; Malcolm Frank, Paul Roehrig, Ben Pring (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the inventor of the most innovative and compelling technology of our era, an international authority on artificial intelligence, and one of our greatest living visionaries. Now he offers a framework for envisioning the twenty-first century&#8211;an age in which the marriage of human sensitivity and artificial intelligence fundamentally alters and improves the way [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the inventor of the most innovative and compelling technology of our era, an international authority on artificial intelligence, and one of our greatest living visionaries. Now he offers a framework for envisioning the twenty-first century&#8211;an age in which the marriage of human sensitivity and artificial intelligence fundamentally alters and improves the way we live. Kurzweil&#8217;s prophetic blueprint for the future takes us through the advances that inexorably result in computers exceeding the memory capacity and computational ability of the human brain by the year 2020 (with human-level capabilities not far behind); in relationships with automated personalities who will be our teachers, companions, and lovers; and in information fed straight into our brains along direct neural pathways. Optimistic and challenging, thought-provoking and engaging, The Age of Spiritual Machines is the ultimate guide on our road into the next century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Move Fast and Break Things : How Facebook, Google and Amazon Have Cornered Culture and Undermined Democracy &#8211; Jonathan Taplin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Network Security]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Financial Times &#8216;Best Thing I Read This Year&#8217; LONGLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD Google. Amazon. Facebook. The modern world is defined by vast digital monopolies turning ever-larger profits. Those of us who consume the content that feeds them are farmed for the purposes of being sold ever [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/">Move Fast and Break Things : How Facebook, Google and Amazon Have Cornered Culture and Undermined Democracy &#8211; Jonathan Taplin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Financial Times &#8216;Best Thing I Read This Year&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    LONGLISTED FOR THE FT &#038; MCKINSEY BUSINESS BOOK OF THE YEAR AWARD    </p>
<p>                    Google. Amazon. Facebook. The modern world is defined by vast digital monopolies turning ever-larger profits. Those of us who consume the content that feeds them are farmed for the purposes of being sold ever more products and advertising. Those that create the content &#8211; the artists, writers and musicians &#8211; are finding they can no longer survive in this unforgiving economic landscape.     </p>
<p>                     But it didn&#8217;t have to be this way.     </p>
<p>                     In Move Fast and Break Things, Jonathan Taplin offers a succinct and powerful history of how online life began to be shaped around the values of the entrepreneurs like Peter Thiel and Larry Page who founded these all-powerful companies. Their unprecedented growth came at the heavy cost of tolerating piracy of books, music and film, while at the same time promoting opaque business practices and subordinating the privacy of individual users to create the surveillance marketing monoculture in which we now live.    </p>
<p>                    It is the story of a massive reallocation of revenue in which $50 billion a year has moved from the creators and owners of content to the monopoly platforms. With this reallocation of money comes a shift in power. Google, Facebook and Amazon now enjoy political power on par with Big Oil and Big Pharma, which in part explains how such a tremendous shift in revenues from creators to platforms could have been achieved and why it has gone unchallenged for so long.    </p>
<p>                    And if you think that&#8217;s got nothing to do with you, their next move is to come after your jobs.     </p>
<p>                    Move Fast and Break Things is a call to arms, to say that is enough is enough and to demand that we do everything in our power to create a different future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/move-fast-and-break-things-how-facebook-google-and-amazon-have-cornered-culture-and-undermined-democracy-jonathan-taplin-abridged/">Move Fast and Break Things : How Facebook, Google and Amazon Have Cornered Culture and Undermined Democracy &#8211; Jonathan Taplin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Breakpoint : Why the Web Will Implode, Search Will be Obsolete, and Everything Else You Need to Know About Technology is in Your Brain &#8211; Robert David Grant, Jeff Stibel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/breakpoint-why-the-web-will-implode-search-will-be-obsolete-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-technology-is-in-your-brain-robert-david-grant-jeff-stibel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/breakpoint-why-the-web-will-implode-search-will-be-obsolete-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-technology-is-in-your-brain-robert-david-grant-jeff-stibel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller USA Today Bestseller We are living in a world in which cows send texts to farmers when they&#8217;re in heat, where the most valuable real estate in New York City houses computers, not people, and some of humanity&#8217;s greatest works are created by crowds, not individuals. We are in the midst [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/breakpoint-why-the-web-will-implode-search-will-be-obsolete-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-technology-is-in-your-brain-robert-david-grant-jeff-stibel-abridged/">Breakpoint : Why the Web Will Implode, Search Will be Obsolete, and Everything Else You Need to Know About Technology is in Your Brain &#8211; Robert David Grant, Jeff Stibel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>New York Times Bestseller     </p>
<p>                    USA Today Bestseller     </p>
<p>                    We are living in a world in which cows send texts to farmers when they&#8217;re in heat, where the most valuable real estate in New York City houses computers, not people, and some of humanity&#8217;s greatest works are created by crowds, not individuals.     </p>
<p>                    We are in the midst of a networking revolution&#8211;set to transform the way we access the world&#8217;s information and the way we connect with one another. Studying biological systems is perhaps the best way to understand such networks, and nature has a lesson for us if we care to listen: bigger is rarely better in the long run. The deadliest creature is the mosquito, not the lion. It is the quality of a network that is important for survival, not the size, and all networks&#8211;the human brain, Facebook, Google, even the internet itself&#8211;eventually reach a breakpoint and collapse. That&#8217;s the bad news. The good news is that reaching a breakpoint can be a step forward, allowing a network to substitute quality for quantity.     </p>
<p>                    In Breakpoint, brain scientist and entrepreneur Jeff Stibel takes readers to the intersection of the brain, biology, and technology. He shows how exceptional companies are using their understanding of the internet&#8217;s brain-like powers to create a competitive advantage by building more effective websites, utilizing cloud computing, engaging social media, monetizing effectively, and leveraging a collective consciousness. Indeed, the result of these technologies is a more tightly connected world with capabilities far beyond the sum of our individual minds. Breakpoint offers a fresh and exciting perspective about the future of technology and its effects on all of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/breakpoint-why-the-web-will-implode-search-will-be-obsolete-and-everything-else-you-need-to-know-about-technology-is-in-your-brain-robert-david-grant-jeff-stibel-abridged/">Breakpoint : Why the Web Will Implode, Search Will be Obsolete, and Everything Else You Need to Know About Technology is in Your Brain &#8211; Robert David Grant, Jeff Stibel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Death of Expertise : The Campaign Against Established Knowledge and Why it Matters &#8211; Tom Nichols (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Epistemology & Theory Of Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>People are now exposed to more information than ever before, provided both by technology and by increasing access to every level of education. These societal gains, however, have also helped fuel a surge in narcissistic and misguided intellectual egalitarianism that has crippled informed debates on any number of issues. Today, everyone knows everything: with only [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/">The Death of Expertise : The Campaign Against Established Knowledge and Why it Matters &#8211; Tom Nichols (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>People are now exposed to more information than ever before, provided both by technology and by increasing access to every level of education. These societal gains, however, have also helped fuel a surge in narcissistic and misguided intellectual egalitarianism that has crippled informed debates on any number of issues. Today, everyone knows everything: with only a quick trip through WebMD or Wikipedia, average citizens believe themselves to be on an equal<br />
                    intellectual footing with doctors and diplomats. All voices, even the most ridiculous, demand to be taken with equal seriousness, and any claim to the contrary is dismissed as undemocratic elitism.    </p>
<p>                    As Tom Nichols shows in The Death of Expertise, this rejection of experts has occurred for many reasons, including the openness of the internet, the emergence of a customer satisfaction model in higher education, and the transformation of the news industry into a 24-hour entertainment machine. Paradoxically, the increasingly democratic dissemination of information, rather than producing an educated public, has instead created an army of ill-informed and angry citizens who denounce<br />
                    intellectual achievement.    </p>
<p>                    Nichols has deeper concerns than the current rejection of expertise and learning, noting that when ordinary citizens believe that no one knows more than anyone else, democratic institutions themselves are in danger of falling either to populism or to technocracy-or in the worst case, a combination of both. The Death of Expertise is not only an exploration of a dangerous phenomenon but also a warning about the stability and survival of modern democracy in the Information<br />
                    Age.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/">The Death of Expertise : The Campaign Against Established Knowledge and Why it Matters &#8211; Tom Nichols (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tools and Weapons : The Promise and the Peril of the Digital Age &#8211; Brad Smith, Carol Ann Browne (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Certification: Microsoft (eg MCSE)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft Windows]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AND WORLD ECONOMIC FORUM BOOK CLUB PICK* &#8216;A clear, compelling guide to some of the most pressing debates in technology today.&#8217; Bill Gates &#8216;A colourful and insightful insiders&#8217; view of how technology is both empowering us and threatening us. From privacy to cyberattacks, this timely book is a useful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/">Tools and Weapons : The Promise and the Peril of the Digital Age &#8211; Brad Smith, Carol Ann Browne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AND WORLD ECONOMIC FORUM BOOK CLUB PICK*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A clear, compelling guide to some of the most pressing debates in technology today.&#8217; Bill Gates    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A colourful and insightful insiders&#8217; view of how technology is both empowering us and threatening us. From privacy to cyberattacks, this timely book is a useful guide for how to navigate the digital future.&#8217;  Walter Isaacson, bestselling author of Steve Jobs    </p>
<p>                    From Microsoft&#8217;s President and one of the tech industry&#8217;s wisest thinkers, a frank and thoughtful reckoning with how to balance enormous promise and existential risk as the digitization of everything accelerates. With new chapters on the pandemic and beyond.<br />
                    __________    </p>
<p>                    Microsoft President Brad Smith operates by a simple core belief: when your technology changes the world, you bear a responsibility to help address the world you have helped create.     </p>
<p>                    This might seem uncontroversial, but it flies in the face of a tech sector long obsessed with rapid growth and sometimes on disruption as an end in itself. While sweeping digital transformation holds great promise, we have reached an inflection point. The world has turned information technology into both a powerful tool and a formidable weapon, and new approaches are needed to manage an era defined by even more powerful inventions like artificial intelligence. Companies that create technology must accept greater responsibility for the future, and governments will need to regulate technology by moving faster and catching up with the pace of innovation.    </p>
<p>                    In Tools and Weapons, Brad Smith and Carol Ann Browne bring us a captivating narrative from the cockpit of one of the world&#8217;s largest and most powerful tech companies as it finds itself in the middle of some of the thorniest emerging issues of our time. These are challenges that come with no pre-existing playbook, including privacy, cybercrime and cyberwar, social media, the moral conundrums of artificial intelligence, big tech&#8217;s relationship to inequality, and the challenges for democracy, far and near. While in no way a self-glorifying &#8220;Microsoft memoir,&#8221; the book pulls back the curtain remarkably wide onto some of the company&#8217;s most crucial recent decision points as it strives to protect the hopes technology offers against the very real threats it also presents. There are huge ramifications for communities and countries, and Brad Smith provides a thoughtful and urgent contribution to that effort.    </p>
<p>                    __________    </p>
<p>                    In Tools and Weapons, Brad Smith takes us behind the scenes on some of the biggest stories to hit the tech industry in the past decade and some of the biggest threats we face. From Edward Snowden&#8217;s NSA leak to the NHS WannaCry ransomware attack, this book is essential reading to understand what&#8217;s happening in the world around us.    </p>
<p>                    Praise for Tools and Weapons:     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The de facto ambassador for the technology industry at large.&#8217; The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;In Tools and Weapons, Brad and Carol Ann Browne wrestle with some of the world&#8217;s toughest technology challenges with common sense and valuable insight reflecting their inside experience. The ideas in Tools and Weapons won&#8217;t solve all our problems, but they&#8217;re a very good place to start.&#8217; &#8211; Reed Hastings, CEO, Netflix    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Tools and Weapons is a glimpse behind the curtain as Microsoft reckoned with the Snowden revelations, defended against the vicious cyberattacks, and took both the Obama and Trump administrations to court.&#8217; &#8211; Rolling Stone</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/">Tools and Weapons : The Promise and the Peril of the Digital Age &#8211; Brad Smith, Carol Ann Browne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world where all the news you see is defined by your salary, where you live, and who your friends are. Imagine a world where you never discover new ideas. And where you can&#8217;t have secrets. Welcome to 2011. Google and Facebook are already feeding you what they think you want to see. Advertisers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/">The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world where all the news you see is defined by your salary, where you live, and who your friends are. Imagine a world where you never discover new ideas. And where you can&#8217;t have secrets.    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to 2011.    </p>
<p>                    Google and Facebook are already feeding you what they think you want to see. Advertisers are following your every click. Your computer monitor is becoming a one-way mirror, reflecting your interests and reinforcing your prejudices.    </p>
<p>                    The internet is no longer a free, independent space. It is commercially controlled and ever more personalised. The Filter Bubble reveals how this hidden web is starting to control our lives &#8211; and shows what we can do about it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/">The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tyranny of E-mail : The Four-Thousand-Year Journey to Your Inbox &#8211; John Freeman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tyranny-of-e-mail-the-four-thousand-year-journey-to-your-inbox-john-freeman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tyranny-of-e-mail-the-four-thousand-year-journey-to-your-inbox-john-freeman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s no question that e-mail is an incredible phenomenon that represents a kind of cultural and technological advancement. The first e-mail was sent less than forty years ago; by 2011, there will be 3.2 billion e-mail users. The average corporate worker now receives upwards of two hundred e-mails per day. The flood of messages is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tyranny-of-e-mail-the-four-thousand-year-journey-to-your-inbox-john-freeman-abridged/">Tyranny of E-mail : The Four-Thousand-Year Journey to Your Inbox &#8211; John Freeman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There&#8217;s no question that e-mail is an incredible phenomenon that represents a kind of cultural and technological advancement. The first e-mail was sent less than forty years ago; by 2011, there will be 3.2 billion e-mail users. The average corporate worker now receives upwards of two hundred e-mails per day. The flood of messages is ceaseless and follows us everywhere.     </p>
<p>                    In The Tyranny of E-mail, John Freeman takes an entertaining look at the unrelenting nature of correspondence through the ages. Put down your smart phone and consider the consequences. As the toll of e-mail mounts, reducing our time for leisure and contemplation and separating us in an unending and lonely battle with the overfull inbox, John Freeman&#8211;one of America&#8217;s preeminent literary critics&#8211;enters a plea for communication that is more selective and nuanced and, above all, more sociable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tyranny-of-e-mail-the-four-thousand-year-journey-to-your-inbox-john-freeman-abridged/">Tyranny of E-mail : The Four-Thousand-Year Journey to Your Inbox &#8211; John Freeman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Humans Are Underrated : What High Achievers Know that Brilliant Machines Never Will &#8211; Geoff Colvin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/humans-are-underrated-what-high-achievers-know-that-brilliant-machines-never-will-geoff-colvin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/humans-are-underrated-what-high-achievers-know-that-brilliant-machines-never-will-geoff-colvin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the dawning age of brilliant machines, what will people do better than computers? It&#8217;s easy to imagine a frightening future in which technology takes over the jobs that we now get paid to do, working more accurately and for barely any cost. Computers can already perform surgery, drive vehicles, write articles and do intricate [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humans-are-underrated-what-high-achievers-know-that-brilliant-machines-never-will-geoff-colvin-abridged/">Humans Are Underrated : What High Achievers Know that Brilliant Machines Never Will &#8211; Geoff Colvin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the dawning age of brilliant machines, what will people do better than computers?    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s easy to imagine a frightening future in which technology takes over the jobs that we now get paid to do, working more accurately and for barely any cost. Computers can already perform surgery, drive vehicles, write articles and do intricate legal work, so what hope will there be for tomorrow&#8217;s workforce?    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on a wealth of research, Geoff Colvin uncovers the skills that will be in great demand as technology advances &#8211; and how they can be developed. In this new machine age, we shouldn&#8217;t try to beat computers at what they can do. We&#8217;ll lose that contest. Instead we must look to unlikely places, learn from the best, and cultivate the human abilities that make us unique.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/humans-are-underrated-what-high-achievers-know-that-brilliant-machines-never-will-geoff-colvin-abridged/">Humans Are Underrated : What High Achievers Know that Brilliant Machines Never Will &#8211; Geoff Colvin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Here Comes Everybody : The Power of Organizing Without Organizations &#8211; Clay Shirky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/here-comes-everybody-the-power-of-organizing-without-organizations-clay-shirky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/here-comes-everybody-the-power-of-organizing-without-organizations-clay-shirky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A fascinating survey of the digital age . . . An eye-opening paean to possibility.&#8221; &#8211;The Boston Globe &#8220;Mr. Shirky writes cleanly and convincingly about the intersection of technological innovation and social change.&#8221; &#8211;New York Observer An extraordinary exploration of how technology can empower social and political organizers For the first time in history, the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/here-comes-everybody-the-power-of-organizing-without-organizations-clay-shirky-abridged/">Here Comes Everybody : The Power of Organizing Without Organizations &#8211; Clay Shirky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A fascinating survey of the digital age . . . An eye-opening paean to possibility.&#8221; &#8211;The Boston Globe &#8220;Mr. Shirky writes cleanly and convincingly about the intersection of technological innovation and social change.&#8221; &#8211;New York Observer An extraordinary exploration of how technology can empower social and political organizers For the first time in history, the tools for cooperating on a global scale are not solely in the hands of governments or institutions. The spread of the internet and mobile phones are changing how people come together and get things done&#8211;and sparking a revolution that, as Clay Shirky shows, is changing what we do, how we do it, and even who we are. Here, we encounter a whoman who loses her phone and recruits an army of volunteers to get it back from the person who stole it. A dissatisfied airline passenger who spawns a national movement by taking her case to the web. And a handful of kids in Belarus who create a political protest that the state is powerless to stop. Here Comes Everybody is a revelatory examination of how the wildfirelike spread of new forms of social interaction enabled by technology is changing the way humans form groups and exist within them. A revolution in social organization has commenced, and Clay Shirky is its brilliant chronicler.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/here-comes-everybody-the-power-of-organizing-without-organizations-clay-shirky-abridged/">Here Comes Everybody : The Power of Organizing Without Organizations &#8211; Clay Shirky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things : Mapping the Relationship between Online Trolling and Mainstream Culture &#8211; Whitney Phillips (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why the troll problem is actually a culture problem: how online trolling fits comfortably within today&#8217;s media landscape. Internet trolls live to upset as many people as possible, using all the technical and psychological tools at their disposal. They gleefully whip the media into a frenzy over a fake teen drug crisis; they post offensive [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/">This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things : Mapping the Relationship between Online Trolling and Mainstream Culture &#8211; Whitney Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why the troll problem is actually a culture problem: how online trolling fits comfortably within today&#8217;s media landscape.    </p>
<p>                    Internet trolls live to upset as many people as possible, using all the technical and psychological tools at their disposal. They gleefully whip the media into a frenzy over a fake teen drug crisis; they post offensive messages on Facebook memorial pages, traumatizing grief-stricken friends and family; they use unabashedly racist language and images. They take pleasure in ruining a complete stranger&#8217;s day and find amusement in their victim&#8217;s anguish. In short, trolling is the obstacle to a kinder, gentler Internet. To quote a famous Internet meme, trolling is why we can&#8217;t have nice things online. Or at least that&#8217;s what we have been led to believe. In this provocative book, Whitney Phillips argues that trolling, widely condemned as obscene and deviant, actually fits comfortably within the contemporary media landscape. Trolling may be obscene, but, Phillips argues, it isn&#8217;t all that deviant. Trolls&#8217; actions are born of and fueled by culturally sanctioned impulses&#8211;which are just as damaging as the trolls&#8217; most disruptive behaviors.     </p>
<p>                    Phillips describes, for example, the relationship between trolling and sensationalist corporate media&#8211;pointing out that for trolls, exploitation is a leisure activity; for media, it&#8217;s a business strategy. She shows how trolls, &#8220;the grimacing poster children for a socially networked world,&#8221; align with social media. And she documents how trolls, in addition to parroting media tropes, also offer a grotesque pantomime of dominant cultural tropes, including gendered notions of dominance and success and an ideology of entitlement. We don&#8217;t just have a trolling problem, Phillips argues; we have a culture problem. This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things isn&#8217;t only about trolls; it&#8217;s about a culture in which trolls thrive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/">This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things : Mapping the Relationship between Online Trolling and Mainstream Culture &#8211; Whitney Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Deep Thinking : Where Machine Intelligence Ends and Human Creativity Begins &#8211; Garry Kasparov, Contributions byMig Greengard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybernetics & Systems Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In May 1997, the world watched as Garry Kasparov, the greatest chess player in the world, was defeated for the first time by the IBM supercomputer Deep Blue. It was a watershed moment in the history of technology: machine intelligence had arrived at the point where it could best human intellect. It wasn&#8217;t a coincidence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/">Deep Thinking : Where Machine Intelligence Ends and Human Creativity Begins &#8211; Garry Kasparov, Contributions byMig Greengard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In May 1997, the world watched as Garry Kasparov, the greatest chess player in the world, was defeated for the first time by the IBM supercomputer Deep Blue. It was a watershed moment in the history of technology: machine intelligence had arrived at the point where it could best human intellect.    </p>
<p>                    It wasn&#8217;t a coincidence that Kasparov became the symbol of man&#8217;s fight against the machines. Chess has long been the fulcrum in development of machine intelligence; the hoax automaton &#8216;The Turk&#8217; in the 18th century and Alan Turing&#8217;s first chess program in 1952 were two early examples of the quest for machines to think like humans &#8212; a talent we measured by their ability to beat their creators at chess. As the pre-eminent chessmaster of the 80s and 90s, it was Kasparov&#8217;s blessing and his curse to play against each generation&#8217;s strongest computer champions, contributing to their development and advancing the field.     </p>
<p>                    Like all passionate competitors, Kasparov has taken his defeat and learned from it. He has devoted much energy to devising ways in which humans can partner with machines in order to produce results better than either can achieve alone. During the twenty years since playing Deep Blue, he&#8217;s played both with and against machines, learning a great deal about our vital relationship with our most remarkable creations. Ultimately, he&#8217;s become convinced that by embracing the competition between human and machine intelligence, we can spend less time worrying about being replaced and more thinking of new challenges to conquer.    </p>
<p>                    In this breakthrough book, Kasparov tells his side of the story of Deep Blue for the first time &#8212; what it was like to strategize against an implacable, untiring opponent &#8212; the mistakes he made and the reasons the odds were against him. But more than that, he tells his story of AI more generally, and how he&#8217;s evolved to embrace it, taking part in an urgent debate with philosophers worried about human values, programmers creating self-learning neural networks, and engineers of cutting edge robotics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/deep-thinking-where-machine-intelligence-ends-and-human-creativity-begins-garry-kasparov-contributions-by-mig-greengard-abridged/">Deep Thinking : Where Machine Intelligence Ends and Human Creativity Begins &#8211; Garry Kasparov, Contributions byMig Greengard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutionary Groups & Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. To manage the risks and spread the benefits, we have to act now, and in the interest of stakeholders everywhere&#8217; Andrew McAfee, Co-Founder, MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy, MIT, USA    </p>
<p>                    We are on the brink of the Fourth Industrial Revolution. And this one will be unlike any other in human history.    </p>
<p>                    Characterized by new technologies fusing the physical, digital and biological worlds, the Fourth Industrial Revolution will impact all disciplines, economies and industries &#8211; and it will do so at an unprecedented rate. World Economic Forum data predicts that by 2025 we will see: commercial use of nanomaterials 200 times stronger than steel and a million times thinner than human hair; the first transplant of a 3D-printed liver; 10% of all cars on US roads being driverless; and much more besides.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Industrial Revolution, Schwab outlines the key technologies driving this revolution, discusses the major impacts on governments, businesses, civil society and individuals, and offers bold ideas for what can be done to shape a better future for all.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The technologies of the Fourth Industrial Revolution are extraordinary. Leadership has to be equally extraordinary to manage the complexities of systemic change&#8217; Eric Schmidt, Technical Advisor, Alphabet, USA</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
