<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Agriculture &amp; Farming Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/agriculture-farming/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/agriculture-farming/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Agriculture &amp; Farming Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/agriculture-farming/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agronomy & Crop Production]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animal Husbandry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Animals & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Primary Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sonia Faruqi, an Ivy League graduate and investment banker, had no idea that the night she arrived at the doorstep of a dairy farm would mark the beginning of a journey that would ultimately wind all the way around the world. Instead of turning away from the animal cruelty she came to witness, Sonia made [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/">Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sonia Faruqi, an Ivy League graduate and investment banker, had no idea that the night she arrived at the doorstep of a dairy farm would mark the beginning of a journey that would ultimately wind all the way around the world. Instead of turning away from the animal cruelty she came to witness, Sonia made the most courageous decision of her life: a commitment to change things.    </p>
<p>                     Driven by impulsive will and searing passion, Sonia left behind everything she knew and loved to search the planet for solutions to benefit animals, human health, and the environment. Over the course of living with farmers, hitchhiking with strangers, and risking her life, she developed surprising insights and solutions-both about the food industry and herself.    </p>
<p>                     Lively and heartfelt, Sonia takes readers on an unforgettable adventure from top-secret egg warehouses in Canada to dairy feedlots in the United States, from farm offices in Mexico to lush pastures in Belize, from flocks of village chickens in Indonesia to factory farms in Malaysia.    </p>
<p>                     Revelatory in scope, Project Animal Farm illuminates a hidden world that plays a part in all of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/project-animal-farm-an-accidental-journey-into-the-secret-world-of-farming-and-the-truth-about-our-food-sonia-faruqi-abridged/">Project Animal Farm : An Accidental Journey into the Secret World of Farming and the Truth About Our Food &#8211; Sonia Faruqi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agricultural Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Beverage Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainable Agriculture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is the future of food looking bleak &#8211; or better than ever? At a time when every day brings news of drought and famine, Amanda Little investigates what it will take to feed a hotter, hungrier, more crowded world. She explores the past along with the present and discovers startling innovations: remote-control crops, vertical farms, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/">The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is the future of food looking bleak &#8211; or better than ever?    </p>
<p>                    At a time when every day brings news of drought and famine, Amanda Little investigates what it will take to feed a hotter, hungrier, more crowded world.    </p>
<p>                    She explores the past along with the present and discovers startling innovations: remote-control crops, vertical farms, robot weedkillers, lab-grown meat, 3D-printed meals, water networks run by supercomputers, cloud seeding and sensors that monitor the microclimate of individual plants. She meets the creative and controversial minds changing the face of modern food production, and tackles fears over genetic modification with hard facts.    </p>
<p>                    The Fate of Food is a fascinating look at the threats and opportunities that lie ahead as we struggle for food security.    </p>
<p>                    Faced with a perilous future, it gives us reason to hope.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/">The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Should We Eat Meat? : Evolution and Consequences of Modern Carnivory &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/should-we-eat-meat-evolution-and-consequences-of-modern-carnivory-vaclav-smil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Beverage Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/should-we-eat-meat-evolution-and-consequences-of-modern-carnivory-vaclav-smil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Meat eating is often a contentious subject, whether considering the technical, ethical, environmental, political, or health-related aspects of production and consumption. This book is a wide-ranging and interdisciplinary examination and critique of meat consumption by humans, throughout their evolution and around the world. Setting the scene with a chapter on meat s role in human [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/should-we-eat-meat-evolution-and-consequences-of-modern-carnivory-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Should We Eat Meat? : Evolution and Consequences of Modern Carnivory &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Meat eating is often a contentious subject, whether considering the technical, ethical, environmental, political, or health-related aspects of production and consumption. This book is a wide-ranging and interdisciplinary examination and critique of meat consumption by humans, throughout their evolution and around the world. Setting the scene with a chapter on meat s role in human evolution and its growing influence during the development of agricultural practices, the book goes on to examine modern production systems, their efficiencies, outputs, and impacts. The major global trends of meat consumption are described in order to find out what part its consumption plays in changing modern diets in countries around the world. The heart of the book addresses the consequences of the &#8220;massive carnivory&#8221; of western diets, looking at the inefficiencies of production and at the huge impacts on land, water, and the atmosphere. Health impacts are also covered, both positive and negative.<br />
                    In conclusion, the author looks forward at his vision of rational meat eating , where environmental and health impacts are reduced, animals are treated more humanely, and alternative sources of protein make a higher contribution. Should We Eat Meat? is not an ideological tract for or against carnivorousness but rather a careful evaluation of meat&#8217;s roles in human diets and the environmental and health consequences of its production and consumption. It will be of interest to a wide readership including professionals and academics in food and agricultural production, human health and nutrition, environmental science, and regulatory and policy making bodies around the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/should-we-eat-meat-evolution-and-consequences-of-modern-carnivory-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Should We Eat Meat? : Evolution and Consequences of Modern Carnivory &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
