<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Biography: Sport Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/biography-sport/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/biography-sport/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Biography: Sport Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/biography-sport/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Into Thin Air : A Personal Account of the Mt. Everest Disaster &#8211; Jon Krakauer</title>
		<link>/into-thin-air-a-personal-account-of-the-mt-everest-disaster-jon-krakauer/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Holidays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Climbing & Mountaineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Endurance & Survival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories Of Heroism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/into-thin-air-a-personal-account-of-the-mt-everest-disaster-jon-krakauer/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; A harrowing tale of the perils of high-altitude climbing, a story of bad luck and worse judgment and of heartbreaking heroism. &#8211;PEOPLE A bank of clouds was assembling on the not-so-distant horizon, but journalist-mountaineer Jon Krakauer, standing on the summit of Mt. Everest, saw nothing that suggested that a murderous storm [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/into-thin-air-a-personal-account-of-the-mt-everest-disaster-jon-krakauer/">Into Thin Air : A Personal Account of the Mt. Everest Disaster &#8211; Jon Krakauer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; A harrowing tale of the perils of high-altitude climbing, a story of bad luck and worse judgment and of heartbreaking heroism. &#8211;PEOPLE  </p>
<p>                    A bank of clouds was assembling on the not-so-distant horizon, but journalist-mountaineer Jon Krakauer, standing on the summit of Mt. Everest, saw nothing that suggested that a murderous storm was bearing down. He was wrong. The storm, which claimed five lives and left countless more&#8211;including Krakauer&#8217;s&#8211;in guilt-ridden disarray, would also provide the impetus for Into Thin Air, Krakauer&#8217;s epic account of the May 1996 disaster. </p>
<p>                    By writing Into Thin Air, Krakauer may have hoped to exorcise some of his own demons and lay to rest some of the painful questions that still surround the event. He takes great pains to provide a balanced picture of the people and events he witnessed and gives due credit to the tireless and dedicated Sherpas. He also avoids blasting easy targets such as Sandy Pittman, the wealthy socialite who brought an espresso maker along on the expedition. Krakauer&#8217;s highly personal inquiry into the catastrophe provides a great deal of insight into what went wrong. But for Krakauer himself, further interviews and investigations only lead him to the conclusion that his perceived failures were directly responsible for a fellow climber&#8217;s death. Clearly, Krakauer remains haunted by the disaster, and although he relates a number of incidents in which he acted selflessly and even heroically, he seems unable to view those instances objectively. In the end, despite his evenhanded and even generous assessment of others&#8217; actions, he reserves a full measure of vitriol for himself. </p>
<p>                    This updated trade paperback edition of Into Thin Air includes an extensive new postscript that sheds fascinating light on the acrimonious debate that flared between Krakauer and Everest guide Anatoli Boukreev in the wake of the tragedy. I have no doubt that Boukreev&#8217;s intentions were good on summit day, writes Krakauer in the postscript, dated August 1999. What disturbs me, though, was Boukreev&#8217;s refusal to acknowledge the possibility that he made even a single poor decision. Never did he indicate that perhaps it wasn&#8217;t the best choice to climb without gas or go down ahead of his clients. As usual, Krakauer supports his points with dogged research and a good dose of humility. But rather than continue the heated discourse that has raged since Into Thin Air&#8217;s denouncement of guide Boukreev, Krakauer&#8217;s tone is conciliatory; he points most of his criticism at G. Weston De Walt, who coauthored The Climb, Boukreev&#8217;s version of events. And in a touching conclusion, Krakauer recounts his last conversation with the late Boukreev, in which the two weathered climbers agreed to disagree about certain points. Krakauer had great hopes to patch things up with Boukreev, but the Russian later died in an avalanche on another Himalayan peak, Annapurna I. </p>
<p>                    In 1999, Krakauer received an Academy Award in Literature from the American Academy of Arts and Letters&#8211;a prestigious prize intended to honor writers of exceptional accomplishment. According to the Academy&#8217;s citation, Krakauer combines the tenacity and courage of the finest tradition of investigative journalism with the stylish subtlety and profound insight of the born writer. His account of an ascent of Mount Everest has led to a general reevaluation of climbing and of the commercialization of what was once a romantic, solitary sport; while his account of the life and death of Christopher McCandless, who died of starvation after challenging the Alaskan wilderness, delves even more deeply and disturbingly into the fascination of nature and the devastating effects of its lure on a young and curious mind.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/into-thin-air-a-personal-account-of-the-mt-everest-disaster-jon-krakauer/">Into Thin Air : A Personal Account of the Mt. Everest Disaster &#8211; Jon Krakauer</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Eleven Rings : The Soul of Success &#8211; Phil Jackson</title>
		<link>/eleven-rings-the-soul-of-success-phil-jackson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basketball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/eleven-rings-the-soul-of-success-phil-jackson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Through candor and comprehensiveness, Jackson writes a convincing revisionist take, in which he emerges as an excellent coach . . . highly readable . . . reflects Jackson&#8217;s polymathy.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review &#8220;Part sports memoir, part New Age spirit quest, part pseudo-management tract . . . But the primary thing with Jackson-as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eleven-rings-the-soul-of-success-phil-jackson/">Eleven Rings : The Soul of Success &#8211; Phil Jackson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Through candor and comprehensiveness, Jackson writes a convincing revisionist take, in which he emerges as an excellent coach . . . highly readable . . . reflects Jackson&#8217;s polymathy.&#8221; -The New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Part sports memoir, part New Age spirit quest, part pseudo-management tract . . . But the primary thing with Jackson-as with all the old bards, who were also known for repeating themselves-is the voice.&#8221; -Sam Anderson, The New York Times Magazine</p>
<p>                    A New York Times Bestseller</p>
<p>                    The inside story of one of basketball&#8217;s most legendary and game-changing figures </p>
<p>                    During his storied career as head coach of the Chicago Bulls and Los Angeles Lakers, Phil Jackson won more championships than any coach in the history of professional sports. Even more important, he succeeded in never wavering from coaching his way, from a place of deep values. Jackson was tagged as the &#8220;Zen master&#8221; half in jest by sportswriters, but the nickname speaks to an important truth: this is a coach who inspired, not goaded; who led by awakening and challenging the better angels of his players&#8217; nature, not their egos, fear, or greed.</p>
<p>                     This is the story of a preacher&#8217;s kid from North Dakota who grew up to be one of the most innovative leaders of our time. In his quest to reinvent himself, Jackson explored everything from humanistic psychology and Native American philosophy to Zen meditation. In the process, he developed a new approach to leadership based on freedom, authenticity, and selfless teamwork that turned the hypercompetitive world of professional sports on its head.</p>
<p>                     In Eleven Rings, Jackson candidly describes how he: </p>
<p>                       *  Learned the secrets of mindfulness and team chemistry while playing for the champion New York Knicks in the 1970s<br />
                       *  Managed Michael Jordan, the greatest player in the world, and got him to embrace selflessness, even if it meant losing a scoring title<br />
                       *  Forged successful teams out of players of varying abilities by getting them to trust one another and perform in sync<br />
                       *  Inspired Dennis Rodman and other &#8220;uncoachable&#8221; personalities to devote themselves to something larger than themselves<br />
                       *  Transformed Kobe Bryant from a rebellious teenager into a mature leader of a championship team. </p>
<p>                     Eleven times, Jackson led his teams to the ultimate goal: the NBA championship-six times with the Chicago Bulls and five times with the Los Angeles Lakers. We all know the legendary stars on those teams, or think we do. What Eleven Rings shows us, however, is that when it comes to the most important lessons, we don&#8217;t know very much at all. This book is full of revelations: about fascinating personalities and their drive to win; about the wellsprings of motivation and competition at the highest levels; and about what it takes to bring out the best in ourselves and others.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/eleven-rings-the-soul-of-success-phil-jackson/">Eleven Rings : The Soul of Success &#8211; Phil Jackson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pipe Dreams : A Surfer&#8217;s Journey &#8211; Kelly Slater</title>
		<link>/pipe-dreams-a-surfers-journey-kelly-slater/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Surfing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Skiing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Sports & Recreations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Windsurfing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/pipe-dreams-a-surfers-journey-kelly-slater/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Six-time world surfing champion, actor, and US heart-throb Kelly Slater tells of the struggles and triumphs he&#8217;s experienced throughout his life and how they have helped him to become one of the world&#8217;s most loved sports figures. From beach blanket bingo to Baywatch, surfing has fascinated people for years, and Kelly Slater is the sport&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pipe-dreams-a-surfers-journey-kelly-slater/">Pipe Dreams : A Surfer&#8217;s Journey &#8211; Kelly Slater</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Six-time world surfing champion, actor, and US heart-throb Kelly Slater tells of the struggles and triumphs he&#8217;s experienced throughout his life and how they have helped him to become one of the world&#8217;s most loved sports figures. From beach blanket bingo to Baywatch, surfing has fascinated people for years, and Kelly Slater is the sport&#8217;s newest star. He&#8217;s one of the world&#8217;s most popular surfers; his radical moves have revolutionised the sport. Born in Cocoa Beach, Florida, in 1972, he found surfing to be a great way to escape problems at home. When he was 11, his parents divorced. Slater and his brother, Sean, were raised by their suddenly single mother, who struggled to support two young sons. After Slater&#8217;s surfing career took off, he made the transition into acting and modelling. He spent a season starring on the popular television show Baywatch, where he won the hearts of women young and old, including Pamela Anderson, whom he dated for about a year. He has also been featured in Versace ads. In Pipe Dreams, he shares the stories that have influenced his life and have inspired him to overcome both personal and professional hurdles and achieve his dreams.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pipe-dreams-a-surfers-journey-kelly-slater/">Pipe Dreams : A Surfer&#8217;s Journey &#8211; Kelly Slater</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Total Recall : My Unbelievably True Life Story &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger</title>
		<link>/total-recall-my-unbelievably-true-life-story-arnold-schwarzenegger/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Training & Coaching]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/total-recall-my-unbelievably-true-life-story-arnold-schwarzenegger/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial, and truly unique life. The greatest immigrant success story of our time. His story is unique, and uniquely entertaining, and he tells it brilliantly in these pages. He was born in a year of famine, in a small [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-my-unbelievably-true-life-story-arnold-schwarzenegger/">Total Recall : My Unbelievably True Life Story &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial, and truly unique life. </p>
<p>                    The greatest immigrant success story of our time. </p>
<p>                     His story is unique, and uniquely entertaining, and he tells it brilliantly in these pages. </p>
<p>                     He was born in a year of famine, in a small Austrian town, the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a movie star. </p>
<p>                     By the age of twenty-one, he was living in Los Angeles and had been crowned Mr. Universe. </p>
<p>                     Within five years, he had learned English and become the greatest bodybuilder in the world. </p>
<p>                     Within ten years, he had earned his college degree and was a millionaire from his business enterprises in real estate, landscaping, and bodybuilding. He was also the winner of a Golden Globe Award for his debut as a dramatic actor in Stay Hungry. </p>
<p>                     Within twenty years, he was the world&#8217;s biggest movie star, the husband of Maria Shriver, and an emerging Republican leader who was part of the Kennedy family. </p>
<p>                     Thirty-six years after coming to America, the man once known by fellow body-builders as the Austrian Oak was elected governor of California, the seventh largest economy in the world. </p>
<p>                     He led the state through a budget crisis, natural disasters, and political turmoil, working across party lines for a better environment, election reforms, and bipartisan solutions. </p>
<p>                     With Maria Shriver, he raised four fantastic children. In the wake of a scandal he brought upon himself, he tried to keep his family together. </p>
<p>                     Until now, he has never told the full story of his life, in his own voice. </p>
<p>                     Here is Arnold, with total recall.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-my-unbelievably-true-life-story-arnold-schwarzenegger/">Total Recall : My Unbelievably True Life Story &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unstoppable : My Life So Far &#8211; Maria Sharapova (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unstoppable-my-life-so-far-maria-sharapova-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tennis]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unstoppable-my-life-so-far-maria-sharapova-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fiercely honest, fearless, darkly funny autobiography of global tennis star Maria Sharapova In the middle of the night, a father and his daughter step off a Greyhound bus in Florida and head straight to the Nick Bollettieri Tennis Academy. They ring the bell, though no one is expecting them and they don&#8217;t speak English. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unstoppable-my-life-so-far-maria-sharapova-abridged/">Unstoppable : My Life So Far &#8211; Maria Sharapova (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fiercely honest, fearless, darkly funny autobiography of global tennis star Maria Sharapova    </p>
<p>                    In the middle of the night, a father and his daughter step off a Greyhound bus in Florida and head straight to the Nick Bollettieri Tennis Academy. They ring the bell, though no one is expecting them and they don&#8217;t speak English. They have arrived from Russia with just seven hundred dollars and the conviction that this six-year-old girl will be the world&#8217;s next great tennis star. They are right.    </p>
<p>                    This is Maria Sharapova&#8217;s gripping and fearless autobiography, telling her story from her roots in the small Siberian town her parents fled to after the Chernobyl disaster, through her arrival in the US with nothing and her phenomenal rise to success &#8211; winning Wimbledon aged just seventeen &#8211; to the disasters that threatened her career and her fight back.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A compelling memoir&#8217; David Shaftel, Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An illuminating account &#8230; This is the bildungsroman of a controversial champion, a portrait of the athlete as an uncommonly driven young woman&#8217; Julia Felsenthal, Vogue</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unstoppable-my-life-so-far-maria-sharapova-abridged/">Unstoppable : My Life So Far &#8211; Maria Sharapova (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tiger Woods : Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year 2018 &#8211; Jeff Benedict, Armen Keteyian (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tiger-woods-shortlisted-for-the-william-hill-sports-book-of-the-year-2018-jeff-benedict-armen-keteyian-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Golf]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tiger-woods-shortlisted-for-the-william-hill-sports-book-of-the-year-2018-jeff-benedict-armen-keteyian-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE WILLIAM HILL SPORTS BOOK OF THE YEAR 2018 WINNER OF THE TELEGRAPH SPORTS BOOK AWARDS BIOGRAPHY OF THE YEAR 2019 THE FULL STORY BEHIND THE RISE, FALL AND RISE AGAIN OF TIGER WOODS &#8216;A rattling read&#8230; Superbly written&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;Arguably the most serious attempt ever made to get behind golf&#8217;s great [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tiger-woods-shortlisted-for-the-william-hill-sports-book-of-the-year-2018-jeff-benedict-armen-keteyian-abridged/">Tiger Woods : Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year 2018 &#8211; Jeff Benedict, Armen Keteyian (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE WILLIAM HILL SPORTS BOOK OF THE YEAR 2018<br />
                     WINNER OF THE TELEGRAPH SPORTS BOOK AWARDS BIOGRAPHY OF THE YEAR 2019<br />
                     THE FULL STORY BEHIND THE RISE, FALL AND RISE AGAIN OF TIGER WOODS<br />
                     &#8216;A rattling read&#8230; Superbly written&#8217; Daily Mail<br />
                    &#8216;Arguably the most serious attempt ever made to get behind golf&#8217;s great enigma&#8217; Guardian<br />
                    &#8216;Exhilarating, depressing, tawdry and moving&#8230; perfectly pitched biography&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                     Based on three years of extensive research and reporting, two of today&#8217;s most acclaimed investigative journalists, Jeff Benedict of Sports Illustrated and eleven-time Emmy Award winner Armen Keteyian, deliver the first major biography of Tiger Woods &#8211; sweeping in scope and packed with groundbreaking, behind-the-scenes details of the Shakespearean rise and epic fall of a global icon.    </p>
<p>                     In 2009, Tiger Woods was the most famous athlete on the planet, a transcendent star of almost unfathomable fame and fortune living what appeared to be the perfect life &#8211; married to a Swedish beauty and the father of two young children. Winner of fourteen major golf championships and seventy-nine PGA Tour events, Woods was the first billion-dollar athlete, earning more than $100 million a year in endorsements from the likes of Nike, Gillette, AT&#038;T and Gatorade.    </p>
<p>                     But it was all a carefully crafted illusion. As it turned out, Woods had been living a double life for years &#8211; one that exploded in the aftermath of a late-night crash that exposed his serial infidelity and sent his personal and professional life off a cliff. In Tiger Woods, Jeff Benedict and Armen Keteyian dig deep behind the headlines to produce a richly reported answer to the question that has mystified millions of sports fans for nearly a decade: who is Tiger Woods?    </p>
<p>                     Drawing on more than four hundred interviews with people from every corner of Woods&#8217;s life &#8211; friends, family members, teachers, romantic partners, swing coaches, business associates, Tour pros and members of Woods&#8217;s inner circle &#8211; Benedict and Keteyian construct a captivating psychological profile of an African-American child programmed by an attention-grabbing father and the original Tiger Mom to be the &#8216;chosen one&#8217;, to change not just the game of golf, but the world as well. But at what cost?    </p>
<p>                    Benedict and Keteyian provide the startling answers in a biography, updated for this edition, destined to make headlines and linger in the minds of readers for years to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tiger-woods-shortlisted-for-the-william-hill-sports-book-of-the-year-2018-jeff-benedict-armen-keteyian-abridged/">Tiger Woods : Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year 2018 &#8211; Jeff Benedict, Armen Keteyian (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ali: A Life : Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year 2017 &#8211; Jonathan Eig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ali-a-life-shortlisted-for-the-william-hill-sports-book-of-the-year-2017-jonathan-eig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Boxing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ali-a-life-shortlisted-for-the-william-hill-sports-book-of-the-year-2017-jonathan-eig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE WILLIAM HILL SPORTS BOOK OF THE YEAR PRIZE. SHORTLISTED FOR THE JAMES TAIT BLACK BIOGRAPHY OF THE YEAR. THE BRITISH SPORTS BOOK AWARDS SPORTS BOOK OF THE YEAR. WINNER OF THE PEN/ESPN AWARD FOR LITERARY SPORTS WRITING. THE TIMES SPORTS BOOK AWARDS BIOGRAPHY OF THE YEAR. The most comprehensive and definitive biography [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ali-a-life-shortlisted-for-the-william-hill-sports-book-of-the-year-2017-jonathan-eig-abridged/">Ali: A Life : Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year 2017 &#8211; Jonathan Eig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE WILLIAM HILL SPORTS BOOK OF THE YEAR PRIZE.<br />
                     SHORTLISTED FOR THE JAMES TAIT BLACK BIOGRAPHY OF THE YEAR.<br />
                     THE BRITISH SPORTS BOOK AWARDS SPORTS BOOK OF THE YEAR.<br />
                     WINNER OF THE PEN/ESPN AWARD FOR LITERARY SPORTS WRITING.<br />
                     THE TIMES SPORTS BOOK AWARDS BIOGRAPHY OF THE YEAR.    </p>
<p>                     The most comprehensive and definitive biography of Muhammad Ali that has ever been published, based on more than 500 interviews with those who knew him best, with many dramatic new discoveries about his life and career.     </p>
<p>                     When the frail, trembling figure of Muhammad Ali lit the Olympic flame in Atlanta in 1996, a TV audience of up to 3 billion people was once again gripped by the story of the world&#8217;s most famous sporting icon. The man who had once been reviled for his refusal to fight for his country and for his fast-talking denunciation of his opponents was now almost universally adored, the true cost of his astonishing boxing career clear to see.    </p>
<p>                     In Jonathan Eig&#8217;s ground-breaking biography, backed up with much detailed new research specially commissioned for this book, we get a stunning portrait of one of the most significant personalities of the second half of the twentieth century. We are not only taken inside the ring for some of the most famous bouts in boxing history, we also learn about his personal life, his finances, his faith and the moments when the first signs of his physical decline began to show. Ali was a symbol of freedom and courage, a hero to many, but this is also a very personal story of a warrior who vanquished every opponent but was finally brought down by his own stubborn refusal to quit.    </p>
<p>                     An epic tale of a fighter who became the world&#8217;s most famous pacifist, Ali: A Life does full justice to an extraordinary man.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Ali: A Life is the business &#8211; 640 pages of patient scholarship and intelligent reassessment written in crackly prose&#8217; Giles Smith, The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;[A] richly researched, sympathetic yet unsparing portrait &#8230; Ali: A Life is an epic of a biography&#8217; Joyce Carol Oates, New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ali-a-life-shortlisted-for-the-william-hill-sports-book-of-the-year-2017-jonathan-eig-abridged/">Ali: A Life : Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year 2017 &#8211; Jonathan Eig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Go Like Hell : Ford, Ferrari and their Battle for Speed and Glory at Le Mans &#8211; A J Baime (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/go-like-hell-ford-ferrari-and-their-battle-for-speed-and-glory-at-le-mans-a-j-baime-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Car Racing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motor Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories: Discovery / Historical / Scientific]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/go-like-hell-ford-ferrari-and-their-battle-for-speed-and-glory-at-le-mans-a-j-baime-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Coming to cinemas in November 2019, under the title LE MANS &#8217;66 ____________________ In the 1960s Enzo Ferrari emerged as the dominant force in sports cars in the world, creating speed machines that were unbeatable on the race track. In America, the Ford Motor Company was quickly losing ground as the pre-eminent brand. Henry Ford [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/go-like-hell-ford-ferrari-and-their-battle-for-speed-and-glory-at-le-mans-a-j-baime-abridged/">Go Like Hell : Ford, Ferrari and their Battle for Speed and Glory at Le Mans &#8211; A J Baime (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Coming to cinemas in November 2019, under the title LE MANS &#8217;66<br />
                    ____________________    </p>
<p>                    In the 1960s Enzo Ferrari emerged as the dominant force in sports cars in the world, creating speed machines that were unbeatable on the race track. In America, the Ford Motor Company was quickly losing ground as the pre-eminent brand.  Henry Ford II saw a solution. He decided to declare war on Ferrari, to build a faster car than anything Ferrari had brought to the track, and to beat him at the world&#8217;s biggest race, Le Mans. Ferrari was just as determined to see off this challenge from across the Atlantic.    </p>
<p>                    With practically no safety regulations in place in the European Grand Prix races, horrific accidents were routine, with both drivers and spectators killed in many races.  The stakes were incredibly high, money and men were thrown at the competition, neither Ford or Ferrari would accept anything but victory. The battle to become the fastest in the world truly became a race to the death.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/go-like-hell-ford-ferrari-and-their-battle-for-speed-and-glory-at-le-mans-a-j-baime-abridged/">Go Like Hell : Ford, Ferrari and their Battle for Speed and Glory at Le Mans &#8211; A J Baime (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Boys In The Boat : An Epic Journey to the Heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin &#8211; Daniel James Brown (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Boating]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olympic Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rowing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories Of Heroism, Endurance & Survival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Water Sports & Recreations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year, this is the bestselling story about a rowing team&#8217;s quest for Olympic gold in Nazi Germany. Cast aside by his family at an early age, abandoned and left to fend for himself in the woods of Washington State, young Joe Rantz turns to rowing as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/">The Boys In The Boat : An Epic Journey to the Heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin &#8211; Daniel James Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the William Hill Sports Book of the Year, this is the bestselling story about a rowing team&#8217;s quest for Olympic gold in Nazi Germany.     </p>
<p>                    Cast aside by his family at an early age, abandoned and left to fend for himself in the woods of Washington State, young Joe Rantz turns to rowing as a way of escaping his past.    </p>
<p>                     What follows is an extraordinary journey, as Joe and eight other working-class boys exchange the sweat and dust of life in 1930s America for the promise of glory at the heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin. Stroke by stroke, a remarkable young man strives to regain his shattered self-regard, to dare again to trust in others &#8211; and to find his way back home.    </p>
<p>                     Told against the backdrop of the Great Depression, Daniel James Brown&#8217;s The Boys in the Boat is narrative non-fiction of the first order; a personal story full of lyricism and unexpected beauty that rises above the grand sweep of history, and captures instead the purest essence of what it means to be alive.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;I really can&#8217;t rave enough about this book . . . I read the last fifty pages with white knuckles, and the last twenty-five with tears in my eyes&#8217; &#8211; David Laskin, author of The Children&#8217;s Blizzard and The Long Way Home.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-boys-in-the-boat-an-epic-journey-to-the-heart-of-hitlers-berlin-daniel-james-brown-abridged/">The Boys In The Boat : An Epic Journey to the Heart of Hitler&#8217;s Berlin &#8211; Daniel James Brown (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Most Likely to Succeed : Preparing Our Kids for the Innovation Era &#8211; Tony Wagner, Ted Dintersmith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Basketball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Sport]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Educational Strategies & Policy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization & Management Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The basis for a major documentary, two leading experts sound an urgent call for the radical reimagining of American education so we can equip students for the realities of the twenty-first-century economy. We prize academic achievement, pressuring our children to get into the &#8220;right&#8221; colleges, have the highest GPAs, and pursue advanced degrees. But while [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/">Most Likely to Succeed : Preparing Our Kids for the Innovation Era &#8211; Tony Wagner, Ted Dintersmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The basis for a major documentary, two leading experts sound an urgent call for the radical reimagining of American education so we can equip students for the realities of the twenty-first-century economy.<br />
                         We prize academic achievement, pressuring our children to get into the &#8220;right&#8221; colleges, have the highest GPAs, and pursue advanced degrees. But while students may graduate with credentials, by and large they lack the competencies needed to be thoughtful, engaged citizens and to get good jobs in our rapidly evolving economy. Alarmingly, our methods of schooling crush the creativity and initiative young people really need to thrive in the twenty-first century.<br />
                         Now bestselling author and education expert Tony Wagner and venture capitalist Ted Dintersmith call for a complete overhaul of American schools, sharing insights and stories from the front lines. Their powerful, urgent message identifies the growing gap between credentials and competence-and offers a framework for change.<br />
                        Most Likely to Succeed presents a new vision of American education, one that puts wonder, creativity, and initiative at the very heart of the learning process and prepares students for today&#8217;s economy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/most-likely-to-succeed-preparing-our-kids-for-the-innovation-era-tony-wagner-ted-dintersmith-abridged/">Most Likely to Succeed : Preparing Our Kids for the Innovation Era &#8211; Tony Wagner, Ted Dintersmith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
