<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Market Research Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/market-research/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/market-research/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Market Research Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/market-research/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Thank You Economy &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</title>
		<link>/the-thank-you-economy-gary-vaynerchuk/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-thank-you-economy-gary-vaynerchuk/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Thank You Economy isn&#8217;t some abstract concept or wacky business strategy. It&#8217;s the way we buy and sell, the way we&#8217;re interacting as consumers, as employees, as entrepreneurs on all levels, right now. The way our marketplace functions has been evolving right before our eyes. Top-down, one-way exchanges are gone, replaced by relationships based [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-thank-you-economy-gary-vaynerchuk/">The Thank You Economy &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Thank You Economy isn&#8217;t some abstract concept or wacky business strategy. It&#8217;s the way we buy and sell, the way we&#8217;re interacting as consumers, as employees, as entrepreneurs on all levels, right now. The way our marketplace functions has been evolving right before our eyes. Top-down, one-way exchanges are gone, replaced by relationships based on open, honest, and constant communication between customers and business. Today, individuals and brands that out-care and out-love their competition &#8211; those emphasising quality, value, responsiveness, and attention to detail, among other essentials &#8211; see the biggest returns. Gary Vaynerchuk contends that the people and companies harnessing the word-of-mouth power provided by multiplatform media &#8211; those that can shift their outlook and operations to be more customer-aware and fan-friendly &#8211; will pull away from the pack and profit in today&#8217;s markets. In &#8220;The Thank You Economy&#8221;, he dissects the companies on the leading edge, showing how they are succeeding &#8211; and sometimes failing.<br />
                    Laying out the ideas and insight that support this enormous change, Vaynerchuk explores these emerging connections &#8211; from consumer to consumer and business to business and everything in between. Passionate and persuasive, he reminds us that, surviving and thriving today it takes more than just hard work-it takes a heartfelt thanks to those who make it possible.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-thank-you-economy-gary-vaynerchuk/">The Thank You Economy &#8211; Gary Vaynerchuk</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Social Media Marketing For Businesses : The Guide To Transform Your Business And Grow Revenue: Using Social Media Platforms For Marketing &#8211; Ara Grayes</title>
		<link>/social-media-marketing-for-businesses-the-guide-to-transform-your-business-and-grow-revenue-using-social-media-platforms-for-marketing-ara-grayes/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/social-media-marketing-for-businesses-the-guide-to-transform-your-business-and-grow-revenue-using-social-media-platforms-for-marketing-ara-grayes/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Social media marketing is a powerful way for businesses of all sizes to reach prospects and customers. Your customers are already interacting with brands through social media, and if you&#8217;re not speaking directly to your audience through social platforms like Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, and Pinterest, you&#8217;re missing out! Great marketing on social media can bring [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-media-marketing-for-businesses-the-guide-to-transform-your-business-and-grow-revenue-using-social-media-platforms-for-marketing-ara-grayes/">Social Media Marketing For Businesses : The Guide To Transform Your Business And Grow Revenue: Using Social Media Platforms For Marketing &#8211; Ara Grayes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Social media marketing is a powerful way for businesses of all sizes to reach prospects and customers. Your customers are already interacting with brands through social media, and if you&#8217;re not speaking directly to your audience through social platforms like Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, and Pinterest, you&#8217;re missing out! Great marketing on social media can bring remarkable success to your business, creating devoted brand advocates and even driving leads and sales.<br />
                    Unlike traditional marketing channels, social media marketing doesn&#8217;t focus on hard selling. It is about leveraging the power of audience relationships and forging strong connections through engagement. Social media marketing is concerning constantly growing your audience base by making perceptive and compelling content. It helps marketers build dramatic brands, fosters client loyalty, and lays the inspiration for marketing.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-media-marketing-for-businesses-the-guide-to-transform-your-business-and-grow-revenue-using-social-media-platforms-for-marketing-ara-grayes/">Social Media Marketing For Businesses : The Guide To Transform Your Business And Grow Revenue: Using Social Media Platforms For Marketing &#8211; Ara Grayes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Purple Cow : Transform Your Business by Being Remarkable &#8211; Seth Godin</title>
		<link>/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re either a Purple Cow or you&#8217;re not. You&#8217;re either remarkable or invisible. Make your choice. What do Apple, Starbucks, Dyson and Pret a Manger have in common? How do they achieve spectacular growth, leaving behind former tried-and-true brands to gasp their last? The old checklist of P&#8217;s used by marketers &#8211; Pricing, Promotion, Publicity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin/">Purple Cow : Transform Your Business by Being Remarkable &#8211; Seth Godin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re either a Purple Cow or you&#8217;re not. You&#8217;re either remarkable or invisible. Make your choice.    </p>
<p>                    What do Apple, Starbucks, Dyson and Pret a Manger have in common? How do they achieve spectacular growth, leaving behind former tried-and-true brands to gasp their last? The old checklist of P&#8217;s used by marketers &#8211; Pricing, Promotion, Publicity &#8211; aren&#8217;t working anymore. The golden age of advertising is over. It&#8217;s time to add a new P &#8211; the Purple Cow.    </p>
<p>                    Purple Cow describes something phenomenal, something counterintuitive and exciting and flat-out unbelievable. In his new bestseller, Seth Godin urges you to put a Purple Cow into everything you build, and everything you do, to create something truly noticeable. It&#8217;s a manifesto for anyone who wants to help create products and services that are worth marketing in the first place.    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed reading this, check out Seth Godin&#8217;s business classic This is Marketing.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin/">Purple Cow : Transform Your Business by Being Remarkable &#8211; Seth Godin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Predictive Analytics : The Power to Predict Who Will Click, Buy, Lie, or Die &#8211; Eric Siegel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/predictive-analytics-the-power-to-predict-who-will-click-buy-lie-or-die-eric-siegel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/predictive-analytics-the-power-to-predict-who-will-click-buy-lie-or-die-eric-siegel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Mesmerizing &#038; fascinating&#8230;&#8221; -The Seattle Post-Intelligencer &#8220;The Freakonomics of big data.&#8221; -Stein Kretsinger, founding executive of Advertising.com Award-winning &#124; Used by over 30 universities &#124; Translated into 9 languages An introduction for everyone. In this rich, fascinating &#8211; surprisingly accessible &#8211; introduction, leading expert Eric Siegel reveals how predictive analytics (aka machine learning) works, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/predictive-analytics-the-power-to-predict-who-will-click-buy-lie-or-die-eric-siegel-abridged/">Predictive Analytics : The Power to Predict Who Will Click, Buy, Lie, or Die &#8211; Eric Siegel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Mesmerizing &#038; fascinating&#8230;&#8221; -The Seattle Post-Intelligencer    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;The Freakonomics of big data.&#8221; -Stein Kretsinger, founding executive of Advertising.com    </p>
<p>                     Award-winning | Used by over 30 universities | Translated into 9 languages    </p>
<p>                     An introduction for everyone. In this rich, fascinating &#8211; surprisingly accessible &#8211; introduction, leading expert Eric Siegel reveals how predictive analytics (aka machine learning) works, and how it affects everyone every day. Rather than a &#8220;how to&#8221; for hands-on techies, the book serves lay readers and experts alike by covering new case studies and the latest state-of-the-art techniques.    </p>
<p>                     Prediction is booming. It reinvents industries and runs the world. Companies, governments, law enforcement, hospitals, and universities are seizing upon the power. These institutions predict whether you&#8217;re going to click, buy, lie, or die.    </p>
<p>                    Why? For good reason: predicting human behavior combats risk, boosts sales, fortifies healthcare, streamlines manufacturing, conquers spam, optimizes social networks, toughens crime fighting, and wins elections.    </p>
<p>                    How? Prediction is powered by the world&#8217;s most potent, flourishing unnatural resource: data. Accumulated in large part as the by-product of routine tasks, data is the unsalted, flavorless residue deposited en masse as organizations churn away. Surprise! This heap of refuse is a gold mine. Big data embodies an extraordinary wealth of experience from which to learn.    </p>
<p>                    Predictive analytics(aka machine learning) unleashes the power of data. With this technology, the computer literally learns from data how to predict the future behavior of individuals. Perfect prediction is not possible, but putting odds on the future drives millions of decisions more effectively, determining whom to call, mail, investigate, incarcerate, set up on a date, or medicate.    </p>
<p>                    In this lucid, captivating introduction &#8211; now in its Revised and Updated edition &#8211; former Columbia University professor and Predictive Analytics World founder Eric Siegel reveals the power and perils of prediction:    </p>
<p>                    What type of mortgage risk Chase Bank predicted before the recession.<br />
                    Predicting which people will drop out of school, cancel a subscription, or get divorced before they even know it themselves.<br />
                    Why early retirement predicts a shorter life expectancy and vegetarians miss fewer flights.<br />
                    Five reasons why organizations predict death &#8211; including one health insurance company.<br />
                    How U.S. Bank and Obama for America calculated the way to most strongly persuade each individual.<br />
                    Why the NSA wants all your data: machine learning supercomputers to fight terrorism.<br />
                    How IBM&#8217;s Watson computer used predictive modeling to answer questions and beat the human champs on TV&#8217;s Jeopardy!<br />
                    How companies ascertain untold, private truths &#8211; how Target figures out you&#8217;re pregnant and Hewlett-Packard deduces you&#8217;re about to quit your job.<br />
                    How judges and parole boards rely on crime-predicting computers to decide how long convicts remain in prison.<br />
                    182 examples from Airbnb, the BBC, Citibank, ConEd, Facebook, Ford, Google, the IRS, LinkedIn, Match.com, MTV, Netflix, PayPal, Pfizer, Spotify, Uber, UPS, Wikipedia, and more.    </p>
<p>                     How does predictive analytics work? This jam-packed book satisfies by demystifying the intriguing science under the hood. For future hands-on practitioners pursuing a career in the field, it sets a strong foundation, delivers the prerequisite knowledge, and whets your appetite for more.    </p>
<p>                     A truly omnipresent science, predictive analytics constantly affects our daily lives. Whether you are a consumer of it &#8211; or consumed by it &#8211; get a handle on the power of Predictive Analytics.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/predictive-analytics-the-power-to-predict-who-will-click-buy-lie-or-die-eric-siegel-abridged/">Predictive Analytics : The Power to Predict Who Will Click, Buy, Lie, or Die &#8211; Eric Siegel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising. For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 Wall Street Journal Bestseller &#038; Instant New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                     A game-changing approach to marketing, sales, and advertising.     </p>
<p>                     For the first time Seth Godin offers the core of his marketing wisdom in one compact, accessible, timeless package. This is Marketing shows you how to do work you&#8217;re proud of, whether you&#8217;re a tech startup founder, a small business owner, or part of a large corporation.     </p>
<p>                     No matter what your product or service, this book will help you reframe how it&#8217;s presented to the world, in order to meaningfully connect with people who want it. Seth employs his signature blend of insight, observation, and memorable examples to teach you:    </p>
<p>                     * How to build trust and permission with your target market.<br />
                     * The art of positioning&#8211;deciding not only who it&#8217;s for, but who it&#8217;s not for.<br />
                     * Why the best way to achieve your goals is to help others become who they want to be.<br />
                     * Why the old approaches to advertising and branding no longer work.<br />
                     * The surprising role of tension in any decision to buy (or not).<br />
                     * How marketing is at its core about the stories we tell ourselves about our social status.    </p>
<p>                     You can do work that matters for people who care. This book shows you the way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;This Is Marketing is a very accessible way into Godin&#8217;s thinking&#8230;. Godin writes in pacy, jargon-free prose and this book is interesting and useful for anyone who wants an insight into how, and why, we buy things or change our habits in any way.&#8221; &#8211; The Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed reading this, check out Seth Godin&#8217;s Purple Cow, a true business classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-marketing-you-cant-be-seen-until-you-learn-to-see-seth-godin-abridged/">This is Marketing : You Can&#8217;t Be Seen Until You Learn To See &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Upside of Irrationality : The Unexpected Benefits of Defying Logic at Work and at Home &#8211; Dan Ariely (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-upside-of-irrationality-the-unexpected-benefits-of-defying-logic-at-work-and-at-home-dan-ariely-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-upside-of-irrationality-the-unexpected-benefits-of-defying-logic-at-work-and-at-home-dan-ariely-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Behavioral economist and New York Times bestselling author of Predictably Irrational Dan Ariely returns to offer a much-needed take on the irrational decisions that influence our dating lives, our workplace experiences, and our general behaviour, up close and personal. In The Upside of Irrationality, behavioral economist Dan Ariely will explore the many ways in which [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upside-of-irrationality-the-unexpected-benefits-of-defying-logic-at-work-and-at-home-dan-ariely-abridged/">The Upside of Irrationality : The Unexpected Benefits of Defying Logic at Work and at Home &#8211; Dan Ariely (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Behavioral economist and New York Times bestselling author of Predictably Irrational Dan Ariely returns to offer a much-needed take on the irrational decisions that influence our dating lives, our workplace experiences, and our general behaviour, up close and personal.    </p>
<p>                              In The Upside of Irrationality, behavioral economist Dan Ariely will explore the many ways in which our behaviour often leads us astray in terms of our romantic relationships, our experiences in the workplace, and our temptations to cheat. Blending everyday experience with groundbreaking research, Ariely explains how expectations, emotions, social norms and other invisible, seemingly illogical forces skew our reasoning abilities.    </p>
<p>                              Among the topics Dan explores are:<br />
                    * What we think will make us happy and what really makes us happy;<br />
                    * How we learn to love the ones we are with;<br />
                    * Why online dating doesn&#8217;t work, and how we can improve on it;<br />
                    * Why learning more about people make us like them less;<br />
                    * Why large bonuses can make CEOs less productive;<br />
                    * How to really motivate people at work;<br />
                    * Why bad directions can help us;<br />
                    * How we fall in love with our ideas;<br />
                    * How we are motivated by revenge; and<br />
                    * What motivates us to cheat.    </p>
<p>                              Drawing on the same experimental methods that made Predictably Irrational such a hit, Dan will emphasize the important role that irrationality plays in our day-to-day decisionmaking-not just in our financial marketplace, but in the most hidden aspects of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-upside-of-irrationality-the-unexpected-benefits-of-defying-logic-at-work-and-at-home-dan-ariely-abridged/">The Upside of Irrationality : The Unexpected Benefits of Defying Logic at Work and at Home &#8211; Dan Ariely (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s Not the Size of the Data &#8212; It&#8217;s How You Use It : Smarter Marketing with Analytics and Dashboards &#8211; Koen Pauwels (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/its-not-the-size-of-the-data-its-how-you-use-it-smarter-marketing-with-analytics-and-dashboards-koen-pauwels-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Enterprise Software]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Operational Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/its-not-the-size-of-the-data-its-how-you-use-it-smarter-marketing-with-analytics-and-dashboards-koen-pauwels-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Did you know that your business already has the world&#8217;s greatest information-tracking team working tirelessly for you 24/7 to gather all the info you could possibly need to find your next customers? Between brand tracking, CRM programs, and online behavior tracking, as well as the always-dependable trade shows and satisfaction studies, mounds of marketing metrics [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-not-the-size-of-the-data-its-how-you-use-it-smarter-marketing-with-analytics-and-dashboards-koen-pauwels-abridged/">It&#8217;s Not the Size of the Data &#8212; It&#8217;s How You Use It : Smarter Marketing with Analytics and Dashboards &#8211; Koen Pauwels (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Did you know that your business already has the world&#8217;s greatest information-tracking team working tirelessly for you 24/7 to gather all the info you could possibly need to find your next customers? Between brand tracking, CRM programs, and online behavior tracking, as well as the always-dependable trade shows and satisfaction studies, mounds of marketing metrics are being generated for you across various touchpoints and channels. The numbers available to you are mind-blowing&#8211;but the amount itself can be mind-numbing. Where can one begin to filter through it all to find what is most beneficial for their company? Locked in the vast quantity of information are accurate, data-driven answers to every marketing question&#8211;and analytic dashboards are the key to finding it all. In It&#8217;s Not the Size of the Data&#8211;It&#8217;s How You Use It, marketing expert Koen Pauwels introduces readers to these transformative web-based tools that gather, synthesize, and visually display essential data in real time, directly connecting marketing with performance. He then supplies a simple yet rigorous methodology that explains step by step how to: &#8211; Gain crucial IT support &#8211; Build a rock-solid database &#8211; Select key leading performance indicators &#8211; Design the optimal dashboard layout &#8211; Use marketing analytics to improve decisions and reap rewards There is simply too much customer-produced information out there today for marketing teams to go with gut decisions or the same old standbys. Dashboard analytics will bring scientific precision and insight to the marketing efforts of any size organization, in any industry, and turn this eye-popping data into a specific plan of attack.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/its-not-the-size-of-the-data-its-how-you-use-it-smarter-marketing-with-analytics-and-dashboards-koen-pauwels-abridged/">It&#8217;s Not the Size of the Data &#8212; It&#8217;s How You Use It : Smarter Marketing with Analytics and Dashboards &#8211; Koen Pauwels (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Curse of Bigness : Antitrust in the New Gilded Age &#8211; Tim Wu (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-curse-of-bigness-antitrust-in-the-new-gilded-age-tim-wu-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Company, Commercial & Competition Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Competition Law / Antitrust Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Governance & Responsibilities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law As It Applies To Other Professions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-curse-of-bigness-antitrust-in-the-new-gilded-age-tim-wu-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the man who coined the term net neutrality, comes a warning about the dangers of excessive corporate and industrial concentration for our economic and political future. We live in an age of extreme corporate concentration, in which global industries are controlled by just a few giant firms&#8211;big banks, big pharma, and big tech, just [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-curse-of-bigness-antitrust-in-the-new-gilded-age-tim-wu-abridged/">The Curse of Bigness : Antitrust in the New Gilded Age &#8211; Tim Wu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the man who coined the term net neutrality, comes a warning about the dangers of excessive corporate and industrial concentration for our economic and political future.     </p>
<p>                    We live in an age of extreme corporate concentration, in which global industries are controlled by just a few giant firms&#8211;big banks, big pharma, and big tech, just to name a few. But concern over what Louis Brandeis called the curse of bigness can no longer remain the province of specialist lawyers and economists, for it has spilled over into policy and politics, even threatening democracy itself. History suggests that tolerance of inequality and failing to control excessive corporate power may prompt the rise of populism, nationalism, extremist politicians, and fascist regimes. In short, as Wu warns, we are in grave danger of repeating the signature errors of the twentieth century.     </p>
<p>                    In The Curse of Bigness, Tim Wu, special assistant to President Biden for technology and competition policy, explains how figures like Brandeis and Theodore Roosevelt first confronted the democratic threats posed by the great trusts of the Gilded Age&#8211;but the lessons of the Progressive Era were forgotten in the last 40 years. He calls for recovering the lost tenets of the trustbusting age as part of a broader revival of American progressive ideas as we confront the fallout of persistent and extreme economic inequality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-curse-of-bigness-antitrust-in-the-new-gilded-age-tim-wu-abridged/">The Curse of Bigness : Antitrust in the New Gilded Age &#8211; Tim Wu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hug Your Haters &#8211; Jay Baer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hug-your-haters-jay-baer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hug-your-haters-jay-baer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Haters are not your problem. . . . Ignoring them is. Eighty percent of companies say they deliver out­standing customer service, but only 8 percent of their customers agree. This book will help you close that gap by reconfiguring your customer service to deliver knockout experiences. The near-universal adoption of smartphones and social media has [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hug-your-haters-jay-baer-abridged/">Hug Your Haters &#8211; Jay Baer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Haters are not your problem. . . .<br />
                    Ignoring them is.     </p>
<p>                    Eighty percent of companies say they deliver out­standing customer service, but only 8 percent of their customers agree. This book will help you close that gap by reconfiguring your customer service to deliver knockout experiences.     </p>
<p>                    The near-universal adoption of smartphones and social media has fundamentally altered the science of complaints. Critics (&#8220;haters&#8221;) can now express their displeasure faster and more pub­licly than ever. These trends have resulted in an overall increase in complaints and a belief by many businesses that they have to &#8220;pick their spots&#8221; when choosing to answer criticisms.     </p>
<p>                    Bestselling author Jay Baer shows why that approach is a major mistake. Based on an exten­sive proprietary study of how, where, and why we complain, Hug Your Haters proves that there are two types of complainers, each with very differ­ent motivations:     </p>
<p>                    -Offstage haters. These people simply want solutions to their problems. They complain via legacy channels where the likelihood of a response is highest&#8211;phone, e-mail, and com­pany websites. Offstage haters don&#8217;t care if any­one else finds out, as long as they get answers.<br />
                    -Onstage haters. These people are often disap­pointed by a substandard interaction via tradi­tional channels, so they turn to indirect venues, such as social media, online review sites, and discussion boards. Onstage haters want more than solutions&#8211;they want an audience to share their righteous indignation.     </p>
<p>                    Hug Your Haters shows exactly how to deal with both groups, drawing on meticulously researched case studies from businesses of all types and sizes from around the world. It includes specific play­books and formulas as well as a fold-out poster of &#8220;the Hatrix,&#8221; which summarizes the best strate­gies for different situations. The book is also filled with poignant and hilarious examples of haters gone wild, and companies gone crazy, as well as inspirational stories of companies responding with speed, compassion, and humanity.     </p>
<p>                    Whether you work for a mom-and-pop store or a global brand, you will have haters&#8211;and you can&#8217;t afford to ignore them. Baer&#8217;s insights and tactics will teach you how to embrace complaints, put haters to work for you, and turn bad news into good outcomes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hug-your-haters-jay-baer-abridged/">Hug Your Haters &#8211; Jay Baer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This is Service Design Thinking : Basics, Tools, Cases &#8211; Marc Stickdorn, Jakob Schneider (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-service-design-thinking-basics-tools-cases-marc-stickdorn-jakob-schneider-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Service Industries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-service-design-thinking-basics-tools-cases-marc-stickdorn-jakob-schneider-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to design and market services to create outstanding customer experiences Service design thinking is the designing and marketing of services that improve the customer experience, and the interactions between the service providers and the customers. If you have two coffee shops right next to each other, and each sell the exact same coffee at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-service-design-thinking-basics-tools-cases-marc-stickdorn-jakob-schneider-abridged/">This is Service Design Thinking : Basics, Tools, Cases &#8211; Marc Stickdorn, Jakob Schneider (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to design and market services to create outstanding customer experiences Service design thinking is the designing and marketing of services that improve the customer experience, and the interactions between the service providers and the customers. If you have two coffee shops right next to each other, and each sell the exact same coffee at the exact same price, service design is what makes you walk into one and not the other. Maybe one plays music and the other doesn&#8217;t. Maybe one takes credit cards and the other is cash only. Maybe you like the layout of one over the other, or one has more comfortable seating. Maybe the staff at one is friendlier, or draws fun shapes on the top of their lattes. All of these nuances relate to service design.<br />
                    This Is Service Design Thinking combines the knowledge of twenty-three international authors and even more online contributors from the global service design community and is divided into three sections: * Basics: outlines service design thinking along five basic principles * Tools: describing a variety of tools and methods used in Service Design Thinking * Cases: vivid examples for the introduced fundamentals with real-life case studies from 5 companies that did inspiring projects within the field of Service Design At the end, a one-page &#8220;Customer Journey Canvas&#8221; is included, which can be used to quickly sketch any service on a single sheet of paper capturing different stakeholder concerns: e.g. customers, front-line staff and management.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-service-design-thinking-basics-tools-cases-marc-stickdorn-jakob-schneider-abridged/">This is Service Design Thinking : Basics, Tools, Cases &#8211; Marc Stickdorn, Jakob Schneider (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unleashing the Ideavirus : Stop Marketing at People! Turn Your Ideas Into Epidemics by Helping Your Customers Do the Marketing Thing for You. &#8211; Seth Godin, Malcolm Gladwell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unleashing-the-ideavirus-stop-marketing-at-people-turn-your-ideas-into-epidemics-by-helping-your-customers-do-the-marketing-thing-for-you-seth-godin-malcolm-gladwell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unleashing-the-ideavirus-stop-marketing-at-people-turn-your-ideas-into-epidemics-by-helping-your-customers-do-the-marketing-thing-for-you-seth-godin-malcolm-gladwell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The book that sparked a marketing revolution. &#8220;This is a subversive book. It says that the marketer is not&#8211;and ought not to be&#8211;at the center of successful marketing. The customer should be. Are you ready for that?&#8221; &#8211;From the Foreword by Malcolm Gladwell, author of The Tipping Point. Counter to traditional marketing wisdom, which tries [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unleashing-the-ideavirus-stop-marketing-at-people-turn-your-ideas-into-epidemics-by-helping-your-customers-do-the-marketing-thing-for-you-seth-godin-malcolm-gladwell-abridged/">Unleashing the Ideavirus : Stop Marketing at People! Turn Your Ideas Into Epidemics by Helping Your Customers Do the Marketing Thing for You. &#8211; Seth Godin, Malcolm Gladwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The book that sparked a marketing revolution.<br />
                    &#8220;This is a subversive book. It says that the marketer is not&#8211;and ought not to be&#8211;at the center of successful marketing. The customer should be. Are you ready for that?&#8221; &#8211;From the Foreword by Malcolm Gladwell, author of The Tipping Point.<br />
                    Counter to traditional marketing wisdom, which tries to count, measure, and manipulate the spread of information, Seth Godin argues that the information can spread most effectively from customer to customer, rather than from business to customer. Godin calls this powerful customer-to- customer dialogue the ideavirus, and cheerfully eggs marketers on to create an environment where their ideas can replicate and spread.<br />
                    In lively detail, Godin looks at the ways companies such as PayPal, Hotmail, GeoCities, even Volkswagen have successfully launched ideaviruses. He offers a &#8220;recipe&#8221; for creating your own ideavirus, identifies the key factors in the successful spread of an ideavirus (powerful sneezers, hives, a clear vector, a smooth, friction-free transmission), and shows how any business, large or small, can use ideavirus marketing to succeed in a world that just doesn&#8217;t want to hear it anymore from the traditional marketers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unleashing-the-ideavirus-stop-marketing-at-people-turn-your-ideas-into-epidemics-by-helping-your-customers-do-the-marketing-thing-for-you-seth-godin-malcolm-gladwell-abridged/">Unleashing the Ideavirus : Stop Marketing at People! Turn Your Ideas Into Epidemics by Helping Your Customers Do the Marketing Thing for You. &#8211; Seth Godin, Malcolm Gladwell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Carrots And Sticks &#8211; Ian Ayres (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/carrots-and-sticks-ian-ayres-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/carrots-and-sticks-ian-ayres-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/carrots-and-sticks-ian-ayres-abridged/">Carrots And Sticks &#8211; Ian Ayres (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/carrots-and-sticks-ian-ayres-abridged/">Carrots And Sticks &#8211; Ian Ayres (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You May Also Like : Taste in an Age of Endless Choice &#8211; Tom Vanderbilt (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/you-may-also-like-taste-in-an-age-of-endless-choice-tom-vanderbilt-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/you-may-also-like-taste-in-an-age-of-endless-choice-tom-vanderbilt-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why do we get so embarrassed when a colleague wears the same shirt? Why do we eat the same thing for breakfast every day, but seek out novelty at lunch and dinner? How has streaming changed the way Netflix makes recommendations? Why do people think the music of their youth is the best? How can [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-may-also-like-taste-in-an-age-of-endless-choice-tom-vanderbilt-abridged/">You May Also Like : Taste in an Age of Endless Choice &#8211; Tom Vanderbilt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why do we get so embarrassed when a colleague wears the same shirt? Why do we eat the same thing for breakfast every day, but seek out novelty at lunch and dinner? How has streaming changed the way Netflix makes recommendations? Why do people think the music of their youth is the best? How can you spot a fake review on Yelp?     </p>
<p>                     Our preferences and opinions are constantly being shaped by countless forces &#8211; especially in the digital age with its nonstop procession of &#8220;thumbs up&#8221; and &#8220;likes&#8221; and &#8220;stars.&#8221; Tom Vanderbilt, bestselling author of Traffic, explains why we like the things we like, why we hate the things we hate, and what all this tell us about ourselves.     </p>
<p>                     With a voracious curiosity, Vanderbilt stalks the elusive beast of taste, probing research in psychology, marketing, and neuroscience to answer myriad complex and fascinating questions. If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how Netflix recommends movies or why books often see a sudden decline in Amazon ratings after they win a major prize, Tom Vanderbilt has answers to these questions and many more that you&#8217;ve probably never thought to ask.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/you-may-also-like-taste-in-an-age-of-endless-choice-tom-vanderbilt-abridged/">You May Also Like : Taste in an Age of Endless Choice &#8211; Tom Vanderbilt (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China&#8217;s Super Consumers : What 1 Billion Customers Want and How to Sell it to Them &#8211; Savio Chan, Michael Zakkour (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chinas-super-consumers-what-1-billion-customers-want-and-how-to-sell-it-to-them-savio-chan-michael-zakkour-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chinas-super-consumers-what-1-billion-customers-want-and-how-to-sell-it-to-them-savio-chan-michael-zakkour-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Chinese Consumers are Changing The World Understand Them and Sell To Them China has transformed itself from a feudal economy in the 19th century, to Mao and Communism in the 20th century, to the largest consumer market in the world by the early 21st century. China&#8217;s Super Consumers explores the extraordinary birth of consumerism in [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chinas-super-consumers-what-1-billion-customers-want-and-how-to-sell-it-to-them-savio-chan-michael-zakkour-abridged/">China&#8217;s Super Consumers : What 1 Billion Customers Want and How to Sell it to Them &#8211; Savio Chan, Michael Zakkour (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Chinese Consumers are Changing The World Understand Them and Sell To Them China has transformed itself from a feudal economy in the 19th century, to Mao and Communism in the 20th century, to the largest consumer market in the world by the early 21st century. China&#8217;s Super Consumers explores the extraordinary birth of consumerism in China and explains who these super consumers are. China&#8217;s Super Consumers offers an in-depth explanation of what&#8217;s inside the minds of Chinese consumers and explores what they buy, where they buy, how they buy, and most importantly why they buy. The book is filled with real-world stories of the foreign and domestic companies, leading brands, and top executives who have succeeded in selling to this burgeoning marketplace. This remarkable book also takes you inside the boardrooms of the people who understand Chinese consumers and have had success in the Chinese market.<br />
                    * A hands-on resource for succeeding in the Chinese marketplace * Filled with real-world stories of companies who have made an impact in China * Discover what the Chinese consumer wants and how to deliver the goods * Written by Savio Chan and Michael Zakkour, two leading experts on the Chinese market This book is an invaluable resource for anyone who wants a clear understanding of how China&#8217;s Super Consumers are changing the world and how to sell to them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chinas-super-consumers-what-1-billion-customers-want-and-how-to-sell-it-to-them-savio-chan-michael-zakkour-abridged/">China&#8217;s Super Consumers : What 1 Billion Customers Want and How to Sell it to Them &#8211; Savio Chan, Michael Zakkour (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oversubscribed : How To Get People Lining Up To Do Business With You &#8211; Daniel Priestley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/oversubscribed-how-to-get-people-lining-up-to-do-business-with-you-daniel-priestley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/oversubscribed-how-to-get-people-lining-up-to-do-business-with-you-daniel-priestley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to get your business oversubscribed in a crowded marketplace to make your business stand out and get people lining up to do business with you Are you constantly chasing customers? Why does it seem like some businesses have their customers begging to purchase their goods or services? Think about it for a moment. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oversubscribed-how-to-get-people-lining-up-to-do-business-with-you-daniel-priestley-abridged/">Oversubscribed : How To Get People Lining Up To Do Business With You &#8211; Daniel Priestley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to get your business oversubscribed in a crowded marketplace to make your business stand out and get people lining up to do business with you     </p>
<p>                     Are you constantly chasing customers? Why does it seem like some businesses have their customers begging to purchase their goods or services? Think about it for a moment. When a new iPhone is released, why do customers camp overnight to be the first through the door? In cities with thousands of great restaurants, why do some restaurants require reservations months in advance? Why is it that some consultants, accountants, lawyers and healthcare professionals can charge exponentially more than others? In the modern marketplace, consumer options are virtually endless, intense competition is rife and so much is given away for free online.  Often businesses are left scrambling to attract enough customers to make a small profit. Yet the opposite is true for a small number of businesses that do things differently-customers chase them. They have buyers who gladly queue up, pay more, and eagerly wait for the chance to hand over their money for the next thing. How do these businesses do it? More importantly, how can you become one of them?     </p>
<p>                     Oversubscribed is the guide to transforming your business into one which customers fight over! Author Daniel Priestley, a successful entrepreneur who has built and sold businesses around the world, shares proven, real-world methods that will not only grab customers&#8217; attention, but will also have them lining up to buy from you. This invaluable guide will teach you how to drive demand for your products or services far beyond supply and will dramatically increase the success of your business. Now in its second edition, this updated version offers new insights and motivating examples that are right for the 2020s. This book will show you:    </p>
<p>                    The principles and philosophies Oversubscribed businesses live by that are often the opposite of what most businesses do<br />
                    Specific steps for getting into the mind of your customer so they only want to buy from your business<br />
                    How to structure campaigns and product launches that systematically get your business Oversubscribed<br />
                    How to implement a process of signalling to market, and collect signals back from market to build up desire and demand for your products and services    </p>
<p>                     The new edition of Oversubscribed: How to get people lining up to do business with you is a must-read for entrepreneurs, marketers, business leaders and owners, team managers, and business students.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oversubscribed-how-to-get-people-lining-up-to-do-business-with-you-daniel-priestley-abridged/">Oversubscribed : How To Get People Lining Up To Do Business With You &#8211; Daniel Priestley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated for the post-COVID economy! The proven low-risk, cost-effective way to launch a successful business Today&#8217;s markets are getting more and more dynamic, and customers are increasingly fickle. Meanwhile the COVID-driven economic crash has made mitigating financial risk more important than ever. From one of today&#8217;s leading experts in content marketing, Content Inc. is the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated for the post-COVID economy! The proven low-risk, cost-effective way to launch a successful business     </p>
<p>                    Today&#8217;s markets are getting more and more dynamic, and customers are increasingly fickle. Meanwhile the COVID-driven economic crash has made mitigating financial risk more important than ever.    </p>
<p>                    From one of today&#8217;s leading experts in content marketing, Content Inc. is the go-to guide to building a solid small-business by establishing a loyal audience before you sell any products or services. In these pages, Joe Pulizzi provides a lower-risk, better way to build a successful business by re-engineering the process that so often leads to failure: You&#8217;ll learn how to develop valuable content, build an audience around that content-and then create a product for that audience. Content Inc. walks you through the entire process, showing how to    </p>
<p>                    Identify the intersection of your expertise and your future customer&#8217;s needs<br />
                    Determine how to &#8220;tilt&#8221; your sweet spot to find a place where little or no competition exists<br />
                    Establish your number-one channel for disseminating content (blog, podcast, YouTube, etc.)<br />
                    Use social-media and SEO to convert one-time visitors into long-term subscribers<br />
                    Grow your business by expanding into multiple delivery channels<br />
                    Monetize your product or service for ultimate business success<br />
                    Understand how to sell your content asset for millions or build the business into a large enterprise    </p>
<p>                    This fully updated edition includes new and enhanced coverage of platforms like TikTok, SnapChat, and Instagram, a new section about the exit strategy for the model, more practical how-tos, and current examples of companies that have successfully implemented these strategies.      </p>
<p>                    Apply the methods laid out for you in Content Inc., and before you know it, you&#8217;ll be running your own profitable, scalable business.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/content-inc-second-edition-start-a-content-first-business-build-a-massive-audience-and-become-radically-successful-with-little-to-no-money-joe-pulizzi-abridged/">Content Inc., Second Edition: Start a Content-First Business, Build a Massive Audience and Become Radically Successful (With Little to No Money) &#8211; Joe Pulizzi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Algebra of Happiness : The pursuit of success, love and what it all means &#8211; Scott Galloway (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-algebra-of-happiness-the-pursuit-of-success-love-and-what-it-all-means-scott-galloway-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Careers Guidance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-algebra-of-happiness-the-pursuit-of-success-love-and-what-it-all-means-scott-galloway-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author, a provocative book of hard-won wisdom for achieving a fulfilling career and life. &#8211; How can you have a meaningful career, not just a lucrative one? &#8211; Is a work/life balance really possible? &#8211; What does it take to make a long-term relationship succeed? &#8211; What can you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-algebra-of-happiness-the-pursuit-of-success-love-and-what-it-all-means-scott-galloway-abridged/">The Algebra of Happiness : The pursuit of success, love and what it all means &#8211; Scott Galloway (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the New York Times bestselling author, a provocative book of hard-won wisdom for achieving a  fulfilling career and life.    </p>
<p>                     &#8211; How can you have a meaningful career, not just a lucrative one?<br />
                    &#8211; Is a work/life balance really possible?<br />
                    &#8211; What does it take to make a long-term relationship succeed?<br />
                    &#8211; What can you do now so there are no regrets aged 40, 50 or 80?    </p>
<p>                                   As Scott Galloway puts it, by the time you hit your mid twenties sh*t gets real. Life become stressful. Even the smart, the hard working and the elite can feel lost in a chaotic, noisy and unpredictable world. As a professor at New York University&#8217;s Stern School of Business, the debate in Galloway&#8217;s MBA class often veers away from business strategy to the challenging issue of life strategies. Which is why Galloway, in his signature, take-no-prisoners style, has developed a dynamic formula for a life well lived.    </p>
<p>                     In The Algebra of Happiness Galloway tells you how life can be navigated and negotiated better to maximise happiness and minimise the inevitable stress. Delivering practical advice and hard-won wisdom on everything from when to own property to how hard to work, this is self-help for anyone struggling with life&#8217;s big questions. Through simple equations that measure the relationship between success, resilience and failure or the correlation between happiness and money, Galloway attempts to convert intangible advice to tangible equations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-algebra-of-happiness-the-pursuit-of-success-love-and-what-it-all-means-scott-galloway-abridged/">The Algebra of Happiness : The pursuit of success, love and what it all means &#8211; Scott Galloway (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Marketing Above the Noise : Achieve Strategic Advantage with Marketing That Matters &#8211; Linda J Popky, Read by Karen Saltus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/marketing-above-the-noise-achieve-strategic-advantage-with-marketing-that-matters-linda-j-popky-read-by-karen-saltus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/marketing-above-the-noise-achieve-strategic-advantage-with-marketing-that-matters-linda-j-popky-read-by-karen-saltus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Marketing today is out of control. With all the new marketing techniques accessible to the masses, it&#8217;s becoming harder and harder to stand out from the crowd. The result is more and more messages, hitting us more often in new and more intrusive ways. For customers, it&#8217;s a lot of noise. Through her work with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/marketing-above-the-noise-achieve-strategic-advantage-with-marketing-that-matters-linda-j-popky-read-by-karen-saltus-abridged/">Marketing Above the Noise : Achieve Strategic Advantage with Marketing That Matters &#8211; Linda J Popky, Read by Karen Saltus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Marketing today is out of control. With all the new marketing techniques accessible to the masses, it&#8217;s becoming harder and harder to stand out from the crowd. The result is more and more messages, hitting us more often in new and more intrusive ways. For customers, it&#8217;s a lot of noise. Through her work with a wide range of organizations from small companies to professional service providers to Fortune 500 companies, Linda Popky has developed Dynamic Market Leverage(TM), an approach to help cut through the clutter, stand out, and effectively build business. What&#8217;s needed is a timeless framework&#8211;a way of looking at marketing as tied to both business growth and the building and nurturing of ongoing customer engagement. It&#8217;s time to move the focus from social media and evangelists, sales and marketing alignment, and the latest hot cloud-based marketing tools, to what really counts: convincing customers to trust you with their business&#8211;not just once, but time and time again.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/marketing-above-the-noise-achieve-strategic-advantage-with-marketing-that-matters-linda-j-popky-read-by-karen-saltus-abridged/">Marketing Above the Noise : Achieve Strategic Advantage with Marketing That Matters &#8211; Linda J Popky, Read by Karen Saltus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fortune Cookie Principle : The 20 Keys to a Great Brand Story and Why Your Business Needs One &#8211; Bernadette Jiwa (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fortune-cookie-principle-the-20-keys-to-a-great-brand-story-and-why-your-business-needs-one-bernadette-jiwa-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fortune-cookie-principle-the-20-keys-to-a-great-brand-story-and-why-your-business-needs-one-bernadette-jiwa-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s not how good you are. It&#8217;s how well you tell your story. Big corporations might have huge marketing and advertising budgets but you&#8217;ve got a story. Your brand story isn&#8217;t just what you tell people. It&#8217;s what they believe about you based on the signals your brand sends. The Fortune Cookie Principle is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fortune-cookie-principle-the-20-keys-to-a-great-brand-story-and-why-your-business-needs-one-bernadette-jiwa-abridged/">The Fortune Cookie Principle : The 20 Keys to a Great Brand Story and Why Your Business Needs One &#8211; Bernadette Jiwa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s not how good you are. It&#8217;s how well you tell your story. Big corporations might have huge marketing and advertising budgets but you&#8217;ve got a story. Your brand story isn&#8217;t just what you tell people. It&#8217;s what they believe about you based on the signals your brand sends. The Fortune Cookie Principle is a brand building framework and communication strategy consisting of 20 keys that enable you to begin telling your brand&#8217;s story from the inside out. It&#8217;s the foundation upon which you can differentiate your brand and make emotional connections with the kind of clients and customers you want to serve. The most successful brands in the world don&#8217;t behave like commodities and neither should you. A great brand story will make you stand out, increase brand awareness, create customer loyalty and power profits. Isn&#8217;t it time to gave your customers a story to tell? The Fortune Cookie Principle will show you how.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fortune-cookie-principle-the-20-keys-to-a-great-brand-story-and-why-your-business-needs-one-bernadette-jiwa-abridged/">The Fortune Cookie Principle : The 20 Keys to a Great Brand Story and Why Your Business Needs One &#8211; Bernadette Jiwa (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello, My Name is Awesome : How to Create Brand Names That Stick &#8211; Alexandra Watkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hello-my-name-is-awesome-how-to-create-brand-names-that-stick-alexandra-watkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hello-my-name-is-awesome-how-to-create-brand-names-that-stick-alexandra-watkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The ultimate guide to naming your product or business has been updated throughout with twice as many resources as before, new stories (of both hits and flops), and an entirely new chapter on the power of names in the workplace. Too many new companies and products have names that look like the results of a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hello-my-name-is-awesome-how-to-create-brand-names-that-stick-alexandra-watkins-abridged/">Hello, My Name is Awesome : How to Create Brand Names That Stick &#8211; Alexandra Watkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The ultimate guide to naming your product or business has been updated throughout with twice as many resources as before, new stories (of both hits and flops), and an entirely new chapter on the power of names in the workplace.     </p>
<p>                     Too many new companies and products have names that look like the results of a drunken Scrabble game (Xobni, Svbtle, Doostang). In this entertaining and engaging book, ace-naming consultant Alexandra Watkins explains how anyone&#8211;even noncreative types&#8211;can create memorable and effective brand names. No degree in linguistics required.     </p>
<p>                     The heart of the book is Watkins&#8217;s proven SMILE and SCRATCH Test. A great name makes you SMILE because it is Suggestive&#8211;evokes something about your brand; is Memorable&#8211;makes an association with the familiar; uses Imagery&#8211;aids memory through evocative visuals; has Legs&#8211;lends itself to a theme for extended mileage; and is Emotional&#8211;moves people.     </p>
<p>                     A bad name, on the other hand, makes you SCRATCH your head because it is Spelling challenged&#8211;looks like a typo; is a Copycat&#8211;similar to competitors&#8217; names; is Restrictive&#8211;limits future growth; is Annoying&#8211;seems forced and frustrates customers; is Tame&#8211;feels flat, merely descriptive, and uninspired; suffers from the Curse of Knowledge&#8211;speaks only to insiders; and is Hard to pronounce&#8211;confuses and distances customers.     </p>
<p>                     This 50 percent-new second edition has double the number of brainstorming tools and techniques, even more secrets and strategies to nab an available domain name, a brand-new chapter on how companies are using creative names around the office to add personality to everything from cafeterias to conference rooms, and much more.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hello-my-name-is-awesome-how-to-create-brand-names-that-stick-alexandra-watkins-abridged/">Hello, My Name is Awesome : How to Create Brand Names That Stick &#8211; Alexandra Watkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Talk Triggers &#8211; Jay Baer, Daniel Lemin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/talk-triggers-jay-baer-daniel-lemin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/talk-triggers-jay-baer-daniel-lemin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Talk Triggers is the definitive, practical guide on how to use bold operational differentiators to create customer conversations, written by best-selling authors and marketing experts Jay Baer and Daniel Lemin. Word of mouth is directly responsible for 19% of all purchases, and influences as much as 90%. Every human on earth relies on word of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/talk-triggers-jay-baer-daniel-lemin-abridged/">Talk Triggers &#8211; Jay Baer, Daniel Lemin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Talk Triggers is the definitive, practical guide on how to use bold operational differentiators to create customer conversations, written by best-selling authors and marketing experts Jay Baer and Daniel Lemin. Word of mouth is directly responsible for 19% of all purchases, and influences as much as 90%. Every human on earth relies on word of mouth to make buying decisions. Yet even today, fewer than 1% of companies have an actual strategy for generating these crucial customer conversations. Talk Triggers provides that strategy in a compelling, relevant, timely book that can be put into practice immediately, by any business. The key to activating customer chatter is the realization that same is lame. Nobody says let me tell you about this perfectly adequate experience I had last night. The strategic, operational differentiator is what gives customers something to tell a story about. Companies (including the 30+ profiled in Talk Triggers) must dare to be different and exceed expectations in one or more palpable ways. That&#8217;s when word of mouth becomes involuntary: the customers of these businesses simply MUST tell someone else. Talk Triggers contains:<br />
                     &#8211; Proprietary research into why and how customers talk<br />
                     &#8211; More than 30 detailed case studies of extraordinary results from Doubletree Hotels by Hilton and their warm cookie upon arrival, The Cheesecake Factory and their giant menu, Five Guys Burgers and their extra fries in the bag, Penn &#038; Teller and their nightly meet and greet sessions, and a host of delightful small businesses<br />
                     &#8211; The 4-5-6 learning system (the 4 requirements for a differentiator to be a talk trigger; the 5 types of talk triggers; and the 6-step process for creating talk triggers)<br />
                     &#8211; Surprises in the text that are (of course) word of mouth propellants Consumers are wired to discuss what is different, and ignore what is average. Talk Triggers not only dares the reader to differentiate, it includes the precise formula for doing it. Combining compelling stories, inspirational examples, and practical how-to, Talk Triggers is the first indispensable book about word of mouth. It&#8217;s a book that will create conversation about the power of conversation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/talk-triggers-jay-baer-daniel-lemin-abridged/">Talk Triggers &#8211; Jay Baer, Daniel Lemin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Membership Economy: Find Your Super Users, Master the Forever Transaction, and Build Recurring Revenue &#8211; Robbie Kellman Baxter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retail Sector]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s business world, it takes more than a website to stay competitive. The smartest, most successful companies are using radically new membership models, subscription-based formats, and freemium pricing structures to grow their customer base-and explode their market valuation-in the most disruptive shift in business since the Industrial Revolution. This is The Membership Economy. Written [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/">The Membership Economy: Find Your Super Users, Master the Forever Transaction, and Build Recurring Revenue &#8211; Robbie Kellman Baxter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In today&#8217;s business world, it takes more than a website to stay competitive. The smartest, most successful companies are using radically new membership models, subscription-based formats, and freemium pricing structures to grow their customer base-and explode their market valuation-in the most disruptive shift in business since the Industrial Revolution.    </p>
<p>                    This is The Membership Economy.    </p>
<p>                     Written by an expertconsultant, this groundbreaking book will show you how to turn ordinary customers into members for life. Learn how to:    </p>
<p>                     Turn digital subscriptions into forever sales Build an online community your customers will loveDevelop new loyalty programs that really pay offTransform freemium users into superusers Create a self-generating revenue stream Keep memberships and profits growing for years to come<br />
                    Whether you&#8217;re a small business with limited resources, an established company using a traditional business model, or a hungry start-up who wants a bigger bang for your buck, this comprehensive guide provides a wealth of membership-building options to suit every need.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll learn the best-kept secrets of top industry leaders, from global giants like Am Ex and Weight Watchers to smaller dot-com successes like SurveyMonkey and Pandora. You&#8217;ll find proven strategies for creating membership programs for everything from vacation timeshares and car rentals to video streaming and Software-as-a-Service.    </p>
<p>                     Most importantly, you&#8217;ll discover what works, and what doesn&#8217;t, from some of the key players in the new membership economy. It&#8217;s not about ownership; it&#8217;s about access, options, and freedom.    </p>
<p>                    When you join forces with your customers, membership has its rewards-for you, your company, and your continued success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-membership-economy-find-your-super-users-master-the-forever-transaction-and-build-recurring-revenue-robbie-kellman-baxter-abridged/">The Membership Economy: Find Your Super Users, Master the Forever Transaction, and Build Recurring Revenue &#8211; Robbie Kellman Baxter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Start At The End : How to Build Products That Create Change &#8211; Matt Wallaert (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/start-at-the-end-how-to-build-products-that-create-change-matt-wallaert-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Product Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technical Design]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/start-at-the-end-how-to-build-products-that-create-change-matt-wallaert-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nudge meets Hooked in a practical approach to designing products and services that change behavior, from what we buy to how we work. Deciding what to create at modern companies often looks like an episode of Mad Men people throw ideas around until one sounds sexy enough to execute and then they scale it to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/start-at-the-end-how-to-build-products-that-create-change-matt-wallaert-abridged/">Start At The End : How to Build Products That Create Change &#8211; Matt Wallaert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nudge meets Hooked in a practical approach to designing products and services that change behavior, from what we buy to how we work. Deciding what to create at modern companies often looks like an episode of Mad Men people throw ideas around until one sounds sexy enough to execute and then they scale it to everyone. The result? Companies overspend on marketing to drive engagement with products and services that people don&#8217;t want and won&#8217;t help them be happier and healthier. Start at the End offers a new framework for design, grounded in behavioral science. Technology executive and behavioral scientist Matt Wallaert argues that the purpose of everything is behavior change. By starting with outcomes instead of processes, the most effective companies understand what people want to do and why they aren&#8217;t already doing it, then build products and services to bridge the gap. Wallaert is a behavioral psychologist who has led product design at organizations ranging from startups like Clover Health to industry leaders such as Microsoft. Whether dissecting the success behind Uber&#8217;s ridesharing service or Flamin&#8217; Hot Cheetos, he underscores with clarity and humor how this approach can improve the way we work and live. This is an essential roadmap for building products that matter&#8211;and changing behavior for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/start-at-the-end-how-to-build-products-that-create-change-matt-wallaert-abridged/">Start At The End : How to Build Products That Create Change &#8211; Matt Wallaert (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>All Marketers are Liars : The Underground Classic That Explains How Marketing Really Works&#8211;and Why Authenticity Is the Best Marketing of All &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The indispensable classic on marketing by the bestselling author of Tribes and Purple Cow. Legendary business writer Seth Godin has three essential questions for every marketer: &#8220;What&#8217;s your story?&#8221; &#8220;Will the people who need to hear this story believe it?&#8221; &#8220;Is it true?&#8221; All marketers tell stories. And if they do it right, we believe [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/">All Marketers are Liars : The Underground Classic That Explains How Marketing Really Works&#8211;and Why Authenticity Is the Best Marketing of All &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The indispensable classic on marketing by the bestselling author of Tribes and Purple Cow.    </p>
<p>                     Legendary business writer Seth Godin has three essential questions for every marketer:     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;What&#8217;s your story?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Will the people who need to hear this story believe it?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Is it true?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     All marketers tell stories. And if they do it right, we believe them. We believe that wine tastes better in a $20 glass than a $1 glass. We believe that an $80,000 Porsche is vastly superior to a $36,000 Volkswagen that&#8217;s virtually the same car. We believe that $225 sneakers make our feet feel better&#8211;and look cooler&#8211;than a $25 brand. And believing it makes it true.     </p>
<p>                     As Seth Godin has taught hundreds of thousands of marketers and students around the world, great marketers don&#8217;t talk about features or even benefits. Instead, they tell a story&#8211;a story we want to believe, whether it&#8217;s factual or not. In a world where most people have an infinite number of choices and no time to make them, every organization is a marketer, and all marketing is about telling stories.     </p>
<p>                     Marketers succeed when they tell us a story that fits our worldview, a story that we intuitively embrace and then share with our friends. Think of the Dyson vacuum cleaner, or Fiji water, or the iPod.     </p>
<p>                     But beware: If your stories are inauthentic, you cross the line from fib to fraud. Marketers fail when they are selfish and scurrilous, when they abuse the tools of their trade and make the world worse. That&#8217;s a lesson learned the hard way by telemarketers, cigarette companies, and sleazy politicians.     </p>
<p>                     But for the rest of us, it&#8217;s time to embrace the power of the story. As Godin writes, &#8220;Stories make it easier to understand the world. Stories are the only way we know to spread an idea. Marketers didn&#8217;t invent storytelling. They just perfected it.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/">All Marketers are Liars : The Underground Classic That Explains How Marketing Really Works&#8211;and Why Authenticity Is the Best Marketing of All &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Or Vocational Training]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personnel & Human Resources Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The age of the faceless corporation is over. In the new business era of the twenty first century, great brands and products must evoke a dynamic personality in order to attract passionate customers. Although many organizations hide their personality behind layers of packaged messaging and advertising, social media guru and influencer Rohit Bhargava counters that philosophy and illustrates how successful businesses have redefined themselves in the new customer universe.    </p>
<p>                    Personality Not Included is a powerhouse resource packed with bold new insights that show you how to shed the lifeless armor of your business and rediscover the soul of your brand. Sharing stories from the ethos of the world&#8217;s weirdest city, to how Manga has taken the comic book industry by storm, to showcasing brands like Intel, Boeing, ING, and Dyson, Bhargava shows you why personality matters from the inside out.    </p>
<p>                    In Part One, you&#8217;ll be introduced to the key components to building a personality and learn how to:    </p>
<p>                    Recognize the greatest myth that most marketers blindly follow, and how to get past itUse the &#8220;UAT Filter&#8221; to understand the personality of your organization and products in order to develop a communication strategy that drives your marketingCreate your company&#8217;s &#8220;marketing backstory&#8221; using techniques pioneered by Hollywood screenwritersHarness the influence of &#8220;accidental spokespeople&#8221; and use it to your advantageNavigate the roadblocks of using personality that come from bosses, peers, investors, and lawyers, without getting fired or flamedPinpoint and capitalize on the moments where personality can make a difference<br />
                    Part Two is packed with guides, tools, and techniques to help you flawlessly implement your plan. It features practical, step-by-step lessons that help you effectively move from theory to action, and includes a valuable collection of guides, checklists, question forms, printable resources, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Don&#8217;t be another faceless company-learn the new rules for succeeding in the social media era with Personality Not Included.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personality-not-included-why-companies-lose-their-authenticity-and-how-great-brands-get-it-back-foreword-by-guy-kawasaki-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Personality Not Included: Why Companies Lose Their Authenticity And How Great Brands Get it Back, Foreword by Guy Kawasaki &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hacking Growth : How Today&#8217;s Fastest-Growing Companies Drive Breakout Success &#8211; Morgan Brown, Sean Ellis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hacking-growth-how-todays-fastest-growing-companies-drive-breakout-success-morgan-brown-sean-ellis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hacking-growth-how-todays-fastest-growing-companies-drive-breakout-success-morgan-brown-sean-ellis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>a compelling methodology&#8230; to increase market share quickly&#8217; &#8212; Eric Ries, bestselling author of THE LEAN STARTUP &#8216;a must-read for anyone in business&#8217; &#8212; James Currier, managing partner, NFX Guild &#8216;will teach you how to think like a marketer of tomorrow&#8217; &#8212; Josh Elman, partner, Greylock Partners Growth is now the first thing that investors, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-growth-how-todays-fastest-growing-companies-drive-breakout-success-morgan-brown-sean-ellis-abridged/">Hacking Growth : How Today&#8217;s Fastest-Growing Companies Drive Breakout Success &#8211; Morgan Brown, Sean Ellis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>a compelling methodology&#8230; to increase market share quickly&#8217; &#8212; Eric Ries, bestselling author of THE LEAN STARTUP    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;a must-read for anyone in business&#8217; &#8212; James Currier, managing partner, NFX Guild    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;will teach you how to think like a marketer of tomorrow&#8217; &#8212; Josh Elman, partner, Greylock Partners    </p>
<p>                    Growth is now the first thing that investors, shareholders and market analysts look for in assessing and valuing companies.      </p>
<p>                    HACKING GROWTH is a highly accessible, practical, method for growth that involves cross-functional teams and continuous testing and iteration. Hacking Growth does for marketshare growth what THE LEAN STARTUP  does for product development and BUSINESS MODEL GENERATION does for strategy. HACKING GROWTH focuses on customers &#8211; how to attain them, retain them, engage them, and monetize them &#8211; rather than product.    </p>
<p>                    Written by the method&#8217;s pioneers, this book is a comprehensive toolkit or &#8220;bible&#8221; that any company in any industry can use to implement their own Growth Hacking strategy, from how to set up and run growth teams, to how to identify and test growth levers, and how to evaluate and act on the results. It is designed for any company or leader looking to break out of the ruts of traditional marketing and become more collaborative, less wasteful, and achieve more consistent, replicable, and data-driven results.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-growth-how-todays-fastest-growing-companies-drive-breakout-success-morgan-brown-sean-ellis-abridged/">Hacking Growth : How Today&#8217;s Fastest-Growing Companies Drive Breakout Success &#8211; Morgan Brown, Sean Ellis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A / B Testing : The Most Powerful Way to Turn Clicks Into Customers &#8211; Dan Siroker, Pete Koomen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-b-testing-the-most-powerful-way-to-turn-clicks-into-customers-dan-siroker-pete-koomen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-b-testing-the-most-powerful-way-to-turn-clicks-into-customers-dan-siroker-pete-koomen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How Your Business Can Use the Science That Helped Win the White House The average conversion rate the rate at which visitors convert into customers across the web is only 2%. That means it&#8217;s likely that 98% of visitors to your website won&#8217;t end up converting into customers. What&#8217;s the solution? A/B testing. A/B testing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-b-testing-the-most-powerful-way-to-turn-clicks-into-customers-dan-siroker-pete-koomen-abridged/">A / B Testing : The Most Powerful Way to Turn Clicks Into Customers &#8211; Dan Siroker, Pete Koomen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How Your Business Can Use the Science That Helped Win the White House The average conversion rate the rate at which visitors convert into customers across the web is only 2%. That means it&#8217;s likely that 98% of visitors to your website won&#8217;t end up converting into customers. What&#8217;s the solution? A/B testing. A/B testing is the simple idea of showing several different versions of a web page to live traffic, and then measuring the effect each version has on visitors. Using A/B testing, companies can improve the effectiveness of their marketing and user experience and, in doing so, can sometimes double or triple their conversion rates. Testing has been fundamental in driving the success of Google, Amazon, Netflix, and other top tech companies. Even Barack Obama and Mitt Romney had dedicated teams A/B testing their campaign websites during the 2012 Presidential race. In the past, marketing teams were unable to unleash the power of A/B testing because it required costly engineering and IT resources.<br />
                    Today, a new generation of technology that enables marketers to run A/B tests without depending on engineers is emerging and quickly becoming one of the most powerful tools for making data-driven decisions. Authors Dan Siroker and Pete Koomen are cofounders of Optimizely, the leading A/B testing platform used by more than 5,000 organizations across the world. A/B Testing: The Most Powerful Way to Turn Clicks Into Customers offers best practices and lessons learned from more than 300,000 experiments run by Optimizely customers. You&#8217;ll learn: * What to test * How to choose the testing solution that&#8217;s right for your organization * How to assemble an A/B testing dream team * How to create personalized experiences for every visitor * And much more Marketers and web professionals will become obsolete if they don&#8217;t embrace a data-driven approach to decision making. This book shows you how, no matter your technical expertise.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-b-testing-the-most-powerful-way-to-turn-clicks-into-customers-dan-siroker-pete-koomen-abridged/">A / B Testing : The Most Powerful Way to Turn Clicks Into Customers &#8211; Dan Siroker, Pete Koomen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buyology : Truth and Lies About Why We Buy &#8211; Martin Lindstrom, Foreword by Paco Underhill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/buyology-truth-and-lies-about-why-we-buy-martin-lindstrom-foreword-by-paco-underhill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Purchasing & Supply Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/buyology-truth-and-lies-about-why-we-buy-martin-lindstrom-foreword-by-paco-underhill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; &#8220;A fascinating look at how consumers perceive logos, ads, commercials, brands, and products.&#8221;&#8211;Time How much do we know about why we buy? What truly influences our decisions in today&#8217;s message-cluttered world? In Buyology, Martin Lindstrom presents the astonishing findings from his groundbreaking three-year, seven-million-dollar neuromarketing study&#8211;a cutting-edge experiment that peered [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buyology-truth-and-lies-about-why-we-buy-martin-lindstrom-foreword-by-paco-underhill-abridged/">Buyology : Truth and Lies About Why We Buy &#8211; Martin Lindstrom, Foreword by Paco Underhill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; &#8220;A fascinating look at how consumers perceive logos, ads, commercials, brands, and products.&#8221;&#8211;Time     </p>
<p>                    How much do we know about why we buy? What truly influences our decisions in today&#8217;s message-cluttered world? In Buyology, Martin Lindstrom presents the astonishing findings from his groundbreaking three-year, seven-million-dollar neuromarketing study&#8211;a cutting-edge experiment that peered inside the brains of 2,000 volunteers from all around the world as they encountered various ads, logos, commercials, brands, and products. His startling results shatter much of what we have long believed about what captures our interest&#8211;and drives us to buy. Among the questions he explores:     </p>
<p>                    &#8211; Does sex actually sell?<br />
                    &#8211; Does subliminal advertising still surround us?<br />
                    &#8211; Can &#8220;cool&#8221; brands trigger our mating instincts?<br />
                    &#8211; Can our other senses&#8211;smell, touch, and sound&#8211;be aroused when we see a product?     </p>
<p>                    Buyology is a fascinating and shocking journey into the mind of today&#8217;s consumer that will captivate anyone who&#8217;s been seduced&#8211;or turned off&#8211;by marketers&#8217; relentless attempts to win our loyalty, our money, and our minds.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buyology-truth-and-lies-about-why-we-buy-martin-lindstrom-foreword-by-paco-underhill-abridged/">Buyology : Truth and Lies About Why We Buy &#8211; Martin Lindstrom, Foreword by Paco Underhill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Managing Online Reputation is a comprehensive look at online reputation management. Drawing on recent examples of organizations managing their online reputations effectively and ineffectively, it provides a practical and visual tool-kit of processes and techniques to help limit and respond effectively to negative situations on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/">Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Managing Online Reputation is a comprehensive look at online reputation management. Drawing on recent examples of organizations managing their online reputations effectively and ineffectively, it provides a practical and visual tool-kit of processes and techniques to help limit and respond effectively to negative situations on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/">Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indistractable : How to Control Your Attention and Choose Your Life &#8211; Nir Eyal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/indistractable-how-to-control-your-attention-and-choose-your-life-nir-eyal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/indistractable-how-to-control-your-attention-and-choose-your-life-nir-eyal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A must-read&#8217; Mark Manson We are living through a crisis of distraction. Plans get sidetracked, friends are ignored, work never seems to get done. Why does it feel like we&#8217;re distracting our lives away? In Indistractable, behavioural designer Nir Eyal reveals the hidden psychology driving you to distraction. Empowering and optimistic, this is the book [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/indistractable-how-to-control-your-attention-and-choose-your-life-nir-eyal-abridged/">Indistractable : How to Control Your Attention and Choose Your Life &#8211; Nir Eyal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A must-read&#8217; Mark Manson    </p>
<p>                    We are living through a crisis of distraction. Plans get sidetracked, friends are ignored, work never seems to get done.     </p>
<p>                    Why does it feel like we&#8217;re distracting our lives away?    </p>
<p>                    In Indistractable, behavioural designer Nir Eyal reveals the hidden psychology driving you to distraction. Empowering and optimistic, this is the book that will help you design your time, realise your ambitions, and live the life you really want.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you value your time, your focus or your relationships, this book is essential reading&#8217; Jonathan Haidt, author of The Righteous Mind    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A guide to staying focused in an age of constant distraction&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Exactly what most of us need in order to focus on what is important, rather than the dazzling, illuminated, unsatisfying distractions of modern life&#8217; Matt Haig    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Does exactly as it promises. Amazing&#8217; Chris Evans    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The best guide I&#8217;ve read for reclaiming our attention, our focus and our lives&#8217; Arianna Huffington</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/indistractable-how-to-control-your-attention-and-choose-your-life-nir-eyal-abridged/">Indistractable : How to Control Your Attention and Choose Your Life &#8211; Nir Eyal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crossing the Chasm, 3rd Edition : Marketing and Selling Disruptive Products to Mainstream Customers &#8211; Geoffrey A Moore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crossing-the-chasm-3rd-edition-marketing-and-selling-disruptive-products-to-mainstream-customers-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crossing-the-chasm-3rd-edition-marketing-and-selling-disruptive-products-to-mainstream-customers-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bible for bringing cutting-edge products to larger markets&#8211;now revised and updated with new insights into the realities of high-tech marketing In Crossing the Chasm, Geoffrey A. Moore shows that in the Technology Adoption Life Cycle&#8211;which begins with innovators and moves to early adopters, early majority, late majority, and laggards&#8211;there is a vast chasm between [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crossing-the-chasm-3rd-edition-marketing-and-selling-disruptive-products-to-mainstream-customers-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/">Crossing the Chasm, 3rd Edition : Marketing and Selling Disruptive Products to Mainstream Customers &#8211; Geoffrey A Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bible for bringing cutting-edge products to larger markets&#8211;now revised and updated with new insights into the realities of high-tech marketing    </p>
<p>                    In Crossing the Chasm, Geoffrey A. Moore shows that in the Technology Adoption Life Cycle&#8211;which begins with innovators and moves to early adopters, early majority, late majority, and laggards&#8211;there is a vast chasm between the early adopters and the early majority. While early adopters are willing to sacrifice for the advantage of being first, the early majority waits until they know that the technology actually offers improvements in productivity. The challenge for innovators and marketers is to narrow this chasm and ultimately accelerate adoption across every segment.     </p>
<p>                    This third edition brings Moore&#8217;s classic work up to date with dozens of new examples of successes and failures, new strategies for marketing in the digital world, and Moore&#8217;s most current insights and findings. He also includes two new appendices, the first connecting the ideas in Crossing the Chasm to work subsequently published in his Inside the Tornado, and the second presenting his recent groundbreaking work for technology adoption models for high-tech consumer markets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crossing-the-chasm-3rd-edition-marketing-and-selling-disruptive-products-to-mainstream-customers-geoffrey-a-moore-abridged/">Crossing the Chasm, 3rd Edition : Marketing and Selling Disruptive Products to Mainstream Customers &#8211; Geoffrey A Moore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Drunk Tank Pink : And Other Unexpected Forces That Shape How We Think, Feel, and Behave &#8211; Adam Alter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/drunk-tank-pink-and-other-unexpected-forces-that-shape-how-we-think-feel-and-behave-adam-alter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/drunk-tank-pink-and-other-unexpected-forces-that-shape-how-we-think-feel-and-behave-adam-alter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller! A revelatory look at how our environment unconsciously yet dramatically shapes the judgments and decisions we make every day Most of us go through life believing that we are in control of the choices we make-that we think and behave almost independently from the world around us. But as Drunk [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/drunk-tank-pink-and-other-unexpected-forces-that-shape-how-we-think-feel-and-behave-adam-alter-abridged/">Drunk Tank Pink : And Other Unexpected Forces That Shape How We Think, Feel, and Behave &#8211; Adam Alter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller!     </p>
<p>                    A revelatory look at how our environment unconsciously yet dramatically shapes the judgments and decisions we make every day    </p>
<p>                    Most of us go through life believing that we are in control of the choices we make-that we think and behave almost independently from the world around us. But as Drunk Tank Pink illustrates, the truth is our environment shapes our thoughts and actions in myriad ways without our permission or even our knowledge. Armed with surprising data and endlessly fascinating examples, Adam Alter addresses the subtle but substantial ways in which outside forces influence us-such as color&#8217;s influence on mood, our bias in favor of names with which we identify, and how sunny days can induce optimism as well as aggression. Drunk Tank Pink proves that the truth behind our feelings and actions goes much deeper than the choices we take for granted every day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/drunk-tank-pink-and-other-unexpected-forces-that-shape-how-we-think-feel-and-behave-adam-alter-abridged/">Drunk Tank Pink : And Other Unexpected Forces That Shape How We Think, Feel, and Behave &#8211; Adam Alter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Habits are more powerful than your will &#8211; if you know how to make them work for you Two strings are hanging from a ceiling, one at the centre of the room, one near the wall. You&#8217;re asked to tie the strings together, but you can&#8217;t reach both at the same time. You look around [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/">Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Habits are more powerful than your will &#8211; if you know how to make them work for you    </p>
<p>                    Two strings are hanging from a ceiling, one at the centre of the room, one near the wall. You&#8217;re asked to tie the strings together, but you can&#8217;t reach both at the same time. You look around the room and see a table and a pair of pliers. How would you solve the problem?    </p>
<p>                    When confronted with challenges, most people let habits rule them (in this case, ignoring the pliers, the creative tool at your disposal). That is not surprising when you realise that at least a third of our waking hours are lived on auto-pilot &#8211; ruminating over past events, clicking through websites trawling for updates and the like. Such unconscious thoughts and actions are powerful. But the habits of the mind do not have to control us &#8211; we can steer them.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on hundreds of fascinating studies, psychologist Jeremy Dean &#8211; the mind behind the hugely popular and insightful website PsyBlog &#8211; shares how the new brain science of habit can be harnessed to your benefit, whether you&#8217;re hoping to eat moreveg, take an evening run, clear out your email backlog, or be more creative when faced with challenges at work and at home.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/">Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Non-Obvious 2018 Edition : How To Predict Trends And Win The Future &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/non-obvious-2018-edition-how-to-predict-trends-and-win-the-future-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/non-obvious-2018-edition-how-to-predict-trends-and-win-the-future-rohit-bhargava-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Seller (2015 Edition) Gold Medal: Non-Fiction Book Awards (2018 Edition) Winner: IPPY Book Awards Silver Medal (2018 Edition) Winner: Axiom Business Theory Silver Medal (2017 Edition) Official Selection: Gary&#8217;s Book Club at CES (2017 Edition) #1 AMAZON OVERALL BUSINESS BEST SELLER (2015 Edition) What secrets can a 400-year-old Turkish cymbal maker [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/non-obvious-2018-edition-how-to-predict-trends-and-win-the-future-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Non-Obvious 2018 Edition : How To Predict Trends And Win The Future &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wall Street Journal Best Seller (2015 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    Gold Medal: Non-Fiction Book Awards (2018 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    Winner: IPPY Book Awards Silver Medal (2018 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    Winner: Axiom Business Theory Silver Medal (2017 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    Official Selection: Gary&#8217;s Book Club at CES (2017 Edition)    </p>
<p>                    #1 AMAZON OVERALL BUSINESS BEST SELLER (2015 Edition)     </p>
<p>                    What secrets can a 400-year-old Turkish cymbal maker and an Icelandic hot tub etiquette video teach you about the power of storytelling?     </p>
<p>                    How do Michelin-ranked food stalls in Singapore and the decline of Swiss watches force all luxury brands to rethink their business models?     </p>
<p>                    What insights can the world&#8217;s quietest place and a clothing dye produced by former tobacco farmers reveal about serving enlightened consumers?    </p>
<p>                    The answers to these questions may not be all that obvious. And that&#8217;s exactly the point. For the past eight years, innovation expert Rohit Bhargava and his team have predicted 15 &#8220;Non-Obvious&#8221; trends each year. In this book, get a sneak peek at the proven methods exclusively taught to thousands of executives at leading brands, organizations and governments to develop unexpected solutions to critical problems. The power of non-obvious thinking can help you see what others miss, grow your business and make a bigger impact in the world.    </p>
<p>                    In this all-new eighth edition, discover what more than a million readers already have: how to use the power of non-obvious thinking to grow your business and make a bigger impact in the world.    </p>
<p>                    In total, the Non-Obvious 2018 Edition features 15 all-new trends across 5 categories including Culture &#038; Consumer Behavior, Marketing &#038; Social Media, Media &#038; Education, Technology &#038; Design plus Economics &#038; Entrepreneurship. The book also features a detailed section with a review and rating for more than 100 previously predicted trends &#8211; with longevity ratings for each.    </p>
<p>                    As with the original version, this new edition of Non-Obvious also delves into the curation process the author has used for years to build his Trend Reports and takes readers behind the scenes of trend curation (much to the delight of past readers who have been asking about this for years), and show them the methodology they can use to predict the future for themselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/non-obvious-2018-edition-how-to-predict-trends-and-win-the-future-rohit-bhargava-abridged/">Non-Obvious 2018 Edition : How To Predict Trends And Win The Future &#8211; Rohit Bhargava (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Psychology of Selling : Increase Your Sales Faster and Easier Than You Ever Thought Possible &#8211; Brian Tracy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Top professional speaker and sales trainer Brian Tracy found that his most important breakthrough was the discovery that it is the &#8220;psychology of selling&#8221; that is more important than the techniques and methods of selling. Learn how to double and triple your sales in any market. It&#8217;s a promise of prosperity that sales guru Brian [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/">The Psychology of Selling : Increase Your Sales Faster and Easier Than You Ever Thought Possible &#8211; Brian Tracy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Top professional speaker and sales trainer Brian Tracy found that his most important breakthrough was the discovery that it is the &#8220;psychology of selling&#8221; that is more important than the techniques and methods of selling.    </p>
<p>                    Learn how to double and triple your sales in any market. It&#8217;s a promise of prosperity that sales guru Brian Tracy has seen fulfilled again and again.    </p>
<p>                    More salespeople have become millionaires by listening to and applying his ideas than from any other sales training process ever developed.    </p>
<p>                    In Psychology of Selling, Tracy teaches you:    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The inner game of sales and selling&#8221;<br />
                    How to eliminate the fear of rejection<br />
                    How to build unshakeable confidence    </p>
<p>                    Tracy shows how salespeople must learn to control their thoughts, feelings and actions to make themselves more effective.    </p>
<p>                    Psychology of Selling gives you a series of ideas, methods, strategies, and techniques that you can use immediately to make more sales, faster and easier than ever before.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/">The Psychology of Selling : Increase Your Sales Faster and Easier Than You Ever Thought Possible &#8211; Brian Tracy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tools and Weapons : The Promise and the Peril of the Digital Age &#8211; Brad Smith, Carol Ann Browne (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Certification: Microsoft (eg MCSE)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft Windows]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AND WORLD ECONOMIC FORUM BOOK CLUB PICK* &#8216;A clear, compelling guide to some of the most pressing debates in technology today.&#8217; Bill Gates &#8216;A colourful and insightful insiders&#8217; view of how technology is both empowering us and threatening us. From privacy to cyberattacks, this timely book is a useful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/">Tools and Weapons : The Promise and the Peril of the Digital Age &#8211; Brad Smith, Carol Ann Browne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AND WORLD ECONOMIC FORUM BOOK CLUB PICK*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A clear, compelling guide to some of the most pressing debates in technology today.&#8217; Bill Gates    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A colourful and insightful insiders&#8217; view of how technology is both empowering us and threatening us. From privacy to cyberattacks, this timely book is a useful guide for how to navigate the digital future.&#8217;  Walter Isaacson, bestselling author of Steve Jobs    </p>
<p>                    From Microsoft&#8217;s President and one of the tech industry&#8217;s wisest thinkers, a frank and thoughtful reckoning with how to balance enormous promise and existential risk as the digitization of everything accelerates. With new chapters on the pandemic and beyond.<br />
                    __________    </p>
<p>                    Microsoft President Brad Smith operates by a simple core belief: when your technology changes the world, you bear a responsibility to help address the world you have helped create.     </p>
<p>                    This might seem uncontroversial, but it flies in the face of a tech sector long obsessed with rapid growth and sometimes on disruption as an end in itself. While sweeping digital transformation holds great promise, we have reached an inflection point. The world has turned information technology into both a powerful tool and a formidable weapon, and new approaches are needed to manage an era defined by even more powerful inventions like artificial intelligence. Companies that create technology must accept greater responsibility for the future, and governments will need to regulate technology by moving faster and catching up with the pace of innovation.    </p>
<p>                    In Tools and Weapons, Brad Smith and Carol Ann Browne bring us a captivating narrative from the cockpit of one of the world&#8217;s largest and most powerful tech companies as it finds itself in the middle of some of the thorniest emerging issues of our time. These are challenges that come with no pre-existing playbook, including privacy, cybercrime and cyberwar, social media, the moral conundrums of artificial intelligence, big tech&#8217;s relationship to inequality, and the challenges for democracy, far and near. While in no way a self-glorifying &#8220;Microsoft memoir,&#8221; the book pulls back the curtain remarkably wide onto some of the company&#8217;s most crucial recent decision points as it strives to protect the hopes technology offers against the very real threats it also presents. There are huge ramifications for communities and countries, and Brad Smith provides a thoughtful and urgent contribution to that effort.    </p>
<p>                    __________    </p>
<p>                    In Tools and Weapons, Brad Smith takes us behind the scenes on some of the biggest stories to hit the tech industry in the past decade and some of the biggest threats we face. From Edward Snowden&#8217;s NSA leak to the NHS WannaCry ransomware attack, this book is essential reading to understand what&#8217;s happening in the world around us.    </p>
<p>                    Praise for Tools and Weapons:     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The de facto ambassador for the technology industry at large.&#8217; The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;In Tools and Weapons, Brad and Carol Ann Browne wrestle with some of the world&#8217;s toughest technology challenges with common sense and valuable insight reflecting their inside experience. The ideas in Tools and Weapons won&#8217;t solve all our problems, but they&#8217;re a very good place to start.&#8217; &#8211; Reed Hastings, CEO, Netflix    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Tools and Weapons is a glimpse behind the curtain as Microsoft reckoned with the Snowden revelations, defended against the vicious cyberattacks, and took both the Obama and Trump administrations to court.&#8217; &#8211; Rolling Stone</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/">Tools and Weapons : The Promise and the Peril of the Digital Age &#8211; Brad Smith, Carol Ann Browne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Purple Cow : Transform Your Business by Being Remarkable &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re either a Purple Cow or you&#8217;re not. You&#8217;re either remarkable or invisible. Make your choice. What do Apple, Starbucks, Dyson and Pret a Manger have in common? How do they achieve spectacular growth, leaving behind former tried-and-true brands to gasp their last? The old checklist of P&#8217;s used by marketers &#8211; Pricing, Promotion, Publicity [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin-abridged/">Purple Cow : Transform Your Business by Being Remarkable &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re either a Purple Cow or you&#8217;re not. You&#8217;re either remarkable or invisible. Make your choice.    </p>
<p>                    What do Apple, Starbucks, Dyson and Pret a Manger have in common? How do they achieve spectacular growth, leaving behind former tried-and-true brands to gasp their last? The old checklist of P&#8217;s used by marketers &#8211; Pricing, Promotion, Publicity &#8211; aren&#8217;t working anymore. The golden age of advertising is over. It&#8217;s time to add a new P &#8211; the Purple Cow.    </p>
<p>                    Purple Cow describes something phenomenal, something counterintuitive and exciting and flat-out unbelievable. In his new bestseller, Seth Godin urges you to put a Purple Cow into everything you build, and everything you do, to create something truly noticeable. It&#8217;s a manifesto for anyone who wants to help create products and services that are worth marketing in the first place.    </p>
<p>                    If you enjoyed reading this, check out Seth Godin&#8217;s business classic This is Marketing.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/purple-cow-transform-your-business-by-being-remarkable-seth-godin-abridged/">Purple Cow : Transform Your Business by Being Remarkable &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Do you know how to find out what people really want to buy? (Not what you think they want, not what they say they want, but what they really want?) The secret is asking the right questions&#8230; and the right questions are not what you might expect. Introducing Ask: the most powerful way to discover [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/">Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Do you know how to find out what people really want to buy? (Not what you think they want, not what they say they want, but what they really want?)    </p>
<p>                    The secret is asking the right questions&#8230; and the right questions are not what you might expect.    </p>
<p>                    Introducing Ask: the most powerful way to discover exactly what people want to buy, and how to give it to them &#8211; and in a way that makes people fall in love with you and your company.     </p>
<p>                    The proven, repeatable (yet slightly counterintuitive) Ask Method has quietly generated over $100 million in online sales across 23 different industries, and counting. In this tell-all book, Ryan Levesque reveals this exact method step-by-step, as well as the unusual story behind its discovery.    </p>
<p>                    Whether you&#8217;re an aspiring Internet entrepreneur, advanced online marketer, or established business owner, this book will both inspire you and show you how to skyrocket your online income-while creating a mass of raving fans in the process-simply by asking the right questions in a surprisingly different way.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ryan has uncovered some enormous misunderstandings about human buying behavior and then utilized his neuroscience background to create this game-changing marketing and survey strategy. Before you finish the first third of the book, you&#8217;ll be eager to jump ahead and implement his process immediately &#8211; it&#8217;s that powerful!&#8217; &#8211; Annie Hyman Pratt, former CEO of The Coffee Bean and Tea Leaf and CEO of IMPAQ Entrepreneur Business Execution Systems    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ask may be the most important book written for anyone who sells products or services directly to consumers since Breakthrough Advertising was published in 1966. Like that masterpiece, Ask gives us a new paradigm for understanding human behavior at the deepest level, which gives rise to a more intelligent and profitable way to sell almost anything. Ryan Levsque will go down in history as the marketer who used his background to change the way products and services are sold online.&#8217; &#8211; Brian Kurtz, business builder of Boardroom Inc. and serial direct marketer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ask-the-counterintuitive-online-method-to-discover-exactly-what-your-customers-want-to-buy-create-a-mass-of-raving-fans-and-take-any-business-to-the-next-level-ryan-levesque-abridged/">Ask : The Counterintuitive Online Method to Discover Exactly What Your Customers Want to Buy . . . Create a Mass of Raving Fans . . . and Take Any Business to the Next Level &#8211; Ryan Levesque (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fascinate, Revised and Updated : How to Make Your Brand Impossible to Resist &#8211; Sally Hogshead (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fascinate-revised-and-updated-how-to-make-your-brand-impossible-to-resist-sally-hogshead-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fascinate-revised-and-updated-how-to-make-your-brand-impossible-to-resist-sally-hogshead-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why is Jagermeister the most popular brand nobody likes? Why do women pay more to be fascinating than they spend on food and clothes? What raises the price of gummy worms by 1000%? And then there&#8217;s the most important question of all: How can your brand become impossible to resist? Master marketer Sally Hogshead reveals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fascinate-revised-and-updated-how-to-make-your-brand-impossible-to-resist-sally-hogshead-abridged/">Fascinate, Revised and Updated : How to Make Your Brand Impossible to Resist &#8211; Sally Hogshead (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why is Jagermeister the most popular brand nobody likes? Why do women pay more to be fascinating than they spend on food and clothes? What raises the price of gummy worms by 1000%?  And then there&#8217;s the most important question of all: How can your brand become impossible to resist? Master marketer Sally Hogshead reveals the surprising answers, providing readers with a framework to fascinating anyone.  The word &#8220;fascinate&#8221; comes from the Latin word fascinare, meaning &#8220;to bewitch or hold captive so others are powerless to resist.&#8221; Fascination is the most powerful force of attraction, drawing customers into a state of intense focus. This extensively revised and updated edition includes Hogshead&#8217;s latest research on the science of fascination. Combining original case studies with award-winning copywriting experience, she gives you the exact words you need to capture the attention of a distracted world.  This new edition includes a free assessment tool called the Brand Fascination Profile, which will help you earn attention in any environment.<br />
                    Dive into the science of fascination and learn how to:  *Increase prices with ideas from poker to Play-Doh*Build revenue by learning about the $14 million license plate*Get better leads through hypnosis by Sigmund Freud and Steve Jobs*Attract raving fans by following the cult of pistachio ice cream Whether you realize it or not, your brand is already applying one of the seven Advantages Hogshead describes here:  Innovation, Passion, Power, Prestige, Mystique, Alert, or Trust. The question is, how can you apply these core Advantages to stand out in a crowded and distracted world? Hundreds of large corporations, small businesses, and universities-including Twitter, IBM, Porsche, and New York University-use the Fascinate system to captivate their customers. Why? The answers are in this book.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fascinate-revised-and-updated-how-to-make-your-brand-impossible-to-resist-sally-hogshead-abridged/">Fascinate, Revised and Updated : How to Make Your Brand Impossible to Resist &#8211; Sally Hogshead (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buyer Personas : How to Gain Insight into your Customer&#8217;s Expectations, Align your Marketing Strategies, and Win More Business &#8211; Adele Revella (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/buyer-personas-how-to-gain-insight-into-your-customers-expectations-align-your-marketing-strategies-and-win-more-business-adele-revella-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/buyer-personas-how-to-gain-insight-into-your-customers-expectations-align-your-marketing-strategies-and-win-more-business-adele-revella-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>See your offering through the buyer&#8217;s eyes for more effective marketing Buyer Personas is the marketer&#8217;s actionable guide to learning what your buyer wants and how they make decisions. Written by the world&#8217;s leading authority on buyer personas, this book provides comprehensive coverage of a compelling new way to conduct buyer studies, plus practical advice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buyer-personas-how-to-gain-insight-into-your-customers-expectations-align-your-marketing-strategies-and-win-more-business-adele-revella-abridged/">Buyer Personas : How to Gain Insight into your Customer&#8217;s Expectations, Align your Marketing Strategies, and Win More Business &#8211; Adele Revella (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>See your offering through the buyer&#8217;s eyes for more effective marketing Buyer Personas is the marketer&#8217;s actionable guide to learning what your buyer wants and how they make decisions. Written by the world&#8217;s leading authority on buyer personas, this book provides comprehensive coverage of a compelling new way to conduct buyer studies, plus practical advice on adopting the buyer persona approach to measurably improve marketing outcomes. Readers will learn how to segment their customer base, investigate each customer type, and apply a radically more relevant process of message selection, content creation, and distribution through the channels that earn the buyers&#8217; trust. Rather than relying on generic data or guesswork to determine what the buyer wants, the buyer persona approach allows companies to ask the buyer directly and obtain more precise and actionable guidance. Buyer personas are composite pictures of the people who buy solutions, services or products, crafted through a unique type of interview with the people the marketer wants to influence.<br />
                    This book provides step-by-step guidance toward implementing the buyer persona approach, with the advice of an internationally-respected expert. * Learn who buys what, and why * Understand your buyer&#8217;s goals and how you can address them * Tailor your marketing activities to your buyer&#8217;s expectations * See the purchase through the customer&#8217;s eyes A recent services industry survey reports that 52 percent of their marketers have buyer personas, and another 28 percent expect to add them within the next two years but only 14.6 percent know how to use them. To avoid letting such a valuable tool go to waste, access the expert perspective in Buyer Personas, and craft a more relevant marketing strategy.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/buyer-personas-how-to-gain-insight-into-your-customers-expectations-align-your-marketing-strategies-and-win-more-business-adele-revella-abridged/">Buyer Personas : How to Gain Insight into your Customer&#8217;s Expectations, Align your Marketing Strategies, and Win More Business &#8211; Adele Revella (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Culture Code : An Ingenious Way to Understand Why People Around the World Live and Buy as They Do &#8211; Clotaire Rapaille (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-culture-code-an-ingenious-way-to-understand-why-people-around-the-world-live-and-buy-as-they-do-clotaire-rapaille-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-culture-code-an-ingenious-way-to-understand-why-people-around-the-world-live-and-buy-as-they-do-clotaire-rapaille-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why are people around the world so very different? What makes us live, buy, even love as we do? The answers are in the codes. In The Culture Code, internationally revered cultural anthropologist and marketing expert Clotaire Rapaille reveals for the first time the techniques he has used to improve profitability and practices for dozens [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-culture-code-an-ingenious-way-to-understand-why-people-around-the-world-live-and-buy-as-they-do-clotaire-rapaille-abridged/">The Culture Code : An Ingenious Way to Understand Why People Around the World Live and Buy as They Do &#8211; Clotaire Rapaille (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why are people around the world so very different? What makes us live, buy, even love as we do? The answers are in the codes. In The Culture Code, internationally revered cultural anthropologist and marketing expert Clotaire Rapaille reveals for the first time the techniques he has used to improve profitability and practices for dozens of Fortune 100 companies. His groundbreaking revelations shed light not just on business but on the way every human being acts and lives around the world. Rapaille&#8217;s breakthrough notion is that we acquire a silent system of codes as we grow up within our culture. These codes&#8211;the Culture Code&#8211;are what make us American, or German, or French, and they invisibly shape how we behave in our personal lives, even when we are completely unaware of our motives. What&#8217;s more, we can learn to crack the codes that guide our actions and achieve new understanding of why we do the things we do. Rapaille has used the Culture Code to help Chrysler build the PT Cruiser&#8211;the most successful American car launch in recent memory. He has used it to help Procter &#038; Gamble design its advertising campaign for Folger&#8217;s coffee &#8211; one of the longest lasting and most successful campaigns in the annals of advertising. He has used it to help companies as diverse as GE, AT&#038;T, Boeing, Honda, Kellogg, and L&#8217;Oréal improve their bottom line at home and overseas. And now, in The Culture Code, he uses it to reveal why Americans act distinctly like Americans, and what makes us different from the world around us. In The Culture Code, Dr. Rapaille decodes two dozen of our most fundamental archetypes&#8211;ranging from sex to money to health to America itself&#8211;to give us &#8220;a new set of glasses&#8221; with which to view our actions and motivations. Why are we so often disillusioned by love? Why is fat a solution rather than a problem? Why do we reject the notion of perfection? Why is fast food in our lives to stay? The answers are in the Codes. Understanding the Codes gives us unprecedented freedom over our lives. It lets us do business in dramatically new ways. And it finally explains why people around the world really are different, and reveals the hidden clues to understanding us all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-culture-code-an-ingenious-way-to-understand-why-people-around-the-world-live-and-buy-as-they-do-clotaire-rapaille-abridged/">The Culture Code : An Ingenious Way to Understand Why People Around the World Live and Buy as They Do &#8211; Clotaire Rapaille (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>YouthNation : Building Remarkable Brands in a Youth-Driven Culture &#8211; Matt Britton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/youthnation-building-remarkable-brands-in-a-youth-driven-culture-matt-britton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/youthnation-building-remarkable-brands-in-a-youth-driven-culture-matt-britton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Youth is no longer an age it&#8217;s a commodity YouthNation is an indispensable brand roadmap to the youth-driven economy. Exploring the idea that youth is no longer an age it&#8217;s a commodity that&#8217;s available to everyone this book shows what it takes to stay connected, agile, authentic, and relevant in today&#8217;s marketplace. Readers will learn [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youthnation-building-remarkable-brands-in-a-youth-driven-culture-matt-britton-abridged/">YouthNation : Building Remarkable Brands in a Youth-Driven Culture &#8211; Matt Britton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Youth is no longer an age it&#8217;s a commodity YouthNation is an indispensable brand roadmap to the youth-driven economy. Exploring the idea that youth is no longer an age it&#8217;s a commodity that&#8217;s available to everyone this book shows what it takes to stay connected, agile, authentic, and relevant in today&#8217;s marketplace. Readers will learn the ins and outs of the new consumer, and the tools, methods, and techniques that ensure brand survival in the age of perpetual youth. Coverage includes marketing in a post-demographic world, crafting the story of the brand, building engaged communities, creating experiences that inspire loyalty and evangelism, and the cutting-edge tricks that help businesses large and small harness the enormous power of youth. The old marketing models are over, and the status quo is dead. Businesses today have to embody the ideals of youth culture in order to succeed, by tapping the new and rapidly evolving resources n business and in life. When everything is changing at the pace of a teenager&#8217;s attention span, how do businesses future-fit for long-term success?<br />
                    This book provides a plan, and the thoughts, strategies, and brass tacks advice for putting it into action. * Use New-Gen psychographics to target markets * Build stronger evangelism with a compelling brand narrative * Create loyal communities with immersive and engaging experiences * Navigate the radically-changed landscape of the future marketplace In today&#8217;s hyper-socialized, Facebook fanatic, selfie-obsessed world, youth is the primary driver of business and culture. Smart companies are looking to tap into the fountain of youth, and the others are sinking fast. YouthNation is a roadmap to brand relevancy in the new economy, giving businesses turn-by-turn direction to their market destination.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youthnation-building-remarkable-brands-in-a-youth-driven-culture-matt-britton-abridged/">YouthNation : Building Remarkable Brands in a Youth-Driven Culture &#8211; Matt Britton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unconscious Branding : How Neuroscience Can Empower (and Inspire) Marketing &#8211; Douglas van Praet (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unconscious-branding-how-neuroscience-can-empower-and-inspire-marketing-douglas-van-praet-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unconscious-branding-how-neuroscience-can-empower-and-inspire-marketing-douglas-van-praet-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For too long marketers have been asking the wrong question. If consumers make decisions unconsciously, why do we persist in asking them directly through traditional marketing research why they do what they do? They simply can&#8217;t tell us because they don&#8217;t really know. Before marketers develop strategies, they need to recognize that consumers have strategies [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unconscious-branding-how-neuroscience-can-empower-and-inspire-marketing-douglas-van-praet-abridged/">Unconscious Branding : How Neuroscience Can Empower (and Inspire) Marketing &#8211; Douglas van Praet (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For too long marketers have been asking the wrong question. If consumers make decisions unconsciously, why do we persist in asking them directly through traditional marketing research why they do what they do? They simply can&#8217;t tell us because they don&#8217;t really know. Before marketers develop strategies, they need to recognize that consumers have strategies too &#8230;human strategies, not consumer strategies. We need to go beyond asking why, and begin to ask how, behavior change occurs. Here, author Douglas Van Praet takes the most brilliant and revolutionary concepts from cognitive science and applies them to how we market, advertise, and consume in the modern digital age. Van Praet simplifies the most complex object in the known universe &#8211; the human brain &#8211; into seven codified actionable steps to behavior change. These steps are illustrated using real world examples from advertising, marketing, media, and business to consciously unravel what brilliant marketers and ad practitioners have long done intuitively, deconstructing the real story behind some of the greatest marketing and business successes in recent history, such as Nike&#8217;s &#8220;Just Do It&#8221; campaign; &#8220;Got Milk?&#8221;<br />
                    ; Wendy&#8217;s &#8220;Where&#8217;s the Beef?&#8221;; and the infamous Volkswagen &#8220;Punch Buggy&#8221; launch as well as their beloved &#8220;The Force&#8221; (Mini Darth Vader) Super Bowl commercial.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unconscious-branding-how-neuroscience-can-empower-and-inspire-marketing-douglas-van-praet-abridged/">Unconscious Branding : How Neuroscience Can Empower (and Inspire) Marketing &#8211; Douglas van Praet (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the past decade, governments and corporations have become increasingly interested in measuring the way people feel: &#8216;the Happiness index&#8217;, &#8216;Gross National Happiness&#8217;, &#8216;well-being&#8217; and positive psychology have come to dominate the way we live our lives. As a result, our emotions have become a new resource to be bought and sold. In a fascinating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/">The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the past decade, governments and corporations have become increasingly interested in measuring the way people feel: &#8216;the Happiness index&#8217;, &#8216;Gross National Happiness&#8217;, &#8216;well-being&#8217; and positive psychology have come to dominate the way we live our lives. As a result, our emotions have become a new resource to be bought and sold. In a fascinating investigation combining history, science and ideas, William Davies shows how well-being influences all aspects of our lives: business, finance, marketing and smart technology. This book will make you rethink everything from the way you work, the power of the &#8216;Nudge&#8217;, the ever-expanding definitions of depression, and the commercialization of your most private feelings. The Happiness Industry is a shocking and brilliantly argued warning about the new religion of the age: our emotions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/">The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Brain Sell : When Science Meets Shopping &#8211; David Lewis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-brain-sell-when-science-meets-shopping-david-lewis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-brain-sell-when-science-meets-shopping-david-lewis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Science has made the leap from the lab to come to a store near you and the effects on us are phenomenal. Corporations in hyper-competition are now using the new mind sciences to analyze how and when we shop, and the hidden triggers that persuade us to consume. From bargains in the Big Apple to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brain-sell-when-science-meets-shopping-david-lewis-abridged/">The Brain Sell : When Science Meets Shopping &#8211; David Lewis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Science has made the leap from the lab to come to a store near you and the effects on us are phenomenal.    </p>
<p>                    Corporations in hyper-competition are now using the new mind sciences to analyze how and when we shop, and the hidden triggers that persuade us to consume. From bargains in the Big Apple to the bustling bazaars of Istanbul, from in-store to interactive and online to mobile, neuromarketing pioneer Dr. David Lewis goes behind the scenes of the persuasion industry to reveal the powerful tools and techniques, technologies and psychologies seeking to stimulate us all to buy more often without us consciously realizing it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-brain-sell-when-science-meets-shopping-david-lewis-abridged/">The Brain Sell : When Science Meets Shopping &#8211; David Lewis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Smarter Screen : What Your Business Can Learn from the Way Consumers Think Online &#8211; Shlomo Benartzi, Jonah Lehrer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[User Interface Design & Usability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The typical office worker now spends the majority of their waking hours staring at a screen. In the 21st century, every business is a digital business, which is why it&#8217;s so critical to understand how we think and behave online. Acclaimed behavioural economist Shlomo Benartzi has teamed up with science writer Jonah Lehrer to reveal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/">The Smarter Screen : What Your Business Can Learn from the Way Consumers Think Online &#8211; Shlomo Benartzi, Jonah Lehrer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The typical office worker now spends the majority of their waking hours staring at a screen. In the 21st century, every business is a digital business, which is why it&#8217;s so critical to understand how we think and behave online.    </p>
<p>                    Acclaimed behavioural economist Shlomo Benartzi has teamed up with science writer Jonah Lehrer to reveal a toolkit of cues and nudges for the digital age. Using provocative case-studies and engaging reader exercises, Benartzi shows how businesses can update their nudges to help consumers make better decisions on screens. Up-to-the-minute research will help optimise your business&#8217;s online presence, from designing a webshop that helps your customers find what they are looking for, to laying out your website so that it both attracts and holds attention.    </p>
<p>                    This book will help you transform the challenges of the digital world into powerful new opportunities that will drive your success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-smarter-screen-what-your-business-can-learn-from-the-way-consumers-think-online-shlomo-benartzi-jonah-lehrer-abridged/">The Smarter Screen : What Your Business Can Learn from the Way Consumers Think Online &#8211; Shlomo Benartzi, Jonah Lehrer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Never Lose A Customer Again &#8211; Joey Coleman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/never-lose-a-customer-again-joey-coleman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/never-lose-a-customer-again-joey-coleman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Award-winning speaker and business consultant Joey Coleman teaches audiences and companies all over the world how to turn a one-time purchaser into a lifelong customer. Coleman&#8217;s theory of building customer loyalty isn&#8217;t about focusing on marketing or closing the sale: It&#8217;s about the First 100 Days(R) after the sale and the interactions the customer experiences. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-lose-a-customer-again-joey-coleman-abridged/">Never Lose A Customer Again &#8211; Joey Coleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Award-winning speaker and business consultant Joey Coleman teaches audiences and companies all over the world how to turn a one-time purchaser into a lifelong customer.     </p>
<p>                    Coleman&#8217;s theory of building customer loyalty isn&#8217;t about focusing on marketing or closing the sale: It&#8217;s about the First 100 Days(R) after the sale and the interactions the customer experiences.     </p>
<p>                    While new customers experience joy, euphoria, and excitement, these feelings quickly shift to fear, doubt, and uncertainty as buyer&#8217;s remorse sets in. Across all industries, somewhere between 20%-70% of newly acquired customers will stop doing business with a company with the first 100 days of being a new customer because they feel neglected in the early stages of customer onboarding.     </p>
<p>                    In Never Lose a Customer Again, Coleman offers a philosophy and methodology for dramatically increasing customer retention and as a result, the bottom line. He identifies eight distinct emotional phases customers go through in the 100 days following a purchase. From an impulse buy at Starbucks to the thoughtful purchase of a first house, all customers have the potential to experience the eight phases of the customer journey. If you can understand and anticipate the customers&#8217; emotions, you can apply a myriad of tools and techniques &#8212; in-person, email, phone, mail, video, and presents &#8212; to cement a long and valuable relationship.     </p>
<p>                    Coleman&#8217;s system is presented through research and case studies showing how best-in-class companies create remarkable customer experiences at each step in the customer lifecycle.     </p>
<p>                     In the Acclimate stage, customers need you to hold their hand and over-explain how to use your product or service. They&#8217;re often too embarrassed to admit they&#8217;re confused. Take a cue from Canadian software company PolicyMedical and their challenge of getting non-technical users to undergo a complex installation and implementation process. They turned a series of project spreadsheets and installation manuals into a beautiful puzzle customers could assemble after completing each milestone.     </p>
<p>                     In the Adopt stage, customers should be welcomed to the highest tier of tribal membership with both public and private recognitions. For instance, Sephora&#8217;s VIB Rogue member welcome gift provides a metallic membership card (private recognition) and a members-only shade of lipstick (for public display).     </p>
<p>                     In the final stage, Advocate, loyal customers and raving fans are primed to provide powerful referrals. That&#8217;s how elite entrepreneurial event MastermindTalks continues to sell-out their conference year after year &#8211; with zero dollars spent on marketing. By surprising their loyal fans with amazing referral bonuses (an all-expenses paid safari?!) they guarantee their community will keep providing perfect referrals.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on nearly two decades of consulting and keynoting, Coleman provides strategies and systems to increase customer loyalty. Applicable to companies in any industry and of any size (whether measured in employee count, revenue, or total number of customers), implementing his methods regularly leads to an increase in profits of 25-100%.     </p>
<p>                    Working with well-known clients like Hyatt Hotels, Zappos, and NASA, as well as mom-and-pop shops and solo entrepreneurs around the world, Coleman&#8217;s customer retention system has produced incredible results in dozens of industries.     </p>
<p>                    His approach to creating remarkable customer experiences requires minimal financial investment and will be fun for owners, employees, and teams to implement. This book is required reading for business owners, CEOs, and managers &#8211; as well as sales and marketing teams, account managers, and customer service representatives looking for easy to implement action steps that result in lasting change, increased profits, and lifelong customer retention.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/never-lose-a-customer-again-joey-coleman-abridged/">Never Lose A Customer Again &#8211; Joey Coleman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Brands Grow : What Marketers Don&#8217;t Know &#8211; Byron Sharp (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-brands-grow-what-marketers-dont-know-byron-sharp-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-brands-grow-what-marketers-dont-know-byron-sharp-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This book provides evidence-based answers to the key questions asked by marketers every day. Tackling issues such as how brands grow, how advertising really works, what price promotions really do and how loyalty programs really affect loyalty, How Brands Grow presents decades of research in a style that is written for marketing professionals to grow [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-brands-grow-what-marketers-dont-know-byron-sharp-abridged/">How Brands Grow : What Marketers Don&#8217;t Know &#8211; Byron Sharp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This book provides evidence-based answers to the key questions asked by marketers every day. Tackling issues such as how brands grow, how advertising really works, what price promotions really do and how loyalty programs really affect loyalty, How Brands Grow presents decades of research in a style that is written for marketing professionals to grow their brands. It is the first book to present these laws in context and to explore their meaning and application.<br />
                    The most distinctive element to this book is that the laws presented are tried and tested; they have been found to hold over varied conditions, time and countries. This is contra to most marketing texts and indeed, much information provides evidence that much modern marketing theory is far from soundly based.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-brands-grow-what-marketers-dont-know-byron-sharp-abridged/">How Brands Grow : What Marketers Don&#8217;t Know &#8211; Byron Sharp (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Contagious : Why Things Catch on &#8211; Jonah Berger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller that explains why certain products and ideas become popular. &#8220;Jonah Berger knows more about what makes information &#8216;go viral&#8217; than anyone in the world.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel Gilbert, author of the bestseller Stumbling on Happiness What makes things popular? If you said advertising, think again. People don&#8217;t listen to advertisements, they listen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/">Contagious : Why Things Catch on &#8211; Jonah Berger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times bestseller that explains why certain products and ideas become popular.      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Jonah Berger knows more about what makes information &#8216;go viral&#8217; than anyone in the world.&#8221; &#8211;Daniel Gilbert, author of the bestseller Stumbling on Happiness     </p>
<p>                    What makes things popular? If you said advertising, think again. People don&#8217;t listen to advertisements, they listen to their peers. But why do people talk about certain products and ideas more than others? Why are some stories and rumors more infectious? And what makes online content go viral?     </p>
<p>                    Wharton marketing professor Jonah Berger has spent the last decade answering these questions. He&#8217;s studied why New York Times articles make the paper&#8217;s own Most E-mailed list, why products get word of mouth, and how social influence shapes everything from the cars we buy to the clothes we wear to the names we give our children.     </p>
<p>                    In Contagious, Berger reveals the secret science behind word-of-mouth and social transmission. Discover how six basic principles drive all sorts of things to become contagious, from consumer products and policy initiatives to workplace rumors and YouTube videos. Learn how a luxury steakhouse found popularity through the lowly cheesesteak, why anti-drug commercials might have actually increased drug use, and why more than 200 million consumers shared a video about one of the most boring products there is: a blender.     </p>
<p>                    Contagious provides specific, actionable techniques for helping information spread&#8211;for designing messages, advertisements, and content that people will share. Whether you&#8217;re a manager at a big company, a small business owner trying to boost awareness, a politician running for office, or a health official trying to get the word out, Contagious will show you how to make your product or idea catch on.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/contagious-why-things-catch-on-jonah-berger-abridged/">Contagious : Why Things Catch on &#8211; Jonah Berger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Focus : The Future of Your Company Depends on It &#8211; Al Ries (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/focus-the-future-of-your-company-depends-on-it-al-ries-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/focus-the-future-of-your-company-depends-on-it-al-ries-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s the secret to a company&#8217;s continued growth and prosperity? Internationally known marketing expert Al Ries has the answer: focus. His commonsense approach to business management is founded on the premise that long-lasting success depends on focusing on core products and eschewing the temptation to diversify into unrelated enterprises. Using real-world examples, Ries shows that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/focus-the-future-of-your-company-depends-on-it-al-ries-abridged/">Focus : The Future of Your Company Depends on It &#8211; Al Ries (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What&#8217;s the secret to a company&#8217;s continued growth and prosperity? Internationally known marketing expert Al Ries has the answer: focus. His commonsense approach to business management is founded on the premise that long-lasting success depends on focusing on core products and eschewing the temptation to diversify into unrelated enterprises.    </p>
<p>                    Using real-world examples, Ries shows that in industry after industry, it is the companies that resist diversification, and focus instead on owning a category in consumers&#8217; minds, that dominate their markets. He offers solid guidance on how to get focused and how to stay focused, laying out a workable blueprint for any company&#8217;s evolution that will increase market share and shareholder value while ensuring future success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/focus-the-future-of-your-company-depends-on-it-al-ries-abridged/">Focus : The Future of Your Company Depends on It &#8211; Al Ries (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Gen Z Frequency : How Brands Tune In and Build Credibility &#8211; Gregg L. Witt, Derek E. Baird (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-gen-z-frequency-how-brands-tune-in-and-build-credibility-gregg-l-witt-derek-e-baird-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-gen-z-frequency-how-brands-tune-in-and-build-credibility-gregg-l-witt-derek-e-baird-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Generation Z, ranging from tweens to young adults, has enormous spending power; yet it is one of the most challenging generational cohorts for brands to reach. It is projected to be the largest consumer demographic in history, driving a forecast from the HRC Retail Advisory of 40% of all US consumer spending, and another 40% [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gen-z-frequency-how-brands-tune-in-and-build-credibility-gregg-l-witt-derek-e-baird-abridged/">The Gen Z Frequency : How Brands Tune In and Build Credibility &#8211; Gregg L. Witt, Derek E. Baird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Generation Z, ranging from tweens to young adults, has enormous spending power; yet it is one of the most challenging generational cohorts for brands to reach. It is projected to be the largest consumer demographic in history, driving a forecast from the HRC Retail Advisory of 40% of all US consumer spending, and another 40% of all consumers in the US, Europe and BRIC by 2020 (Brazil, Russia, India, China), according to other sources. Embodying an unrelenting relationship with information and mobile technology from a young age, Generation Z&#8217;s ecosystem is infinitely more complex and varied than any generation before. Staying tuned-in to this demographic&#8217;s impatience, confidence and constantly evolving trends can be daunting for any marketer trying to keep up.    </p>
<p>                    The Gen Z Frequency offers a comprehensive guide for any brand or organization trying to reach this demographic, covering fundamental truths, content creation, engagement strategies and tactics such as social media, experiential, emerging technologies, and much more. It is woven with fascinating case studies and real-world stories from the trenches, plus key insights from leading youth  brands and Gen Z themselves. Whether you are new to marketing or a seasoned expert, The Gen Z Frequency is the ultimate resource for tuning in to Generation Z.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-gen-z-frequency-how-brands-tune-in-and-build-credibility-gregg-l-witt-derek-e-baird-abridged/">The Gen Z Frequency : How Brands Tune In and Build Credibility &#8211; Gregg L. Witt, Derek E. Baird (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Data : The Tiny Clues That Uncover Huge Trends &#8211; Martin Lindstrom Company (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/small-data-the-tiny-clues-that-uncover-huge-trends-martin-lindstrom-company-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/small-data-the-tiny-clues-that-uncover-huge-trends-martin-lindstrom-company-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller named one of the &#8220;Most Important Books of 2016&#8221; by Inc, and a Forbes 2016 &#8220;Must Read Business Book&#8221; &#8216;If you love &#8216;Bones&#8217; and &#8216;CSI&#8217;, this book is your kind of candy&#8217; Paco Underhill, author of Why We Buy &#8216;Martin&#8217;s best book to date. A personal, intuitive, powerful way to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-data-the-tiny-clues-that-uncover-huge-trends-martin-lindstrom-company-abridged/">Small Data : The Tiny Clues That Uncover Huge Trends &#8211; Martin Lindstrom Company (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller named one of the &#8220;Most Important Books of 2016&#8221; by Inc, and a Forbes 2016 &#8220;Must Read Business Book&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you love &#8216;Bones&#8217; and &#8216;CSI&#8217;, this book is your kind of candy&#8217; Paco Underhill, author of Why We Buy    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Martin&#8217;s best book to date. A personal, intuitive, powerful way to look at making an impact with your work&#8217; Seth Godin, author of Purple Cow    </p>
<p>                    Martin Lindstrom, one of Time Magazine&#8217;s 100 Most Influential People in The World and a modern-day Sherlock Holmes, harnesses the power of &#8220;small data&#8221; in his quest to discover the next big thing.    </p>
<p>                    In an era where many believe Big Data has rendered human perception and observation &#8216;old-school&#8217; or passe, Martin Lindstrom shows that mining and matching technological data with up-close psychological insight creates the ultimate snapshot of who we really are and what we really want. He works like a modern-day Sherlock Holmes, accumulating small clues &#8211; the progressively weaker handshakes of Millenials, a notable global decrease in the use of facial powder, a change in how younger consumers approach eating ice cream cones &#8211; to help solve a stunningly diverse array of challenges. In Switzerland, a stuffed teddy bear in a teenage girl&#8217;s bedroom helped revolutionise 1,000 stores &#8211; spread across twenty countries &#8211; for one of Europe&#8217;s largest fashion retailers. In Dubai, a distinctive bracelet strung with pearls helped Jenny Craig offset its declining membership in the United States and increase loyalty by 159% in only one year. In China, the look of a car dashboard led to the design of the iRobot, or Roomba, floor cleaner &#8211; a great success story.    </p>
<p>                    SMALL DATA combines armchair travel with forensic psychology in an interlocking series of international clue-gathering detective stories. It shows Lindstrom using his proprietary CLUES Framework &#8211; where big data is merely one part of the overall puzzle &#8211; to get radically close to consumers and come up with the counter-intuitive insights that have in some cases helped transform entire industries.     </p>
<p>                    SMALL DATA presents a rare behind-the-scenes look at what it takes to create global brands, and reveals surprising and counter-intuitive truths about what connects us all as humans.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-data-the-tiny-clues-that-uncover-huge-trends-martin-lindstrom-company-abridged/">Small Data : The Tiny Clues That Uncover Huge Trends &#8211; Martin Lindstrom Company (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Automatic Customer : Creating a Subscription Business in Any Industry &#8211; John Warrillow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-automatic-customer-creating-a-subscription-business-in-any-industry-john-warrillow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-automatic-customer-creating-a-subscription-business-in-any-industry-john-warrillow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Automatic Customer, John Warrillow provides the essential blueprint for turning your customers into subscribers The lifeblood of your business is repeat customers. But customers can be fickle, markets shift and competitors are ruthless. So how do you ensure a steady flow of business? The secret &#8211; no matter what industry you&#8217;re in &#8211; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-automatic-customer-creating-a-subscription-business-in-any-industry-john-warrillow-abridged/">The Automatic Customer : Creating a Subscription Business in Any Industry &#8211; John Warrillow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Automatic Customer, John Warrillow provides the essential blueprint for turning your customers into subscribers    </p>
<p>                    The lifeblood of your business is repeat customers. But customers can be fickle, markets shift and competitors are ruthless. So how do you ensure a steady flow of business? The secret &#8211; no matter what industry you&#8217;re in &#8211; is finding and keeping automatic customers.    </p>
<p>                    These days virtually anything you need can come through a subscription. Far beyond Spotify and Netflix, companies in nearly any industry, from home contractors to florists, can build subscriptions into their business.    </p>
<p>                    Subscription is the key to increasing cash flow, igniting growth and boosting the value of your company. Whether you want to transform your entire business into a recurring revenue engine or just pick up an extra 5 per cent of sales growth, The Automatic Customer will be your secret weapon.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Read, apply and watch your bank deposits grow every month&#8217;  Chris Guillebeau, bestselling author of The $100 Startup    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you have a business, or are thinking about starting one, this book will be the best investment you&#8217;ve ever made&#8217;  Bo Burlingham, editor-at-large of Inc. and author of Small Giants and Finish Big    </p>
<p>                    John Warrillow, the author of Built to Sell, is the founder of The Value Builder System (TM) where advisors help company owners increase the value of their business. Previously, he founded Warrillow &#038; Co., a subscription-based research business dedicated to helping Fortune 500 companies market to small business owners. A sought-after speaker and popular Inc.com columnist, he lives in Toronto.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-automatic-customer-creating-a-subscription-business-in-any-industry-john-warrillow-abridged/">The Automatic Customer : Creating a Subscription Business in Any Industry &#8211; John Warrillow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Superforecasting : The Art and Science of Prediction &#8211; Philip E. Tetlock, Dan Gardner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognitivism, Cognitive Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY THE ECONOMIST &#8220;The most important book on decision making since Daniel Kahneman&#8217;s Thinking, Fast and Slow.&#8221;&#8211;Jason Zweig, The Wall Street Journal Everyone would benefit from seeing further into the future, whether buying stocks, crafting policy, launching a new product, or [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/">Superforecasting : The Art and Science of Prediction &#8211; Philip E. Tetlock, Dan Gardner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY THE ECONOMIST      </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The most important book on decision making since Daniel Kahneman&#8217;s Thinking, Fast and Slow.&#8221;&#8211;Jason Zweig, The Wall Street Journal     </p>
<p>                     Everyone would benefit from seeing further into the future, whether buying stocks, crafting policy, launching a new product, or simply planning the week&#8217;s meals. Unfortunately, people tend to be terrible forecasters. As Wharton professor Philip Tetlock showed in a landmark 2005 study, even experts&#8217; predictions are only slightly better than chance. However, an important and underreported conclusion of that study was that some experts do have real foresight, and Tetlock has spent the past decade trying to figure out why. What makes some people so good? And can this talent be taught?     </p>
<p>                     In Superforecasting, Tetlock and coauthor Dan Gardner offer a masterwork on prediction, drawing on decades of research and the results of a massive, government-funded forecasting tournament. The Good Judgment Project involves tens of thousands of ordinary people&#8211;including a Brooklyn filmmaker, a retired pipe installer, and a former ballroom dancer&#8211;who set out to forecast global events. Some of the volunteers have turned out to be astonishingly good. They&#8217;ve beaten other benchmarks, competitors, and prediction markets. They&#8217;ve even beaten the collective judgment of intelligence analysts with access to classified information. They are superforecasters.     </p>
<p>                     In this groundbreaking and accessible book, Tetlock and Gardner show us how we can learn from this elite group. Weaving together stories of forecasting successes (the raid on Osama bin Laden&#8217;s compound) and failures (the Bay of Pigs) and interviews with a range of high-level decision makers, from David Petraeus to Robert Rubin, they show that good forecasting doesn&#8217;t require powerful computers or arcane methods. It involves gathering evidence from a variety of sources, thinking probabilistically, working in teams, keeping score, and being willing to admit error and change course.     </p>
<p>                    Superforecasting offers the first demonstrably effective way to improve our ability to predict the future&#8211;whether in business, finance, politics, international affairs, or daily life&#8211;and is destined to become a modern classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/superforecasting-the-art-and-science-of-prediction-philip-e-tetlock-dan-gardner-abridged/">Superforecasting : The Art and Science of Prediction &#8211; Philip E. Tetlock, Dan Gardner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
