<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Sex &amp; Sexuality, Sex Manuals Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/sex-sexuality-sex-manuals/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/sex-sexuality-sex-manuals/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Sex &amp; Sexuality, Sex Manuals Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/sex-sexuality-sex-manuals/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dating Sucks, But You Don&#8217;t : The Modern Guy&#8217;s Guide to Total Confidence, Romantic Connection, and Finding the Perfect Partner &#8211; Connell Barrett</title>
		<link>/dating-sucks-but-you-dont-the-modern-guys-guide-to-total-confidence-romantic-connection-and-finding-the-perfect-partner-connell-barrett/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dating-sucks-but-you-dont-the-modern-guys-guide-to-total-confidence-romantic-connection-and-finding-the-perfect-partner-connell-barrett/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From renowned international dating coach comes an essential, must-have dating guide for men looking to gain confidence and find lasting love in the #MeToo era.Rejection. Ghosting. Not knowing how to talk to women. For many men, dating just sucks. But it doesn&#8217;t have to. There&#8217;s a simple, yet powerful, way to gain instant confidence and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dating-sucks-but-you-dont-the-modern-guys-guide-to-total-confidence-romantic-connection-and-finding-the-perfect-partner-connell-barrett/">Dating Sucks, But You Don&#8217;t : The Modern Guy&#8217;s Guide to Total Confidence, Romantic Connection, and Finding the Perfect Partner &#8211; Connell Barrett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From renowned international dating coach comes an essential, must-have dating guide for men looking to gain confidence and find lasting love in the #MeToo era.Rejection. Ghosting. Not knowing how to talk to women. For many men, dating just sucks. But it doesn&#8217;t have to. There&#8217;s a simple, yet powerful, way to gain instant confidence and attract a great girlfriend: Be authentic. Whether you want to confidently approach women, get quality matches on dating apps, or learn how to avoid the &#8220;friend zone,&#8221; Dating Sucks, but You Don&#8217;t is your step-by-step blueprint for landing your soulmate. Using the power of &#8220;radical authenticity,&#8221; you&#8217;ll unlock your most awesome self and learn how to: -Be magnetic as you&#8230;even if you&#8217;re not rich, tall, or great-looking -Always know what to say to ignite chemistry -Get dates and connect with great women without using creepy &#8220;pickup artist&#8221; tricks -Conquer fear and anxiety and confidently approach women (in a way they love) -Get great matches and dates on Tinder, Bumble, Match, Hinge, or any other dating app -Be a true gentleman of the #MeToo era who respects women and understands the boundaries surrounding consent -Create a healthy, supportive relationship with someone who loves you for you You definitely don&#8217;t suck. And when you have total self-confidence and great results, neither does dating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dating-sucks-but-you-dont-the-modern-guys-guide-to-total-confidence-romantic-connection-and-finding-the-perfect-partner-connell-barrett/">Dating Sucks, But You Don&#8217;t : The Modern Guy&#8217;s Guide to Total Confidence, Romantic Connection, and Finding the Perfect Partner &#8211; Connell Barrett</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sex Guide : This Book Includes: (1) Kama Sutra for Beginners (2) How to Talk Dirty (3) Sex Positions &#8211; Joshua Matthew</title>
		<link>/sex-guide-this-book-includes-1-kama-sutra-for-beginners-2-how-to-talk-dirty-3-sex-positions-joshua-matthew/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sex-guide-this-book-includes-1-kama-sutra-for-beginners-2-how-to-talk-dirty-3-sex-positions-joshua-matthew/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SEX GUIDE: 3 BOOKS IN 1 1. KAMA SUTRA FOR BEGINNERS: 30 Best Sex Positions with Illustrations, Dirty Talk Examples and Sex Tips for Couples Do you feel passionate, inspired, excited, creative, enthusiastic, attracted or aroused? Does all of these emotions produce sensations and cravings that stoke your internal fires? The physical act of sex [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-guide-this-book-includes-1-kama-sutra-for-beginners-2-how-to-talk-dirty-3-sex-positions-joshua-matthew/">Sex Guide : This Book Includes: (1) Kama Sutra for Beginners (2) How to Talk Dirty (3) Sex Positions &#8211; Joshua Matthew</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SEX GUIDE: 3 BOOKS IN 1    </p>
<p>                    1. KAMA SUTRA FOR BEGINNERS:     </p>
<p>                    30 Best Sex Positions with Illustrations, Dirty Talk Examples and Sex Tips for Couples    </p>
<p>                    Do you feel passionate, inspired, excited, creative, enthusiastic, attracted or aroused?    </p>
<p>                    Does all of these emotions produce sensations and cravings that stoke your internal fires?    </p>
<p>                    The physical act of sex is actually an outward expression of these forces. Sexual energy is a primal energy that continually creates.    </p>
<p>                    The Kama Sutra was developed to focus and heighten this physical expression to create and sustain this sexual energy in a creative manner.    </p>
<p>                    With this in mind, Kama Sutra for Beginners focuses on the physical aspects of the ancient book that will elevate any couples lovemaking to new heights. This book explores and details the sexual positions of the Kama Sutra in simple language and provides a detailed description of each position with a modern twist.    </p>
<p>                    2. HOW TO TALK DIRTY:     </p>
<p>                    263 Best Dirty Talk Examples and Tips to Drive Your Partner Absolutely Wild    </p>
<p>                    Do you find yourself wondering how to spice up or rekindle your sex life?    </p>
<p>                    Want to make sex more exciting, express your inner desires comfortably, or remove that awkward silence?    </p>
<p>                    Or simply want to find a clever way to connect with your partner intimately when you&#8217;re apart?    </p>
<p>                    Regardless of what level of dirty talking you and/or your partner are at &#8211; this book can help to increase understanding of the role dirty talk plays, get into the basics, and improvise from examples. Here are some things you&#8217;ll find:     </p>
<p>                    getting you and your partner into dirty talktips on how to start dirty talking (including a cheat sheet)tips on sexting, dirty talking online, and roleplayingover 200+ examples for subtle to hardcore dirty talk    </p>
<p>                    There will also be elaborate explanations as to how you&#8217;ll gain mastery into the art of dirty talk.    </p>
<p>                    Apply directly what&#8217;s in the book, or be guided to creatively adapt from the examples provided and assimilate it into your own vocabulary &#8211; making &#8220;dirty talk&#8221; tailored to suit your personality.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Dirty talk&#8221; is in fact never dirty, but incredibly sexy. Use this book to gain better sexual self-awareness, heightened confidence and foster a better relationship via sexual communications.    </p>
<p>                    3. SEX POSITIONS    </p>
<p>                    Top 50 Crazy and Adventurous Sex Positions With Illustrations    </p>
<p>                    Why on earth, after all these years, is the missionary position still popular? There is nothing more fantastic, fun, joy inductive, creative, life affirming, celebrative, crazy, bonding and playful for adventuresome adults, than trying out a range of sexual positions, even crazy, unique ones.    </p>
<p>                    Some are too athletic for most. Some work for senior citizens and mobility impaired. Some will leave you in hysterical giggling. Others will take you where you&#8217;ve probably never been before! A few play with dominance and control by one partner or the other. Many are gender and preference fluid.    </p>
<p>                    Some may leave you with a perplexed raise of the eyebrows, but the range of positions represented here are sure to inspire and reward anyone who is open to trying something new and advanced, whether radically different or just slightly experimental.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-guide-this-book-includes-1-kama-sutra-for-beginners-2-how-to-talk-dirty-3-sex-positions-joshua-matthew/">Sex Guide : This Book Includes: (1) Kama Sutra for Beginners (2) How to Talk Dirty (3) Sex Positions &#8211; Joshua Matthew</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sex and the Citadel : Intimate Life in a Changing Arab World &#8211; Shereen El Feki (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sex-and-the-citadel-intimate-life-in-a-changing-arab-world-shereen-el-feki-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Story & History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Islamic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sex-and-the-citadel-intimate-life-in-a-changing-arab-world-shereen-el-feki-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Kirkus Reviews Best Book of the Year As the &#8220;Arab Spring&#8221; and its aftermath sweep streets and squares, parliaments and presidential palaces of the Middle East, Shereen El Feki&#8211;an award-winning Canadian-Egyptian journalist&#8211;has been looking at unrest a little closer to home: in the sexual lives of Arab men and women. The result is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-and-the-citadel-intimate-life-in-a-changing-arab-world-shereen-el-feki-abridged/">Sex and the Citadel : Intimate Life in a Changing Arab World &#8211; Shereen El Feki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Kirkus Reviews Best Book of the Year     </p>
<p>                    As the &#8220;Arab Spring&#8221; and its aftermath sweep streets and squares, parliaments and presidential palaces of the Middle East, Shereen El Feki&#8211;an award-winning Canadian-Egyptian journalist&#8211;has been looking at unrest a little closer to home: in the sexual lives of Arab men and women. The result is an informative, insightful, and engaging account of this sensitive and still largely secret aspect of Arab society.     </p>
<p>                     Sexual attitudes and behaviors are shaped by politics and economics, religion and tradition, gender and generations&#8211;not only a reflection of the conditions that led to the uprisings, but also a measure of hard-won reforms in the years to come. Highly personal, rich with original research and remarkable stories, Sex and the Citadel gives us unprecedented and timely insight into a part of the world that is changing before our eyes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-and-the-citadel-intimate-life-in-a-changing-arab-world-shereen-el-feki-abridged/">Sex and the Citadel : Intimate Life in a Changing Arab World &#8211; Shereen El Feki (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Curious History of Dating : From Jane Austen to Tinder &#8211; Nichi Hodgson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-curious-history-of-dating-from-jane-austen-to-tinder-nichi-hodgson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humour Collections & Anthologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-curious-history-of-dating-from-jane-austen-to-tinder-nichi-hodgson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN EMPHATICALLY FEMINIST HISTORY OF DATING &#8216;A new approach to romance&#8230; The heroines of Regency novels could teach today&#8217;s young women a trick or two&#8217; Sunday Times What if Mr Darcy had simply been able to swipe right? &#8216;This book was a real education for me. It&#8217;s like a Lonely Planet guidebook to dating.&#8217; Gilo [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-curious-history-of-dating-from-jane-austen-to-tinder-nichi-hodgson-abridged/">The Curious History of Dating : From Jane Austen to Tinder &#8211; Nichi Hodgson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN EMPHATICALLY FEMINIST HISTORY OF DATING    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A new approach to romance&#8230; The heroines of Regency novels could teach today&#8217;s young women a trick or two&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    What if Mr Darcy had simply been able to swipe right?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book was a real education for me. It&#8217;s like a Lonely Planet guidebook to dating.&#8217;<br />
                    Gilo    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Lessons to learn for committed singletons and happily married alike, and everyone in between.&#8217;<br />
                    Anon    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I loved it.&#8217;<br />
                    Adele Taylor    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I found it hard to put down.&#8217;<br />
                    richie666    </p>
<p>                    Dating has never been easy. The road to true love has always been rutted with heartbreak, but do we have it any easier today?     </p>
<p>                    How did Victorians &#8216;come out&#8217;? How did love blossom in war-torn Europe? And why did 80s video-dating never take off?    </p>
<p>                    Bursting with little-known facts and tantalizing tales of lovelorn men and besotted women, Nichi Hodgson&#8217;s intriguing history of amorous relationships, from enamoured Georgians to frenziedly swiping millennials (and everyone in between) may leave you grateful that you live &#8211; and love &#8211; today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-curious-history-of-dating-from-jane-austen-to-tinder-nichi-hodgson-abridged/">The Curious History of Dating : From Jane Austen to Tinder &#8211; Nichi Hodgson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Vagina Bible : The vulva and the vagina &#8211; separating the myth from the medicine &#8211; Dr. Jennifer Gunter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-vagina-bible-the-vulva-and-the-vagina-separating-the-myth-from-the-medicine-dr-jennifer-gunter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-vagina-bible-the-vulva-and-the-vagina-separating-the-myth-from-the-medicine-dr-jennifer-gunter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Does eating sugar cause yeast infections? Does pubic hair have a function? Should you have a vulvovaginal care regimen? Will your vagina shrivel up if you go without sex? What&#8217;s the truth about the HPV vaccine? So many important questions, so much convincing, confusing, contradictory misinformation! In this age of click bait, pseudoscience, and celebrity-endorsed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-vagina-bible-the-vulva-and-the-vagina-separating-the-myth-from-the-medicine-dr-jennifer-gunter-abridged/">The Vagina Bible : The vulva and the vagina &#8211; separating the myth from the medicine &#8211; Dr. Jennifer Gunter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Does eating sugar cause yeast infections? Does pubic hair have a function?<br />
                    Should you have a vulvovaginal care regimen?<br />
                    Will your vagina shrivel up if you go without sex?<br />
                    What&#8217;s the truth about the HPV vaccine?    </p>
<p>                    So many important questions, so much convincing, confusing, contradictory misinformation! In this age of click bait, pseudoscience, and celebrity-endorsed products, it&#8217;s easy to be overwhelmed-whether it&#8217;s websites, advice from well-meaning friends, uneducated partners, and even healthcare providers. So how do you separate facts from fiction? Obstetrician Jen Gunter, an expert on women&#8217;s health-and the internet&#8217;s most popular go-to doc-comes to the rescue with a book that debunks the myths and educates and empowers women. From reproductive health to the impact of antibiotics and probiotics, and the latest trends, including vaginal steaming, vaginal marijuana products, and jade eggs, Gunter takes us on a factual, fun-filled journey.     </p>
<p>                    Discover the truth about:    </p>
<p>                    *         The vaginal microbiome<br />
                    *         Genital hygiene, lubricants, and hormone myths and fallacies<br />
                    *         How diet impacts vaginal health<br />
                    *         Stem cells and the vagina<br />
                    *         Cosmetic vaginal surgery<br />
                    *         What changes to expect during pregnancy, after childbirth, and through menopause<br />
                    *         How medicine fails women by dismissing symptoms    </p>
<p>                    Plus:<br />
                    *         Thongs vs. lace: the best underwear for vaginal health<br />
                    *         How to select a tampon<br />
                    *         The full glory of the clitoris and the myth of the G Spot    </p>
<p>                    &#8230; And so much more. Whether you&#8217;re a twenty-six-year-old worried that her labia are &#8216;uncool&#8217; or a sixty-six-year-old dealing with painful sex, this comprehensive guide is sure to become a lifelong trusted resource.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-vagina-bible-the-vulva-and-the-vagina-separating-the-myth-from-the-medicine-dr-jennifer-gunter-abridged/">The Vagina Bible : The vulva and the vagina &#8211; separating the myth from the medicine &#8211; Dr. Jennifer Gunter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Truth : An Uncomfortable Book about Relationships &#8211; Neil Strauss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-truth-an-uncomfortable-book-about-relationships-neil-strauss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-truth-an-uncomfortable-book-about-relationships-neil-strauss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-an-uncomfortable-book-about-relationships-neil-strauss-abridged/">The Truth : An Uncomfortable Book about Relationships &#8211; Neil Strauss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-truth-an-uncomfortable-book-about-relationships-neil-strauss-abridged/">The Truth : An Uncomfortable Book about Relationships &#8211; Neil Strauss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>She Comes First &#8211; Ian PhD. Kerner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/she-comes-first-ian-phd-kerner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Birth Control, Contraception, Family Planning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/she-comes-first-ian-phd-kerner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As women everywhere will attest, when it comes to understanding female sexuality, most guys know more about what&#8217;s under the hood of a car than under the hood of a clitoris. And while it seems that men have struggled valiantly since the dawn of time to find ways to reliably elicit the female orgasm, rare [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-comes-first-ian-phd-kerner-abridged/">She Comes First &#8211; Ian PhD. Kerner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As women everywhere will attest, when it comes to understanding female sexuality, most guys know more about what&#8217;s under the hood of a car than under the hood of a clitoris. And while it seems that men have struggled valiantly since the dawn of time to find ways to reliably elicit the female orgasm, rare is the guy who has the modesty to ask: &#8220;What do I do?&#8221; Ironically, the answer has always been right there on the tip of his tongue.  Welcome to the world of &#8220;She Comes First, &#8221; where the mystery of female satisfaction is solved and the tongue is proven mightier than the sword. According to Ian Kerner, clinical sexologist and evangelist of the female orgasm, oral sex has long been deemed an optional aspect of foreplay, but, in fact, it&#8217;s coreplay &#8212; simply the best way for leading a woman through the entire process of sexual response.  Fun, informative, and easy to read, &#8220;She Comes First&#8221; is a virtual encyclopedia of female pleasure, detailing dozens of tried-and-true techniques for consistently satisfying a woman and illustrated step-by-step instructions to ensure success. These simple methods represent a new era in sexual intimacy, one in which the exchange of pleasure occurs on a level playing field and fulfillment is mutual.  &#8220;She Comes First&#8221; exuberantly offers a fresh new sexual philosophy that inspires every man to make a mantra of Rhett Butler&#8217;s infamous line to Scarlett O&#8217;Hara, &#8220;You should be kissed, and often, and by someone who knows how.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-comes-first-ian-phd-kerner-abridged/">She Comes First &#8211; Ian PhD. Kerner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Come as You Are: Revised and Updated : The Surprising New Science That Will Transform Your Sex Life &#8211; Emily Nagoski (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/come-as-you-are-revised-and-updated-the-surprising-new-science-that-will-transform-your-sex-life-emily-nagoski-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/come-as-you-are-revised-and-updated-the-surprising-new-science-that-will-transform-your-sex-life-emily-nagoski-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revised and updated edition of Emily Nagoski&#8217;s game-changing New York Times bestseller Come As You Are, featuring new information and research on mindfulness, desire, and pleasure that will radically transform your sex life. For much of the 20th and 21st centuries, women&#8217;s sexuality was an uncharted territory in science, studied far less frequently&#8211;and far [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/come-as-you-are-revised-and-updated-the-surprising-new-science-that-will-transform-your-sex-life-emily-nagoski-abridged/">Come as You Are: Revised and Updated : The Surprising New Science That Will Transform Your Sex Life &#8211; Emily Nagoski (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revised and updated edition of Emily Nagoski&#8217;s game-changing New York Times bestseller Come As You Are, featuring new information and research on mindfulness, desire, and pleasure that will radically transform your sex life.     </p>
<p>                    For much of the 20th and 21st centuries, women&#8217;s sexuality was an uncharted territory in science, studied far less frequently&#8211;and far less seriously&#8211;than its male counterpart.     </p>
<p>                    That is, until Emily Nagoski&#8217;s Come As You Are, which used groundbreaking science and research to prove that the most important factor in creating and sustaining a sex life filled with confidence and joy is not what the parts are or how they&#8217;re organized but how you feel about them. In the years since the book&#8217;s initial publication, countless women have learned through Nagoski&#8217;s accessible and informative guide that things like stress, mood, trust, and body image are not peripheral factors in a woman&#8217;s sexual wellbeing; they are central to it&#8211;and that even if you don&#8217;t always feel like it, you are already sexually whole by just being yourself. This revised and updated edition continues that mission with new information and advanced research, demystifying and decoding the science of sex so that everyone can create a better sex life and discover more pleasure than you ever thought possible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/come-as-you-are-revised-and-updated-the-surprising-new-science-that-will-transform-your-sex-life-emily-nagoski-abridged/">Come as You Are: Revised and Updated : The Surprising New Science That Will Transform Your Sex Life &#8211; Emily Nagoski (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Invisible Orientation : An Introduction to Asexuality * Next Generation Indie Book Awards Winner in LGBT * &#8211; Julie Sondra Decker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-invisible-orientation-an-introduction-to-asexuality-next-generation-indie-book-awards-winner-in-lgbt-julie-sondra-decker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay & Lesbian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gay Studies (Gay Men)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-invisible-orientation-an-introduction-to-asexuality-next-generation-indie-book-awards-winner-in-lgbt-julie-sondra-decker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Next Generation Indie Book Awards Winner in LGBT . &#8220;An important resource for readers of any age who are struggling to understand their sexual orientation, or those who would like to better understand asexuality.&#8221; -Library Journal, starred review Julie Sondra Decker&#8217;s book functions as a starting point for people interested in asexuality. It covers the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-invisible-orientation-an-introduction-to-asexuality-next-generation-indie-book-awards-winner-in-lgbt-julie-sondra-decker-abridged/">The Invisible Orientation : An Introduction to Asexuality * Next Generation Indie Book Awards Winner in LGBT * &#8211; Julie Sondra Decker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Next Generation Indie Book Awards Winner in LGBT . &#8220;An important resource for readers of any age who are struggling to understand their sexual orientation, or those who would like to better understand asexuality.&#8221; -Library Journal, starred review<br />
                    Julie Sondra Decker&#8217;s book functions as a starting point for people interested in asexuality. It covers the basics of what asexuality is and isn&#8217;t, explores the most common issues asexual people may be dealing with, presents some pointers for newly asexual-identified people and the people who love them, and includes some resources to find out more. It&#8217;s for the layperson, written in everyday language.    </p>
<p>                    She writes for people who are on the asexual spectrum, people who think they might be asexual, friends and family and partners of people who have come out as asexual, curious parties, and those looking for information on the subject for their school papers, sexuality studies, and alternative sexuality resources. And it&#8217;s for people who think asexuality doesn&#8217;t exist. Chapters include:    </p>
<p>                    Asexuality as a Sexual Orientation<br />
                    Romantic Orientation<br />
                    Libido and Masturbation<br />
                    Intimate and Sexual Activity<br />
                    Asexual Relationships<br />
                    Asexual Community<br />
                    Should Asexual People Get Therapy and Be Fixed<br />
                    Am I Asexual?<br />
                    Should I Come Out?<br />
                    And much more    </p>
<p>                    If you think you may be asexual, or if you have a friend or partner who may be a sexual, this personal book will help you better understand what it means to be asexual in a world dominated by sexuality.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-invisible-orientation-an-introduction-to-asexuality-next-generation-indie-book-awards-winner-in-lgbt-julie-sondra-decker-abridged/">The Invisible Orientation : An Introduction to Asexuality * Next Generation Indie Book Awards Winner in LGBT * &#8211; Julie Sondra Decker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Is Sex Fun? : The Evolution of Human Sexuality &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fascinating insight into how human sexuality came to be the way it is now &#8211; Jared Diamond explains why we are different from the animal kingdom. Why are humans one of the few species to have sex in private? Why do humans have sex any day of the month or year, including when the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/">Why Is Sex Fun? : The Evolution of Human Sexuality &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fascinating insight into how human sexuality came to be the way it is now &#8211; Jared Diamond explains why we are different from the animal kingdom.    </p>
<p>                    Why are humans one of the few species to have sex in private? Why do humans have sex any day of the month or year, including when the female is pregnant, beyond her reproductive years, or between her fertile cycles? Why are human females one of the few mammals to go through menopause?    </p>
<p>                    Human sexuality seems normal to us but it is bizarre by the standards of other animals. Jared Diamond argues that our strange sex lives were as crucial to our rise to human status as were our large brains. He also describes the battle of the sexes in the human and animal world over parental care, and why sex differences in the genetic value of parental care provide a biological basis for the all-too-familiar different attitudes of men and women towards extramarital sex.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/">Why Is Sex Fun? : The Evolution of Human Sexuality &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Think More About Sex &#8211; Alain De Botton, The School of Life (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-think-more-about-sex-alain-de-botton-the-school-of-life-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-think-more-about-sex-alain-de-botton-the-school-of-life-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this rigorous and supremely honest book Alain de Botton helps us navigate the intimate and exciting &#8211; yet often confusing and difficult &#8211; experience that is sex. Few of us tend to feel we&#8217;re entirely normal when it comes to sex, and what we&#8217;re supposed to be feeling rarely matches up with the reality. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-think-more-about-sex-alain-de-botton-the-school-of-life-abridged/">How To Think More About Sex &#8211; Alain De Botton, The School of Life (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this rigorous and supremely honest book Alain de Botton helps us navigate the intimate and exciting &#8211; yet often confusing and difficult &#8211; experience that is sex. Few of us tend to feel we&#8217;re entirely normal when it comes to sex, and what we&#8217;re supposed to be feeling rarely matches up with the reality. This book argues that 21st-century sex is ultimately fated to be a balancing act between love and desire, and adventure and commitment. Covering topics that include lust, fetishism, adultery and pornography, Alain de Botton frankly articulates the dilemmas of modern sexuality, offering insights and consolation to help us think more deeply and wisely about the sex we are, or aren&#8217;t, having.    </p>
<p>                     One in the new series of books from The School of Life, launched May 2012:    </p>
<p>                     How to Stay Sane by Philippa Perry    </p>
<p>                     How to Find Fulfilling Work by Roman Krznaric    </p>
<p>                     How to Worry Less About Money by John Armstrong    </p>
<p>                     How to Change the World by John-Paul Flintoff    </p>
<p>                     How to Thrive in the Digital Age by Tom Chatfield    </p>
<p>                     How to Think More About Sex by Alain de Botton</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-think-more-about-sex-alain-de-botton-the-school-of-life-abridged/">How To Think More About Sex &#8211; Alain De Botton, The School of Life (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sex Myth : The Gap Between Our Fantasies and Reality &#8211; Rachel Hills (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-sex-myth-the-gap-between-our-fantasies-and-reality-rachel-hills-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sex-myth-the-gap-between-our-fantasies-and-reality-rachel-hills-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fifty years after the sexual revolution, we are told that we live in a time of unprecedented sexual freedom; that if anything, we are too free now. But beneath the veneer of glossy hedonism, millennial journalist Rachel Hills argues that we are controlled by a new brand of sexual convention: one which influences all of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sex-myth-the-gap-between-our-fantasies-and-reality-rachel-hills-abridged/">The Sex Myth : The Gap Between Our Fantasies and Reality &#8211; Rachel Hills (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fifty years after the sexual revolution, we are told that we live in a time of unprecedented sexual freedom; that if anything, we are too free now. But beneath the veneer of glossy hedonism, millennial journalist Rachel Hills argues that we are controlled by a new brand of sexual convention: one which influences all of us-woman or man, straight or gay, liberal or conservative. At the root of this silent code lies the Sex Myth-the defining significance we invest in sexuality that once meant we were dirty if we didhave sex, and now means we are defective if we don&#8217;tdo it enough.     </p>
<p>                    Equal parts social commentary, pop culture, and powerful personal anecdotes from people across the English-speaking world, The Sex Mythexposes the invisible norms and unspoken assumptions that shape the way we think about sex today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sex-myth-the-gap-between-our-fantasies-and-reality-rachel-hills-abridged/">The Sex Myth : The Gap Between Our Fantasies and Reality &#8211; Rachel Hills (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mating in Captivity : How to keep desire and passion alive in long-term relationships &#8211; Esther Perel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/mating-in-captivity-how-to-keep-desire-and-passion-alive-in-long-term-relationships-esther-perel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/mating-in-captivity-how-to-keep-desire-and-passion-alive-in-long-term-relationships-esther-perel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When you love someone, how does it feel? And when you desire someone, how is it different? In Mating in Captivity, Esther Perel looks at the story of sex in committed couples. Modern romance promises it all &#8211; a lifetime of togetherness, intimacy and erotic desire. In reality, it&#8217;s hard to want what you already [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mating-in-captivity-how-to-keep-desire-and-passion-alive-in-long-term-relationships-esther-perel-abridged/">Mating in Captivity : How to keep desire and passion alive in long-term relationships &#8211; Esther Perel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When you love someone, how does it feel? And when you desire someone, how is it different?     </p>
<p>                    In Mating in Captivity, Esther Perel looks at the story of sex in committed couples. Modern romance promises it all &#8211; a lifetime of togetherness, intimacy and erotic desire. In reality, it&#8217;s hard to want what you already have. Our quest for secure love conflicts with our pursuit of passion. And often, the very thing that got us to into our relationships &#8211; lust &#8211; is the one thing that goes missing from them.     </p>
<p>                    Determined to reconcile the erotic and the domestic, Perel explains why democracy is a passion killer in the bedroom. Argues for playfulness, distance, and uncertainty. And shows what it takes to bring lust home. Smart, sexy and explosively original, Mating in Captivity is the monogamist&#8217;s essential bedside read.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/mating-in-captivity-how-to-keep-desire-and-passion-alive-in-long-term-relationships-esther-perel-abridged/">Mating in Captivity : How to keep desire and passion alive in long-term relationships &#8211; Esther Perel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Better Sex Through Mindfulness : How Women Can Cultivate Desire &#8211; Lori A. Brotto, Foreword by Emily Nagoski (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/better-sex-through-mindfulness-how-women-can-cultivate-desire-lori-a-brotto-foreword-by-emily-nagoski-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/better-sex-through-mindfulness-how-women-can-cultivate-desire-lori-a-brotto-foreword-by-emily-nagoski-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As Seen/Heard in Bustle * Dan Savage&#8217;s Savage Lovecast * Jezebel * Women&#8217;s Health * Prevention * The New York Times * VICE * Pleasure Mechanics A groundbreaking method for improving desire, arousal, and sexual satisfaction through mindfulness. Studies show that approximately half of all women experience some kind of sexual difficulty at one point [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/better-sex-through-mindfulness-how-women-can-cultivate-desire-lori-a-brotto-foreword-by-emily-nagoski-abridged/">Better Sex Through Mindfulness : How Women Can Cultivate Desire &#8211; Lori A. Brotto, Foreword by Emily Nagoski (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As Seen/Heard in Bustle * Dan Savage&#8217;s Savage Lovecast * Jezebel * Women&#8217;s Health * Prevention * The New York Times * VICE * Pleasure Mechanics    </p>
<p>                    A groundbreaking method for improving desire, arousal, and sexual satisfaction through mindfulness.     </p>
<p>                    Studies show that approximately half of all women experience some kind of sexual difficulty at one point in their lives, with lack of interest in sex being by far the most common and the most distressing. And when sex suffers, so do all other areas of life.    </p>
<p>                    But it doesn&#8217;t have to be that way. In Better Sex through Mindfulness, acclaimed psychologist and sex researcher Lori A. Brotto offers a revolutionary approach to improving desire, arousal, and satisfaction inside and outside of the bedroom. A pioneer in the use of mindfulness for treating sexual difficulties, Brotto has helped hundreds of women cultivate more exciting, fulfilling sexual experiences.    </p>
<p>                    In this accessible, relatable book, she explores the various reasons for sexual problems, such as stress and incessant multitasking, and tells the stories of many of the women she has treated over the years. She also provides easy, effective exercises that readers can do on their own to increase desire and sexual enjoyment, whether their goal is to overcome a sexual difficulty or simply give their love life a boost.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/better-sex-through-mindfulness-how-women-can-cultivate-desire-lori-a-brotto-foreword-by-emily-nagoski-abridged/">Better Sex Through Mindfulness : How Women Can Cultivate Desire &#8211; Lori A. Brotto, Foreword by Emily Nagoski (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Boys &#038; Sex : Young Men on Hook-ups, Love, Porn, Consent and Navigating the New Masculinity &#8211; Peggy Orenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/boys-sex-young-men-on-hook-ups-love-porn-consent-and-navigating-the-new-masculinity-peggy-orenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/boys-sex-young-men-on-hook-ups-love-porn-consent-and-navigating-the-new-masculinity-peggy-orenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller &#8216;Blows your mind on every page&#8217; Caitlin Moran &#8216;Should be mandatory reading for anyone who cares about the next generation&#8217; Lori Gottlieb, New York Times bestselling author of Maybe You Should Talk to Someone Peggy Orenstein broke ground with her bestselling Girls &#038; Sex, exploring young women&#8217;s right to pleasure [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boys-sex-young-men-on-hook-ups-love-porn-consent-and-navigating-the-new-masculinity-peggy-orenstein-abridged/">Boys &#038; Sex : Young Men on Hook-ups, Love, Porn, Consent and Navigating the New Masculinity &#8211; Peggy Orenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Blows your mind on every page&#8217; Caitlin Moran    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Should be mandatory reading for anyone who cares about the next generation&#8217; Lori Gottlieb, New York Times bestselling author of Maybe You Should Talk to Someone    </p>
<p>                    Peggy Orenstein broke ground with her bestselling Girls &#038; Sex, exploring young women&#8217;s right to pleasure and agency in sexual encounters. Now she turns her focus to boys with an examination of how young men are navigating sexual culture in these changing times &#8211; and what we need to do to help them.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on comprehensive interviews with young  men, psychologists and experts in the field, Boys &#038; Sex dissects &#8216;locker room talk&#8217;; pornography as the new sex education; the role of empathy; boys&#8217; understanding of hookup culture and consent; and their experience as both perpetrators and victims of sexual assault.    </p>
<p>                    By presenting young men&#8217;s experience in all its complexity, Orenstein unravels the hidden truths, hard lessons and important realities of young male sexuality in today&#8217;s world. The result is a provocative and paradigm-shifting work that offers a much-needed vision of how boys can truly move forward as better men.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/boys-sex-young-men-on-hook-ups-love-porn-consent-and-navigating-the-new-masculinity-peggy-orenstein-abridged/">Boys &#038; Sex : Young Men on Hook-ups, Love, Porn, Consent and Navigating the New Masculinity &#8211; Peggy Orenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Girls &#038; Sex &#8211; Navigating the Complicated New Landscape &#8211; Peggy Orenstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/girls-sex-navigating-the-complicated-new-landscape-peggy-orenstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/girls-sex-navigating-the-complicated-new-landscape-peggy-orenstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re going to talk about women in the 21st century, you MUST read Peggy Orenstein&#8217;s Girls &#038; Sex.&#8217; &#8211; CAITLIN MORAN, author of How to Be a Woman *TIME Top 10 non-fiction books of 2016* *Amazon Best Non-fiction of 2016* A generation gap has emerged between parents and their daughters. Mothers and fathers have [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girls-sex-navigating-the-complicated-new-landscape-peggy-orenstein-abridged/">Girls &#038; Sex &#8211; Navigating the Complicated New Landscape &#8211; Peggy Orenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&#8217;re going to talk about women in the 21st century, you MUST read Peggy Orenstein&#8217;s Girls &#038; Sex.&#8217; &#8211; CAITLIN MORAN, author of How to Be a Woman    </p>
<p>                    *TIME Top 10 non-fiction books of 2016*    </p>
<p>                    *Amazon Best Non-fiction of 2016*    </p>
<p>                    A generation gap has emerged between parents and their daughters. Mothers and fathers have little idea about the pressures and expectations they face or how they feel about them.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on in-depth interviews with young women and a wide range of psychologists and experts, renowned journalist and bestselling author Peggy Orenstein goes where most others fear to tread, pulling back the curtain on the hidden truths and hard lessons of girls&#8217; sex lives in the modern world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/girls-sex-navigating-the-complicated-new-landscape-peggy-orenstein-abridged/">Girls &#038; Sex &#8211; Navigating the Complicated New Landscape &#8211; Peggy Orenstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>She Comes First &#8211; Ian Kerner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/she-comes-first-ian-kerner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/she-comes-first-ian-kerner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Every man&#8217;s must-read. Tell your guy to put down the remote and pick up She Comes First.&#8221; &#8211;Cosmopolitan Ian Kerner offers a radical new philosophy for pleasuring women in She Comes First&#8211;an essential guidebook to oral sex from the author of Be Honest&#8211;You&#8217;re Not That Into Him Either. The New York Times praises Kerner&#8217;s &#8220;cool [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-comes-first-ian-kerner-abridged/">She Comes First &#8211; Ian Kerner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Every man&#8217;s must-read. Tell your guy to put down the remote and pick up She Comes First.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Cosmopolitan    </p>
<p>                    Ian Kerner offers a radical new philosophy for pleasuring women in She Comes First&#8211;an essential guidebook to oral sex from the author of Be Honest&#8211;You&#8217;re Not That Into Him Either. The New York Times praises Kerner&#8217;s &#8220;cool sense of humor and an obsessive desire to inform,&#8221; as he &#8220;encourages men through an act that many find mystifying.&#8221; An indispensable aid to a healthier, more fulfilling sex life for her and him, She Comes First offers techniques and philosophy that have already earned raves from the likes of bestselling author and Loveline co-host Dr. Drew Pinsky as well as Playgirl magazine, which cheers, &#8220;Hallelujah!&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-comes-first-ian-kerner-abridged/">She Comes First &#8211; Ian Kerner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Game &#8211; Neil Strauss (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/game-neil-strauss-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Men]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/game-neil-strauss-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The Game&#8221; recounts the incredible adventures of an everyday man who transforms himself from a shy, awkward writer into the quick-witted, smooth-talking Style, a character irresistible to women. But just when life is better than he could have ever dreamed (he uses his techniques on Britney Spears, receives life coaching from Tom Cruise, moves into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/game-neil-strauss-abridged/">Game &#8211; Neil Strauss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The Game&#8221; recounts the incredible adventures of an everyday man who transforms himself from a shy, awkward writer into the quick-witted, smooth-talking Style, a character irresistible to women. But just when life is better than he could have ever dreamed (he uses his techniques on Britney Spears, receives life coaching from Tom Cruise, moves into a mansion with Courtney Love and is officially voted the World&#8217;s Number One Pickup Artist) he falls head over heels for a woman who can beat him at his own game.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/game-neil-strauss-abridged/">Game &#8211; Neil Strauss (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Second Sex (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Simone de Beauvoir, Translated by Constance Borde, Translated by Sheila Malovany-Chevallier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-second-sex-vintage-feminism-short-edition-simone-de-beauvoir-translated-by-constance-borde-translated-by-sheila-malovany-chevallier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-second-sex-vintage-feminism-short-edition-simone-de-beauvoir-translated-by-constance-borde-translated-by-sheila-malovany-chevallier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Vintage Feminism: classic feminist texts in short form WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY NATALIE HAYNES When this book was first published in 1949 it was to outrage and scandal. Never before had the case for female liberty been so forcefully and successfully argued. De Beauvoir&#8217;s belief that &#8216;One is not born, but rather becomes, woman&#8217; switched [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-second-sex-vintage-feminism-short-edition-simone-de-beauvoir-translated-by-constance-borde-translated-by-sheila-malovany-chevallier-abridged/">The Second Sex (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Simone de Beauvoir, Translated by Constance Borde, Translated by Sheila Malovany-Chevallier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vintage Feminism: classic feminist texts in short form    </p>
<p>                    WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY NATALIE HAYNES    </p>
<p>                    When this book was first published in 1949 it was to outrage and scandal. Never before had the case for female liberty been so forcefully and successfully argued. De Beauvoir&#8217;s belief that &#8216;One is not born, but rather becomes, woman&#8217; switched on light bulbs in the heads of a generation of women and began a fight for greater equality and economic independence. These pages contain the key passages of the book that changed perceptions of women forever.    </p>
<p>                    TRANSLATED BY CONSTANCE BORDE AND SHEILA MALOVANY-CHEVALLIER<br />
                    ANNOTATED AND INTRODUCED BY MARTINE REID</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-second-sex-vintage-feminism-short-edition-simone-de-beauvoir-translated-by-constance-borde-translated-by-sheila-malovany-chevallier-abridged/">The Second Sex (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Simone de Beauvoir, Translated by Constance Borde, Translated by Sheila Malovany-Chevallier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
