<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Mind, Body &amp; Spirit Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/mind-body-spirit/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/mind-body-spirit/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Mind, Body &amp; Spirit Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/mind-body-spirit/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>How to Analyze People : Persuasion, and Dark Psychology &#8211; 3 Books in 1 &#8211; How to Recognize The Signs Of a Toxic Person Manipulating You, and The Best Defense Against It &#8211; James W Williams</title>
		<link>/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanistic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neuro Linguistic Programming (NLP)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Dark Psychology Series Complete 3 Book Compilation This book includes: How to Analyze People: Dark Psychology &#8211; Dark Secrets to Analyze and Influence Anyone Using Body Language, Human Psychology, Subliminal Persuasion and NLP Persuasion: Dark Psychology &#8211; How People are Influencing You to Do What They Want Using Manipulation, NLP, and Subliminal Persuasion Dark Psychology: [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/">How to Analyze People : Persuasion, and Dark Psychology &#8211; 3 Books in 1 &#8211; How to Recognize The Signs Of a Toxic Person Manipulating You, and The Best Defense Against It &#8211; James W Williams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Dark Psychology Series Complete 3 Book Compilation    </p>
<p>                    This book includes: How to Analyze People: Dark Psychology &#8211; Dark Secrets to Analyze and Influence Anyone Using Body Language, Human Psychology, Subliminal Persuasion and NLP<br />
                    Persuasion: Dark Psychology &#8211; How People are Influencing You to Do What They Want Using Manipulation, NLP, and Subliminal Persuasion<br />
                    Dark Psychology: The Practical Uses and Best Defenses of Psychological Warfare in Everyday Life &#8211; How to Detect and Defend Against Manipulation, Deception, Dark Persuasion, and Covert NLP    </p>
<p>                    If you&#8217;re tired of being manipulated, whether you&#8217;re being tricked into doing things you don&#8217;t want, or others are taking advantage of you, there are ways to stop manipulation and persuasion in its tracks.    </p>
<p>                    In this book, you will get a groundwork for what different types of persuasion and manipulation might be. You will learn the process of how people use these tactics to their advantage.    </p>
<p>                    The first half of the book will discuss what makes up an individual. The way you use your body, the words that you choose to speak, and the way that they were raised all play important roles in what makes an individual. You will also have to look at your own self and pick out all of these unique things that make them different from everyone else as well.    </p>
<p>                    There are psychological studies that back up the idea of certain methods of persuasion, such as NLP tactics, that prove that anyone has the power to persuade others.    </p>
<p>                    Inside this book, you will discover: WhatDark Psychologyis and how it&#8217;s used to control people.How to plant different emotional seeds that will grow in people&#8217;s mindsHow to use words to steer people however you likeHow to identify and work with different types of people like contrarians and control freaks.The jobs/roles in society that you are most likely to be manipulated inThe language of the subconsciousThedirty trickslovers and family members use to control their victims.How to analyze different personality typesMind-blowing tricks for manipulationMagic words for influencing othersA step-by-step guide on influencing others with NLPForbidden secrets of dark psychologyCase studies showcasing how much damage a master manipulator can do.And much more&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Although there are many differences among people, there are also many things that make us the same. In order to better analyze and understand those around you, it&#8217;s crucial to find those things that we do connect on, and the things that bring us together rather than the things that tear us apart.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s important when reading this book to remember that not all manipulation is bad. In the first book of this boxset, it is emphasized that those who might be manipulating you might also be taking advantage of you.    </p>
<p>                    When reading this book, you should remember that manipulation is a tool, much like a hammer. You can either use that hammer to destroy everything around you, or you could alternatively use that hammer to create something organic, something new.    </p>
<p>                    This book will take you first through the discovery and analyzation of those around you, and then it will provide different ways that you can persuade them.    </p>
<p>                    The only thing you need before starting this book is the willingness to change. You might have to confront some of your darkest issues, and you might have to put yourself through future scenarios that elicit a feeling of discomfort. In the end, however, you&#8217;ll find yourself to be much more self-aware and independent.Click &#8220;Add to Cart&#8221; nowand learn how to defend against dark psychology and keep your mind and life in control.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-analyze-people-persuasion-and-dark-psychology-3-books-in-1-how-to-recognize-the-signs-of-a-toxic-person-manipulating-you-and-the-best-defense-against-it-james-w-williams/">How to Analyze People : Persuasion, and Dark Psychology &#8211; 3 Books in 1 &#8211; How to Recognize The Signs Of a Toxic Person Manipulating You, and The Best Defense Against It &#8211; James W Williams</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Attractor : Methods for Manifesting a Life beyond Your Wildest Dreams &#8211; Gabrielle Bernstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-attractor-methods-for-manifesting-a-life-beyond-your-wildest-dreams-gabrielle-bernstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-attractor-methods-for-manifesting-a-life-beyond-your-wildest-dreams-gabrielle-bernstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER! ** Ready to take the next step toward living in alignment with the Universe? The #1 New York Times best-selling author of The Universe Has Your Back shows you how. In Super Attractor, Gabrielle Bernstein lays out the essential steps for living in alignment with the Universe&#8211;more fully than you&#8217;ve [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-attractor-methods-for-manifesting-a-life-beyond-your-wildest-dreams-gabrielle-bernstein-abridged/">Super Attractor : Methods for Manifesting a Life beyond Your Wildest Dreams &#8211; Gabrielle Bernstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER! ** Ready to take the next step toward living in alignment with the Universe? The #1 New York Times best-selling author of The Universe Has Your Back shows you how.    </p>
<p>                    In Super Attractor, Gabrielle Bernstein lays out the essential steps for living in alignment with the Universe&#8211;more fully than you&#8217;ve ever done before. &#8220;I&#8217;ve always known that there is a nonphysical presence beyond my visible sight,&#8221; Gabby writes. &#8220;All my life I&#8217;ve intuitively tuned in to it and used it as a source for good. . . . What we call it is irrelevant. Connecting to it is imperative.&#8221; Super Attractor is a manifesto for making that connection and marrying your spiritual life with your day-to-day experience. In these pages, you&#8217;ll learn to:    </p>
<p>                    * Move beyond dabbling in your practice, when it&#8217;s convenient, to living a spiritual life all the time<br />
                    * Take practical steps to create a life filled with purpose, happiness, and freedom<br />
                    * Feel a sense of awe each day as you witness miracles unfold<br />
                    * Release the past and live without fear of the future<br />
                    * Tap into the infinite source of abundance, joy, and well-being that is your birthright<br />
                    * Bring more light to your own life and the world around you    </p>
<p>                    This book is a journey of remembering where your true power lies. You&#8217;ll learn how to co-create the life you want. You&#8217;ll accept that life can flow, that attracting is fun, and that you don&#8217;t have to work so hard to get what you want. Most important, you&#8217;ll feel good. And when you feel good, you&#8217;ll give off a presence of joy that can elevate everyone around you. After reading this book, you will know how to fulfill your function: to be a force of love in the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-attractor-methods-for-manifesting-a-life-beyond-your-wildest-dreams-gabrielle-bernstein-abridged/">Super Attractor : Methods for Manifesting a Life beyond Your Wildest Dreams &#8211; Gabrielle Bernstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happier at Home : Kiss More, Jump More, Abandon a Project, Read Samuel Johnson, and My Other Experiments in the Practice of Everyday Life &#8211; Gretchen Rubin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/happier-at-home-kiss-more-jump-more-abandon-a-project-read-samuel-johnson-and-my-other-experiments-in-the-practice-of-everyday-life-gretchen-rubin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/happier-at-home-kiss-more-jump-more-abandon-a-project-read-samuel-johnson-and-my-other-experiments-in-the-practice-of-everyday-life-gretchen-rubin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Happiness Project, she worked out general theories of happiness. Here she goes deeper on factors that matter for home, such as possessions, marriage, time and parenthood. How can she control the cubicle in her pocket? How might she spotlight her family&#8217;s treasured possessions? And it really was time to replace that dud toaster. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happier-at-home-kiss-more-jump-more-abandon-a-project-read-samuel-johnson-and-my-other-experiments-in-the-practice-of-everyday-life-gretchen-rubin-abridged/">Happier at Home : Kiss More, Jump More, Abandon a Project, Read Samuel Johnson, and My Other Experiments in the Practice of Everyday Life &#8211; Gretchen Rubin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Happiness Project, she worked out general theories of happiness. Here she goes deeper on factors that matter for home, such as possessions, marriage, time and parenthood. How can she control the cubicle in her pocket? How might she spotlight her family&#8217;s treasured possessions? And it really was time to replace that dud toaster.    </p>
<p>                    And what does she want from her home? A place that calms her, and energises her. A place that, by making her feel safe, will free her to take risks. Also, while Rubin wants to be happier at home, she wants to appreciate how much happiness is there already.    </p>
<p>                    So, starting in September (the new January), Rubin dedicates a school year &#8211; September through May &#8211; to making her home a place of greater simplicity, comfort and love.     </p>
<p>                    Each month, Rubin tackles a different theme as she experiments with concrete, manageable resolutions &#8211; and this time, she coaxes her family to try some resolutions, as well.     </p>
<p>                    With her signature blend of memoir, science, philosophy and experimentation, Rubin&#8217;s passion for her subject jumps off the page, and reading just a few chapters of this book will inspire readers to find more happiness in their own lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/happier-at-home-kiss-more-jump-more-abandon-a-project-read-samuel-johnson-and-my-other-experiments-in-the-practice-of-everyday-life-gretchen-rubin-abridged/">Happier at Home : Kiss More, Jump More, Abandon a Project, Read Samuel Johnson, and My Other Experiments in the Practice of Everyday Life &#8211; Gretchen Rubin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ikigai : The Japanese secret to a long and happy life &#8211; Hector Garcia, Francesc Miralles (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ikigai-the-japanese-secret-to-a-long-and-happy-life-hector-garcia-francesc-miralles-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ikigai-the-japanese-secret-to-a-long-and-happy-life-hector-garcia-francesc-miralles-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER We all have an ikigai. It&#8217;s the Japanese word for &#8216;a reason to live&#8217; or &#8216;a reason to jump out of bed in the morning&#8217;. It&#8217;s the place where your needs, desires, ambitions, and satisfaction meet. A place of balance. Small wonder that finding your ikigai is closely linked to living longer. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ikigai-the-japanese-secret-to-a-long-and-happy-life-hector-garcia-francesc-miralles-abridged/">Ikigai : The Japanese secret to a long and happy life &#8211; Hector Garcia, Francesc Miralles (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    We all have an ikigai.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s the Japanese word for &#8216;a reason to live&#8217; or &#8216;a reason to jump out of bed in the morning&#8217;.     </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s the place where your needs, desires, ambitions, and satisfaction meet. A place of balance. Small wonder that finding your ikigai is closely linked to living longer.    </p>
<p>                    Finding your ikigai is easier than you might think. This book will help you work out what your own ikigai really is, and equip you to change your life. You have a purpose in this world: your skills, your interests, your desires and your history have made you the perfect candidate for something. All you have to do is find it.    </p>
<p>                    Do that, and you can make every single day of your life joyful and meaningful.<br />
                    ______________________________<br />
                    &#8216;I read it and it&#8217;s bewitched me ever since. I&#8217;m spellbound.&#8217;<br />
                    Chris Evans    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A refreshingly simple recipe for happiness.&#8217; Stylist    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ikigai gently unlocks simple secrets we can all use to live long, meaningful, happy lives. Warm, patient, and kind, this book pulls you gently along your own journey rather than pushing you from behind.&#8217; Neil Pasricha, bestselling author of The Happiness Equation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ikigai-the-japanese-secret-to-a-long-and-happy-life-hector-garcia-francesc-miralles-abridged/">Ikigai : The Japanese secret to a long and happy life &#8211; Hector Garcia, Francesc Miralles (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Radical Compassion : Learning to Love Yourself and Your World with the Practice of RAIN &#8211; Tara Brach (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/radical-compassion-learning-to-love-yourself-and-your-world-with-the-practice-of-rain-tara-brach-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/radical-compassion-learning-to-love-yourself-and-your-world-with-the-practice-of-rain-tara-brach-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A powerful book that will free you from shame, fear, and negative self-beliefs. You will feel wiser, happier, and kinder after reading it&#8217; Haemin Sunim World-renowned meditation teacher Tara Brach shares a simple four-step practice to awaken compassion and release the grip of painful emotions: Recognize Allow Investigate Nurture Heartfelt and deeply practical, Radical Compassion [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-compassion-learning-to-love-yourself-and-your-world-with-the-practice-of-rain-tara-brach-abridged/">Radical Compassion : Learning to Love Yourself and Your World with the Practice of RAIN &#8211; Tara Brach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A powerful book that will free you from shame, fear, and negative self-beliefs. You will feel wiser, happier, and kinder after reading it&#8217; Haemin Sunim     </p>
<p>                    World-renowned meditation teacher Tara Brach shares a simple four-step practice to awaken compassion and release the grip of painful emotions:    </p>
<p>                    Recognize<br />
                    Allow<br />
                    Investigate<br />
                    Nurture    </p>
<p>                    Heartfelt and deeply practical, Radical Compassion teaches us to find healing and freedom through the sources of love, courage and deep wisdom alive within us all.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Radical Compassion lays out a path of straightforward, accessible practices grounded in both modern brain science and ancient wisdom &#8230; a masterpiece&#8217; Rick Hanson    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book is a treasure from one of the most spiritual teachers of our time&#8217; Kristin Neff</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/radical-compassion-learning-to-love-yourself-and-your-world-with-the-practice-of-rain-tara-brach-abridged/">Radical Compassion : Learning to Love Yourself and Your World with the Practice of RAIN &#8211; Tara Brach (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Screamfree Parenting : The Revolutionary Approach to Raising your Kids by Keeping your Cool &#8211; Hal Edward Runkel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/screamfree-parenting-the-revolutionary-approach-to-raising-your-kids-by-keeping-your-cool-hal-edward-runkel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Aspects Of Sexuality, Gender & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/screamfree-parenting-the-revolutionary-approach-to-raising-your-kids-by-keeping-your-cool-hal-edward-runkel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Parents are facing the toughest challenge of their lives. They want to create a loving family environment filled with mutual respect and cooperation&#8230; but they find instead that human nature and the influence of our culture combine to produce an atmosphere of anxiety, exhaustion, and far too much screaming. Perhaps you can relate! Whether you [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/screamfree-parenting-the-revolutionary-approach-to-raising-your-kids-by-keeping-your-cool-hal-edward-runkel-abridged/">Screamfree Parenting : The Revolutionary Approach to Raising your Kids by Keeping your Cool &#8211; Hal Edward Runkel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Parents are facing the toughest challenge of their lives. They want to create a loving family environment filled with mutual respect and cooperation&#8230; but they find instead that human nature and the influence of our culture combine to produce an atmosphere of anxiety, exhaustion, and far too much screaming. Perhaps you can relate!     </p>
<p>                    Whether you scream at your children or not, you no doubt feel anxious about them and their choices. You worry how they&#8217;ll turn out. Unfortunately for parents, many of the techniques some experts present only seem to make matters worse. Hal Edward Runkel has discovered why: Parents are spending far too much time orbiting their lives around their children. They need to return the focus to themselves. They need to grow up and calm down.     </p>
<p>                    ScreamFree Parenting is about taming your reactive responses to your deep anxiety. Rather than learning new techniques, you&#8217;ll discover the liberating principles, based on scriptural truths, that are inspiring parents just like you to revolutionize their family life. Principles that will enable you to remain cool, calm, and connected with your children, no matter what.     </p>
<p>                    Learn how to parent less out of your deepest fears and more out of the highest principles in ScreamFree Parenting.     </p>
<p>                    Special edition distributed through Christian booksellers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/screamfree-parenting-the-revolutionary-approach-to-raising-your-kids-by-keeping-your-cool-hal-edward-runkel-abridged/">Screamfree Parenting : The Revolutionary Approach to Raising your Kids by Keeping your Cool &#8211; Hal Edward Runkel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zen: The Art of Simple Living &#8211; Shunmyo Masuno, Illustrated by Harry Goldhawk, Illustrated by Zanna Goldhawk (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Worship, Rites & Ceremonies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feng Shui]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zen Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Be more Zen in 2022 with this little book of 100 tips and activities to soothe the soul &#8216;Brings the spirit of Zen Buddhism to everyday life . . . 100 snack-size Zen activities you can do daily to add more calm to your life&#8217; Daily Telegraph _______ Zen is the perfect antidote to the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/">Zen: The Art of Simple Living &#8211; Shunmyo Masuno, Illustrated by Harry Goldhawk, Illustrated by Zanna Goldhawk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Be more Zen in 2022 with this little book of 100 tips and activities to soothe the soul    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Brings the spirit of Zen Buddhism to everyday life . . . 100 snack-size Zen activities you can do daily to add more calm to your life&#8217; Daily Telegraph<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    Zen is the perfect antidote to the stress and uncertainty of modern life . . .    </p>
<p>                    In clear, practical and easy to follow lessons &#8211; one a day for 100 days &#8211; renowned Buddhist monk Shunmyo Masuno draws on centuries of wisdom to show you how to apply the essence of Zen to modern life.    </p>
<p>                    You will learn how to exhale deeply to eliminate negative emotions, to arrange your house simply to clear your thinking, to line up your shoes at night to bring order to your mind, to plant a single flower and watch it grow, to worry less about what you cannot control, and so much more . . .    </p>
<p>                    You will even make time to think about nothing at all.    </p>
<p>                    Simplify your life with the art of Zen, and learn how to feel more relaxed, fulfilled, and with a renewed sense of peace.<br />
                    _______    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Full of the simplest yet richest rituals to adopt in order to live a long and happy life, this book of wisdom is a soothing balm of peace for anyone living in the busy modern world&#8217; Psychologies    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Does for mental clutter what Marie Kondo has done for household clutter&#8217; Publisher&#8217;s Weekly    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This little treasure needs to be at every bedside&#8217; llan Lokos, author of Through the Flames, Patience, and Pocket Peace    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Zen: The Art of Simple Living makes the wisdom of the Buddha radically accessible&#8217; Dzogchen Ponlop Rinpoche, author of Emotional Rescue and Rebel Buddha</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-the-art-of-simple-living-shunmyo-masuno-illustrated-by-harry-goldhawk-illustrated-by-zanna-goldhawk-abridged/">Zen: The Art of Simple Living &#8211; Shunmyo Masuno, Illustrated by Harry Goldhawk, Illustrated by Zanna Goldhawk (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agnosticism & Atheism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eclectic & Esoteric Religions & Belief Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An extraordinary book . . . It will shake up your most fundamental beliefs about everyday experience, and it just might change your life.&#8217; Paul Bloom ___ For the millions of people who want spirituality without religion, Sam Harris&#8217;s new book is a guide to meditation as a rational spiritual practice informed by neuroscience and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/">Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An extraordinary book . . . It will shake up your most fundamental beliefs about everyday experience, and it just might change your life.&#8217; Paul Bloom<br />
                    ___    </p>
<p>                    For the millions of people who want spirituality without religion, Sam Harris&#8217;s new book is a guide to meditation as a rational spiritual practice informed by neuroscience and psychology.    </p>
<p>                     Throughout the book, Harris argues that there are important truths to be found in the experience of contemplatives such as Jesus, Buddha and other saints and sages of history-and, therefore, that there is more to understanding reality than science and secular culture generally allow.    </p>
<p>                    Waking Up is part seeker&#8217;s memoir and part exploration of the scientific underpinnings of spirituality. No other book marries contemplative wisdom and modern science in this way, and no author other than Sam Harris-a scientist, philosopher, and famous sceptic-could write it.<br />
                     ___    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A demanding, illusion-shattering book.&#8217; Kirkus Reviews<br />
                    &#8216;A pleasure to read.&#8217; Huffington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/">Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unplug : A Simple Guide to Meditation for Busy Sceptics and Modern Soul Seekers &#8211; Suze Yalof Schwartz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unplug-a-simple-guide-to-meditation-for-busy-sceptics-and-modern-soul-seekers-suze-yalof-schwartz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unplug-a-simple-guide-to-meditation-for-busy-sceptics-and-modern-soul-seekers-suze-yalof-schwartz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Unplug is the book I wish I had when I first started meditating. Simple, smart, and inspirational, it provides concrete tools you can use to live a more fulfilling, happier, and yes, more productive life&#8217; Arianna Huffington THE MODERN GUIDE TO MEDITATION FOR BUSY PEOPLE Unplug is the modern, minimalist guide to meditation for busy [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unplug-a-simple-guide-to-meditation-for-busy-sceptics-and-modern-soul-seekers-suze-yalof-schwartz-abridged/">Unplug : A Simple Guide to Meditation for Busy Sceptics and Modern Soul Seekers &#8211; Suze Yalof Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Unplug is the book I wish I had when I first started meditating. Simple, smart, and inspirational, it provides concrete tools you can use to live a more fulfilling, happier, and yes, more productive life&#8217;  Arianna Huffington    </p>
<p>                    THE MODERN GUIDE TO MEDITATION FOR BUSY PEOPLE    </p>
<p>                    Unplug is the modern, minimalist guide to meditation for busy people. Whether you&#8217;re a Fortune 500 CEO or someone bogged down with a never ending to-do list, Suze Yalof-Schwartz shows that you can get more done &#8211; and do it better &#8211; by consciously unplugging for just a few minutes each day.    </p>
<p>                    This revolutionary book brilliantly simplifies the art of meditation and reveals the life-changing benefits you will experience, from improved memory and a more positive outlook to a reduction in anxiety and stress.    </p>
<p>                    Through easy techniques and tips for incorporating meditation into your daily life, Unplug shows you that everyone can meditate, even if &#8211; especially if &#8211; you believe you think too much, have no time, can&#8217;t sit still or that it&#8217;s just &#8216;not you&#8217;.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unplug-a-simple-guide-to-meditation-for-busy-sceptics-and-modern-soul-seekers-suze-yalof-schwartz-abridged/">Unplug : A Simple Guide to Meditation for Busy Sceptics and Modern Soul Seekers &#8211; Suze Yalof Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Own the Day, Own Your Life : Optimised Practices for Waking, Working, Learning, Eating, Training, Playing, Sleeping and Sex &#8211; Aubrey Marcus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Revolutionise your life one day at a time with this empowering handbook designed for men and women which provides simple strategies for each element of your day. Marcus Aubrey, author of the book is CEO of Onnit, a human performance company that he has built into one of the fastest growing companies in the world. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/">Own the Day, Own Your Life : Optimised Practices for Waking, Working, Learning, Eating, Training, Playing, Sleeping and Sex &#8211; Aubrey Marcus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Revolutionise your life one day at a time with this empowering handbook designed for men and women which provides simple strategies for each element of your day. Marcus Aubrey, author of the book is CEO of Onnit, a human performance company that he has built into one of the fastest growing companies in the world.    </p>
<p>                              How can we get the most out of our body and mind on a daily basis? Want to change your life for the better?    </p>
<p>                              Aubrey Marcus answers these questions in this handbook that guides the reader to optimise each moment of the day. With small, actionable changes implemented throughout the course of one day we can feel better, perform more efficiently and live happier. And these habits turn into weekly routines, ultimately becoming part of a lifelong healthy choice.    </p>
<p>                              From workouts and diet to inbox triage, mindfulness, shower temperature and sex this groundbreaking manual provides strategies for each element of your day. Drawing on the latest studies and traditional practices from around the world, this book delivers cutting-edge life hacks, nutritional expertise, brain upgrades and fitness regimes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/own-the-day-own-your-life-optimised-practices-for-waking-working-learning-eating-training-playing-sleeping-and-sex-aubrey-marcus-abridged/">Own the Day, Own Your Life : Optimised Practices for Waking, Working, Learning, Eating, Training, Playing, Sleeping and Sex &#8211; Aubrey Marcus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Love &#8211; Thich Nhat Hanh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-love-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Buddhist Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-love-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How to Love is part of a charming series of books from Zen Master, Thich Nhat Hanh, exploring the essential foundations of mindful meditation and practise. How to Love shows that when we feel closer to our loved ones, we are also more connected to the world as a whole. Nhat Hanh brings his signature [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-love-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/">How To Love &#8211; Thich Nhat Hanh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How to Love is part of a charming series of books from Zen Master, Thich Nhat Hanh, exploring the essential foundations of mindful meditation and practise.     </p>
<p>                    How to Love shows that when we feel closer to our loved ones, we are also more connected to the world as a whole. Nhat Hanh brings his signature clarity, compassion and humour to the thorny question of how to love and distils one of our strongest emotions down to four essentials: you can only love another when you feel true love for yourself; love is understanding; understanding brings compassion; and deep listening and loving speech are key ways of showing our love.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-love-thich-nhat-hanh-abridged/">How To Love &#8211; Thich Nhat Hanh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crafts & Hobbies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**From the author of the international bestseller The Little Book of Hygge &#8211; over one million copies sold** Lykke (Luu-kah) (n): Happiness Meik Wiking is the CEO of the world&#8217;s only Happiness Research Institute in Copenhagen. His job is to travel around the world, seeking out the happiest people and uncovering what they do differently. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/">The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**From the author of the international bestseller The Little Book of Hygge  &#8211; over one million copies sold**    </p>
<p>                    Lykke (Luu-kah) (n): Happiness    </p>
<p>                    Meik Wiking is the CEO of the world&#8217;s only Happiness Research Institute in Copenhagen. His job is to travel around the world, seeking out the happiest people and uncovering what they do differently. In The Little Book of Lykke, he reveals what he has found.    </p>
<p>                    This captivating read features case studies from Bhutan to Australia, South Korea to Canada, France to Denmark, taking the reader on a happiness treasure hunt. Written in the same warm tone as Meik&#8217;s phenomenal bestseller The Little Book of Hygge, this easy-to-understand book will change the way you think about how you relate to your neighbours, the rituals around cooking and eating dinner, and when to book your next holiday &#8211; and is guaranteed to put a smile on your face.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It is a happy book about happiness, written with a twinkle and packaged with Danish style&#8217; (John Helliwell, Economist and Editor of the World Happiness Report)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-little-book-of-lykke-the-danish-search-for-the-worlds-happiest-people-meik-wiking-abridged/">The Little Book of Lykke : The Danish Search for the World&#8217;s Happiest People &#8211; Meik Wiking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Learning : An Inner Journey to Optimal Performance &#8211; Josh Waitzkin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-learning-an-inner-journey-to-optimal-performance-josh-waitzkin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-learning-an-inner-journey-to-optimal-performance-josh-waitzkin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In THE ART OF LEARNING,Waitzkin offers an inside look at two of the world&#8217;s most intense subcultures while also sharing the principles at the core of his success. One must focus on long-term goals, Waitzkin argues, instead of the immediate thrill of victory or crush of defeat, enduring the difficult periods that result in growth [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-learning-an-inner-journey-to-optimal-performance-josh-waitzkin-abridged/">The Art of Learning : An Inner Journey to Optimal Performance &#8211; Josh Waitzkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In THE ART OF LEARNING,Waitzkin offers an inside look at two of the world&#8217;s most intense subcultures while also sharing the principles at the core of his success. One must focus on long-term goals, Waitzkin argues, instead of the immediate thrill of victory or crush of defeat, enduring the difficult periods that result in growth to reach higher levels of achievement.     </p>
<p>                    As the details of his life are unfolding, Waitzkin explains how these principles apply to his own story, creating a narrative that is as inspiring and instructional as it is gripping.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-learning-an-inner-journey-to-optimal-performance-josh-waitzkin-abridged/">The Art of Learning : An Inner Journey to Optimal Performance &#8211; Josh Waitzkin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Metahuman : Unleashing your infinite potential &#8211; Dr Deepak Chopra (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/metahuman-unleashing-your-infinite-potential-dr-deepak-chopra-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spiritualism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/metahuman-unleashing-your-infinite-potential-dr-deepak-chopra-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is it possible to venture beyond daily living and experience heightened states of awareness? In this highly anticipated new book, integrative medicine pioneer and New York Times bestselling author Deepak Chopra states that a higher state of consciousness is available here and now, for us all. Chopra unlocks the secrets to moving beyond our present [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/metahuman-unleashing-your-infinite-potential-dr-deepak-chopra-abridged/">Metahuman : Unleashing your infinite potential &#8211; Dr Deepak Chopra (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is it possible to venture beyond daily living and experience heightened states of awareness?     </p>
<p>                    In this highly anticipated new book, integrative medicine pioneer and New York Times bestselling author Deepak Chopra states that a higher state of consciousness is available here and now, for us all. Chopra unlocks the secrets to moving beyond our present limitations of the mind to access a field of infinite possibilities and reach our full potential. How do you achieve this? By becoming metahuman.    </p>
<p>                     Drawing from the latest research on neuroscience, artificial intelligence and biometrics, Chopra offers a practical 31 day guide to help us &#8216;wake up&#8217; at the deepest level in order to liberate ourselves from the conditioning and constructs that underlie anxiety, tension and ego driven demands. Only then does your infinite potential become your personal reality.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Grasping this revolutionary idea will effectively remove the limiting belief systems and negativity that may be holding us back from achieving our maximum human potential. Highly recommended!&#8221; Dr Rudolph E. Tanzi    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Metahuman helps us harvest peak experiences so we can see our Truth and mold the universe&#8217;s chaos into a form that brings light to the world&#8217; Dr Mehmet Oz</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/metahuman-unleashing-your-infinite-potential-dr-deepak-chopra-abridged/">Metahuman : Unleashing your infinite potential &#8211; Dr Deepak Chopra (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A New Earth : The life-changing follow up to The Power of Now. &#8216;My No.1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans &#8211; Eckhart Tolle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Anxiety & Phobias]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Stress]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>LIFE-CHANGING&#8217; CAROLINE HINNES Learn to harness the strength of mindfulness and positivity to change your life with Eckhart Tolle THE BOOK THAT INSPIRED THE CHART-TOPPING PODCAST OPRAH &#038; ECKHART TOLLE: A NEW EARTH ____________ Are you ready to change your life? In Eckhart Tolle&#8217;s ground-breaking book, he gives you the spiritual framework to: &#8211; Understand [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/">A New Earth : The life-changing follow up to The Power of Now. &#8216;My No.1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans &#8211; Eckhart Tolle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>LIFE-CHANGING&#8217; CAROLINE HINNES    </p>
<p>                    Learn to harness the strength of mindfulness and positivity to change your life with Eckhart Tolle    </p>
<p>                    THE BOOK THAT INSPIRED THE CHART-TOPPING PODCAST OPRAH &#038; ECKHART TOLLE: A NEW EARTH<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    Are you ready to change your life?    </p>
<p>                    In Eckhart Tolle&#8217;s ground-breaking book, he gives you the spiritual framework to:<br />
                    &#8211; Understand yourself better<br />
                    &#8211; Manage, manifest and achieve your goals<br />
                    &#8211; Reach your full potential<br />
                    &#8211; Channel conflict into something positive<br />
                    &#8211; Change negative habits<br />
                    &#8211; Live in the moment    </p>
<p>                    Open your mind and follow Tolle&#8217;s guidance to happiness and health in the modern world.<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A wake up call for the entire planet. A New Earth helps us to stop creating our own suffering and obsessing over the past and what the future might be and to put ourselves in the now&#8217; Oprah Winfrey    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;My No. 1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans, Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;m gonna have to listen to [this podcast] several times! Too good!&#8217; Fearne Cotton on the &#8216;Oprah and Eckhart Tolle: A New Earth&#8217; podcast    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book changed my life. It&#8217;s a brilliant and very practical spiritual guide that teaches the way to inner peace: how to live in the moment and get beyond the ego&#8217; Santa Montefiore, bestselling author of The Secret Hours</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-new-earth-the-life-changing-follow-up-to-the-power-of-now-my-no-1-guru-will-always-be-eckhart-tolle-chris-evans-eckhart-tolle-abridged/">A New Earth : The life-changing follow up to The Power of Now. &#8216;My No.1 guru will always be Eckhart Tolle&#8217; Chris Evans &#8211; Eckhart Tolle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Book of Joy. The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Dalai Lama, Desmond Tutu (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-book-of-joy-the-sunday-times-bestseller-dalai-lama-desmond-tutu-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious & Spiritual Leaders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tibetan Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-book-of-joy-the-sunday-times-bestseller-dalai-lama-desmond-tutu-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two spiritual giants. Seven days. One timeless question. &#8216;The ultimate source of happiness is within us.&#8217; DALAI LAMA &#8216;We grow in kindness when our kindness is tested.&#8217; DESMOND TUTU Archbishop Desmond Tutu and the Dalai Lama have been friends for many, many years. Between them, they have endured exile, violence and oppression. And in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-joy-the-sunday-times-bestseller-dalai-lama-desmond-tutu-abridged/">The Book of Joy. The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Dalai Lama, Desmond Tutu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two spiritual giants. Seven days. One timeless question.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The ultimate source of happiness is within us.&#8217; DALAI LAMA    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We grow in kindness when our kindness is tested.&#8217; DESMOND TUTU    </p>
<p>                    Archbishop Desmond Tutu and the Dalai Lama have been friends for many, many years. Between them, they have endured exile, violence and oppression. And in the face of these hardships, they have continued to radiate compassion, humour and above all, joy.    </p>
<p>                    To celebrate His Holiness&#8217;s eightieth birthday, Archbishop Tutu travelled to the Dalai Lama&#8217;s home in Dharamsala. The two men spent a week discussing a single burning question: how do we find joy in the face of suffering?    </p>
<p>                    This book is a gift from two of the most important spiritual figures of our time. Full of love, warmth and hope, The Book of Joy offers us the chance to experience their journey from first embrace to final goodbye.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-book-of-joy-the-sunday-times-bestseller-dalai-lama-desmond-tutu-abridged/">The Book of Joy. The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Dalai Lama, Desmond Tutu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Will to Change : Men, Masculinity, and Love &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Men]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everyone needs to love and be loved-even men. But to know love, men must be able to look at the ways that patriarchal culture keeps them from knowing themselves, from being in touch with their feelings, from loving. In The Will to Change, bell hooks gets to the heart of the matter and shows men [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/">The Will to Change : Men, Masculinity, and Love &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everyone needs to love and be loved-even men. But to know love, men must be able to look at the ways that patriarchal culture keeps them from knowing themselves, from being in touch with their feelings, from loving.    </p>
<p>                    In The Will to Change, bell hooks gets to the heart of the matter and shows men how to express the emotions that are a fundamental part of who they are-whatever their age, marital status, ethnicity, or sexual orientation. But toxic masculinity punishes those fundamental emotions, and it&#8217;s so deeply ingrained in our society that it&#8217;s hard for men to not comply-but hooks wants to help change that.    </p>
<p>                    With trademark candor and fierce intelligence, hooks addresses the most common concerns of men, such as fear of intimacy and loss of their patriarchal place in society, in new and challenging ways. She believes men can find the way to spiritual unity by getting back in touch with the emotionally open part of themselves-and lay claim to the rich and rewarding inner lives that have historically been the exclusive province of women. A brave and astonishing work, The Will to Change is designed to help men reclaim the best part of themselves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-will-to-change-men-masculinity-and-love-bell-hooks-abridged/">The Will to Change : Men, Masculinity, and Love &#8211; bell hooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Surrender Experiment : My Journey into Life&#8217;s Perfection &#8211; Michael A. Singer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-surrender-experiment-my-journey-into-lifes-perfection-michael-a-singer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-surrender-experiment-my-journey-into-lifes-perfection-michael-a-singer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael A. Singer, author of The Untethered Soul, tells the extraordinary story of what happened when, after a deep spiritual awakening, he decided to let go of his personal preferences and simply let life call the shots. As Singer takes you on this great experiment and journey into life&#8217;s perfection, the events that transpire will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-surrender-experiment-my-journey-into-lifes-perfection-michael-a-singer-abridged/">The Surrender Experiment : My Journey into Life&#8217;s Perfection &#8211; Michael A. Singer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael A. Singer, author of The Untethered Soul, tells the extraordinary story of what happened when, after a deep spiritual awakening, he decided to let go of his personal preferences and simply let life call the shots. As Singer takes you on this great experiment and journey into life&#8217;s perfection, the events that transpire will both challenge your deepest assumptions about life and inspire you to look at your own life in a radically different way.    </p>
<p>                    Spirituality is meant to bring about harmony and peace. But the diversity of our philosophies, beliefs, concepts, and views about the soul often leads to confusion. To reconcile the noise that clouds spirituality, Michael Singer combines accounts of his own life journey to enlightenment &#8211; from his years as a hippie-loner to his success as a computer program engineer to his work in spiritual and humanitarian efforts &#8211; with lessons on how to put aside conflicting beliefs, let go of worries, and transform misdirected desires. Singer provides a road map to a new way of living not in the moment, but to exist in a state of perpetual happiness.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-surrender-experiment-my-journey-into-lifes-perfection-michael-a-singer-abridged/">The Surrender Experiment : My Journey into Life&#8217;s Perfection &#8211; Michael A. Singer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Hardware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics & Communications Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mobile Phones: Consumer/user Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is your phone the first thing you reach for when you wake up? And the last thing you see before you sleep? Do you find the hours slip away as you idly scroll through your social media timeline? In short, are you addicted to your phone? If so, How to Break Up with Your Phone [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/">How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is your phone the first thing you reach for when you wake up? And the  last thing you see before you sleep? Do you find the hours slip away as  you idly scroll through your social media timeline?     </p>
<p>                     In short, are you addicted to your phone? If so, How to Break Up with Your Phone is here to help.     </p>
<p>                     How to Break Up With Your Phone  is a smart, practical and useful plan to help you conquer your mobile  phone addiction in just 30 days &#8211; and take back your life in the  process.     </p>
<p>                    Recent studies have shown that spending extended time  on our phones affects our ability to form new memories, think deeply,  focus and absorb information, and the hormones triggered every time we  hear our phones buzz both add to our stress levels and are the hallmark  signs of addiction. In How to Break Up with Your Phone,  award-winning science journalist Catherine Price explores the effects  that our constant connectivity is having on our brains, bodies,  relationships, and society at large and asks, how much time do you really want to spend on your phone?     </p>
<p>                    Over  the course of 30 days, Catherine will guide you through an  easy-to-follow plan that enables you to identify your goals, priorities  and bad habits, tidy your apps, prune your email, and take time away.  Lastly, you will create a new, healthier relationship with your phone  and establish habits and routines to ensure this new relationship  sticks.     </p>
<p>                    You don&#8217;t have to give up your phone forever; instead  you will be more mindful not only of how you use your phone, but also  about how you choose to spend the precious moments of your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-break-up-with-your-phone-the-30-day-plan-to-take-back-your-life-catherine-price-abridged/">How to Break Up With Your Phone : The 30-Day Plan to Take Back Your Life &#8211; Catherine Price (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flow : The Psychology of Optimal Experience &#8211; Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/flow-the-psychology-of-optimal-experience-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flow-the-psychology-of-optimal-experience-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Csikszentmihalyi arrives at an insight that many of us can intuitively grasp, despite our insistent (and culturally supported) denial of this truth. That is, it is not what happens to us that determines our happiness, but the manner in which we make sense of that reality. . . . The manner in which Csikszentmihalyi integrates [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flow-the-psychology-of-optimal-experience-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi-abridged/">Flow : The Psychology of Optimal Experience &#8211; Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Csikszentmihalyi arrives at an insight that many of us can intuitively grasp, despite our insistent (and culturally supported) denial of this truth. That is, it is not what happens to us that determines our happiness, but the manner in which we make sense of that reality. . . . The manner in which Csikszentmihalyi integrates research on consciousness, personal psychology and spirituality is illuminating.&#8221; &#8211;Los Angeles Times Book Review    </p>
<p>                    The bestselling classic that holds the key to unlocking meaning, creativity, peak performance, and true happiness.     </p>
<p>                    Legendary psychologist Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi&#8217;s famous investigations of optimal experience have revealed that what makes an experience genuinely satisfying is a state of consciousness called flow. During flow, people typically experience deep enjoyment, creativity, and a total involvement with life. In this new edition of his groundbreaking classic work, Csikszentmihalyi (the leading researcher into &#8216;flow states&#8217; &#8211;Newsweek) demonstrates the ways this positive state can be controlled, not just left to chance. Flow: The Psychology of Optimal Experience teaches how, by ordering the information that enters our consciousness, we can discover true happiness, unlock our potential, and greatly improve the quality of our lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flow-the-psychology-of-optimal-experience-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi-abridged/">Flow : The Psychology of Optimal Experience &#8211; Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Minimalism : Live a Meaningful Life &#8211; Joshua Fields Millburn, Ryan Nicodemus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/minimalism-live-a-meaningful-life-joshua-fields-millburn-ryan-nicodemus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/minimalism-live-a-meaningful-life-joshua-fields-millburn-ryan-nicodemus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Minimalism is the thing that gets us past the things so we can make room for life&#8217;s most important things-which actually aren&#8217;t things at all. At age 30, best friends Joshua Fields Millburn &#038; Ryan Nicodemus walked away from their six-figure corporate careers, jettisoned most of their material possessions, and started focusing on what&#8217;s truly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/minimalism-live-a-meaningful-life-joshua-fields-millburn-ryan-nicodemus-abridged/">Minimalism : Live a Meaningful Life &#8211; Joshua Fields Millburn, Ryan Nicodemus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Minimalism is the thing that gets us past the things so we can make room for life&#8217;s most important things-which actually aren&#8217;t things at all. At age 30, best friends Joshua Fields Millburn &#038; Ryan Nicodemus walked away from their six-figure corporate careers, jettisoned most of their material possessions, and started focusing on what&#8217;s truly important. In their debut book, Joshua &#038; Ryan, authors of the popular website THE MINIMALISTS, explore their troubled pasts and descent into depression. Though they had achieved the American Dream, they worked ridiculous hours, wastefully spent money, and lived paycheck to paycheck. Instead of discovering their passions, they pacified themselves with ephemeral indulgences-which only led to more debt, depression, and discontent. After a pair of life-changing events, Joshua &#038; Ryan discovered minimalism, allowing them to eliminate their excess material things so they could focus on life&#8217;s most important &#8220;things&#8221;: health, relationships, passion, growth, and contribution.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/minimalism-live-a-meaningful-life-joshua-fields-millburn-ryan-nicodemus-abridged/">Minimalism : Live a Meaningful Life &#8211; Joshua Fields Millburn, Ryan Nicodemus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Power of Nunchi : The Korean Secret to Happiness and Success &#8211; Euny Hong (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-power-of-nunchi-the-korean-secret-to-happiness-and-success-euny-hong-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Style Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-power-of-nunchi-the-korean-secret-to-happiness-and-success-euny-hong-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A must-read for anyone interested in the art of intuitively knowing what others feel.&#8217; Haemin Sunim, author of The Things You Can See Only When You Slow Down and Love for Imperfect Things &#8216;A lovely book to have in your home and your lives.&#8217; Chris Evans, Breakfast Show ___________________________ Nunchi (noon-chee): eye measure. The subtle [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-nunchi-the-korean-secret-to-happiness-and-success-euny-hong-abridged/">The Power of Nunchi : The Korean Secret to Happiness and Success &#8211; Euny Hong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A must-read for anyone interested in the art of intuitively knowing what others feel.&#8217; Haemin Sunim, author of The Things You Can See Only When You Slow Down and Love for Imperfect Things     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A lovely book to have in your home and your lives.&#8217; Chris Evans, Breakfast Show<br />
                    ___________________________    </p>
<p>                    Nunchi (noon-chee): eye measure. The subtle art of gauging other people&#8217;s thoughts, and feelings in order to build trust, harmony and connection.<br />
                    ___________________________    </p>
<p>                    Why did she get promoted? Why does the party only start when he walks in? And why do they always catch the bartender&#8217;s eye? It sounds like they&#8217;re all experts in the art of nunchi, even if they don&#8217;t know it.     </p>
<p>                    Nunchi is the guiding principle of Korean life, but anyone can use it: it&#8217;s the art of reading a room, your way of understanding what other people are thinking and feeling, and using that to get ahead.    </p>
<p>                    Korean parents believe that teaching their children nunchi is as important as teaching them to cross the road safely. With great nunchi, it feels like the world is on your side. Without it, you might get hit by something you never saw coming.    </p>
<p>                    If you&#8217;re thinking &#8216;not another Eastern fad, Marie Kondo already made me throw half my clothes away&#8217;, don&#8217;t worry: it&#8217;s not a fad. Koreans have been using nunchi to overcome slings and arrows for over 5000 years.    </p>
<p>                    The great news is that anyone can hone their nunchi, immediately: all you need are your eyes and ears. In everything, from finding love to excelling at work, improving your nunchi will help you to open doors you never knew existed.    </p>
<p>                    Improve your nunchi, improve your life.<br />
                    ___________________________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Whip-smart, hilarious, and filled with eye-opening insights on every page.&#8217; Amy Chua, author of Battle Hymn of the Tiger Mother    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Beautifully written and filled with actionable advice . . . It really feels like having a superpower!&#8217; Hector Garcia, co-author of Ikigai: The Japanese Secret to a Long and Happy Life    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Nunchi is the Korean superpower you need now&#8217; Evening Standard    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We could all help ourselves by practising the ancient art of Nunchi&#8217; The Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-power-of-nunchi-the-korean-secret-to-happiness-and-success-euny-hong-abridged/">The Power of Nunchi : The Korean Secret to Happiness and Success &#8211; Euny Hong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Make Your Bed : Feel grounded and think positive in 10 simple steps &#8211; Admiral William H. McRaven (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Therapies, Healing & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Men's Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Make a new start in 2022 with positive daily habits for a healthy mind, from the incredible No. 1 New York Times bestseller THE INCREDIBLE NO. 1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;SUPERB, SMART, AND SUCCINCT&#8217; FORBES ______ Struggling to find structure? Finding yourself lacking motivation? Start by making your bed. Maintaining routine and structure is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/">Make Your Bed : Feel grounded and think positive in 10 simple steps &#8211; Admiral William H. McRaven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Make a new start in 2022 with positive daily habits for a healthy mind, from the incredible No. 1 New York Times bestseller    </p>
<p>                    THE INCREDIBLE NO. 1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;SUPERB, SMART, AND SUCCINCT&#8217; FORBES<br />
                    ______    </p>
<p>                    Struggling to find structure? Finding yourself lacking motivation?    </p>
<p>                    Start by making your bed.    </p>
<p>                    Maintaining routine and structure is more important than ever in the age of home working, flexi-time and the general chaos of life.    </p>
<p>                    In Make Your Bed, Admiral William H. McRaven shares 10 life lessons he learned during his Navy Seal training that helped him overcome challenges not only in his long Naval career, but also throughout his life.    </p>
<p>                    He will teach you how to . . .<br />
                    * Master the essential daily habits for staying grounded<br />
                    * Learn how to keep your mind calm and ready for the day ahead<br />
                    * Find solace and companionship in the people around you<br />
                    * Cope with setbacks and keep moving forward<br />
                    * Stray beyond your comfort zone and take risks    </p>
<p>                    Written with great humility and optimism, this timeless book provides simple and universal wisdom, practical advice, and words of encouragement that will inspire every reader.<br />
                    ______    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book to inspire your children and grandchildren to become everything that they can&#8217; The Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/make-your-bed-feel-grounded-and-think-positive-in-10-simple-steps-admiral-william-h-mcraven-abridged/">Make Your Bed : Feel grounded and think positive in 10 simple steps &#8211; Admiral William H. McRaven (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Women Food and God : An Unexpected Path to Almost Everything &#8211; Geneen Roth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/women-food-and-god-an-unexpected-path-to-almost-everything-geneen-roth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/women-food-and-god-an-unexpected-path-to-almost-everything-geneen-roth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Millions of us are locked into an unwinnable weight game, as our self-worth is shredded with every diet failure. Combine the utter inefficacy of dieting with the lack of spiritual nourishment and we have generations of mad, ravenous self-loathing women. So says Geneen Roth, in her life-changing new book, Women, Food and God. Since her [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-food-and-god-an-unexpected-path-to-almost-everything-geneen-roth-abridged/">Women Food and God : An Unexpected Path to Almost Everything &#8211; Geneen Roth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Millions of us are locked into an unwinnable weight game, as our self-worth is shredded with every diet failure. Combine the utter inefficacy of dieting with the lack of spiritual nourishment and we have generations of mad, ravenous self-loathing women. So says Geneen Roth, in her life-changing new book, Women, Food and God. Since her 1991 bestseller, When Food Is Love, was published, Roth has taken the sum total of her experience and combined it with spirituality and psychology to explain women&#8217;s true hunger. Roth&#8217;s approach to eating is that it is the same as any addiction &#8211; an activity to avoid feeling emotions. From the first page, readers will be struck by the author&#8217;s intelligence, humour and sensitivity, as she traces the path of overeating from its subtle beginnings through to its logical end. Whether the drug is booze or brownies, the problem is the same: opting out of life. She powerfully urges readers to pay attention to what they truly need &#8211; which cannot be found in a supermarket.<br />
                    She provides seven basic guidelines for eating (the most important is to never diet) and shares reassuring, practical advice that has helped thousands of women who have attended her highly successful seminars. Truly a thinking woman&#8217;s guide to eating &#8211; and an anti-diet book &#8211; women everywhere will find insights and revelations on every page.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/women-food-and-god-an-unexpected-path-to-almost-everything-geneen-roth-abridged/">Women Food and God : An Unexpected Path to Almost Everything &#8211; Geneen Roth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Joy Of Movement : How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage &#8211; Kelly Mcgonigal (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Exercise & Workout Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of The Willpower Instinct introduces a surprising science-based book that doesn&#8217;t tell us why we should exercise but instead shows us how to fall in love with movement. Exercise is health-enhancing and life-extending, yet many of us feel it&#8217;s a chore. But, as Kelly McGonigal reveals, it doesn&#8217;t have to be. Movement [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/">The Joy Of Movement : How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage &#8211; Kelly Mcgonigal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling author of The Willpower Instinct introduces a surprising science-based book that doesn&#8217;t tell us why we should exercise but instead shows us how to fall in love with movement.    </p>
<p>                    Exercise is health-enhancing and life-extending, yet many of us feel it&#8217;s a chore. But, as Kelly McGonigal reveals, it doesn&#8217;t have to be. Movement can and should be a source of joy.    </p>
<p>                    Through her trademark blend of science and storytelling, McGonigal draws on insights from neuroscience, psychology, anthropology, and evolutionary biology, as well as memoirs, ethnographies, and philosophers. She shows how movement is intertwined with some of the most basic human joys, including self-expression, social connection, and mastery&#8211;and why it is a powerful antidote to the modern epidemics of depression, anxiety, and loneliness.    </p>
<p>                    McGonigal tells the stories of people who have found fulfillment and belonging through running, walking, dancing, swimming, weightlifting, and more, with examples that span the globe, from Tanzania, where one of the last hunter-gatherer tribes on the planet live, to a dance class at Juilliard for people with Parkinson&#8217;s disease, to the streets of London, where volunteers combine fitness and community service, to races in the remote wilderness, where athletes push the limits of what a human can endure. Along the way, McGonigal paints a portrait of human nature that highlights our capacity for hope, cooperation, and self-transcendence.    </p>
<p>                    The result is a revolutionary narrative that goes beyond familiar arguments in favor of exercise, to illustrate why movement is integral to both our happiness and our humanity. Readers will learn what they can do in their own lives and communities to harness the power of movement to create happiness, meaning, and connection.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-joy-of-movement-how-exercise-helps-us-find-happiness-hope-connection-and-courage-kelly-mcgonigal-abridged/">The Joy Of Movement : How Exercise Helps Us Find Happiness, Hope, Connection, and Courage &#8211; Kelly Mcgonigal (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret &#8211; Rhonda Byrne (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-secret-rhonda-byrne-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-rhonda-byrne-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2006, a groundbreaking feature-length film revealed the great mystery of the universe &#8211; The Secret. Later that year, Rhonda Byrne followed with a book that became a worldwide bestseller. Fragments of a Great Secret have been found in the oral traditions, in literature, in religions and philosophies throughout the centuries. For the first time, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-rhonda-byrne-abridged/">The Secret &#8211; Rhonda Byrne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2006, a groundbreaking feature-length film revealed the great mystery of the universe &#8211; The Secret. Later that year, Rhonda Byrne followed with a book that became a worldwide bestseller.     </p>
<p>                    Fragments of a Great Secret have been found in the oral traditions, in literature, in religions and philosophies throughout the centuries. For the first time, all the pieces of The Secret come together in an incredible revelation that will be life-transforming for all who experience it.    </p>
<p>                    In this book, you&#8217;ll learn how to use The Secret in every aspect of your life &#8211; money, health, relationships, happiness, and in every interaction you have in the world. You&#8217;ll begin to understand the hidden, untapped power that&#8217;s within you, and this revelation can bring joy to every aspect of your life.    </p>
<p>                    The Secret contains wisdom from modern-day teachers &#8211; men and women who have used it to achieve health, wealth and happiness. By applying the knowledge of The Secret, they bring to light compelling stories of eradicating obstacles, and achieving what many would regard as impossible.    </p>
<p>                    Discover the book which has been changing millions of lives around the world. No matter who you are, where you are right now, no matter what you want &#8211; when you realise The Secret you can have anything.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-rhonda-byrne-abridged/">The Secret &#8211; Rhonda Byrne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Altruism : The Science and Psychology of Kindness &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/altruism-the-science-and-psychology-of-kindness-matthieu-ricard-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Meditation & Visualisation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/altruism-the-science-and-psychology-of-kindness-matthieu-ricard-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The concern for the well-being of others could be the saving grace of the 21st century. Matthieu Ricard&#8217;s Altruism, an erudite, brilliantly ranging synthesis of philosophy, psychology and ages old wisdom, is a radical call to kindness, which has the potential as a new global movement to answer the biggest problems of our time: the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/altruism-the-science-and-psychology-of-kindness-matthieu-ricard-abridged/">Altruism : The Science and Psychology of Kindness &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The concern for the well-being of others could be the saving grace of the 21st century. Matthieu Ricard&#8217;s Altruism, an erudite, brilliantly ranging synthesis of philosophy, psychology and ages old wisdom, is a radical call to kindness, which has the potential as a new global movement to answer the biggest problems of our time: the economy in the short term, life satisfaction in the mid-term, and the environment in the long term. As the faultlines of inequality and nationalism leave us ever more divided, Ricard challenges us to be better people &#8211; and in the process, make the world a better place.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/altruism-the-science-and-psychology-of-kindness-matthieu-ricard-abridged/">Altruism : The Science and Psychology of Kindness &#8211; Matthieu Ricard (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
