<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>International Relations Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/international-relations/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/international-relations/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>International Relations Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/international-relations/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Accessory to War : The Unspoken Alliance Between Astrophysics and the Military &#8211; Neil deGrasse Tyson</title>
		<link>/accessory-to-war-the-unspoken-alliance-between-astrophysics-and-the-military-neil-degrasse-tyson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrophysics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Space Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Warfare & Military Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/accessory-to-war-the-unspoken-alliance-between-astrophysics-and-the-military-neil-degrasse-tyson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this fascinating foray into the millennia-long relationship between science and military power, acclaimed astrophysicist and &#8220;the world&#8217;s best science communicator&#8221; (Times Literary Supplement) Neil deGrasse Tyson and writer-researcher Avis Lang examine how the methods and tools of astrophysics have been enlisted in the service of war. &#8220;The overlap is strong, and the knowledge flows [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accessory-to-war-the-unspoken-alliance-between-astrophysics-and-the-military-neil-degrasse-tyson/">Accessory to War : The Unspoken Alliance Between Astrophysics and the Military &#8211; Neil deGrasse Tyson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this fascinating foray into the millennia-long relationship between science and military power, acclaimed astrophysicist and &#8220;the world&#8217;s best science communicator&#8221; (Times Literary Supplement) Neil deGrasse Tyson and writer-researcher Avis Lang examine how the methods and tools of astrophysics have been enlisted in the service of war. &#8220;The overlap is strong, and the knowledge flows in both directions&#8221;, say the authors, because astrophysicists and military planners care about many of the same things: multi-spectral detection, ranging, tracking, imaging, high ground, nuclear fusion and access to space. Tyson and Lang call it a &#8220;curiously complicit&#8221; alliance. &#8220;The universe is both the ultimate frontier and the highest of high grounds&#8221;, they write. &#8220;Shared by both space scientists and space warriors, it&#8217;s a laboratory for one and a battlefield for the other. The explorer wants to understand it; the soldier wants to dominate it. But without the right technology-which is more or less the same technology for both parties-nobody can get to it, operate in it, scrutinise it, dominate it or use it to their advantage and someone else&#8217;s disadvantage.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                     Spanning early celestial navigation to satellite-enabled warfare, Accessory to War is a richly researched and provocative examination of the intersection of science, technology, industry and power that will introduce Tyson&#8217;s millions of fans to yet another dimension of how the universe has shaped our lives and our world.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/accessory-to-war-the-unspoken-alliance-between-astrophysics-and-the-military-neil-degrasse-tyson/">Accessory to War : The Unspoken Alliance Between Astrophysics and the Military &#8211; Neil deGrasse Tyson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Monsoon : The Indian Ocean and the Future of American Power &#8211; Robert D. Kaplan</title>
		<link>/monsoon-the-indian-ocean-and-the-future-of-american-power-robert-d-kaplan/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/monsoon-the-indian-ocean-and-the-future-of-american-power-robert-d-kaplan/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>On the world maps common in America, the Western Hemisphere lies front and center, while the Indian Ocean region all but disappears. This convention reveals the geopolitical focus of the now-departed twentieth century, but in the twenty-first century that focus will fundamentally change. In this pivotal examination of the countries known as &#8220;Monsoon Asia&#8221;&#8211;which include [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/monsoon-the-indian-ocean-and-the-future-of-american-power-robert-d-kaplan/">Monsoon : The Indian Ocean and the Future of American Power &#8211; Robert D. Kaplan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On the world maps common in America, the Western Hemisphere lies front and center, while the Indian Ocean region all but disappears. This convention reveals the geopolitical focus of the now-departed twentieth century, but in the twenty-first century that focus will fundamentally change. In this pivotal examination of the countries known as &#8220;Monsoon Asia&#8221;&#8211;which include India, Pakistan, China, Indonesia, Burma, Oman, Sri Lanka, Bangladesh, and Tanzania&#8211;bestselling author Robert D. Kaplan shows how crucial this dynamic area has become to American power. It is here that the fight for democracy, energy independence, and religious freedom will be lost or won, and it is here that American foreign policy must concentrate if the United States is to remain relevant in an ever-changing world. From the Horn of Africa to the Indonesian archipelago and beyond, Kaplan exposes the effects of population growth, climate change, and extremist politics on this unstable region, demonstrating why Americans can no longer afford to ignore this important area of the world.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/monsoon-the-indian-ocean-and-the-future-of-american-power-robert-d-kaplan/">Monsoon : The Indian Ocean and the Future of American Power &#8211; Robert D. Kaplan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</title>
		<link>/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As President Trump&#8217;s National Security Advisor, John Bolton spent many of his 453 days in the room where it happened, and the facts speak for themselves. The result is a White House memoir that is the most comprehensive and substantial account of the Trump Administration, and one of the few to date by a top-level [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/">The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As President Trump&#8217;s National Security Advisor, John Bolton spent many of his 453 days in the room where it happened, and the facts speak for themselves. </p>
<p>                    The result is a White House memoir that is the most comprehensive and substantial account of the Trump Administration, and one of the few to date by a top-level official. With almost daily access to the President, John Bolton has produced a precise rendering of his days in and around the Oval Office. What Bolton saw astonished him: a President for whom getting reelected was the only thing that mattered, even if it meant endangering or weakening the nation. &#8220;I am hard-pressed to identify any significant Trump decision during my tenure that wasn&#8217;t driven by reelection calculations,&#8221; he writes. In fact, he argues that the House committed impeachment malpractice by keeping their prosecution focused narrowly on Ukraine when Trump&#8217;s Ukraine-like transgressions existed across the full range of his foreign policy-and Bolton documents exactly what those were, and attempts by him and others in the Administration to raise alarms about them.</p>
<p>                    He shows a President addicted to chaos, who embraced our enemies and spurned our friends, and was deeply suspicious of his own government. In Bolton&#8217;s telling, all this helped put Trump on the bizarre road to impeachment. &#8220;The differences between this presidency and previous ones I had served were stunning,&#8221; writes Bolton, who worked for Reagan, Bush 41, and Bush 43. He discovered a President who thought foreign policy is like closing a real estate deal-about personal relationships, made-for-TV showmanship, and advancing his own interests. As a result, the US lost an opportunity to confront its deepening threats, and in cases like China, Russia, Iran, and North Korea ended up in a more vulnerable place. </p>
<p>                    Bolton&#8217;s account starts with his long march to the West Wing as Trump and others woo him for the National Security job. The minute he lands, he has to deal with Syria&#8217;s chemical attack on the city of Douma, and the crises after that never stop. As he writes in the opening pages, &#8220;If you don&#8217;t like turmoil, uncertainty, and risk-all the while being constantly overwhelmed with information, decisions to be made, and sheer amount of work-and enlivened by international and domestic personality and ego conflicts beyond description, try something else.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    The turmoil, conflicts, and egos are all there-from the upheaval in Venezuela, to the erratic and manipulative moves of North Korea&#8217;s Kim Jong Un, to the showdowns at the G7 summits, the calculated warmongering by Iran, the crazy plan to bring the Taliban to Camp David, and the placating of an authoritarian China that ultimately exposed the world to its lethal lies. But this seasoned public servant also has a great eye for the Washington inside game, and his story is full of wit and wry humor about how he saw it played.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/">The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EU & European Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Crises & Disasters]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>** The Sunday Times #1 Bestseller** &#8216;One of the greatest political memoirs of all time&#8217; Guardian What happens when you take on the European establishment? Read as world-famous, provocative economist, and former Greece finance minister, Yanis Varoufakis, blows the lid on his battle with EU officials over the Greek debt crisis. Varoufakis sparked one of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/">Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>** The Sunday Times #1 Bestseller**    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the greatest political memoirs of all time&#8217; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    What happens when you take on the European establishment?     </p>
<p>                    Read as world-famous, provocative economist, and former Greece finance minister, Yanis Varoufakis, blows the lid on his battle with EU officials over the Greek debt crisis.     </p>
<p>                                                                                                                                                                                              Varoufakis sparked one of the most spectacular and controversial battles in recent political history with his attempt to renegotiate Greece&#8217;s relationship with the European Union. Yet despite the mass support of the Greek people, and simple logic of his arguments, he succeeded only in provoking the fury of Europe&#8217;s political, financial and media elite.<br />
                                                                                                                                                                                          Exposing the real business taking place behind the EU&#8217;s closed doors, Varoufakis reveals all in this fearless, personal account. Adults In The Room is an extraordinary tale of brinkmanship, hypocrisy, collusion and betrayal that will shake the European and economic establishment to its foundations.     </p>
<p>                    Varoufakis is sending out an urgent wake-up call to renew European democracy before it is too late.    </p>
<p>                    **ONE OF THE GUARDIAN&#8217;S 100 BEST BOOKS OF THE 21st CENTURY**</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adults-in-the-room-my-battle-with-europes-deep-establishment-yanis-varoufakis-abridged/">Adults In The Room : My Battle With Europe&#8217;s Deep Establishment &#8211; Yanis Varoufakis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Clash Of Civilizations : And The Remaking Of World Order &#8211; Samuel P. Huntington (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-clash-of-civilizations-and-the-remaking-of-world-order-samuel-p-huntington-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Defence Strategy, Planning & Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-clash-of-civilizations-and-the-remaking-of-world-order-samuel-p-huntington-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 1993 the esteemed journal FOREIGN AFFAIRS published an article entitled &#8220;The Clash of Civilizations?&#8221; by Samuel P. Huntington. According to the journal&#8217;s editors it went on to generate more discussion than anything they had published since the Second World War. In the article, Huntington posed the question whether conflicts between civilizations would dominate the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-clash-of-civilizations-and-the-remaking-of-world-order-samuel-p-huntington-abridged/">The Clash Of Civilizations : And The Remaking Of World Order &#8211; Samuel P. Huntington (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 1993 the esteemed journal FOREIGN AFFAIRS published an article entitled &#8220;The Clash of Civilizations?&#8221; by Samuel P. Huntington. According to the journal&#8217;s editors it went on to generate more discussion than anything they had published since the Second World War. In the article, Huntington posed the question whether conflicts between civilizations would dominate the future of world politics. In the book, he gives the answer, showing not only how clashes between civilizations are the greatest threat to world peace but also how an international order based on civilizations is the best safeguard against war. Since September 11, his thesis has seemed even more prescient and acute. THE CLASH OF CIVILIZATIONS AND THE REMAKING OF WORLD ORDER is now recognised as a classic study of international relations in an increasingly uncertain world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-clash-of-civilizations-and-the-remaking-of-world-order-samuel-p-huntington-abridged/">The Clash Of Civilizations : And The Remaking Of World Order &#8211; Samuel P. Huntington (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Two Nations Indivisible : Mexico, the United States, and the Road Ahead &#8211; Shannon K. O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/two-nations-indivisible-mexico-the-united-states-and-the-road-ahead-shannon-k-oneil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/two-nations-indivisible-mexico-the-united-states-and-the-road-ahead-shannon-k-oneil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Overlooked in today&#8217;s bloody headlines is Mexico&#8217;s fundamental transformation. In over three short decades it has gone from a poor to a middle class nation, a closed to an open economy, an authoritarian to a vibrant (if at times messy) democracy, and a local to an increasingly binational society. But while things are much better [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/two-nations-indivisible-mexico-the-united-states-and-the-road-ahead-shannon-k-oneil-abridged/">Two Nations Indivisible : Mexico, the United States, and the Road Ahead &#8211; Shannon K. O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Overlooked in today&#8217;s bloody headlines is Mexico&#8217;s fundamental transformation. In over three short decades it has gone from a poor to a middle class nation, a closed to an open economy, an authoritarian to a vibrant (if at times messy) democracy, and a local to an increasingly binational society. But while things are much better than portrayed, Mexico does face a true security challenge. It stands at a crossroads. It can follow a path toward a top ten economy, an<br />
                    open democracy, and a leading world voice, or one that spirals down into drug-fueled corruption and violence. Today&#8217;s choices will define not only Mexico&#8217;s future, but also that of the United States. Perhaps no other nation is as indelibly intertwined with our economy, society, and daily lives. What<br />
                    happens in Mexico will affect the United States for decades to come.    </p>
<p>                    Two Nations Indivisible tells the story of the making of modern Mexico, and what it means for the United States. Recounting the economic, political, social, and security changes of the last thirty years, it provides a roadmap for the greatest overlooked foreign policy challenge of our time -relations with our southern neighbor. For the good of both countries, it argues against walling the United States off from its neighbor; and instead for investing finally in a true<br />
                    partnership.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/two-nations-indivisible-mexico-the-united-states-and-the-road-ahead-shannon-k-oneil-abridged/">Two Nations Indivisible : Mexico, the United States, and the Road Ahead &#8211; Shannon K. O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Every Nation for Itself : Winners and Losers in a G-Zero World &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Following the acclaim for The End of the Free Market, Ian Bremmer is back with Every Nation for Itself, now in paperback, where he addresses the next big issue for the shifting world economy. &#8216;Smart and snappy &#8230; provides the most cogent prediction of how the politics of a post-America world will play out&#8217; New [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Every Nation for Itself : Winners and Losers in a G-Zero World &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Following the acclaim for The End of the Free Market, Ian Bremmer is back with Every Nation for Itself, now in paperback, where he addresses the next big issue for the shifting world economy.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Smart and snappy &#8230; provides the most cogent prediction of how the politics of a post-America world will play out&#8217;  New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    What happens when nobody&#8217;s running the world?    </p>
<p>                    The United States is in financial crisis and can&#8217;t hold onto the reins of the G-20. But China has no interest in international leadership, Europe is trying to save the euro, and emerging powers like Brazil and India are focused on domestic development. No government has the time, resources or political capital needed to take an international lead. The world power structure is about to have a vacancy&#8230;at the top.    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to the G-Zero world, in which no single country has the power to shape a truly global agenda. That means we are about to see 20 years of conflict over economics, finance and climate change.    </p>
<p>                    Bestselling author and strategist Ian Bremmer reveals how world powers are rapidly turning into gated communities, locked in competition. Who will prevail?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A prodigy in the US global commentariat. Mr Bremmer&#8217;s rehearsal of the consequences should make us all wise up&#8217; Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An author who is always full of insights&#8217; George Osborne    </p>
<p>                    Ian Bremmer is the president of the world&#8217;s leading global political risk research and consulting firm, Eurasia Group. He has written for the Wall Street Journal, Washington Post, Newsweek, and Harvard Business Review. His six books include The J Curve and The End Of The Free Market.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/every-nation-for-itself-winners-and-losers-in-a-g-zero-world-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Every Nation for Itself : Winners and Losers in a G-Zero World &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Connection is a story of political skullduggery unprecedented in American history. It weaves together tales of international intrigue, cyber espionage, and superpower rivalry. After US-Russia relations soured, as Vladimir Putin moved to reassert Russian strength on the global stage, Moscow trained its best hackers on US political targets and exploited Julian Assange and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/">Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Connection is a story of political skullduggery unprecedented in American history. It weaves together tales of international intrigue, cyber espionage, and superpower rivalry. After US-Russia relations soured, as Vladimir Putin moved to reassert Russian strength on the global stage, Moscow trained its best hackers on US political targets and exploited Julian Assange and Wikileaks to disseminate information that could affect the 2016 election.     </p>
<p>                    The Russians were wildly successful and the great break-in of 2016 was no &#8220;third rate burglary.&#8221; It was far more sophisticated and sinister &#8212; a brazen act of political espionage designed to interfere with American democracy, and at the end of the day, Trump, the candidate with business ties to Russia, won. And millions of Americans were left wondering, what the hell happened?    </p>
<p>                    This story of high-tech spying and multiple political feuds will be told against the backdrop of Donald Trump and his strange relationship with Putin, and his inner circle of advisers with profitable ties to Russia, most notably Michael Flynn and Paul Manafort.    </p>
<p>                    The Russian Connection will chronicle and examine all these bizarre events and relationships, explain the stakes, and seek to answer one of the biggest questions in American politics: How and why did a foreign government infiltrate the country&#8217;s political process and implant its tentacles in Washington?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/">Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Looming Tower : Al Qaeda&#8217;s Road to 9/11 &#8211; Lawrence Wright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-looming-tower-al-qaedas-road-to-9-11-lawrence-wright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism, Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-looming-tower-al-qaedas-road-to-9-11-lawrence-wright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE PULITZER PRIZE-WINNING BESTSELLER, NOW AN ACCLAIMED TV SERIES This is the definitive account of the run-up to 9/11: from the man who lit the spark of radical Islam in 1948, to those who built up a terror network, and to the FBI agent whose warnings of &#8216;something big&#8217; coming were ignored until the Twin [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-looming-tower-al-qaedas-road-to-9-11-lawrence-wright-abridged/">The Looming Tower : Al Qaeda&#8217;s Road to 9/11 &#8211; Lawrence Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE PULITZER PRIZE-WINNING BESTSELLER, NOW AN ACCLAIMED TV SERIES    </p>
<p>                    This is the definitive account of the run-up to 9/11: from the man who lit the spark of radical Islam in 1948, to those who built up a terror network, and to the FBI agent whose warnings of &#8216;something big&#8217; coming were ignored until the Twin Towers fell.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The Looming Tower is a thriller. And it&#8217;s a tragedy, too&#8217; The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The most detailed (and thrilling) account we have of the events that led to the destruction of the Twin Towers&#8217; Observer, Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Possibly the best book yet written on the rise of al-Qaeda &#8230; beautifully written and wonderfully compelling&#8217; William Dalrymple    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We meet some formidable schemers and killers &#8230; fabulists crazed with blood and death&#8217; Martin Amis</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-looming-tower-al-qaedas-road-to-9-11-lawrence-wright-abridged/">The Looming Tower : Al Qaeda&#8217;s Road to 9/11 &#8211; Lawrence Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Short History of Brexit : From Brentry to Backstop &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Rourke (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EU & European Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Institutions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Crisp, clear and quietly devastating&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Excellent, authoritative, highly readable&#8217; Irish Times A succinct, expert guide to how we got to Brexit After all the debates, manoeuvrings, recriminations and exaltations, Brexit is upon us. But, as Kevin O&#8217;Rourke writes, Brexit did not emerge out of nowhere: it is the culmination of events that have been [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/">A Short History of Brexit : From Brentry to Backstop &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Rourke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Crisp, clear and quietly devastating&#8217; Guardian<br />
                    &#8216;Excellent, authoritative, highly readable&#8217; Irish Times    </p>
<p>                    A succinct, expert guide to how we got to Brexit    </p>
<p>                    After all the debates, manoeuvrings, recriminations and exaltations,  Brexit is upon us. But, as Kevin O&#8217;Rourke writes, Brexit did not emerge  out of nowhere: it is the culmination of events  that have been under  way for decades and have historical roots stretching back well beyond  that. Brexit has a history.    </p>
<p>                    O&#8217;Rourke, one of the leading economic  historians of his generation, explains not only how British attitudes  to Europe have evolved, but also how the EU&#8217;s history explains why it  operates as it does today &#8211; and how that history has shaped the ways in  which it has responded to Brexit. Why are the economics, the politics  and the history so tightly woven together? Crucially, he also explains  why the question of the Irish border is not just one of customs and  trade, but for the EU goes to the heart of what it is about.  The way in  which British, Irish and European histories continue to interact with  each other will shape the future of Brexit &#8211; and of the continent.    </p>
<p>                    Calm and lucid, A Short History of Brexit  rises above the usual fray of discussions to provide fresh perspectives  and understanding of the most momentous political and economic change  in Britain and the EU for decades.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-short-history-of-brexit-from-brentry-to-backstop-kevin-orourke-abridged/">A Short History of Brexit : From Brentry to Backstop &#8211; Kevin O&#8217;Rourke (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The WikiLeaks Files : The World According to US Empire &#8211; Wikileaks, Introduction by Julian Assange (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-wikileaks-files-the-world-according-to-us-empire-wikileaks-introduction-by-julian-assange-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wikileaks-files-the-world-according-to-us-empire-wikileaks-introduction-by-julian-assange-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When WikiLeaks first came to prominence in 2010, releasing millions of top secret State Department cables, the world saw for the first time what the US really thought about national leaders, friendly dictators, and supposed allies. It also discovered the dark truths of national policies, human rights violations, covert operations, and cover-ups done in your [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wikileaks-files-the-world-according-to-us-empire-wikileaks-introduction-by-julian-assange-abridged/">The WikiLeaks Files : The World According to US Empire &#8211; Wikileaks, Introduction by Julian Assange (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When WikiLeaks first came to prominence in 2010, releasing millions of top secret State Department cables, the world saw for the first time what the US really thought about national leaders, friendly dictators, and supposed allies. It also discovered the dark truths of national policies, human rights violations, covert operations, and cover-ups done in your name. The WikiLeaks Files is the first volume that uses experts to collate and analyze the most important cables and show their historic importance. An essential book for anyone who is interested in America&#8217;s role in the world and the history of the twenty-first century. Regional expert contributors include Tim Shorrock, Richard Heydarian, Russ Wellen, Conn Hallinan, Michael Busch, Robert Prince, Stephen Zunes, Peter Certo, Francis Nesbitt, Phyllis Bennis, and Gareth Porter.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wikileaks-files-the-world-according-to-us-empire-wikileaks-introduction-by-julian-assange-abridged/">The WikiLeaks Files : The World According to US Empire &#8211; Wikileaks, Introduction by Julian Assange (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A World In Disarray : American Foreign Policy and the Crisis of the Old Order &#8211; Richard Haass (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-world-in-disarray-american-foreign-policy-and-the-crisis-of-the-old-order-richard-haass-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-world-in-disarray-american-foreign-policy-and-the-crisis-of-the-old-order-richard-haass-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A valuable primer on foreign policy: a primer that concerned citizens of all political persuasions&#8211;not to mention the president and his advisers&#8211;could benefit from reading.&#8221; &#8211;The New York Times An examination of a world increasingly defined by disorder and a United States unable to shape the world in its image, from the president of the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-world-in-disarray-american-foreign-policy-and-the-crisis-of-the-old-order-richard-haass-abridged/">A World In Disarray : American Foreign Policy and the Crisis of the Old Order &#8211; Richard Haass (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A valuable primer on foreign policy: a primer that concerned citizens of all political persuasions&#8211;not to mention the president and his advisers&#8211;could benefit from reading.&#8221; &#8211;The New York Times An examination of a world increasingly defined by disorder and a United States unable to shape the world in its image, from the president of the Council on Foreign Relations Things fall apart; the center cannot hold. The rules, policies, and institutions that have guided the world since World War II have largely run their course. Respect for sovereignty alone cannot uphold order in an age defined by global challenges from terrorism and the spread of nuclear weapons to climate change and cyberspace. Meanwhile, great power rivalry is returning. Weak states pose problems just as confounding as strong ones. The United States remains the world&#8217;s strongest country, but American foreign policy has at times made matters worse, both by what the U.S. has done and by what it has failed to do. The Middle East is in chaos, Asia is threatened by China&#8217;s rise and a reckless North Korea, and Europe, for decades the world&#8217;s most stable region, is now anything but. As Richard Haass explains, the election of Donald Trump and the unexpected vote for &#8220;Brexit&#8221; signals that many in modern democracies reject important aspects of globalization, including borders open to trade and immigrants.  In A World in Disarray, Haass argues for an updated global operating system&#8211;call it world order 2.0&#8211;that reflects the reality that power is widely distributed and that borders count for less. One critical element of this adjustment will be adopting a new approach to sovereignty, one that embraces its obligations and responsibilities as well as its rights and protections. Haass also details how the U.S. should act towards China and Russia, as well as in Asia, Europe, and the Middle East. He suggests, too, what the country should do to address its dysfunctional politics, mounting debt, and the lack of agreement on the nature of its relationship with the world.  A World in Disarray is a wise examination, one rich in history, of the current world, along with how we got here and what needs doing. Haass shows that the world cannot have stability or prosperity without the United States, but that the United States cannot be a force for global stability and prosperity without its politicians and citizens reaching a new understanding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-world-in-disarray-american-foreign-policy-and-the-crisis-of-the-old-order-richard-haass-abridged/">A World In Disarray : American Foreign Policy and the Crisis of the Old Order &#8211; Richard Haass (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Viruses, Trojans & Worms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award! There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life. In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award!<br />
                    There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life.<br />
                    In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest spam and hacker operations targeting Americans and their bank accounts. Tracing the rise, fall, and alarming resurrection of the digital mafia behind the two largest spam pharmacies-and countless viruses, phishing, and spyware attacks-he delivers the first definitive narrative of the global spam problem and its threat to consumers everywhere.<br />
                    Blending cutting-edge research, investigative reporting, and firsthand interviews, this terrifying true story reveals how we unwittingly invite these digital thieves into our lives every day. From unassuming computer programmers right next door to digital mobsters like &#8220;Cosma&#8221;-who unleashed a massive malware attack that has stolen thousands of Americans&#8217; logins and passwords-Krebs uncovers the shocking lengths to which these people will go to profit from our data and our wallets.<br />
                    Not only are hundreds of thousands of Americans exposing themselves to fraud and dangerously toxic products from rogue online pharmacies, but even those who never open junk messages are at risk. As Krebs notes, spammers can-and do-hack into accounts through these emails, harvest personal information like usernames and passwords, and sell them on the digital black market. The fallout from this global epidemic doesn&#8217;t just cost consumers and companies billions, it costs lives too.<br />
                    Fast-paced and utterly gripping, Spam Nation ultimately proposes concrete solutions for protecting ourselves online and stemming this tidal wave of cybercrime-before it&#8217;s too late.<br />
                    &#8220;Krebs&#8217;s talent for exposing the weaknesses in online security has earned him respect in the IT business and loathing among cybercriminals&#8230; His track record of scoops&#8230;has helped him become the rare blogger who supports himself on the strength of his reputation for hard-nosed reporting.&#8221; -Bloomberg Businessweek</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Brave New War : The Next Stage of Terrorism and the End of Globalization &#8211; John Robb, Foreword by James Fallows (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/brave-new-war-the-next-stage-of-terrorism-and-the-end-of-globalization-john-robb-foreword-by-james-fallows-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism, Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/brave-new-war-the-next-stage-of-terrorism-and-the-end-of-globalization-john-robb-foreword-by-james-fallows-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>For my money, John Robb, a former Air Force officer and tech guru, is the futurists&#8217; futurist. &#8211;Slate The counterterrorism expert John Robb reveals how the same technology that has enabled globalization also allows terrorists and criminals to join forces against larger adversaries with relative ease and to carry out small, inexpensive actions&#8211;like sabotaging an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-war-the-next-stage-of-terrorism-and-the-end-of-globalization-john-robb-foreword-by-james-fallows-abridged/">Brave New War : The Next Stage of Terrorism and the End of Globalization &#8211; John Robb, Foreword by James Fallows (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>For my money, John Robb, a former Air Force officer and tech guru, is the futurists&#8217; futurist.<br />
                    &#8211;Slate    </p>
<p>                    The counterterrorism expert John Robb reveals how the same technology that has enabled globalization also allows terrorists and criminals to join forces against larger adversaries with relative ease and to carry out small, inexpensive actions&#8211;like sabotaging an oil pipeline&#8211;that generate a huge return. He shows how combating the shutdown of the world&#8217;s oil, high-tech, and financial markets could cost us the thing we&#8217;ve come to value the most&#8211;worldwide economic and cultural integration&#8211;and what we must do now to safeguard against this new method of warfare.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/brave-new-war-the-next-stage-of-terrorism-and-the-end-of-globalization-john-robb-foreword-by-james-fallows-abridged/">Brave New War : The Next Stage of Terrorism and the End of Globalization &#8211; John Robb, Foreword by James Fallows (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Splendid Exchange : How Trade Shaped the World &#8211; William J Bernstein (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-splendid-exchange-how-trade-shaped-the-world-william-j-bernstein-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economic & Trade Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-splendid-exchange-how-trade-shaped-the-world-william-j-bernstein-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A sweeping narrative history of world trade&#8211;from Sumer in 3000 BC to the firestorm over globalization today&#8211;that brilliantly explores trade&#8217;s colorful and contentious past and provides fresh insights into social, political, cultural, and economic history, as well as a timely assessment of trade&#8217;s future. Adam Smith wrote that man has an intrinsic &#8220;propensity to truck, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-splendid-exchange-how-trade-shaped-the-world-william-j-bernstein-abridged/">A Splendid Exchange : How Trade Shaped the World &#8211; William J Bernstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A sweeping narrative history of world trade&#8211;from Sumer in 3000 BC to the firestorm over globalization today&#8211;that brilliantly explores trade&#8217;s colorful and contentious past and provides fresh insights into social, political, cultural, and economic history, as well as a timely assessment of trade&#8217;s future.    </p>
<p>                    Adam Smith wrote that man has an intrinsic &#8220;propensity to truck, barter, and exchange one thing for another.&#8221; But how did trade evolve to the point where we don&#8217;t think twice about biting into an apple from the other side of the world?    </p>
<p>                    In A Splendid Exchange, William J. Bernstein tells the extraordinary story of global commerce from its prehistoric origins to the myriad controversies surrounding it today. He transports readers from ancient sailing ships that brought the silk trade from China to Rome in the second century to the rise and fall of the Portuguese monopoly in spices in the sixteenth; from the rush for sugar that brought the British to Jamaica in 1655 to the American trade battles of the early twentieth century; from key innovations such as steam, steel, and refrigeration to the modern era of televisions from Taiwan, lettuce from Mexico, and T-shirts from China.    </p>
<p>                    Along the way, Bernstein examines how our age-old dependency on trade has contributed to our planet&#8217;s agricultural bounty, stimulated intellectual progress, and made us both prosperous and vulnerable. Although the impulse to trade often takes a backseat to xenophobia and war, Bernstein concludes that trade is ultimately a force for good among nations, and he argues that societies are far more successful and stable when they are involved in vigorous trade with their neighbors.    </p>
<p>                    Lively, authoritative, and astonishing in scope, A Splendid Exchange is a riveting narrative that views trade and globalization not in political terms, but rather as an evolutionary process as old as war and religion&#8211;a historical constant&#8211;that will continue to foster the growth of intellectual capital, shrink the world, and propel the trajectory of the human species.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-splendid-exchange-how-trade-shaped-the-world-william-j-bernstein-abridged/">A Splendid Exchange : How Trade Shaped the World &#8211; William J Bernstein (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Terrorism And The Constitution : Sacrificing Civil Liberties in the Name of National Security &#8211; David Cole (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/terrorism-and-the-constitution-sacrificing-civil-liberties-in-the-name-of-national-security-david-cole-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terrorism, Armed Struggle]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/terrorism-and-the-constitution-sacrificing-civil-liberties-in-the-name-of-national-security-david-cole-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Tracing the history of government intrusions on Constitutional rights in response to threats from abroad, Cole and Dempsey warn that a society in which civil liberties are sacrificed in the name of national security is in fact less secure than one in which they are upheld. A new chapter includes a discussion of domestic spying, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/terrorism-and-the-constitution-sacrificing-civil-liberties-in-the-name-of-national-security-david-cole-abridged/">Terrorism And The Constitution : Sacrificing Civil Liberties in the Name of National Security &#8211; David Cole (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tracing the history of government intrusions on Constitutional rights in response to threats from abroad, Cole and Dempsey warn that a society in which civil liberties are sacrificed in the name of national security is in fact less secure than one in which they are upheld.    </p>
<p>                    A new chapter includes a discussion of domestic spying, preventive detention, the many court challenges to post-9/11 abuses, implementation of the PATRIOT ACT, and efforts to reestablish the checks and balances left behind in the rush to strengthen governmental powers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/terrorism-and-the-constitution-sacrificing-civil-liberties-in-the-name-of-national-security-david-cole-abridged/">Terrorism And The Constitution : Sacrificing Civil Liberties in the Name of National Security &#8211; David Cole (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Back Channel to Cuba : The Hidden History of Negotiations between Washington and Havana, Updated Edition &#8211; William M. Leogrande, Peter Kornbluh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/back-channel-to-cuba-the-hidden-history-of-negotiations-between-washington-and-havana-updated-edition-william-m-leogrande-peter-kornbluh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/back-channel-to-cuba-the-hidden-history-of-negotiations-between-washington-and-havana-updated-edition-william-m-leogrande-peter-kornbluh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>History is being made in U.S.-Cuban relations. Now updated to tell the story behind the stunning December 17, 2014, announcement by President Obama and President Castro of their move to restore full diplomatic relations, this powerful book is essential to understanding ongoing efforts towards normalization. Challenging the conventional wisdom of perpetual conflict and aggression between [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/back-channel-to-cuba-the-hidden-history-of-negotiations-between-washington-and-havana-updated-edition-william-m-leogrande-peter-kornbluh-abridged/">Back Channel to Cuba : The Hidden History of Negotiations between Washington and Havana, Updated Edition &#8211; William M. Leogrande, Peter Kornbluh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>History is being made in U.S.-Cuban relations. Now updated to tell the story behind the stunning December 17, 2014, announcement by President Obama and President Castro of their move to restore full diplomatic relations, this powerful book is essential to understanding ongoing efforts towards normalization. Challenging the conventional wisdom of perpetual conflict and aggression between the United States and Cuba since 1959, Back Channel to Cuba chronicles a surprising, untold history of bilateral efforts toward rapprochement and reconciliation. William M. LeoGrande and Peter Kornbluh here present a remarkably new and relevant account, describing how, despite the intense political clamor surrounding efforts to improve relations with Havana, negotiations have been conducted by every presidential administration since Eisenhower&#8217;s through secret, back-channel diplomacy. From John F. Kennedy&#8217;s offering of an olive branch to Fidel Castro after the missile crisis, to Henry Kissinger&#8217;s top secret quest for normalization, to Barack Obama&#8217;s promise of a new approach, LeoGrande and Kornbluh uncovered hundreds of formerly secret U.S. documents and conducted interviews with dozens of negotiators, intermediaries, and policy makers, including Fidel Castro and Jimmy Carter. They reveal a fifty-year record of dialogue and negotiations, both open and furtive, that provides the historical foundation for the dramatic breakthrough in U.S.-Cuba ties.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/back-channel-to-cuba-the-hidden-history-of-negotiations-between-washington-and-havana-updated-edition-william-m-leogrande-peter-kornbluh-abridged/">Back Channel to Cuba : The Hidden History of Negotiations between Washington and Havana, Updated Edition &#8211; William M. Leogrande, Peter Kornbluh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sea Power : The History and Geopolitics of the World&#8217;s Oceans &#8211; Admiral James Stavridis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sea-power-the-history-and-geopolitics-of-the-worlds-oceans-admiral-james-stavridis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Naval Forces & Warfare]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sea-power-the-history-and-geopolitics-of-the-worlds-oceans-admiral-james-stavridis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From one of the most admired admirals of his generation-and the only admiral to serve as Supreme Allied Commander at NATO-comes a remarkable voyage through all of the world&#8217;s most important bodies of water, providing the story of naval power as a driver of human history and a crucial element in our current geopolitical path. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sea-power-the-history-and-geopolitics-of-the-worlds-oceans-admiral-james-stavridis-abridged/">Sea Power : The History and Geopolitics of the World&#8217;s Oceans &#8211; Admiral James Stavridis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From one of the most admired admirals of his generation-and the only admiral to serve as Supreme Allied Commander at NATO-comes a remarkable voyage through all of the world&#8217;s most important bodies of water, providing the story of naval power as a driver of human history and a crucial element in our current geopolitical path.     </p>
<p>                     From the time of the Greeks and the Persians clashing in the Mediterranean, sea power has determined world power.  To an extent that is often underappreciated, it still does. No one understands this better than Admiral Jim Stavridis. In Sea Power, Admiral Stavridis takes us with him on a tour of the world&#8217;s oceans from the admiral&#8217;s chair, showing us how the geography of the oceans has shaped the destiny of nations, and how naval power has in a real sense made the world we live in today, and will shape the world we live in tomorrow.      </p>
<p>                     Not least, Sea Power is marvelous naval history, giving us fresh insight into great naval engagements from the battles of Salamis and Lepanto through to Trafalgar, the Battle of the Atlantic, and submarine conflicts of the Cold War. It is also a keen-eyed reckoning with the likely sites of our next major naval conflicts, particularly the Arctic Ocean, Eastern Mediterranean, and the South China Sea. Finally, Sea Power steps back to take a holistic view of the plagues to our oceans that are best seen that way, from piracy to pollution.    </p>
<p>                     When most of us look at a globe, we focus on the shape of the of the seven continents. Admiral Stavridis sees the shapes of the seven seas.  After reading Sea Power, you will too. Not since Alfred Thayer Mahan&#8217;s legendary The Influence of Sea Power upon History have we had such a powerful reckoning with this vital subject.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sea-power-the-history-and-geopolitics-of-the-worlds-oceans-admiral-james-stavridis-abridged/">Sea Power : The History and Geopolitics of the World&#8217;s Oceans &#8211; Admiral James Stavridis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Next Decade : Empire and Republic in a Changing World &#8211; George Friedman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Forecasting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed New York Times bestseller The Next 100 Years now focuses his geopolitical forecasting acumen on the next decade and the imminent events and challenges that will test America and the world, specifically addressing the skills that will be required by the decade&#8217;s leaders. In the long view, history is seen [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/">The Next Decade : Empire and Republic in a Changing World &#8211; George Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The author of the acclaimed New York Times bestseller The Next 100 Years now focuses his geopolitical forecasting acumen on the next decade and the imminent events and challenges that will test America and the world, specifically addressing the skills that will be required by the decade&#8217;s leaders.     </p>
<p>                    In the long view, history is seen as a series of events&#8211;but the course of those events is determined by individuals and their actions. During the next ten years, individual leaders will face significant transitions for their nations: the United States&#8217; relationships with Iran and Israel will be undergoing changes, China will likely confront a major crisis, and the wars in the Islamic world will subside. Unexpected energy and technology developments will emerge, and labor shortages will begin to matter more than financial crises. Distinguished geopolitical forecaster George Friedman analyzes these events from the perspectives of the men and women leading these global changes, focusing in particular on the American president, who will require extraordinary skills to shepherd the United States through this transitional period. The Next Decade is a provocative and fascinating look at the conflicts and opportunities that lie ahead.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-next-decade-empire-and-republic-in-a-changing-world-george-friedman-abridged/">The Next Decade : Empire and Republic in a Changing World &#8211; George Friedman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Run The World &#8211; Parag Khanna (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-run-the-world-parag-khanna-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-run-the-world-parag-khanna-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is a stunning and provocative guide to the future of international relations&#8211;a system for managing global problems beyond the stalemates of business versus government, East versus West, rich versus poor, democracy versus authoritarianism, free markets versus state capitalism. Written by the most esteemed and innovative adventurer-scholar of his generation, Parag Khanna&#8217;s &#8220;How to Run [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-run-the-world-parag-khanna-abridged/">How To Run The World &#8211; Parag Khanna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here is a stunning and provocative guide to the future of international relations&#8211;a system for managing global problems beyond the stalemates of business versus government, East versus West, rich versus poor, democracy versus authoritarianism, free markets versus state capitalism. Written by the most esteemed and innovative adventurer-scholar of his generation, Parag Khanna&#8217;s &#8220;How to Run the World&#8221; posits a chaotic modern era that resembles the Middle Ages, with Asian empires, Western militaries, Middle Eastern sheikhdoms, magnetic city-states, wealthy multinational corporations, elite clans, religious zealots, tribal hordes, and potent media seething in an ever more unpredictable and dangerous storm. But just as that initial &#8220;dark age&#8221; ended with the Renaissance, Khanna believes that our time can become a great and enlightened age as well&#8211;only, though, if we harness our technology and connectedness to forge new networks among governments, businesses, and civic interest groups to tackle the crises of today and avert those of tomorrow.<br />
                    With his trademark energy, intellect, and wit, Khanna reveals how a new &#8220;mega-diplomacy&#8221; consisting of coalitions among motivated technocrats, influential executives, super-philanthropists, cause-mopolitan activists, and everyday churchgoers can assemble the talent, pool the money, and deploy the resources to make the global economy fairer, rebuild failed states, combat terrorism, promote good governance, deliver food, water, health care, and education to those in need, and prevent environmental collapse. With examples taken from the smartest capital cities, most progressive boardrooms, and frontline NGOs, Khanna shows how mega-diplomacy is more than an ad hoc approach to running a world where no one is in charge&#8211;it is the playbook for creating a stable and self-correcting world for future generations.<br />
                    &#8220;How to Run the World&#8221; is the cutting-edge manifesto for diplomacy in a borderless world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-run-the-world-parag-khanna-abridged/">How To Run The World &#8211; Parag Khanna (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>China&#8217;s Second Continent : How a Million Migrants Are Building a New Empire in Africa &#8211; Howard W. French (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/chinas-second-continent-how-a-million-migrants-are-building-a-new-empire-in-africa-howard-w-french-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[African History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Migration, Immigration & Emigration]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/chinas-second-continent-how-a-million-migrants-are-building-a-new-empire-in-africa-howard-w-french-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book Chinese immigrants of the recent past and unfolding twenty-first century are in search of the African dream. So explains indefatigable traveler Howard W. French, prize-winning investigative journalist and former New York Times bureau chief in Africa and China, in the definitive account of this seismic geopolitical development. China&#8217;s burgeoning [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chinas-second-continent-how-a-million-migrants-are-building-a-new-empire-in-africa-howard-w-french-abridged/">China&#8217;s Second Continent : How a Million Migrants Are Building a New Empire in Africa &#8211; Howard W. French (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times Notable Book     </p>
<p>                    Chinese immigrants of the recent past and unfolding twenty-first century are in search of the African dream. So explains indefatigable traveler Howard W. French, prize-winning investigative journalist and former New York Times bureau chief in Africa and China, in the definitive account of this seismic geopolitical development. China&#8217;s burgeoning presence in Africa is already shaping, and reshaping, the future of millions of people. From Liberia to Senegal to Mozambique, in creaky trucks and by back roads, French introduces us to the characters who make up China&#8217;s dogged emigrant population: entrepreneurs singlehandedly reshaping African infrastructure, and less-lucky migrants barely scraping by but still convinced of Africa&#8217;s opportunities. French&#8217;s acute observations offer illuminating insight into the most pressing unknowns of modern Sino-African relations: Why China is making these cultural and economic incursions into the continent; what Africa&#8217;s role is in this equation; and what the ramifications for both parties and their people&#8211;and the watching world&#8211;will be in the foreseeable future.     </p>
<p>                    One of the Best Books of the Year at &#8211; The Economist &#8211; The Guardian &#8211; Foreign Affairs</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chinas-second-continent-how-a-million-migrants-are-building-a-new-empire-in-africa-howard-w-french-abridged/">China&#8217;s Second Continent : How a Million Migrants Are Building a New Empire in Africa &#8211; Howard W. French (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Revolutionary Groups & Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this book, Klaus Schwab and the World Economic Forum contribute significantly to one of the most important issues of our time &#8211; how to move forward in the Fourth Industrial Revolution&#8217; Jack Ma, Executive Chairman, Alibaba Group Holding, People&#8217;s Republic of China    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s no secret that technologies are reshaping the world&#8217;s economies and societies. To manage the risks and spread the benefits, we have to act now, and in the interest of stakeholders everywhere&#8217; Andrew McAfee, Co-Founder, MIT Initiative on the Digital Economy, MIT, USA    </p>
<p>                    We are on the brink of the Fourth Industrial Revolution. And this one will be unlike any other in human history.    </p>
<p>                    Characterized by new technologies fusing the physical, digital and biological worlds, the Fourth Industrial Revolution will impact all disciplines, economies and industries &#8211; and it will do so at an unprecedented rate. World Economic Forum data predicts that by 2025 we will see: commercial use of nanomaterials 200 times stronger than steel and a million times thinner than human hair; the first transplant of a 3D-printed liver; 10% of all cars on US roads being driverless; and much more besides.    </p>
<p>                    In The Fourth Industrial Revolution, Schwab outlines the key technologies driving this revolution, discusses the major impacts on governments, businesses, civil society and individuals, and offers bold ideas for what can be done to shape a better future for all.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The technologies of the Fourth Industrial Revolution are extraordinary. Leadership has to be equally extraordinary to manage the complexities of systemic change&#8217; Eric Schmidt, Technical Advisor, Alphabet, USA</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fourth-industrial-revolution-klaus-schwab-abridged/">The Fourth Industrial Revolution &#8211; Klaus Schwab (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the bestselling tradition of The World Is Flat and The Next 100 Years comes a contrarian and eye-opening assessment of American power. In THE ACCIDENTAL SUPERPOWER, international strategist Peter Zeihan examines how the hard rules of geography are eroding the American commitment to free trade; how much of the planet is aging into a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/">The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the bestselling tradition of The World Is Flat and The Next 100 Years comes a contrarian and eye-opening assessment of American power.    </p>
<p>                    In THE ACCIDENTAL SUPERPOWER, international strategist Peter Zeihan examines how the hard rules of geography are eroding the American commitment to free trade; how much of the planet is aging into a mass retirement that will enervate capital supplies; and how it is the ever-ravenous American economy that is rapidly approaching energy independence. Combined, these factors are overturning the global system and ushering in a new (dis)order. For most, that is a disaster-in-waiting, but not for the Americans. The shale revolution allows Americans to sidestep a dangerous energy market. Only the U.S. boasts a youth population large enough to escape the sucking maw of global aging. Geography will matter more than ever in a de-globalizing world, and America&#8217;s geography is simply sublime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/">The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hard Choices : A Memoir &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hard-choices-a-memoir-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hard-choices-a-memoir-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>HILLARY RODHAM CLINTON&#8217;S INSIDE ACCOUNT OF THE CRISES, CHOICES AND CHALLENGES SHE FACED DURING HER FOUR YEARS AS AMERICA&#8217;S 67THSECRETARY OF STATE, AND HOW THOSE EXPERIENCES DRIVE HER VIEW OF THE FUTURE, INCLUDING A NEW EPILOGUE. &#8216;All of us face hard choices in our lives,&#8217; Hillary Rodham Clinton writes at the start of this personal [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hard-choices-a-memoir-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/">Hard Choices : A Memoir &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>HILLARY RODHAM CLINTON&#8217;S INSIDE ACCOUNT OF THE CRISES, CHOICES AND CHALLENGES SHE FACED DURING HER FOUR YEARS AS AMERICA&#8217;S 67THSECRETARY OF STATE, AND HOW THOSE EXPERIENCES DRIVE HER VIEW OF THE FUTURE, INCLUDING A NEW EPILOGUE.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;All of us face hard choices in our lives,&#8217; Hillary Rodham Clinton writes at the start of this personal chronicle of years at the centre of world events. &#8216;Life is about making such choices. Our choices and how we handle them shape the people we become.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                     In the aftermath of her 2008 presidential run, she expected to return to representing New York in the Unites States Senate. To her surprise, her formal rival for the Democratic Party nomination, newly elected President Barack Obama, asked her to serve in his administration as Secretary of State. This memoir is the story of the four extraordinary and historic years that followed, and the hard choices that she and her colleagues confronted.     </p>
<p>                     Secretary Clinton and President Obama had to decide how to repair fractured alliances, wind down two wars and address a global financial crisis. They faced a rising competitor in China, growing threats from Iran and North Korea, and revolutions across the Middle East. Along the way, they grappled with some of the toughest dilemmas of US foreign policy, especially the decision to send Americans into harm&#8217;s way, from Afghanistan to Libya to the hunt for Osama bin Laden.     </p>
<p>                    By the end of her tenure, Secretary Clinton had visited 112 countries, travelled nearly one million miles and gained a truly global perspective on many of the major trends reshaping the landscape of the twenty-first century, from economic inequality to climate change to revolutions in energy, communications and health. Drawing on conversations with numerous leaders and experts, Secretary Clinton offers her views on what it will take for the United States to compete and thrive in an interdependent world. She makes a passionate case for human rights and the full participation in society of girls, youth and LGBT people. An astute eyewitness to decades of social change, she distinguishes the trendlines from the headlines and describes the progress occurring throughout the world, day after day.     </p>
<p>                     Secretary Clinton&#8217;s descriptions of diplomatic conversations at the highest levels offer readers a masterclass in international relations, as does her analysis of how we can best use &#8216;smart power&#8217; to deliver security and prosperity in a rapidly changing world &#8211; one in which America remains the indispensable nation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hard-choices-a-memoir-hillary-rodham-clinton-abridged/">Hard Choices : A Memoir &#8211; Hillary Rodham Clinton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
