<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Journalistic Style Guides Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/journalistic-style-guides/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/journalistic-style-guides/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Journalistic Style Guides Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/journalistic-style-guides/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</title>
		<link>/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR </p>
<p>                     When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch a cable news network in 1996, American politics and media changed forever. With a remarkable level of detail and insight, Vanity Fair magazine reporter Gabriel Sherman puts Ailes&#8217;s unique genius on display, along with the outsize personalities&#8211;Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Sean Hannity, Megyn Kelly, Sarah Palin, Karl Rove, Glenn Beck, Mike Huckabee, Gretchen Carlson, Bill Shine, and others&#8211;who have helped Fox News play a defining role in the great social and political controversies of the past two decades. From the Clinton-Lewinsky scandal to the Bush-Gore recount, from the war in Iraq to the Tea Party attack on the Obama presidency, Roger Ailes developed an unrivaled power to sway the national agenda. Even more, he became the indispensable figure in conservative America and the man any Republican politician with presidential aspirations had to court. </p>
<p>                     How did this man become the master strategist of our political landscape? In revelatory detail, Sherman chronicles the rise of Ailes, a frail kid from an Ohio factory town who, through sheer willpower, the flair of a showman, fierce corporate politicking, and a profound understanding of the priorities of middle America, built the most influential television news empire of our time. </p>
<p>                     Drawing on hundreds of interviews with Fox News insiders past and present, Sherman documents Ailes&#8217;s tactical acuity as he battled the press, business rivals, and countless real and perceived enemies inside and outside Fox. Sherman takes us inside the morning meetings in which Ailes and other high-level executives strategized Fox&#8217;s presentation of the news to advance Ailes&#8217;s political agenda; provides behind-the-scenes details of Ailes&#8217;s crucial role as finder and shaper of talent, including his sometimes rocky relationships with Fox News stars such as O&#8217;Reilly, Hannity, and Carlson; and probes Ailes&#8217;s fraught partnership with his equally brash and mercurial boss, Rupert Murdoch. </p>
<p>                     Roger Ailes&#8217;s life is a story worthy of Citizen Kane. Featuring an afterword about Ailes&#8217;s epic downfall during the extraordinary 2016 election, The Loudest Voice in the Room is an extraordinary feat of reportage with a compelling human drama at its heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Once There Was a War &#8211; John Steinbeck</title>
		<link>/once-there-was-a-war-john-steinbeck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Books & Novels]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/once-there-was-a-war-john-steinbeck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic &#8220;Age can never dull this kind of writing,&#8221; writes the Chicago Tribune of John Steinbeck&#8217;s dispatches from World War II, filed for the New York Herald Tribune in 1943, which vividly captured the human side of war. Writing from England in the midst of the London blitz, North Africa, and Italy, Steinbeck [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/once-there-was-a-war-john-steinbeck/">Once There Was a War &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Penguin Classic     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Age can never dull this kind of writing,&#8221; writes the Chicago Tribune of John Steinbeck&#8217;s dispatches from World War II, filed for the New York Herald Tribune in 1943, which vividly captured the human side of war. Writing from England in the midst of the London blitz, North Africa, and Italy, Steinbeck focuses on the people as opposed to the battles, portraying everyone from the guys in the bomber crew to Bob Hope on his USO tour. He eats and drinks with soldiers behind enemy lines, talks with them, and fights beside them. First published in book form in 1958, these writings, now with a new introduction by Mark Bowden, create an unforgettable portrait of life in wartime that continues to resonate with truth and humanity.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/once-there-was-a-war-john-steinbeck/">Once There Was a War &#8211; John Steinbeck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Right Stuff &#8211; Tom Wolfe</title>
		<link>/the-right-stuff-tom-wolfe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aerospace & Aviation Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aircraft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Astronomy & Space]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Space Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-right-stuff-tom-wolfe/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A wildly vivid and entertaining chronicle of America&#8217;s manned space program, from the author of The Electric Kool-Aid Acid Test `What is it&#8217; asks Tom Wolfe, `that makes a man willing to sit on top of an enormous Roman Candle&#8230;and wait for someone to light the fuse?&#8217; Arrogance? Stupidity? Bravery? Courage? Or, simply, that quality [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-right-stuff-tom-wolfe/">The Right Stuff &#8211; Tom Wolfe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A wildly vivid and entertaining chronicle of America&#8217;s manned space program, from the author of The Electric Kool-Aid Acid Test    </p>
<p>                    `What is it&#8217; asks Tom Wolfe, `that makes a man willing to sit on top of an enormous Roman Candle&#8230;and wait for someone to light the fuse?&#8217; Arrogance? Stupidity? Bravery? Courage? Or, simply, that quality we call &#8216;the right stuff&#8217;?    </p>
<p>                    A monument to the men who battled to beat the Russians into space, The Right Stuff is a voyage into the mythology of the American space program, and a dizzying dive into the sweat, fear, beauty and danger of being on the white-hot edge of history in the making.    </p>
<p>                    `Tom Wolfe at his very best&#8230; Learned, cheeky, risky, touching, tough, compassionate, nostalgic, worshipful, jingoistic&#8230;The Right Stuff is superb&#8217; &#8211; New York Times Book Review    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-right-stuff-tom-wolfe/">The Right Stuff &#8211; Tom Wolfe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thinking About It Only Makes It Worse : And Other Lessons from Modern Life &#8211; David Mitchell</title>
		<link>/thinking-about-it-only-makes-it-worse-and-other-lessons-from-modern-life-david-mitchell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Other Performing Arts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thinking-about-it-only-makes-it-worse-and-other-lessons-from-modern-life-david-mitchell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES-BESTSELLING BOOK BY ONE OF BRITAIN&#8217;S BEST-LOVED COMIC WRITERS **Pre-order now: David Mitchell&#8217;s new book Dishonesty is the Second-best Policy** There are many aspects of modern life that trouble award-winning comedian David Mitchell, such as: Why is every film or TV programme a sequel or a remake? Why are people so f***ing hung [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinking-about-it-only-makes-it-worse-and-other-lessons-from-modern-life-david-mitchell/">Thinking About It Only Makes It Worse : And Other Lessons from Modern Life &#8211; David Mitchell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES-BESTSELLING BOOK BY ONE OF BRITAIN&#8217;S BEST-LOVED COMIC WRITERS</p>
<p>                    **Pre-order now: David Mitchell&#8217;s new book Dishonesty is the Second-best Policy**</p>
<p>                    There are many aspects of modern life that trouble award-winning comedian David Mitchell, such as: </p>
<p>                    Why is every film or TV programme a sequel or a remake? </p>
<p>                    Why are people so f***ing hung up about swearing? </p>
<p>                    Why do the asterisks in that sentence make it ok? </p>
<p>                    Why do so many people want to stop other people doing things, and how can they be stopped from stopping them?</p>
<p>                    Join Mitchell on a tour of the absurdities of our times &#8211; from Ryanair to Richard III, Downton Abbey to phone etiquette, UKIP to hotdogs made of cats. Funny, provocative and shot through with refreshing amounts of common sense, Thinking About It Only Makes It Worse celebrates and commiserates on the state of things in our not entirely glorious modern world.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Mitchell is an exceptionally clever, eloquent and spot-on commentator. We should be grateful for him.&#8217; Daily Mail, Books of the Year</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinking-about-it-only-makes-it-worse-and-other-lessons-from-modern-life-david-mitchell/">Thinking About It Only Makes It Worse : And Other Lessons from Modern Life &#8211; David Mitchell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smile Or Die : How Positive Thinking Fooled America and the World &#8211; Barbara Ehrenreich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/smile-or-die-how-positive-thinking-fooled-america-and-the-world-barbara-ehrenreich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/smile-or-die-how-positive-thinking-fooled-america-and-the-world-barbara-ehrenreich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bombarded by pink ribbons and platitudes following a breast cancer diagnosis, Ehrenreich was shocked to find that her anger was seen as unhealthy and dangerous by health professionals and other professionals. From health to academia, the economy to Iraq, Ehrenreich exposes a trail of denial, delusion, and bad faith, and reveals the often disastrous consequences [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smile-or-die-how-positive-thinking-fooled-america-and-the-world-barbara-ehrenreich-abridged/">Smile Or Die : How Positive Thinking Fooled America and the World &#8211; Barbara Ehrenreich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bombarded by pink ribbons and platitudes following a breast cancer diagnosis, Ehrenreich was shocked to find that her anger was seen as unhealthy and dangerous by health professionals and other professionals. From health to academia, the economy to Iraq, Ehrenreich exposes a trail of denial, delusion, and bad faith, and reveals the often disastrous consequences of putting on &#8216;a happy face&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    Rigorous, insightful and also incredibly funny, Smile or Die is a sharp-witted knockdown of America&#8217;s love affair with positive thinking.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smile-or-die-how-positive-thinking-fooled-america-and-the-world-barbara-ehrenreich-abridged/">Smile Or Die : How Positive Thinking Fooled America and the World &#8211; Barbara Ehrenreich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nothing To Envy : Real Lives In North Korea &#8211; Barbara Demick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/nothing-to-envy-real-lives-in-north-korea-barbara-demick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/nothing-to-envy-real-lives-in-north-korea-barbara-demick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE BBC SAMUEL JOHNSON PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION 2010 A spectacularly revealing and harrowing portrait of ordinary lives in the world&#8217;s least ordinary country, North Korea North Korea is Orwell&#8217;s 1984 made reality: it is the only country in the world not connected to the internet; Gone with the Wind is a dangerous, banned [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nothing-to-envy-real-lives-in-north-korea-barbara-demick-abridged/">Nothing To Envy : Real Lives In North Korea &#8211; Barbara Demick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE BBC SAMUEL JOHNSON PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION 2010    </p>
<p>                    A spectacularly revealing and harrowing portrait of ordinary lives in the world&#8217;s least ordinary country, North Korea    </p>
<p>                    North Korea is Orwell&#8217;s 1984 made reality: it is the only country in the world not connected to the internet; Gone with the Wind is a dangerous, banned book; during political rallies, spies study your expression to check your sincerity. After the death of the country&#8217;s great leader Kim Il Sung in 1994, famine descended, and Nothing to Envy &#8211; winner of the 2010 BBC Samuel Johnson Prize for Non-Fiction &#8211; weaves together the stories of adversity and resilience of six residents of Chongin, North Korea&#8217;s third-largest city. From extensive interviews and with tenacious investigative work, Barbara Demick has recreated the concerns, culture and lifestyles of North Korean citizens in a gripping narrative, and vividly reconstructed the inner workings of this extraordinary and secretive country.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nothing-to-envy-real-lives-in-north-korea-barbara-demick-abridged/">Nothing To Envy : Real Lives In North Korea &#8211; Barbara Demick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Propaganda]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Does &#8216;fake news&#8217; really exist? Find out from the ultimate insider. After years of working as a respected journalist, Nick Davies, in this shocking expose, reveals what really goes on behind the scenes of this contentious industry. From a prestigious newspaper that allowed intelligence agencies to plant fiction in its columns, to the newsroom that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/">Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Does &#8216;fake news&#8217; really exist? Find out from the ultimate insider.    </p>
<p>                    After years of working as a respected journalist, Nick Davies, in this shocking expose, reveals what really goes on behind the scenes of this contentious industry.     </p>
<p>                    From a prestigious newspaper that allowed intelligence agencies to plant fiction in its columns, to the newsroom that routinely rejected stories due to racial bias, to the number of papers that accepted cash bribes. Gripping, thought-provoking and revelatory, this is an insider&#8217;s look at one of the most tainted professions.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Meticulous, fair-minded and utterly gripping&#8217; Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Powerful and timely&#8230;his analysis is fair, meticulously researched and fascinating&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/">Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A provocative, timely account of the changing face of jounalism from a pioneer of the new-media revolution. For a long time, media organisations have controlled the news, treating their audiences as products for advertisers. Yet as journalism has moved online and behind paywalls, the public is demanding more say in how the news is created. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/">The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A provocative, timely account of the changing face of jounalism from a pioneer of the new-media revolution.    For a long time, media organisations have controlled the news, treating their audiences as products for advertisers.       Yet as journalism has moved online and behind paywalls, the public is demanding more say in how the news is created.       They are using blogs, Twitter, and Facebook to share stories, and selecting their sources to create their own &#8216;front page&#8217;.   In this lively, biting critique, media commentator Tim Dunlop explores the rise of the audience, and how unprepared the mainstream media has been for this changing balance of power.       Drawing on his experiences as prominent political blogger, he argues that the future of meaningful journalism &#8211; the sort we need in order to be informed citizens &#8211; will increasingly rely on journalists and editors taking the audience into their confidence and working with them, rather than against them.   The New Front Page is a passionate plea on behalf of those tired of being talked down to by the fourth estate.       Perceptive and illuminating, it asks audiences and media to work together to hold the powerful to account, and to produce the sort of news and analysis that enriches public debate.   &#8216;A fascinating account of how digital technology has changed Australian media forever.&#8217;       Katharine Viner, editor-in-chief of The Guardian Australia   &#8216;An essential guide to understanding our insurgent new media.&#8217;       Lindsay Tanner, author of Sideshow   &#8216;Dunlop writes with humour, passion, and insight.&#8217;       Gay Alcorn, journalist</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/">The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Work]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Explosive&#8217; Margaret Atwood &#8216;Seismic&#8217; Observer &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Nigella Lawson &#8216;Gripping&#8217; Jon Ronson *SOON TO BE A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE STARRING CAREY MULLIGAN AND ZOE KAZAN* A FINANCIAL TIMES, NEW STATESMAN, DAILY TELEGRAPH, METRO AND ELLE BOOK OF THE YEAR On 5 October 2017, the New York Times published an article by Jodi Kantor and Megan Twohey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/">She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Explosive&#8217; Margaret Atwood<br />
                    &#8216;Seismic&#8217; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Nigella Lawson<br />
                    &#8216;Gripping&#8217; Jon Ronson    </p>
<p>                    *SOON TO BE A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE STARRING CAREY MULLIGAN AND ZOE KAZAN*    </p>
<p>                    A FINANCIAL TIMES, NEW STATESMAN, DAILY TELEGRAPH, METRO AND ELLE BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    On 5 October 2017, the New York Times published an article by Jodi Kantor and Megan Twohey that helped change the world.    </p>
<p>                    Hollywood was talking as never before. Kantor and Twohey outmanoeuvred Harvey Weinstein, his team of defenders and private investigators, convincing some of the most famous women in the world &#8211; and some unknown ones &#8211; to go on the record. Three years later, it helped lead to his conviction.    </p>
<p>                    This is how they did it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-said-the-new-york-times-bestseller-from-the-journalists-who-broke-the-harvey-weinstein-story-jodi-kantor-megan-twohey-abridged/">She Said : The New York Times bestseller from the journalists who broke the Harvey Weinstein story &#8211; Jodi Kantor, Megan Twohey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bird by Bird : Some Instructions on Writing and Life &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bird-by-bird-some-instructions-on-writing-and-life-anne-lamott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Creative Writing & Creative Writing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Linguistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing & Editing Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Writing Skills]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bird-by-bird-some-instructions-on-writing-and-life-anne-lamott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An essential volume for generations of writers young and old, Bird by Bird is a modern classic. This twenty-fifth anniversary edition will continue to spark creative minds for years to come. For a quarter century, more than a million readers&#8211;scribes and scribblers of all ages and abilities&#8211;have been inspired by Anne Lamott&#8217;s hilarious, big-hearted, homespun [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bird-by-bird-some-instructions-on-writing-and-life-anne-lamott-abridged/">Bird by Bird : Some Instructions on Writing and Life &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An essential volume for generations of writers young and old, Bird by Bird is a modern classic. This twenty-fifth anniversary edition will continue to spark creative minds for years to come.     </p>
<p>                    For a quarter century, more than a million readers&#8211;scribes and scribblers of all ages and abilities&#8211;have been inspired by Anne Lamott&#8217;s hilarious, big-hearted, homespun advice. Advice that begins with the simple words of wisdom passed down from Anne&#8217;s father&#8211;also a writer&#8211;in the iconic passage that gives the book its title:     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Thirty years ago my older brother, who was ten years old at the time, was trying to get a report on birds written that he&#8217;d had three months to write. It was due the next day. We were out at our family cabin in Bolinas, and he was at the kitchen table close to tears, surrounded by binder paper and pencils and unopened books on birds, immobilized by the hugeness of the task ahead. Then my father sat down beside him, put his arm around my brother&#8217;s shoulder, and said, &#8216;Bird by bird, buddy. Just take it bird by bird.'&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bird-by-bird-some-instructions-on-writing-and-life-anne-lamott-abridged/">Bird by Bird : Some Instructions on Writing and Life &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The War on Journalism &#8211; Andrew Fowler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-war-on-journalism-andrew-fowler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-war-on-journalism-andrew-fowler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The War on Journalism The War on Journalism is a harrowing story of megalomaniac press barons, conspiracies, sackings, cutbacks, and self censoring journalists, cowed by what legendary investigative reporter Seymour Hersh called ochicken shit editorso. When first Chelsea Manning and then Edward Snowden blew the whistle, they did more than reveal extraordinary secrets, they struck [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-journalism-andrew-fowler-abridged/">The War on Journalism &#8211; Andrew Fowler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The War on Journalism    </p>
<p>                    The War on Journalism is a harrowing story of  megalomaniac press barons, conspiracies, sackings, cutbacks, and self censoring journalists, cowed by what legendary investigative reporter Seymour Hersh called ochicken shit editorso.     </p>
<p>                    When first Chelsea Manning and then Edward Snowden blew the whistle, they did more than reveal extraordinary secrets, they struck the first solid blows against centuries old traditions, where journalism was played by agreed rules.  Governments oleakedo secret information to their favorite journalists in return for sympathetic coverage.     </p>
<p>                    Now racked by public distrust, the cash-starved mainstream media  is struggling to survive. Newspapers which flourished for hundreds of years  and TV networks that once ruled the world are in serious decline.   Andrew Fowler gives the inside story on how and why the media helped write its own epitaph. Fowler, an investigate reporter with Australia&#8217;s prestigious Four Corners documentary program for almost 20 years, and author of the international best seller The Most Dangerous Man in the World, the revelatory story of Julian Assange and the rise of WikiLeaks, has pieced together the extraordinary story on the decline of mainstream journalism.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s not just the notorious tabloids like Rupert Murdoch&#8217;s News of the World, infamous for its phone hacking crimes, which have caused the trouble.  The BBC,  Australia&#8217;s ABC, the Washington Post and the New York Times, and the Guardian, are also in the firing line.    </p>
<p>                    Now the establishment is fighting back with draconian laws to silence the new journalism. From the UK to the US to Australia, governments are harassing journalists, threatening to jail both the whistleblowers and those who publish  their leaks     </p>
<p>                    A battle, shrouded in the cloak of national security, pitting the public&#8217;s right to know against the powerful interests of those who want business as usual, it&#8217;s a stark choice- an increasingly democratic world, or one dominated by executive government, often unchallenged and unaccountable, spying on its own citizens and producing fraudulent arguments to fight horrific wars. Just who wins this information battle will not only define the kind of journalism that survives but also the kind of world we will all live in.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-war-on-journalism-andrew-fowler-abridged/">The War on Journalism &#8211; Andrew Fowler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Conspiracy : A True Story of Power, Sex, and a Billionaire&#8217;s Secret Plot to Destroy a Media Empire &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2016, one of the giants of modern journalism fell: Gawker Media, infamous for saying what other outlets wouldn&#8217;t say, was sued for publishing Hulk Hogan&#8217;s sex tape, lost the case and went bust. After countless other lawsuits it seemed that Gawker had finally run out of luck. But luck had nothing to do with [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Conspiracy : A True Story of Power, Sex, and a Billionaire&#8217;s Secret Plot to Destroy a Media Empire &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2016, one of the giants of modern journalism fell: Gawker Media, infamous for saying what other outlets wouldn&#8217;t say, was sued for publishing Hulk Hogan&#8217;s sex tape, lost the case and went bust. After countless other lawsuits it seemed that Gawker had finally run out of luck. But luck had nothing to do with it.     </p>
<p>                    Peter Thiel, PayPal founder and billionaire investor, had masterminded the whole thing. Still furious at an article that had outed him ten years previously, and increasingly disgusted at Gawker&#8217;s unscrupulous reporting methods, Thiel had spent nearly a decade meticulously plotting a conspiracy that would lead to the demise of Gawker and its founder, Nick Denton. After a multi-year proxy war through the Florida legal system, the settlement of $140million in favour of Hogan ended it.    </p>
<p>                    The verdict would stun the world and so would Peter&#8217;s ultimate unmasking as the man who had set it all in motion. Why had he done this? How had no one discovered it? What would this mean&#8211;for free speech? For privacy? For culture?    </p>
<p>                    In Holiday&#8217;s masterful telling of this nearly unbelievable conspiracy, informed by exclusive interviews with all the key players, this case transcends the narrative of how one billionaire took down a media empire or the current state of the free press. It&#8217;s a study in power, strategy, and one of the most wildly ambitious &#8211; and successful &#8211; secret plots in recent memory.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/conspiracy-a-true-story-of-power-sex-and-a-billionaires-secret-plot-to-destroy-a-media-empire-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Conspiracy : A True Story of Power, Sex, and a Billionaire&#8217;s Secret Plot to Destroy a Media Empire &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Six-time New York Times bestselling author, FOX News star, and radio host Mark R. Levin &#8220;trounces the news media&#8221; (The Washington Times) in this timely and groundbreaking book demonstrating how the great tradition of American free press has degenerated into a standardless profession that has squandered the faith and trust of the public. Unfreedom of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/">Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Six-time New York Times bestselling author, FOX News star, and radio host Mark R. Levin &#8220;trounces the news media&#8221; (The Washington Times) in this timely and groundbreaking book demonstrating how the great tradition of American free press has degenerated into a standardless profession that has squandered the faith and trust of the public.     </p>
<p>                    Unfreedom of the Press is not just another book about the press. In &#8220;Levin&#8217;s finest work&#8221; (Breitbart), he shows how those entrusted with news reporting today are destroying freedom of the press from within-not through actions of government officials, but with its own abandonment of reportorial integrity and objective journalism.    </p>
<p>                    With the depth of historical background for which his books are renowned, Levin takes you on a journey through the early American patriot press, which proudly promoted the principles set forth in the Declaration of Independence and the Constitution. This is followed by the early decades of the Republic during which newspapers around the young country were open and transparent about their fierce allegiance to one political party or another.    </p>
<p>                    It was only at the start of the Progressive Era and the 20th century that the supposed &#8220;objectivity of the press&#8221; first surfaced, leaving us where we are today: with a partisan party-press overwhelmingly aligned with a political ideology but hypocritically engaged in a massive untruth as to its real nature.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/unfreedom-of-the-press-mark-r-levin-abridged/">Unfreedom of the Press &#8211; Mark R. Levin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas : A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream &#8211; Hunter S. Thompson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Literary]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Story Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>50th Anniversary Edition &#8211; With an introduction by Caity Weaver, acclaimed New York Times journalist This cult classic of gonzo journalism is the best chronicle of drug-soaked, addle-brained, rollicking good times ever committed to the printed page. It is also the tale of a long weekend road trip that has gone down in the annals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/">Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas : A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream &#8211; Hunter S. Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>50th Anniversary Edition &#8211; With an introduction by Caity Weaver, acclaimed New York Times journalist     </p>
<p>                    This cult classic of gonzo journalism is the best chronicle of drug-soaked, addle-brained, rollicking good times ever committed to the printed page. It is also the tale of a long weekend road trip that has gone down in the annals of American pop culture as one of the strangest journeys ever undertaken.     </p>
<p>                    Also a major motion picture directed by Terry Gilliam, starring Johnny Depp and Benicio del Toro.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-and-loathing-in-las-vegas-a-savage-journey-to-the-heart-of-the-american-dream-hunter-s-thompson-abridged/">Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas : A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream &#8211; Hunter S. Thompson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal: to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221; major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal:  to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221;  major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair way.     </p>
<p>                    Breitbart burst on to the national media scene thanks to his coverage of  the ACORN controversy, where a local ACORN community group leader was videotaped giving business advice to a &#8220;gentleman&#8221; who ran a prostitution ring. When the major news media at first tried to bury the story, Breitbart used his extraordinary marketing savvy to make sure the story got full national attention.     </p>
<p>                    More recently, Congressman Anthony Weiner took on Breitbart, claiming that scurrilous photos of Weiner were being sent on the internet by the conservative right. In a new chapter in RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart details how &#8220;Weinergate&#8221; was entirely the personal fault of Congressman Weiner, and how Weiner derailed his own promising career by trying to implicate Breitbart and conservative journalists.    </p>
<p>                    In short, RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart talks about the key issues that Americans face, how he has aligned himself with the Tea Party, and how one needs to deal with the liberal news world head on. Along the way, he details his early years, working with Matt Drudge, the Huffington Post, and so on, and how Breitbart developed his unique style of launching key websites to help get the word out to conservatives all over.     </p>
<p>                    A rollicking and controversial read, Breitbart will certainly raise your blood pressure, one way or another.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh : The Story of Heredity, Its Past, Present and Future &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2018 BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh presents a profoundly original perspective on what we pass along from generation to generation. Charles Darwin played a crucial part in turning heredity into a scientific question, and yet he failed spectacularly to answer it. The birth of genetics in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/">She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh : The Story of Heredity, Its Past, Present and Future &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2018 BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION    </p>
<p>                    She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh presents a profoundly original perspective on what we pass along from generation to generation. Charles Darwin played a crucial part in turning heredity into a scientific question, and yet he failed spectacularly to answer it. The birth of genetics in the early 1900s seemed to do precisely that. Gradually, people translated their old notions about heredity into a language of genes. As the technology for studying genes became cheaper, millions of people ordered genetic tests to link themselves to missing parents, to distant ancestors, to ethnic identities . . .    </p>
<p>                    But, award-winning science writer Carl Zimmer argues, heredity isn&#8217;t just about genes that pass from parent to child. Heredity continues within our own bodies, as a single cell gives rise to trillions of cells that make up our bodies. We say we inherit genes from our ancestors but we inherit other things that matter as much or more to our lives, from microbes to technologies we use to make life more comfortable. We need a new definition of what heredity is and, through Carl Zimmer&#8217;s lucid exposition and storytelling, this resounding tour de force delivers it.    </p>
<p>                    Weaving together historical and current scientific research, his own experience with his two daughters, and the kind of original reporting expected of one of the world&#8217;s best science journalists, Zimmer ultimately unpacks urgent bioethical quandaries arising from new biomedical technologies, but also long-standing presumptions about who we really are and what we can pass on to future generations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/">She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh : The Story of Heredity, Its Past, Present and Future &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The captivating, inside story of the woman who helmed the Washington Post during one of the most turbulent periods in the history of American media. Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Biography In this bestselling and widely acclaimed memoir, Katharine Graham, the woman who piloted the Washington Post through the scandals of the Pentagon Papers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/">Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The captivating, inside story of the woman who helmed the Washington Post during one of the most turbulent periods in the history of American media.     </p>
<p>                    Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Biography    </p>
<p>                    In this bestselling and widely acclaimed memoir, Katharine Graham, the woman who piloted the Washington Post through the scandals of the Pentagon Papers and Watergate, tells her story&#8211;one that is extraordinary both for the events it encompasses and for the courage, candor, and dignity of its telling.     </p>
<p>                     Here is the awkward child who grew up amid material wealth and emotional isolation; the young bride who watched her brilliant, charismatic husband&#8211;a confidant to John F. Kennedy and Lyndon Johnson&#8211;plunge into the mental illness that would culminate in his suicide. And here is the widow who shook off her grief and insecurity to take on a president and a pressman&#8217;s union as she entered the profane boys&#8217; club of the newspaper business.     </p>
<p>                     As timely now as ever, Personal History is an exemplary record of our history and of the woman who played such a shaping role within them, discovering her own strength and sense of self as she confronted&#8211;and mastered&#8211;the personal and professional crises of her fascinating life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/">Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Investigation & Detection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING * &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    * UPDATED WITH NEW REPORTING *     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s all here in this stunning first draft of the history of the presidency of Donald Trump&#8217; Sydney Morning Herald    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An icy, Iago-like glimpse of the emotional and moral nullity that may be the source of Trump&#8217;s power&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A damning, well-reported, well-sourced and clearly written haymaker&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on nearly three years of reporting, hundreds of hours of interviews and more than two hundred sources, including some of the most senior members of the administration, friends and first-hand witnesses who have never spoken before, Philip Rucker and Carol Leonnig take us inside some of the most controversial moments of Trump&#8217;s presidency. They peer deeply into Trump&#8217;s White House &#8211; at the aides pressured to lie to the public, the lawyers scrambling to clear up norm-breaking disasters, and the staffers whose careers have been reduced to ashes &#8211; to paint an unparalleled group portrait of an administration driven by self-preservation and paranoia.     </p>
<p>                    Rucker and Leonnig reveal Trump at his most unvarnished, showing the unhinged decision-making and incompetence that has floored officials and stunned foreign leaders. They portray unscripted calls with Vladimir Putin, steak dinners with Kim Jong-un, and calls with Theresa May so hostile that they left her aides shaken. They also take a hard look at Robert Mueller, Trump&#8217;s greatest antagonist to date, and how his investigation slowly unravelled an administration whose universal value is loyalty &#8211; not to country, but to the president himself.    </p>
<p>                    Grippingly told, A Very Stable Genius is a behind-the-scenes account of Trump&#8217;s vainglorious pursuit of power in his first term.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-stable-genius-donald-j-trumps-testing-of-america-carol-d-leonnig-philip-rucker-abridged/">A Very Stable Genius : Donald J. Trump&#8217;s Testing of America &#8211; Carol D. Leonnig, Philip Rucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER* &#8216;HELL YES. This is one of those books that has the potential to change things &#8211; a monumental piece of research&#8217; Caitlin Moran Imagine a world where&#8230; * Your phone is too big for your hand * Your doctor prescribes a drug that is wrong for your body * [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/">Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;HELL YES. This is one of those books that has the potential to change things &#8211; a monumental piece of research&#8217; Caitlin Moran    </p>
<p>                    Imagine a world where&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    *        Your phone is too big for your hand<br />
                    *        Your doctor prescribes a drug that is wrong for your body<br />
                    *        In a car accident you are 47% more likely to be injured.    </p>
<p>                    If any of that sounds familiar, chances are you&#8217;re a woman.    </p>
<p>                    From government policy and medical research, to technology, workplaces, and the media. Invisible Women reveals how in a world built for and by men we are systematically ignoring half of the population, often with disastrous consequences. Caroline Criado Perez brings together for the first time an impressive range of case studies, stories and new research from across the world that illustrate the hidden ways in which women are forgotten, and the profound impact this has on us all.    </p>
<p>                    Discover the shocking gender bias that affects our everyday lives.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A book that changes the way you see the world&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Revelatory, frightening, hopeful&#8217; Jeanette Winterson</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/invisible-women-the-sunday-times-number-one-bestseller-exposing-the-gender-bias-women-face-every-day-caroline-criado-perez-abridged/">Invisible Women : the Sunday Times number one bestseller exposing the gender bias women face every day &#8211; Caroline Criado Perez (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
