<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Coping With Disability Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/coping-with-disability/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/coping-with-disability/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Coping With Disability Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/coping-with-disability/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Listening Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BRILLIANT&#8217; Chris Evans, Virgin Radio Breakfast Show When was the last time you listened to someone, or someone really listened to you? This life-changing book will transform your conversations forever. At work, we&#8217;re taught to lead the conversation. On social media, we shape our personal narratives. At parties, we talk over one another. So do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/">You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BRILLIANT&#8217; Chris Evans, Virgin Radio Breakfast Show    </p>
<p>                    When was the last time you listened to someone, or someone really listened to you?     </p>
<p>                    This life-changing book will transform your conversations forever.    </p>
<p>                     At work, we&#8217;re taught to lead the conversation.    </p>
<p>                     On social media, we shape our personal narratives.    </p>
<p>                     At parties, we talk over one another. So do our politicians.    </p>
<p>                     We&#8217;re not listening.    </p>
<p>                     And no one is listening to us.    </p>
<p>                    Now more than ever, we need to listen to those around us. New York Times contributor Kate Murphy draws on countless conversations she has had with everyone from priests to CIA interrogators, focus group moderators to bartenders, her great-great aunt to her friend&#8217;s toddler, to show how only by listening well can we truly connect with others.    </p>
<p>                     Listening has the potential to transform our relationships and our working lives, improve our self-knowledge, and increase our creativity and happiness. While it may take some effort, it&#8217;s a skill that can be learnt and perfected.    </p>
<p>                     When all we crave is to understand and be understood, You&#8217;re Not Listening shows us how.    </p>
<p>                    * With a new afterword by the author *    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book couldn&#8217;t be more timely. Inspiringly profound&#8230;smart and playful&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;ll be adopting Murphy&#8217;s advice&#8217; Sunday Times, Style</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/">You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Old Age]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the creator of Bulletproof coffee and the bestselling author of Head Strong and The Bulletproof Diet comes a plan to bypass plateaus and &#8216;up&#8217; your game at every age. Dave Asprey suffered countless symptoms of ageing as a young man, which sparked a lifelong burning desire to grow younger with each birthday. For more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/">Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the creator of Bulletproof coffee and the bestselling author of Head Strong and The Bulletproof Diet comes a plan to bypass plateaus and &#8216;up&#8217; your game at every age.    </p>
<p>                              Dave Asprey suffered countless symptoms of ageing as a young man, which sparked a lifelong burning desire to grow younger with each birthday. For more than twenty years, he has been on a quest to find innovative, science-backed methods to upgrade human biology and redefine the limits of the mind, body, and spirit. The results speak for themselves. Now in his forties, Dave is smarter, happier, and more fit and successful than ever before.    </p>
<p>                              In Super Human, he shows how this is level of health and performance possible for all of us. While we assume we will peak in middle age and then decline, Asprey&#8217;s research reveals there is another way. It is possible to make changes on the sub-cellular level to dramatically extend life span. And the tools to live longer also give you more energy and brainpower right now.    </p>
<p>                              The answers lie in Dave&#8217;s Seven Pillars of Ageing that contribute to degeneration and disease while diminishing your performance in the moment. Using simple interventions &#8211; like diet, sleep, light, exercise, and little-known but powerful hacks from ozone therapy to proper jaw alignment, you can decelerate cellular ageing and supercharge your body&#8217;s ability to heal and rejuvenate.    </p>
<p>                              A self-proclaimed human guinea pig, Asprey arms readers with practical advice to maximize their lives at every age with his signature mix of science-geek wonder, candour, and enthusiasm. Getting older no longer has to mean decline. Now it&#8217;s an opportunity to become Super Human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/super-human-the-bulletproof-plan-to-age-backward-and-maybe-even-live-forever-dave-asprey-abridged/">Super Human : The Bulletproof Plan to Age Backward and Maybe Even Live Forever &#8211; Dave Asprey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The ADHD Advantage : What You Thought Was a Diagnosis May Be Your Greatest Strength &#8211; Dale Archer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-adhd-advantage-what-you-thought-was-a-diagnosis-may-be-your-greatest-strength-dale-archer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-adhd-advantage-what-you-thought-was-a-diagnosis-may-be-your-greatest-strength-dale-archer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times-bestselling author of Better Than Normal, esteemed psychiatrist Dale Archer, M.D., reveals how ADHD might be the key to your success. For decades, in the United States and in countries around the world, physicians delivered the diagnosis of ADHD to patients as bad news and warned them about a lifelong struggle of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-adhd-advantage-what-you-thought-was-a-diagnosis-may-be-your-greatest-strength-dale-archer-abridged/">The ADHD Advantage : What You Thought Was a Diagnosis May Be Your Greatest Strength &#8211; Dale Archer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times-bestselling author of Better Than Normal, esteemed psychiatrist Dale Archer, M.D., reveals how ADHD might be the key to your success.     </p>
<p>                     For decades, in the United States and in countries around the world, physicians delivered the diagnosis of ADHD to patients as bad news and warned them about a lifelong struggle of managing symptoms. But The ADHD Advantage explodes this outlook, arguing that some of the most highly successful entrepreneurs, leaders, and entertainers have reached the pinnacle of success not in spite of their ADHD but because of it.     </p>
<p>                    People with ADHD are restless, endlessly curious, often adventurous, willing to take smart risks, and unusually resilient, and their ranks include some of the greatest entrepreneurs of our time. Sharing the stories of highly successful people with ADHD, Archer offers a vitally important and inspiring new way to recognize ADHD traits in oneself or in one&#8217;s loved ones and then leverage them to great advantage. Readers will learn to harness mental energy for greater creativity, embrace multitasking, and build a path to great success&#8211;without medication. As someone who not only has ADHD himself but has never used medication to treat it, Dr. Archer understands the condition from a unique professional and personal standpoint. Armed with new science and research, and his own personal experience, he teaches readers to embrace their natural strengths and innate potential.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-adhd-advantage-what-you-thought-was-a-diagnosis-may-be-your-greatest-strength-dale-archer-abridged/">The ADHD Advantage : What You Thought Was a Diagnosis May Be Your Greatest Strength &#8211; Dale Archer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Can Hear You Whisper : An Intimate Journey Through the Science of Sound and Language &#8211; Lydia Denworth (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Audiology & Otology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Speech & Language Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A skilled science translator, Denworth makes decibels, teslas and brain plasticity understandable to all.&#8221;-Washington Post Lydia Denworth&#8217;s third son, Alex, was nearly two when he was identified with significant hearing loss that was likely to get worse. Denworth knew the importance of enrichment to the developing brain but had never contemplated the opposite: deprivation. How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/">I Can Hear You Whisper : An Intimate Journey Through the Science of Sound and Language &#8211; Lydia Denworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A skilled science translator, Denworth makes decibels, teslas and brain plasticity understandable to all.&#8221;-Washington Post    </p>
<p>                    Lydia Denworth&#8217;s third son, Alex, was nearly two when he was identified with significant hearing loss that was likely to get worse. Denworth knew the importance of enrichment to the developing brain but had never contemplated the opposite: deprivation. How would a child&#8217;s brain grow outside the world of sound? How would he communicate? Would he learn to read and write?    </p>
<p>                    An acclaimed science journalist as well as a mother, Denworth made it her mission to find out, interviewing experts on language development, inventors of groundbreaking technology, Deaf leaders, and neuroscientists at the frontiers of brain plasticity research. I Can Hear You Whisper chronicles Denworth&#8217;s search for answers-and her new understanding of Deaf culture and the exquisite relationship between sound, language, and learning.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-can-hear-you-whisper-an-intimate-journey-through-the-science-of-sound-and-language-lydia-denworth-abridged/">I Can Hear You Whisper : An Intimate Journey Through the Science of Sound and Language &#8211; Lydia Denworth (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
