<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Law For The Lay Person Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/law-for-the-lay-person/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/law-for-the-lay-person/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Law For The Lay Person Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/law-for-the-lay-person/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Venture Deals : Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist &#8211; Brad Feld, Jason Mendelson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Help take your startup to the next step with the new and revised edition of the popular book on the VC deal process-from the co-founders of the Foundry Group How do venture capital deals come together? This is one of the most frequent questions asked by each generation of new entrepreneurs. Surprisingly, there is little [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/">Venture Deals : Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist &#8211; Brad Feld, Jason Mendelson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Help take your startup to the next step with the new and revised edition of the popular book on the VC deal process-from the co-founders of the Foundry Group    </p>
<p>                     How do venture capital deals come together? This is one of the most frequent questions asked by each generation of new entrepreneurs. Surprisingly, there is little reliable information on the subject. No one understands this better than Brad Feld and Jason Mendelson. The founders and driving force behind the Foundry Group-a venture capital firm focused on investing in early-stage information technology companies-Brad and Jason have been involved in hundreds of venture capital financings. Their investments range from small startups to large Series A venture financing rounds. The new edition of Venture Deals continues to show fledgling entrepreneurs the inner-workings of the VC process, from the venture capital term sheet and effective negotiating strategies to the initial seed and the later stages of development.    </p>
<p>                     Fully updated to reflect the intricacies of startups and entrepreneurship in today&#8217;s dynamic economic environment, this new edition includes revisions and updates to coverage on negotiating, gender issues, ICO&#8217;s, and economic terms. New chapters examine legal and procedural considerations relevant to fundraising, bank debt, equity and convertible debt, how to hire an investment banker to sell a company, and more.    </p>
<p>                    Provides valuable, real-world insights into venture capital structure and strategy<br />
                    Explains and clarifies the VC term sheet and other misunderstood aspects of capital funding<br />
                    Helps to build collaborative and supportive relationships between entrepreneurs and investors<br />
                    Draws from the author&#8217;s years of practical experience in the VC arena<br />
                    Includes extensively revised and updated content throughout to increase readability and currency    </p>
<p>                     Venture Deals: Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist is a must-have resource for Any aspiring entrepreneur, venture capitalist, or lawyer involved in VC deals as well as students and instructors in related areas of study.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/venture-deals-be-smarter-than-your-lawyer-and-venture-capitalist-brad-feld-jason-mendelson-abridged/">Venture Deals : Be Smarter Than Your Lawyer and Venture Capitalist &#8211; Brad Feld, Jason Mendelson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oversubscribed : How To Get People Lining Up To Do Business With You &#8211; Daniel Priestley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/oversubscribed-how-to-get-people-lining-up-to-do-business-with-you-daniel-priestley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/oversubscribed-how-to-get-people-lining-up-to-do-business-with-you-daniel-priestley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to get your business oversubscribed in a crowded marketplace to make your business stand out and get people lining up to do business with you Are you constantly chasing customers? Why does it seem like some businesses have their customers begging to purchase their goods or services? Think about it for a moment. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oversubscribed-how-to-get-people-lining-up-to-do-business-with-you-daniel-priestley-abridged/">Oversubscribed : How To Get People Lining Up To Do Business With You &#8211; Daniel Priestley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Learn how to get your business oversubscribed in a crowded marketplace to make your business stand out and get people lining up to do business with you     </p>
<p>                     Are you constantly chasing customers? Why does it seem like some businesses have their customers begging to purchase their goods or services? Think about it for a moment. When a new iPhone is released, why do customers camp overnight to be the first through the door? In cities with thousands of great restaurants, why do some restaurants require reservations months in advance? Why is it that some consultants, accountants, lawyers and healthcare professionals can charge exponentially more than others? In the modern marketplace, consumer options are virtually endless, intense competition is rife and so much is given away for free online.  Often businesses are left scrambling to attract enough customers to make a small profit. Yet the opposite is true for a small number of businesses that do things differently-customers chase them. They have buyers who gladly queue up, pay more, and eagerly wait for the chance to hand over their money for the next thing. How do these businesses do it? More importantly, how can you become one of them?     </p>
<p>                     Oversubscribed is the guide to transforming your business into one which customers fight over! Author Daniel Priestley, a successful entrepreneur who has built and sold businesses around the world, shares proven, real-world methods that will not only grab customers&#8217; attention, but will also have them lining up to buy from you. This invaluable guide will teach you how to drive demand for your products or services far beyond supply and will dramatically increase the success of your business. Now in its second edition, this updated version offers new insights and motivating examples that are right for the 2020s. This book will show you:    </p>
<p>                    The principles and philosophies Oversubscribed businesses live by that are often the opposite of what most businesses do<br />
                    Specific steps for getting into the mind of your customer so they only want to buy from your business<br />
                    How to structure campaigns and product launches that systematically get your business Oversubscribed<br />
                    How to implement a process of signalling to market, and collect signals back from market to build up desire and demand for your products and services    </p>
<p>                     The new edition of Oversubscribed: How to get people lining up to do business with you is a must-read for entrepreneurs, marketers, business leaders and owners, team managers, and business students.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/oversubscribed-how-to-get-people-lining-up-to-do-business-with-you-daniel-priestley-abridged/">Oversubscribed : How To Get People Lining Up To Do Business With You &#8211; Daniel Priestley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Four Steps to the Epiphany : Successful Strategies for Products that Win &#8211; Steve Blank (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-four-steps-to-the-epiphany-successful-strategies-for-products-that-win-steve-blank-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-four-steps-to-the-epiphany-successful-strategies-for-products-that-win-steve-blank-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling classic that launched 10,000 startups and new corporate ventures &#8211; The Four Steps to the Epiphany is one of the most influential and practical business books of all time. The Four Steps to the Epiphany launched the Lean Startup approach to new ventures. It was the first book to offer that startups are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-four-steps-to-the-epiphany-successful-strategies-for-products-that-win-steve-blank-abridged/">The Four Steps to the Epiphany : Successful Strategies for Products that Win &#8211; Steve Blank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling classic that launched 10,000 startups and new corporate ventures &#8211; The Four Steps to the Epiphany is one of the most influential and practical business books of all time.<br />
                    The Four Steps to the Epiphany launched the Lean Startup approach to new ventures. It was the first book to offer that startups are not smaller versions of large companies and that new ventures are different than existing ones. Startups search for business models while existing companies execute them.    </p>
<p>                    The book offers the practical and proven four-step Customer Development process for search and offers insight into what makes some startups successful and leaves others selling off their furniture.<br />
                    Rather than blindly execute a plan, The Four Steps helps uncover flaws in product and business plans and correct them before they become costly. Rapid iteration, customer feedback, testing your assumptions are all explained in this book.    </p>
<p>                    Packed with concrete examples of what to do, how to do it and when to do it, the book will leave you with new skills to organize sales, marketing and your business for success.<br />
                    If your organization is starting a new venture, and you&#8217;re thinking how to successfully organize sales, marketing and business development you need The Four Steps to the Epiphany.<br />
                    Essential reading for anyone starting something new.     </p>
<p>                     The Four Steps to the Epiphany  was originally published by K&#038;S Ranch Publishing Inc. and is now available from Wiley. The cover, design, and content are the same as the prior release and should not be considered a new or updated product.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-four-steps-to-the-epiphany-successful-strategies-for-products-that-win-steve-blank-abridged/">The Four Steps to the Epiphany : Successful Strategies for Products that Win &#8211; Steve Blank (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free : Laws for the Internet Age &#8211; Cory Doctorow, Foreword by Neil Gaiman, Foreword by Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Copyright Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Filled with wisdom and thought experiments and things that will mess with your mind.&#8221; &#8212; Neil Gaiman, author of The Graveyard Book and American Gods In sharply argued, fast-moving chapters, Cory Doctorow&#8217;s Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free takes on the state of copyright and creative success in the digital age. Can small artists still [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/">Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free : Laws for the Internet Age &#8211; Cory Doctorow, Foreword by Neil Gaiman, Foreword by Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Filled with wisdom and thought experiments and things that will mess with your mind.&#8221; &#8212; Neil Gaiman, author of The Graveyard Book and American Gods     </p>
<p>                    In sharply argued, fast-moving chapters, Cory Doctorow&#8217;s Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free takes on the state of copyright and creative success in the digital age. Can small artists still thrive in the Internet era? Can giant record labels avoid alienating their audiences? This is a book about the pitfalls, and the opportunities, creative industries (and individuals) are confronting today&#8211;about how the old models have failed or found new footing, and about what might soon replace them. An essential read for anyone with a stake in the future of the arts, Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free offers a vivid guide to the ways creativity and the Internet interact today, and to what might be coming next.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/">Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free : Laws for the Internet Age &#8211; Cory Doctorow, Foreword by Neil Gaiman, Foreword by Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
