<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Regional Government Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/regional-government/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/regional-government/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Regional Government Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/regional-government/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Profiles in Corruption : Abuse of Power by America&#8217;s Progressive Elite &#8211; Peter Schweizer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER! Washington insiders operate by a proven credo: When a Peter Schweizer book drops, duck and brace for impact. For over a decade, the work of six-time New York Times bestselling investigative reporter Peter Schweizer has sent shockwaves through the political universe. Clinton Cash revealed the Clintons&#8217; international money flow, exposed global [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/">Profiles in Corruption : Abuse of Power by America&#8217;s Progressive Elite &#8211; Peter Schweizer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER!    </p>
<p>                    Washington insiders operate by a proven credo: When a Peter Schweizer book drops, duck and brace for impact.    </p>
<p>                    For over a decade, the work of six-time New York Times bestselling investigative reporter Peter Schweizer has sent shockwaves through the political universe.    </p>
<p>                    Clinton Cash revealed the Clintons&#8217; international money flow, exposed global corruption, and sparked an FBI investigation. Secret Empires exposed bipartisan corruption and launched congressional investigations. And Throw Them All Out and Extortion prompted passage of the STOCK Act. Indeed, Schweizer&#8217;s &#8220;follow the money&#8221; bombshell revelations have been featured on the front pages of the New York Times and the Wall Street Journal, and regularly appear on national news programs, including 60 Minutes.    </p>
<p>                    Now Schweizer and his team of seasoned investigators turn their focus to the nation&#8217;s top progressives-politicians who strive to acquire more government power to achieve their political ends.    </p>
<p>                    Can they be trusted with more power?    </p>
<p>                    In Profiles in Corruption, Schweizer offers a deep-dive investigation into the private finances, and secrets deals of some of America&#8217;s top political leaders. And, as usual, he doesn&#8217;t disappoint, with never-before-reported revelations that uncover corruption and abuse of power-all backed up by a mountain of corporate documents and legal filings from around the globe. Learn about how they are making sweetheart deals, generating side income, bending the law to their own benefits, using legislation to advance their own interests, and much more.    </p>
<p>                    Profiles in Corruption contains tomorrow&#8217;s headlines.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/profiles-in-corruption-abuse-of-power-by-americas-progressive-elite-peter-schweizer-abridged/">Profiles in Corruption : Abuse of Power by America&#8217;s Progressive Elite &#8211; Peter Schweizer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Films, Cinema]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Actors & Performers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial and truly unique life. Born in a small Austrian town in 1947, a year of famine, he was the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/">Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his signature larger-than-life style, Arnold Schwarzenegger&#8217;s Total Recall is a revealing self-portrait of his illustrious, controversial and truly unique life.    </p>
<p>                     Born in a small Austrian town in 1947, a year of famine, he was the son of an austere police chief. He dreamed of moving to America to become a bodybuilding champion and a movie star. By the age of 21, he was living in Los Angeles and had been crowned Mr Universe. Within five years, he had learned English and become the greatest bodybuilder in the world. Within ten years, he had earned his college degree and was a millionaire from his business enterprises in real estate, landscaping and bodybuilding. He was also the winner of a Golden Globe Award for his debut as a dramatic actor in Stay Hungry.    </p>
<p>                     But that was only the beginning. The Terminator spawned numerous sequels and made him one of Hollywood&#8217;s biggest stars, as he had a series of hit films including Predator, Total Recall, True Lies and Twins. He married Maria Shriver, becoming part of the Kennedy clan, while going on to become the Republican governor of California, where he led the state through a budget crisis, natural disasters and political turmoil.     </p>
<p>                    It is the greatest immigrant success story of our time. His story is unique, and uniquely entertaining, and he tells it brilliantly in these pages. Until now, he has never told the full story of his life, in his own voice. Here is Arnold, with total recall.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/total-recall-arnold-schwarzenegger-abridged/">Total Recall &#8211; Arnold Schwarzenegger (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
