<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Clinical &amp; Internal Medicine Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/clinical-internal-medicine/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/clinical-internal-medicine/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Clinical &amp; Internal Medicine Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/clinical-internal-medicine/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Biological Mind : How Brain, Body, and Environment Collaborate to Make Us Who We Are &#8211; Alan Jasanoff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-biological-mind-how-brain-body-and-environment-collaborate-to-make-us-who-we-are-alan-jasanoff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-biological-mind-how-brain-body-and-environment-collaborate-to-make-us-who-we-are-alan-jasanoff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A pioneering neuroscientist argues that we are more than our brains To many, the brain is the seat of personal identity and autonomy. But the way we talk about the brain is often rooted more in mystical conceptions of the soul than in scientific fact. This blinds us to the physical realities of mental function. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-biological-mind-how-brain-body-and-environment-collaborate-to-make-us-who-we-are-alan-jasanoff-abridged/">The Biological Mind : How Brain, Body, and Environment Collaborate to Make Us Who We Are &#8211; Alan Jasanoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A pioneering neuroscientist argues that we are more than our brains    </p>
<p>                    To many, the brain is the seat of personal identity and autonomy. But the way we talk about the brain is often rooted more in mystical conceptions of the soul than in scientific fact. This blinds us to the physical realities of mental function. We ignore bodily influences on our psychology, from chemicals in the blood to bacteria in the gut, and overlook the ways that the environment affects our behavior, via factors varying from subconscious sights and sounds to the weather. As a result, we alternately overestimate our capacity for free will or equate brains to inorganic machines like computers. But a brain is neither a soul nor an electrical network: it is a bodily organ, and it cannot be separated from its surroundings. Our selves aren&#8217;t just inside our heads&#8211;they&#8217;re spread throughout our bodies and beyond. Only once we come to terms with this can we grasp the true nature of our humanity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-biological-mind-how-brain-body-and-environment-collaborate-to-make-us-who-we-are-alan-jasanoff-abridged/">The Biological Mind : How Brain, Body, and Environment Collaborate to Make Us Who We Are &#8211; Alan Jasanoff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Period Power : Harness Your Hormones and Get Your Cycle Working For You &#8211; Maisie Hill (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/period-power-harness-your-hormones-and-get-your-cycle-working-for-you-maisie-hill-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gynaecology & Obstetrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Reproduction, Growth & Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Midwifery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Women's Health]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/period-power-harness-your-hormones-and-get-your-cycle-working-for-you-maisie-hill-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hill&#8217;s advice is straightforward and no-nonsense&#8217; &#8211; The Guardian &#8216;A life-transforming book&#8230; fascinating &#8211; Daily Mail &#8216;Maisie Hill has written a bloody brilliant book (pun intended). Everything you need to know about periods and how they affect you and your life is here. It&#8217;s revolutionary&#8217; &#8211; Miranda Sawyer &#8216;Thank GOODNESS for Maisie Hill! Flipping open [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/period-power-harness-your-hormones-and-get-your-cycle-working-for-you-maisie-hill-abridged/">Period Power : Harness Your Hormones and Get Your Cycle Working For You &#8211; Maisie Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hill&#8217;s advice is straightforward and no-nonsense&#8217; &#8211; The Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A life-transforming book&#8230; fascinating &#8211; Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Maisie Hill has written a bloody brilliant book (pun intended). Everything you need to know about periods and how they affect you and your life is here. It&#8217;s revolutionary&#8217; &#8211; Miranda Sawyer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thank GOODNESS for Maisie Hill! Flipping open the lid on a vital conversation. It&#8217;s about time we claimed the power of our periods!&#8217; &#8211; Gemma Cairney, broadcaster &#038; co-founder of Boom Shakalaka Productions    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This is such an important book. Maisie&#8217;s insights and cycle strategy have changed my life and my cycle. Period Power is written with such intelligence, humour and a deep understanding of women&#8217;s health. If you have a period you need to read this book.&#8217; &#8211; Anna Jones, author of The Modern Cook&#8217;s Year    </p>
<p>                    A profound and practical blueprint for aligning daily life with your menstrual cycle.    </p>
<p>                    Period Power is the handbook to periods and hormones that will leave you wondering why the hell nobody told you this sooner.    </p>
<p>                    The hormones of the menstrual cycle profoundly influence our energy, mood and behaviour, but all too often we&#8217;re taught that our hormones make us unreliable, moody bitches, or that it&#8217;s our lot in life to put up with &#8216;women&#8217;s problems&#8217;. Maisie Hill, a women&#8217;s health practitioner, knows the power of working with the menstrual cycle and refuses to accept this theory. Instead, Maisie believes that our hormones are there to serve us and, if utilized correctly, can be used to help you get what you want out of life. Yes, we are hormonal, and that&#8217;s a very good thing.    </p>
<p>                    This revolutionary book reveals everything you need to know about taking control of your menstrual cycle and outlines The Cycle Strategy to help us perform at our best, throughout our cycle. In Period Power you will discover how to:    </p>
<p>                    &#8211; maximise your natural superpowers each month while making adjustments for the darker days, and use Maisie&#8217;s favourite tips to improve them<br />
                    &#8211; identify your personal patterns, powers and pitfalls for each phase of the menstrual cycle<br />
                    &#8211; plan your month to perform at your best in all aspects of your life<br />
                    &#8211; figure out if you have a hormonal imbalance and what to do about it.    </p>
<p>                    Period Power is a no-nonsense guide with all the tools you need to improve your menstrual health.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/period-power-harness-your-hormones-and-get-your-cycle-working-for-you-maisie-hill-abridged/">Period Power : Harness Your Hormones and Get Your Cycle Working For You &#8211; Maisie Hill (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Into the Magic Shop : A neurosurgeon&#8217;s true story of the life-changing magic of mindfulness and compassion that inspired the hit K-pop band BTS &#8211; Dr James Doty (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/into-the-magic-shop-a-neurosurgeons-true-story-of-the-life-changing-magic-of-mindfulness-and-compassion-that-inspired-the-hit-k-pop-band-bts-dr-james-doty-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Religious & Spiritual]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurology & Clinical Neurophysiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosurgery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/into-the-magic-shop-a-neurosurgeons-true-story-of-the-life-changing-magic-of-mindfulness-and-compassion-that-inspired-the-hit-k-pop-band-bts-dr-james-doty-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The award-winning New York Times bestseller that inspired BTS&#8217;s K-pop song &#8216;Magic Shop&#8217;. The day that 12-year-old James Doty walked in to his local magic shop is the day that changed his life. Once the neglected son of an alcoholic father and a mother with chronic depression, he has gone on to become a leading [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/into-the-magic-shop-a-neurosurgeons-true-story-of-the-life-changing-magic-of-mindfulness-and-compassion-that-inspired-the-hit-k-pop-band-bts-dr-james-doty-abridged/">Into the Magic Shop : A neurosurgeon&#8217;s true story of the life-changing magic of mindfulness and compassion that inspired the hit K-pop band BTS &#8211; Dr James Doty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The award-winning New York Times bestseller that inspired BTS&#8217;s K-pop song &#8216;Magic Shop&#8217;.    </p>
<p>                    The day that 12-year-old James Doty walked in to his local magic shop is the day that changed his life.     </p>
<p>                    Once the neglected son of an alcoholic father and a mother with chronic depression, he has gone on to become a leading neurosurgeon, based at Stanford University. He credits Ruth for this incredible turnaround: the remarkable woman he met at the Cactus Rabbit Magic Shop, who devoted the summer to transforming his mind and opening his heart.    </p>
<p>                    In this uplifting memoir, Jim explains the visualisation techniques Ruth taught him that gave him the self-esteem to imagine a new future for himself. He examines the science behind mindfulness and why the skills he learned &#8211; of focus and attention &#8211; now help him to think fast and keep calm in the operating theatre. And he shows us what is possible when you start to change your brain and your heart. Into the Magic Shop imparts some powerful life lessons about how to live better, and inspires us to believe that we all have inside us the capacity to change our own destiny.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;m sure many readers will be moved by this inspiring story to open their hearts and see what they too can do for others&#8217; &#8211; His Holiness the Dalai Lama</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/into-the-magic-shop-a-neurosurgeons-true-story-of-the-life-changing-magic-of-mindfulness-and-compassion-that-inspired-the-hit-k-pop-band-bts-dr-james-doty-abridged/">Into the Magic Shop : A neurosurgeon&#8217;s true story of the life-changing magic of mindfulness and compassion that inspired the hit K-pop band BTS &#8211; Dr James Doty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Doctor/patient Relationship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Systems & Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Administration & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Equipment & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Profession]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nursing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Telemedicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Therapy & Therapeutics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A trip to the doctor is almost a guarantee of misery. You&#8217;ll make an appointment months in advance. You&#8217;ll probably wait for several hours until you hear &#8220;the doctor will see you now&#8221;,but only for fifteen minutes! Then you&#8217;ll wait even longer for lab tests, the results of which you&#8217;ll likely never see, unless they [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/">The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A trip to the doctor is almost a guarantee of misery. You&#8217;ll make an appointment months in advance. You&#8217;ll probably wait for several hours until you hear &#8220;the doctor will see you now&#8221;,but only for fifteen minutes! Then you&#8217;ll wait even longer for lab tests, the results of which you&#8217;ll likely never see, unless they indicate further (and more invasive) tests, most of which will probably prove unnecessary (much like physicals themselves). And your bill will be astronomical.In  The Patient Will See You Now , Eric Topol, one of the nation&#8217;s top physicians, shows why medicine does not have to be that way. Instead, you could use your smartphone to get rapid test results from one drop of blood, monitor your vital signs both day and night, and use an artificially intelligent algorithm to receive a diagnosis without having to see a doctor, all at a small fraction of the cost imposed by our modern healthcare system. The change is powered by what Topol calls medicine&#8217;s &#8220;Gutenberg moment.&#8221; Much as the printing press took learning out of the hands of a priestly class, the mobile internet is doing the same for medicine, giving us unprecedented control over our healthcare. With smartphones in hand, we are no longer beholden to an impersonal and paternalistic system in which &#8220;doctor knows best.&#8221; Medicine has been digitized, Topol argues now it will be democratized. Computers will replace physicians for many diagnostic tasks, citizen science will give rise to citizen medicine, and enormous data sets will give us new means to attack conditions that have long been incurable. Massive, open, online medicine, where diagnostics are done by Facebook-like comparisons of medical profiles, will enable real-time, real-world research on massive populations. There&#8217;s no doubt the path forward will be complicated: the medical establishment will resist these changes, and digitized medicine inevitably raises serious issues surrounding privacy. Nevertheless, the result,better, cheaper, and more human health care,will be worth it.Provocative and engrossing,  The Patient Will See You Now  is essential reading for anyone who thinks they deserve better health care. That is, for all of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-patient-will-see-you-now-the-future-of-medicine-is-in-your-hands-eric-topol-abridged/">The Patient Will See You Now : The Future of Medicine Is in Your Hands &#8211; Eric Topol (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of Illness &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Complementary Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diseases & Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling work that overturns conventional conceptions of health and illness to offer new methods for increasing vital longevity. CAN WE LIVE ROBUSTLY UNTIL OUR LAST BREATH? Do we have to suffer from debilitating conditions and sickness? Is it possible to add more vibrant years to our lives? In the #1 [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/">The End of Illness &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 New York Times bestselling work that overturns conventional conceptions of health and illness to offer new methods for increasing vital longevity. CAN WE LIVE ROBUSTLY UNTIL OUR LAST BREATH? Do we have to suffer from debilitating conditions and sickness? Is it possible to add more vibrant years to our lives? In the #1 New York Times bestselling The End of Illness, Dr. David Agus tackles these fundamental questions and dismantles misperceptions about what &#8220;health&#8221; really means. Presenting an eye-opening picture of the human body and all the ways it works&#8211;and fails&#8211;Dr. Agus shows us how a new perspective on our individual health will allow us to achieve a long, vigorous life. Offering insights and access to powerful new technologies that promise to transform medicine, Dr. Agus emphasizes his belief that there is no &#8220;right&#8221; answer, no master guide that is &#8220;one size fits all.&#8221; Each one of us must get to know our bodies in uniquely personal ways, and he shows us exactly how to do that. A bold call for all of us to become our own personal health advocates, The End of Illness is a moving departure from orthodox thinking.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-illness-david-b-agus-abridged/">The End of Illness &#8211; David B Agus (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In a Different Key : The Story of Autism &#8211; John Donvan, Caren Zucker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-a-different-key-the-story-of-autism-john-donvan-caren-zucker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical & Internal Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-a-different-key-the-story-of-autism-john-donvan-caren-zucker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A magnificent opus &#8230; extraordinary, spellbinding &#8230; this book does what no other on autism has done&#8217; Ann Bauer, Washington Post *Pulitzer finalist 2017* The stunning history of autism as it has been discovered and felt by parents, children and doctors Nearly seventy-five years ago, Donald Triplett of Forest, Mississippi became the first child diagnosed [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-a-different-key-the-story-of-autism-john-donvan-caren-zucker-abridged/">In a Different Key : The Story of Autism &#8211; John Donvan, Caren Zucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A magnificent opus &#8230; extraordinary, spellbinding &#8230; this book does what no other on autism has done&#8217; Ann Bauer, Washington Post    </p>
<p>                    *Pulitzer finalist 2017*    </p>
<p>                    The stunning history of autism as it has been discovered and felt by parents, children and doctors    </p>
<p>                    Nearly seventy-five years ago, Donald Triplett of Forest, Mississippi became the first child diagnosed with autism. In a Different Key tells the extraordinary story of the world his diagnosis created &#8211; a riveting human drama that takes us across continents and through some of the great social movements of the twentieth century.    </p>
<p>                    The history of autism is, above all, the story of families fighting for a place in the world for their children. It is the story of women like Ruth Sullivan, who rebelled against a medical establishment that blamed &#8220;refrigerator mothers&#8221; for causing autism, of fathers who pushed scientists to dig harder for treatments, of parents who forced schools to accept their children. But many others played starring roles too: doctors like Leo Kanner, who pioneered our understanding of autism, scientists who sparred over how to treat autism, and those with autism, like Temple Grandin and Ari Ne&#8217;eman, who explained their inner worlds and championed a philosophy of &#8216;neurodiversity&#8217;.     </p>
<p>                    This is also a story of fierce controversy: from the question of whether there is truly an autism &#8216;epidemic&#8217;, and whether vaccines played a part in it, to scandals involving &#8216;facilitated communication&#8217;, one of many treatments that have proved to be blind alleys. And there are dark turns too: we learn about experimenters feeding LSD to children with autism, or shocking them with electricity to change their behaviour; and the authors reveal, for the first time, that Hans Asperger, discoverer of the syndrome named after him, may have cooperated with the Nazis in sending disabled children to their deaths.    </p>
<p>                    By turns intimate and panoramic, In a Different Key takes us on a journey from an era when families were shamed and children were condemned to institutions, to one in which parents and people with autism push not simply for inclusion, but for a new understanding of autism: as difference rather than disability.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-a-different-key-the-story-of-autism-john-donvan-caren-zucker-abridged/">In a Different Key : The Story of Autism &#8211; John Donvan, Caren Zucker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
