<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Retirement Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/retirement/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/retirement/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Retirement Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/retirement/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Index Card &#8211; Helaine Olen, Harold Pollack (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-index-card-helaine-olen-harold-pollack-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-index-card-helaine-olen-harold-pollack-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The newbie investor will not find a better guide to personal finance.&#8221; &#8211;Burton Malkiel, author of A RANDOM WALK DOWN WALL STREET TV analysts and money managers would have you believe your finances are enormously complicated, and if you don&#8217;t follow their guidance, you&#8217;ll end up in the poorhouse. They&#8217;re wrong. When University of Chicago [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-index-card-helaine-olen-harold-pollack-abridged/">The Index Card &#8211; Helaine Olen, Harold Pollack (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;The newbie investor will not find a better guide to personal finance.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Burton Malkiel, author of A RANDOM WALK DOWN WALL STREET       </p>
<p>                    TV analysts and money managers would have you believe your finances are enormously complicated, and if you don&#8217;t follow their guidance, you&#8217;ll end up in the poorhouse.     </p>
<p>                    They&#8217;re wrong.     </p>
<p>                    When University of Chicago professor Harold Pollack interviewed Helaine Olen, an award-winning financial journalist and the author of the bestselling Pound Foolish, he made an off­hand suggestion: everything you need to know about managing your money could fit on an index card. To prove his point, he grabbed a 4 x 6 card, scribbled down a list of rules, and posted a picture of the card online. The post went viral.     </p>
<p>                    Now, Pollack teams up with Olen to explain why the ten simple rules of the index card outperform more complicated financial strategies. Inside is an easy-to-follow action plan that works in good times and bad, giving you the tools, knowledge, and confidence to seize control of your financial life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-index-card-helaine-olen-harold-pollack-abridged/">The Index Card &#8211; Helaine Olen, Harold Pollack (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Make Your Money Last &#8211; Completely Updated for Planning Today : The Indispensable Retirement Guide &#8211; Jane Bryant Quinn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-make-your-money-last-completely-updated-for-planning-today-the-indispensable-retirement-guide-jane-bryant-quinn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-make-your-money-last-completely-updated-for-planning-today-the-indispensable-retirement-guide-jane-bryant-quinn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NOW COMPLETELY UPDATED to reflect the changes in tax legislation, health insurance, and the new investment realities. In this &#8220;highly valuable resource&#8221; (Publishers Weekly, starred review) Quinn &#8220;provides simple, straightforward&#8221; (The New York Times) solutions to the universal retirement dilemma&#8211;how to make your limited savings last for life&#8211;covering mortgages, social security, income investing, annuities, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-make-your-money-last-completely-updated-for-planning-today-the-indispensable-retirement-guide-jane-bryant-quinn-abridged/">How to Make Your Money Last &#8211; Completely Updated for Planning Today : The Indispensable Retirement Guide &#8211; Jane Bryant Quinn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NOW COMPLETELY UPDATED to reflect the changes in tax legislation, health insurance, and the new investment realities. In this &#8220;highly valuable resource&#8221; (Publishers Weekly, starred review) Quinn &#8220;provides simple, straightforward&#8221; (The New York Times) solutions to the universal retirement dilemma&#8211;how to make your limited savings last for life&#8211;covering mortgages, social security, income investing, annuities, and more!      </p>
<p>                    Will you run out of money in your older age? That&#8217;s the biggest worry for people newly retired or planning to retire. Fortunately, you don&#8217;t have to plan in the dark. Jane Bryant Quinn tells you how to squeeze a higher income from all your assets&#8211;including your social security account (get every dollar you&#8217;re entitled to), a pension (discover whether a lump sum or a lifetime monthly income will pay you more), your home equity (sell, rent, or take a reverse mortgage?), savings (how to use them safely to raise your monthly income), retirement accounts (invest the money for growth in ways that let you sleep at night), and&#8211;critically&#8211;how much of your savings you can afford to spend every year without running out. There are easy ways to figure all this out. Who knew?     </p>
<p>                    Quinn also shows you how to evaluate your real risks. If you stick with super-safe investment choices, your money might not last and your lifestyle might erode. The same might be true if you rely on traditional income investments. Quinn rethinks the meaning of &#8220;income investing,&#8221; by combining reliable cash flow during the early years of your retirement with low-risk growth investments, to provide extra money for your later years. Odds are, you&#8217;ll live longer than you might imagine, meaning that your savings will stretch for many more years than you might have planned for. With the help of this book, you can turn those retirement funds into a &#8220;homemade&#8221; paycheck that will last for life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-make-your-money-last-completely-updated-for-planning-today-the-indispensable-retirement-guide-jane-bryant-quinn-abridged/">How to Make Your Money Last &#8211; Completely Updated for Planning Today : The Indispensable Retirement Guide &#8211; Jane Bryant Quinn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Get What&#8217;s Yours : The Secrets to Maxing Out Your Social Security &#8211; Professor of Economics Laurence J Kotlikoff, Philip Moeller, Paul Solman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/get-whats-yours-the-secrets-to-maxing-out-your-social-security-professor-of-economics-laurence-j-kotlikoff-philip-moeller-paul-solman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Welfare & Benefit Systems]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/get-whats-yours-the-secrets-to-maxing-out-your-social-security-professor-of-economics-laurence-j-kotlikoff-philip-moeller-paul-solman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Social Security law has changed! Get What&#8217;s Yours has been revised and updated to reflect new regulations that took effect on April 29, 2016. Get What&#8217;s Yours has proven itself to be the definitive book about how to navigate the forbidding maze of Social Security and emerge with the highest possible benefits. It is an [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-whats-yours-the-secrets-to-maxing-out-your-social-security-professor-of-economics-laurence-j-kotlikoff-philip-moeller-paul-solman-abridged/">Get What&#8217;s Yours : The Secrets to Maxing Out Your Social Security &#8211; Professor of Economics Laurence J Kotlikoff, Philip Moeller, Paul Solman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Social Security law has changed! Get What&#8217;s Yours has been revised and updated to reflect new regulations that took effect on April 29, 2016.     </p>
<p>                    Get What&#8217;s Yours has proven itself to be the definitive book about how to navigate the forbidding maze of Social Security and emerge with the highest possible benefits. It is an engaging manual of tactics and strategies written by well-known financial commentators that is unobtainable elsewhere. You could try reading all 2,728 rules of the Social Security system (and the thousands of explanations of these rules), but academia&#8217;s Kotlikoff, the popular press&#8217;s Moeller, and public television&#8217;s Solman explain the Social Security system just as comprehensively, and a lot more comprehensibly. Moreover, they demonstrate that what you don&#8217;t know can seriously hurt you: wrong decisions about which Social Security benefits to apply for cost individual retirees tens of thousands of dollars in lost income every year. (Some of those people are even in the book.)     </p>
<p>                    Changes to Social Security that take effect in 2016 make it more important than ever to wait as long as possible (until age 70, if possible) to claim Social Security benefits. The new law also has significant implications for those who wish to claim divorced spousal benefits (and how many Social Security recipients even know about divorced spousal benefits?). Besides addressing these and other issues, this revised edition contains a chapter explaining how Medicare rules can shape Social Security decisions.     </p>
<p>                    Many other personal-finance books briefly address Social Security, but none offers the full, authoritative, yet conversational analysis of Get What&#8217;s Yours.     </p>
<p>                    Get What&#8217;s Yours explains Social Security benefits through basic strategies and stirring stories. It covers the most frequent benefit scenarios faced by married retired couples; by divorced retirees; by widows and widowers. It explains what to do if you&#8217;re a retired parent of dependent children; disabled; an eligible beneficiary who continues to work. It addresses the tax consequences of your choices, as well as the financial implications for other investments. It does all this and more.     </p>
<p>                    There are more than 52 million Americans aged 54 to 69. Ten thousand of them reach Social Security&#8217;s full retirement age of 66 every day. For all these people&#8211;and for their families and friends&#8211;Get What&#8217;s Yours has proven to be an invaluable, and therefore indispensable, tool.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/get-whats-yours-the-secrets-to-maxing-out-your-social-security-professor-of-economics-laurence-j-kotlikoff-philip-moeller-paul-solman-abridged/">Get What&#8217;s Yours : The Secrets to Maxing Out Your Social Security &#8211; Professor of Economics Laurence J Kotlikoff, Philip Moeller, Paul Solman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Your Retirement Salary : How to use your lifetime of pension savings to pay yourself an income in your retirement &#8211; Richard Dyson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/your-retirement-salary-how-to-use-your-lifetime-of-pension-savings-to-pay-yourself-an-income-in-your-retirement-richard-dyson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/your-retirement-salary-how-to-use-your-lifetime-of-pension-savings-to-pay-yourself-an-income-in-your-retirement-richard-dyson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You have spent a few decades working, earning a salary from your employers, and saving into company and personal pensions along the way. Now, retirement is approaching. How will you turn your savings into a salary to pay for essentials and leisure time in retirement? How will you make sure that you don&#8217;t run out [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/your-retirement-salary-how-to-use-your-lifetime-of-pension-savings-to-pay-yourself-an-income-in-your-retirement-richard-dyson-abridged/">Your Retirement Salary : How to use your lifetime of pension savings to pay yourself an income in your retirement &#8211; Richard Dyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You have spent a few decades working, earning a salary from your employers, and saving into company and personal pensions along the way. Now, retirement is approaching.<br />
                     How will you turn your savings into a salary to pay for essentials and leisure time in retirement? How will you make sure that you don&#8217;t run out of money too soon? What do the UK pension freedoms mean for you?     </p>
<p>                    In this one-of-a-kind book, personal finance experts Richard Dyson and Richard Evans answer these questions and equip you with everything you need to know to turn your pension savings into an income that will last throughout your retirement.<br />
                     You will learn:<br />
                    &#8212; How to take control of your pension savings by tracking down all of your pension pots and combining them.<br />
                    &#8212; When you can afford to retire.<br />
                    &#8212; Steps to take to avoid running out of money.<br />
                    &#8212; How to build an income-paying portfolio of fund investments from scratch.<br />
                    &#8212; How to withdraw a sustainable income from your portfolio.<br />
                    &#8212; How annuities work and whether they have a role for you.<br />
                    &#8212; How to make the most of the tax rules.<br />
                    &#8212; The contribution made by the State Pension.<br />
                    &#8212; When to seek professional advice.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/your-retirement-salary-how-to-use-your-lifetime-of-pension-savings-to-pay-yourself-an-income-in-your-retirement-richard-dyson-abridged/">Your Retirement Salary : How to use your lifetime of pension savings to pay yourself an income in your retirement &#8211; Richard Dyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everyday Millionaires &#8211; Chris Hogan, Foreword by Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everyday-millionaires-chris-hogan-foreword-by-dave-ramsey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Retirement]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everyday-millionaires-chris-hogan-foreword-by-dave-ramsey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Everyday Millionaires, #1 national best-selling author Chris Hoganwill show you how ordinary people built extraordinary wealth&#8211;and how you can too. You&#8217;ll learn how millionaires live on less than they make, avoid debt, invest, are disciplined and responsible! This book is based on the largest study EVER conducted on 10,000 U.S. millionaires&#8211;and the results will [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everyday-millionaires-chris-hogan-foreword-by-dave-ramsey-abridged/">Everyday Millionaires &#8211; Chris Hogan, Foreword by Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Everyday Millionaires, #1 national best-selling author Chris Hoganwill show you how ordinary people built extraordinary wealth&#8211;and how you can too. You&#8217;ll learn how millionaires live on less than they make, avoid debt, invest, are disciplined and responsible!    </p>
<p>                    This book is based on the largest study EVER conducted on 10,000 U.S. millionaires&#8211;and the results will shock you! You&#8217;ll learn that building wealth has almost NOTHING to do with your income or your background! It doesn&#8217;t matter where you come from. It matters where you&#8217;re going.    </p>
<p>                    Most people think it takes crazy investing knowledge, a giant salary, a streak of luck, or a huge inheritance to become a millionaire. But that couldn&#8217;t be further from the truth! Here&#8217;s what you need to understand: if you&#8217;re willing to do the work&#8211;if you&#8217;ll follow the stuff we teach, if you&#8217;ll commit to our plan&#8211;then you CAN become a millionaire.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everyday-millionaires-chris-hogan-foreword-by-dave-ramsey-abridged/">Everyday Millionaires &#8211; Chris Hogan, Foreword by Dave Ramsey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
