<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Religion: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/religion-general/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/religion-general/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:00:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Religion: General Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/religion-general/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Ultimate Journey &#8211; Robert A. Monroe</title>
		<link>/the-ultimate-journey-robert-a-monroe/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astral Projection & Out-of-body Experiences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Body]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spiritualism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Unexplained Phenomena / The Paranormal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ultimate-journey-robert-a-monroe/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 1958, a successful businessman named Robert Mornroe began to have experiences that drastically altered his life. Unpredictably, and without his willing it, Monroe found himself leaving his physical body to travel via a second body to locales far removed from the physical and spiritual realities of his life. He was inhabiting a place unbounded [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultimate-journey-robert-a-monroe/">The Ultimate Journey &#8211; Robert A. Monroe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 1958, a successful businessman named Robert Mornroe began to have experiences that drastically altered his life. Unpredictably, and without his willing it, Monroe found himself leaving his physical body to travel via a second body to locales far removed from the physical and spiritual realities of his life. He was inhabiting a place unbounded by life or death.     </p>
<p>                    Monroe recorded these experiences in two bestselling, landmark books, Journeys Out of the Body and Far Journeys. Ultimate Journey, his final and career-defining work, takes us further than we thought possible&#8211;and reveals to us what it all means.     </p>
<p>                    Ultimate Journey charts that area which lies over the edge, beyond the limits of the physical world. It presents us with a map of the interstate&#8211;the route that opens to us when we leave our physical lives, with their entry and exit ramps, their singposts and their hazards. It also tells us how Monroe found the route and travelled it, and uncovered the reason and the purpose of this pioneering expedition. It is a journey that reveals basic truths about the meaning and purpose of life&#8211;and of what lies beyond.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ultimate-journey-robert-a-monroe/">The Ultimate Journey &#8211; Robert A. Monroe</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Revival: Economics for the Twenty-first Century (2001) : The Economics of the Economist-fox &#8211; Andrew M. Kamarck</title>
		<link>/revival-economics-for-the-twenty-first-century-2001-the-economics-of-the-economist-fox-andrew-m-kamarck/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/revival-economics-for-the-twenty-first-century-2001-the-economics-of-the-economist-fox-andrew-m-kamarck/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This title was first published in 2001. To be effective, economics must take into consideration the complex nature of human beings and the contextual, institutional, social and historical factors at play. This text is designed to help economists to be economic foxes by increasing the range of economists&#8217; tools, drawing on the knowledge and experience [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/revival-economics-for-the-twenty-first-century-2001-the-economics-of-the-economist-fox-andrew-m-kamarck/">Revival: Economics for the Twenty-first Century (2001) : The Economics of the Economist-fox &#8211; Andrew M. Kamarck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This title was first published in 2001. To be effective, economics must take into consideration the complex nature of human beings and the contextual, institutional, social and historical factors at play. This text is designed to help economists to be economic foxes by increasing the range of economists&#8217; tools, drawing on the knowledge and experience of other disciplines, to cope better with the extraordinary complexity of the modern economy. The objective is to provide the same kind of revelation in understanding an economy that an artist possesses in the visual arts. A beginner looking at a still life sees a green bottle, a red apple and a yellow cloth on a table top. An artist, however, can point out to him all the nuances of colour. Following a rapid dissection of the canonical hypotheses of contemporary economic theory, different sectors of the real economy are explored: the corporation; corporate governance; services; the public sector; civil society; professions; social capital; national cultures; and the tropics.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/revival-economics-for-the-twenty-first-century-2001-the-economics-of-the-economist-fox-andrew-m-kamarck/">Revival: Economics for the Twenty-first Century (2001) : The Economics of the Economist-fox &#8211; Andrew M. Kamarck</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Sign and the Seal : The Quest for the Lost Ark of the Covenant &#8211; Graham Hancock</title>
		<link>/the-sign-and-the-seal-the-quest-for-the-lost-ark-of-the-covenant-graham-hancock/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biblical Studies & Exegesis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-sign-and-the-seal-the-quest-for-the-lost-ark-of-the-covenant-graham-hancock/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The fact of the Lost Ark of the Covenant is one of the grant historical mysteries of all time. To believers, the Ark is the legendary vesel holding the stone tablets of the Ten Commandments. The Bible contains hundreds of references to the Ark&#8217;s power to level mountains, destroy armies, and lay waste to cities. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sign-and-the-seal-the-quest-for-the-lost-ark-of-the-covenant-graham-hancock/">The Sign and the Seal : The Quest for the Lost Ark of the Covenant &#8211; Graham Hancock</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The fact of the Lost Ark of the Covenant is one of the grant historical mysteries of all time. To believers, the Ark is the legendary vesel holding the stone tablets of the Ten Commandments. The Bible contains hundreds of references to the Ark&#8217;s power to level mountains, destroy armies, and lay waste to cities. The Ark itself, however, mysteriously disappears from recorded history sometime after the building of the Temple of Solomon.<br />
                     After ten years of searching through the dusty archives of Europe and the Middle East, as well as braving the real-life dangers of a bloody civil war in Ethiopia, Graham Hancock has succeeded where scores of others have failed. This intrepid journalist has tracked down the true story behind the myths and legends &#8212; revealing where the Ark is today, how it got there, and why it remains hidden.<br />
                     Part fascinating scholarship and part entertaining adventure yarn, tying together some of the most intriguing tales of all time &#8212; from the Knights Templar and Prester John to Parsival and the Holy Grail &#8212; this book will appeal to anyone fascinated by the revelation of hidden truths, the discovery of secret mysteries.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-sign-and-the-seal-the-quest-for-the-lost-ark-of-the-covenant-graham-hancock/">The Sign and the Seal : The Quest for the Lost Ark of the Covenant &#8211; Graham Hancock</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>For Small Creatures Such As We : Rituals and reflections for finding wonder &#8211; Sasha Sagan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/for-small-creatures-such-as-we-rituals-and-reflections-for-finding-wonder-sasha-sagan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanist & Secular Alternatives To Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/for-small-creatures-such-as-we-rituals-and-reflections-for-finding-wonder-sasha-sagan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sasha Sagan&#8217;s parents &#8211; the astronomer Carl Sagan and the writer and producer, Ann Druyan &#8211; taught her that the natural world and vast cosmos are full of profound beauty, and that science reveals truths more wondrous than any myth or fable. When Sagan herself became a mother, she began her own hunt for the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/for-small-creatures-such-as-we-rituals-and-reflections-for-finding-wonder-sasha-sagan-abridged/">For Small Creatures Such As We : Rituals and reflections for finding wonder &#8211; Sasha Sagan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sasha Sagan&#8217;s parents &#8211; the astronomer Carl Sagan and the writer and producer, Ann Druyan &#8211; taught her that the natural world and vast cosmos are full of profound beauty, and that science reveals truths more wondrous than any myth or fable. When Sagan herself became a mother, she began her own hunt for the phenomena behind our most treasured occasions &#8211; from births to deaths, holidays to weddings, anniversaries, and more &#8211; growing these roots into a new set of rituals for her young daughter to honour the joy and significance of each experience without relying on a religious framework.    </p>
<p>                    Part memoir, part handbook and part social history, For Small Creatures Such as We is a luminous exploration of all of Earth&#8217;s marvels that requires no faith in order to be believed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/for-small-creatures-such-as-we-rituals-and-reflections-for-finding-wonder-sasha-sagan-abridged/">For Small Creatures Such As We : Rituals and reflections for finding wonder &#8211; Sasha Sagan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Greatest Salesman in the World &#8211; Og Mandino (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-og-mandino-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Christian Testimony & Popular Inspirational Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious & Spiritual Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-og-mandino-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The runaway bestseller with more than four million copies in print! You too can change your life with the priceless wisdom of ten ancient scrolls handed down for thousands of years. &#8220;Every sales manager should read The Greatest Salesman in the World. It is a book to keep at the bedside, or on the living [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-og-mandino-abridged/">The Greatest Salesman in the World &#8211; Og Mandino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The runaway bestseller with more than four million copies in print! You too can change your life with the priceless wisdom of ten ancient scrolls handed down for thousands of years.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Every sales manager should read The Greatest Salesman in the World. It is a book to keep at the bedside, or on the living room table&#8211;a book to dip into as needed, to browse in now and then, to enjoy in small stimulating portions. It is a book for the hours and for the years, a book to turn to over and over again, as to a friend, a book of moral, spiritual and ethical guidance, an unfailing source of comfort and inspiration.&#8221;&#8211;Lester J. Bradshaw, Jr., Former Dean, Dale Carnegie Institute of Effective Speaking &#038; Human Relations     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I have read almost every book that has ever been written on salesmanship, but I think Og Mandino has captured all of them in The Greatest Salesman in the World. No one who follows these principles will ever fail as a salesman, and no one will ever be truly great without them; but, the author has done more than present the principles&#8211;he has woven them into the fabric of one of the most fascinating stories I have ever read.&#8221;&#8211;Paul J. Meyer, President of Success Motivation Institute, Inc.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I was overwhelmed by The Greatest Salesman in the World. It is, without doubt, the greatest and the most touching story I have ever read. It is so good that there are two musts that I would attach to it: First, you must not lay it down until you have finished it; and secondly, every individual who sells anything, and that includes us all, must read it.&#8221;&#8211;Robert B. Hensley, President, Life Insurance Co. of Kentucky</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-greatest-salesman-in-the-world-og-mandino-abridged/">The Greatest Salesman in the World &#8211; Og Mandino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stitches : A Handbook on Meaning, Hope, and Repair &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stitches-a-handbook-on-meaning-hope-and-repair-anne-lamott-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Institutions & Organizations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stitches-a-handbook-on-meaning-hope-and-repair-anne-lamott-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What do we do when life lurches out of balance? How can we reconnect to one another and to what&#8217;s sustaining, when evil and catastrophe seem inescapable? These questions lie at the heart of Stitches, Anne Lamott&#8217;s follow-up to her New York Times-bestselling work, Help, Thanks, Wow. In this book, she explores how we find [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stitches-a-handbook-on-meaning-hope-and-repair-anne-lamott-abridged/">Stitches : A Handbook on Meaning, Hope, and Repair &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What do we do when life lurches out of balance? How can we reconnect to one another and to what&#8217;s sustaining, when evil and catastrophe seem inescapable?    </p>
<p>                    These questions lie at the heart of Stitches, Anne Lamott&#8217;s follow-up to her New York Times-bestselling work, Help, Thanks, Wow. In this book, she explores how we find meaning and peace in these loud and frantic times; where we start again after personal and public devastation; how we recapture wholeness after loss; and how we locate our true identities in this frazzled age. We begin, Lamott says, by collecting the ripped sheets of our emotional and spiritual fabric and sewing them back together &#8211; one stitch at a time.    </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s in these stitches that the quilt of life begins, and embedded in them are strength, warmth, humour and humanity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stitches-a-handbook-on-meaning-hope-and-repair-anne-lamott-abridged/">Stitches : A Handbook on Meaning, Hope, and Repair &#8211; Anne Lamott (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Psychology of Selling : Increase Your Sales Faster and Easier Than You Ever Thought Possible &#8211; Brian Tracy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Top professional speaker and sales trainer Brian Tracy found that his most important breakthrough was the discovery that it is the &#8220;psychology of selling&#8221; that is more important than the techniques and methods of selling. Learn how to double and triple your sales in any market. It&#8217;s a promise of prosperity that sales guru Brian [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/">The Psychology of Selling : Increase Your Sales Faster and Easier Than You Ever Thought Possible &#8211; Brian Tracy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Top professional speaker and sales trainer Brian Tracy found that his most important breakthrough was the discovery that it is the &#8220;psychology of selling&#8221; that is more important than the techniques and methods of selling.    </p>
<p>                    Learn how to double and triple your sales in any market. It&#8217;s a promise of prosperity that sales guru Brian Tracy has seen fulfilled again and again.    </p>
<p>                    More salespeople have become millionaires by listening to and applying his ideas than from any other sales training process ever developed.    </p>
<p>                    In Psychology of Selling, Tracy teaches you:    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The inner game of sales and selling&#8221;<br />
                    How to eliminate the fear of rejection<br />
                    How to build unshakeable confidence    </p>
<p>                    Tracy shows how salespeople must learn to control their thoughts, feelings and actions to make themselves more effective.    </p>
<p>                    Psychology of Selling gives you a series of ideas, methods, strategies, and techniques that you can use immediately to make more sales, faster and easier than ever before.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-psychology-of-selling-increase-your-sales-faster-and-easier-than-you-ever-thought-possible-brian-tracy-abridged/">The Psychology of Selling : Increase Your Sales Faster and Easier Than You Ever Thought Possible &#8211; Brian Tracy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Ruthless Elimination of Hurry : How to stay emotionally healthy and spiritually alive in the chaos of the modern world &#8211; John Mark Comer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-ruthless-elimination-of-hurry-how-to-stay-emotionally-healthy-and-spiritually-alive-in-the-chaos-of-the-modern-world-john-mark-comer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Christian Life & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spiritualism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-ruthless-elimination-of-hurry-how-to-stay-emotionally-healthy-and-spiritually-alive-in-the-chaos-of-the-modern-world-john-mark-comer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Who are you becoming? That was the question nagging pastor and author John Mark Comer. By outward metrics, everything appeared successful. But inwardly, things weren&#8217;t pretty. So he turned to a trusted mentor for guidance and heard these words: &#8216;Ruthlessly eliminate hurry from your life. Hurry is the great enemy of the spiritual life.&#8217; It [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ruthless-elimination-of-hurry-how-to-stay-emotionally-healthy-and-spiritually-alive-in-the-chaos-of-the-modern-world-john-mark-comer-abridged/">The Ruthless Elimination of Hurry : How to stay emotionally healthy and spiritually alive in the chaos of the modern world &#8211; John Mark Comer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Who are you becoming? That was the question nagging pastor and author John Mark Comer. By outward metrics, everything appeared successful. But inwardly, things weren&#8217;t pretty. So he turned to a trusted mentor for guidance and heard these words: &#8216;Ruthlessly eliminate hurry from your life. Hurry is the great enemy of the spiritual life.&#8217; It wasn&#8217;t the response he expected, but it continues to be the answer he needs.    </p>
<p>                    Too often we treat the symptoms of toxicity in our modern world instead of trying to pinpoint the cause. A growing number of voices are pointing at hurry, or busyness as a root of much evil. Within the pages of this book, you&#8217;ll find a compelling emotional and spiritual case against hurry and in favour of a slower, simpler way of life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-ruthless-elimination-of-hurry-how-to-stay-emotionally-healthy-and-spiritually-alive-in-the-chaos-of-the-modern-world-john-mark-comer-abridged/">The Ruthless Elimination of Hurry : How to stay emotionally healthy and spiritually alive in the chaos of the modern world &#8211; John Mark Comer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Seven Spiritual Laws of Success : A Pocketbook Guide to Fulfilling Your Dreams &#8211; Deepak Chopra (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-seven-spiritual-laws-of-success-a-pocketbook-guide-to-fulfilling-your-dreams-deepak-chopra-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-seven-spiritual-laws-of-success-a-pocketbook-guide-to-fulfilling-your-dreams-deepak-chopra-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is a book you will cherish for a lifetime, for within its pages are the secrets to making all your dreams come true. Based on natural laws that govern all of creation, this book shatters the myth that success is the result of hard work, exacting plans, or driving ambition. Instead, Deepak Chopra offers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seven-spiritual-laws-of-success-a-pocketbook-guide-to-fulfilling-your-dreams-deepak-chopra-abridged/">The Seven Spiritual Laws of Success : A Pocketbook Guide to Fulfilling Your Dreams &#8211; Deepak Chopra (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is a book you will cherish for a lifetime, for within its pages are the secrets to making all your dreams come true.     </p>
<p>                    Based on natural laws that govern all of creation, this book shatters the myth that success is the result of hard work, exacting plans, or driving ambition. Instead, Deepak Chopra offers a life-altering perspective on the attainment of success: When we understand our true nature and learn to live in harmony with natural law, a sense of well-being, good health, fulfilling relationships, and material abundance spring forth easily and effortlessly.     </p>
<p>                     Filled with timeless wisdom and practical steps you can apply right away, this pocketbook edition of Chopra&#8217;s classic bestselling book makes it easy for you to read and refer to again and again. Carry it with you in your purse or your pocket, and in less than one hour, learn the seven powerful principles that can easily be applied to create success in all areas of your life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-seven-spiritual-laws-of-success-a-pocketbook-guide-to-fulfilling-your-dreams-deepak-chopra-abridged/">The Seven Spiritual Laws of Success : A Pocketbook Guide to Fulfilling Your Dreams &#8211; Deepak Chopra (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Varieties of Religious Experience : A Study in Human Nature &#8211; William James, Introduction by Martin Marty (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-varieties-of-religious-experience-a-study-in-human-nature-william-james-introduction-by-martin-marty-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Religion]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy, From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-varieties-of-religious-experience-a-study-in-human-nature-william-james-introduction-by-martin-marty-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Standing at the crossroads of psychology and religion, this catalyzing work applied the scientific method to a field abounding in abstract theory. William James believed that individual religious experiences, rather than the precepts of organized religions, were the backbone of the world&#8217;s religious life. His discussions of conversion, repentance, mysticism and saintliness, and his observations [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-varieties-of-religious-experience-a-study-in-human-nature-william-james-introduction-by-martin-marty-abridged/">The Varieties of Religious Experience : A Study in Human Nature &#8211; William James, Introduction by Martin Marty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Standing at the crossroads of psychology and religion, this catalyzing work applied the scientific method to a field abounding in abstract theory. William James believed that individual religious experiences, rather than the precepts of organized religions, were the backbone of the world&#8217;s religious life. His discussions of conversion, repentance, mysticism and saintliness, and his observations on actual, personal religious experiences &#8211; all support this thesis. In his introduction, Martin E. Marty discusses how James&#8217;s pluralistic view of religion led to his remarkable tolerance of extreme forms of religious behaviour, his challenging, highly original theories, and his welcome lack of pretension in all of his observations on the individual and the divine.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-varieties-of-religious-experience-a-study-in-human-nature-william-james-introduction-by-martin-marty-abridged/">The Varieties of Religious Experience : A Study in Human Nature &#8211; William James, Introduction by Martin Marty (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
