<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Comparative Politics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/comparative-politics/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/comparative-politics/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Comparative Politics Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/comparative-politics/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</title>
		<link>/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Taxation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Economic and other outcomes differ vastly among individuals, groups, and nations. Many explanations have been offered for the differences. Some believe that those with less fortunate outcomes are victims of genetics. Others believe that those who are less fortunate are victims of the more fortunate. Discrimination and Disparities gathers a wide array of empirical evidence [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/">Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Economic and other outcomes differ vastly among individuals, groups, and nations. Many explanations have been offered for the differences. Some believe that those with less fortunate outcomes are victims of genetics. Others believe that those who are less fortunate are victims of the more fortunate.    </p>
<p>                    Discrimination and Disparities gathers a wide array of empirical evidence to challenge the idea that different economic outcomes can be explained by any one factor, be it discrimination, exploitation, or genetics. This revised and enlarged edition also analyzes the human consequences of the prevailing social vision of these disparities and the policies based on that vision&#8211;from educational disasters to widespread crime and violence.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discrimination-and-disparities-thomas-sowell/">Discrimination and Disparities &#8211; Thomas Sowell</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Two Nations Indivisible : Mexico, the United States, and the Road Ahead &#8211; Shannon K. O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/two-nations-indivisible-mexico-the-united-states-and-the-road-ahead-shannon-k-oneil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diplomacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/two-nations-indivisible-mexico-the-united-states-and-the-road-ahead-shannon-k-oneil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Overlooked in today&#8217;s bloody headlines is Mexico&#8217;s fundamental transformation. In over three short decades it has gone from a poor to a middle class nation, a closed to an open economy, an authoritarian to a vibrant (if at times messy) democracy, and a local to an increasingly binational society. But while things are much better [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/two-nations-indivisible-mexico-the-united-states-and-the-road-ahead-shannon-k-oneil-abridged/">Two Nations Indivisible : Mexico, the United States, and the Road Ahead &#8211; Shannon K. O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Overlooked in today&#8217;s bloody headlines is Mexico&#8217;s fundamental transformation. In over three short decades it has gone from a poor to a middle class nation, a closed to an open economy, an authoritarian to a vibrant (if at times messy) democracy, and a local to an increasingly binational society. But while things are much better than portrayed, Mexico does face a true security challenge. It stands at a crossroads. It can follow a path toward a top ten economy, an<br />
                    open democracy, and a leading world voice, or one that spirals down into drug-fueled corruption and violence. Today&#8217;s choices will define not only Mexico&#8217;s future, but also that of the United States. Perhaps no other nation is as indelibly intertwined with our economy, society, and daily lives. What<br />
                    happens in Mexico will affect the United States for decades to come.    </p>
<p>                    Two Nations Indivisible tells the story of the making of modern Mexico, and what it means for the United States. Recounting the economic, political, social, and security changes of the last thirty years, it provides a roadmap for the greatest overlooked foreign policy challenge of our time -relations with our southern neighbor. For the good of both countries, it argues against walling the United States off from its neighbor; and instead for investing finally in a true<br />
                    partnership.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/two-nations-indivisible-mexico-the-united-states-and-the-road-ahead-shannon-k-oneil-abridged/">Two Nations Indivisible : Mexico, the United States, and the Road Ahead &#8211; Shannon K. O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Political Order and Political Decay : From the Industrial Revolution to the Globalisation of Democracy &#8211; Francis Fukuyama (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/political-order-and-political-decay-from-the-industrial-revolution-to-the-globalisation-of-democracy-francis-fukuyama-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/political-order-and-political-decay-from-the-industrial-revolution-to-the-globalisation-of-democracy-francis-fukuyama-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Origins of Political Order, Francis Fukuyama took us from the dawn of mankind to the French and American Revolutions. Here, he picks up the thread again in the second instalment of his definitive account of mankind&#8217;s emergence as a political animal. This is the story of how state, law and democracy developed after [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/political-order-and-political-decay-from-the-industrial-revolution-to-the-globalisation-of-democracy-francis-fukuyama-abridged/">Political Order and Political Decay : From the Industrial Revolution to the Globalisation of Democracy &#8211; Francis Fukuyama (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Origins of Political Order, Francis Fukuyama took us from the dawn of mankind to the French and American Revolutions.  Here, he picks up the thread again in the second instalment of his definitive account of mankind&#8217;s emergence as a political animal.    </p>
<p>                    This is the story of how state, law and democracy developed after these cataclysmic events, how the modern landscape &#8211; with its uneasy tension between dictatorships and liberal democracies &#8211; evolved and how in the United States and in other developed democracies, unmistakable signs of decay have emerged.     </p>
<p>                    If we want to understand the political systems that dominate and order our lives, we must first address their origins &#8211; in our own recent past as well as in the earliest systems of human government. Fukuyama argues that the key to successful government can be reduced to three key elements: a strong state, the rule of law and institutions of democratic accountability.    </p>
<p>                    This magisterial account is required reading for anyone wishing to know more about mankind&#8217;s greatest achievements.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/political-order-and-political-decay-from-the-industrial-revolution-to-the-globalisation-of-democracy-francis-fukuyama-abridged/">Political Order and Political Decay : From the Industrial Revolution to the Globalisation of Democracy &#8211; Francis Fukuyama (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bully Pulpit : Theodore Roosevelt, William Howard Taft, and the Golden Age of Journalism &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-bully-pulpit-theodore-roosevelt-william-howard-taft-and-the-golden-age-of-journalism-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-bully-pulpit-theodore-roosevelt-william-howard-taft-and-the-golden-age-of-journalism-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the Best Books of the Year as chosen by The New York Times, The Washington Post, The Economist, Time, USA TODAY, Christian Science Monitor, and more. &#8220;A tale so gripping that one questions the need for fiction when real life is so plump with drama and intrigue&#8221; (Associated Press). Doris Kearns Goodwin&#8217;s The [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bully-pulpit-theodore-roosevelt-william-howard-taft-and-the-golden-age-of-journalism-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/">The Bully Pulpit : Theodore Roosevelt, William Howard Taft, and the Golden Age of Journalism &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the Best Books of the Year as chosen by The New York Times, The Washington Post, The Economist, Time, USA TODAY, Christian Science Monitor, and more. &#8220;A tale so gripping that one questions the need for fiction when real life is so plump with drama and intrigue&#8221; (Associated Press).     </p>
<p>                    Doris Kearns Goodwin&#8217;s The Bully Pulpit is a dynamic history of the first decade of the Progressive era, that tumultuous time when the nation was coming unseamed and reform was in the air.     </p>
<p>                    The story is told through the intense friendship of Theodore Roosevelt and William Howard Taft&#8211;a close relationship that strengthens both men before it ruptures in 1912, when they engage in a brutal fight for the presidential nomination that divides their wives, their children, and their closest friends, while crippling the progressive wing of the Republican Party, causing Democrat Woodrow Wilson to be elected, and changing the country&#8217;s history.     </p>
<p>                    The Bully Pulpit is also the story of the muckraking press, which arouses the spirit of reform that helps Roosevelt push the government to shed its laissez-faire attitude toward robber barons, corrupt politicians, and corporate exploiters of our natural resources. The muckrakers are portrayed through the greatest group of journalists ever assembled at one magazine&#8211;Ida Tarbell, Ray Stannard Baker, Lincoln Steffens, and William Allen White&#8211;teamed under the mercurial genius of publisher S.S. McClure.     </p>
<p>                    Goodwin&#8217;s narrative is founded upon a wealth of primary materials. The correspondence of more than four hundred letters between Roosevelt and Taft begins in their early thirties and ends only months before Roosevelt&#8217;s death. Edith Roosevelt and Nellie Taft kept diaries. The muckrakers wrote hundreds of letters to one another, kept journals, and wrote their memoirs. The letters of Captain Archie Butt, who served as a personal aide to both Roosevelt and Taft, provide an intimate view of both men.     </p>
<p>                    The Bully Pulpit, like Goodwin&#8217;s brilliant chronicles of the Civil War and World War II, exquisitely demonstrates her distinctive ability to combine scholarly rigor with accessibility. It is a major work of history&#8211;an examination of leadership in a rare moment of activism and reform that brought the country closer to its founding ideals.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-bully-pulpit-theodore-roosevelt-william-howard-taft-and-the-golden-age-of-journalism-doris-kearns-goodwin-abridged/">The Bully Pulpit : Theodore Roosevelt, William Howard Taft, and the Golden Age of Journalism &#8211; Doris Kearns Goodwin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fantasyland : How America Went Haywire: A 500-Year History &#8211; Kurt Andersen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re entitled to your own opinion but not your own facts Fantasy is the USA&#8217;s primary product. From the Pilgrim Fathers onward America has been a place where renegades and freaks came in search of freedom to create their own realities with little objectively regulated truth standing in their way. The freedom to invent and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/">Fantasyland : How America Went Haywire: A 500-Year History &#8211; Kurt Andersen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re entitled to your own opinion but not your own facts    </p>
<p>                    Fantasy is the USA&#8217;s primary product. From the Pilgrim Fathers onward America has been a place where renegades and freaks came in search of freedom to create their own realities with little objectively regulated truth standing in their way. The freedom to invent and believe whatever the hell you like is, in some ways, an unwritten constitutional right. But, this do-your-own-thing freedom also is the driving credo of America&#8217;s current transformation where the difference between opinion and fact is rapidly crumbling.     </p>
<p>                    So how did we get to this weird pseudo-reality, where science and objective facts are dismissed in favour of opinions and wild speculation, or indeed, fantasies? The post truth, fake news, free-for-all mentality isn&#8217;t exactly a new phenomenon. If you want to understand Trump&#8217;s America, how the lines between reality and illusion have become dangerously blurred, you have to go back to the very beginning and take a dizzying road trip across five centuries of crackpot delusion and make-believe from Salem to Scientology.    </p>
<p>                    Fantasyland is a journey that connects the dots between crazed franchises of true believers &#8211; a rich freak show tapestry from Mormons to Flat-Earthers and satanic panic, new age quacks to anti-vaxxers, conspiracy theorists of every stripe, creationists to climate change deniers, UFO-obsessives to gun-toting libertarians, showmen hucksters from P T Barnum to Trump himself, all topped off with a dangerous dose of anti-government paranoia and pseudoscience. Along the way, New York Times bestselling author Kurt Andersen has created a unique and raucous history of America and a new paradigm for understanding our post-factual world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/">Fantasyland : How America Went Haywire: A 500-Year History &#8211; Kurt Andersen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the 2018 Waterstones Book of the Year Winner at the 2018 Parliamentary Book Awards Longlisted for the Orwell Prize, 2019 ____________ &#8220;A really good book&#8230; Well-structured and well-written.&#8221; Observer &#8220;Well written and incisive.&#8221; The Times &#8220;Vital and compelling.&#8221; New Statesman In an era when politicians are responsible for the Brexit logjam and embroiled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/">Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the 2018 Waterstones Book of the Year<br />
                    Winner at the 2018 Parliamentary Book Awards<br />
                    Longlisted for the Orwell Prize, 2019<br />
                    ____________    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A really good book&#8230;  Well-structured and well-written.&#8221; Observer<br />
                    &#8220;Well written and incisive.&#8221; The Times<br />
                    &#8220;Vital and compelling.&#8221; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    In an era when politicians are responsible for the Brexit logjam and embroiled in sexual-harassment and expenses scandals, it&#8217;s no wonder we&#8217;ve lost our faith in government. Every year, they introduce new legislation that doesn&#8217;t do what it sets out to achieve &#8211; often with terrible financial and human costs. But, with some notable exceptions, they are decent, hard-working people, doing a hugely difficult and demanding job. In this searching examination of our political class, award-winning journalist Isabel Hardman investigates the strange and demanding world of Westminster, and asks why we end up with representatives we no longer trust &#8211; and how might faith be restored.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-we-get-the-wrong-politicians-isabel-hardman-abridged/">Why We Get the Wrong Politicians &#8211; Isabel Hardman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The American Presidency: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Charles O. Jones (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-american-presidency-a-very-short-introduction-charles-o-jones-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-american-presidency-a-very-short-introduction-charles-o-jones-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The American founding fathers were dedicated to the project of creating a government both functional and incapable of devolving into tyranny. To do this, they intentionally decentralized decision making among the legislative, executive, and judiciary branches. They believed this separation of powers would force compromise and achieve their goal of &#8220;separating to unify.&#8221; In the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-american-presidency-a-very-short-introduction-charles-o-jones-abridged/">The American Presidency: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Charles O. Jones (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The American founding fathers were dedicated to the project of creating a government both functional and incapable of devolving into tyranny. To do this, they intentionally decentralized decision making among the legislative, executive, and judiciary branches. They believed this separation of powers would force compromise and achieve their goal of &#8220;separating to unify.&#8221; In the second edition of this Very Short Introduction, Charles O. Jones delves into the<br />
                    constitutional roots of the American presidency to show how presidents faced the challenges of governing within a system of separation of powers.    </p>
<p>                    This updated edition of The American Presidency reviews crucial themes, including democratization of presidential elections, transitioning into and organizing a presidency, challenges in leading the permanent government, making law and policy, and reforming and changing the institution. It also introduces new case studies from the Obama administration, providing compelling insights into contemporary critical issues such as military power, the role of the First Lady, and the new trends<br />
                    in electoral campaigning-including the stunning advances in mass media and campaign technology.    </p>
<p>                    Jones lucidly shows that American presidents are not, and simply cannot be, as powerful as most Americans believe them to be. Accordingly, he stresses the necessity to acknowledge the president&#8217;s political status and style within the constitutional structure: the president is not the presidency, and the presidency is not the government.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-american-presidency-a-very-short-introduction-charles-o-jones-abridged/">The American Presidency: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Charles O. Jones (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the bestselling tradition of The World Is Flat and The Next 100 Years comes a contrarian and eye-opening assessment of American power. In THE ACCIDENTAL SUPERPOWER, international strategist Peter Zeihan examines how the hard rules of geography are eroding the American commitment to free trade; how much of the planet is aging into a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/">The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the bestselling tradition of The World Is Flat and The Next 100 Years comes a contrarian and eye-opening assessment of American power.    </p>
<p>                    In THE ACCIDENTAL SUPERPOWER, international strategist Peter Zeihan examines how the hard rules of geography are eroding the American commitment to free trade; how much of the planet is aging into a mass retirement that will enervate capital supplies; and how it is the ever-ravenous American economy that is rapidly approaching energy independence. Combined, these factors are overturning the global system and ushering in a new (dis)order. For most, that is a disaster-in-waiting, but not for the Americans. The shale revolution allows Americans to sidestep a dangerous energy market. Only the U.S. boasts a youth population large enough to escape the sucking maw of global aging. Geography will matter more than ever in a de-globalizing world, and America&#8217;s geography is simply sublime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-accidental-superpower-the-next-generation-of-american-preeminence-and-the-coming-global-disaster-peter-zeihan-abridged/">The Accidental Superpower : The Next Generation of American Preeminence and the Coming Global Disaster &#8211; Peter Zeihan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
