<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Environmentalist Thought &amp; Ideology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/environmentalist-thought-ideology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/environmentalist-thought-ideology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Environmentalist Thought &amp; Ideology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/environmentalist-thought-ideology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consumerism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How does our economic system impact the way we live? Does it really affect what we truly care about? Oxford economist E. F. Schumacher provides an enlightening study of our economic system and its purpose, challenging the current state of excessive consumption in our society. Offering a crucial message for the modern world struggling to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/">Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How does our economic system impact the way we live? Does it really affect what we truly care about?     </p>
<p>                    Oxford economist E. F. Schumacher provides an enlightening study of our economic system and its purpose, challenging the current state of excessive consumption in our society. Offering a crucial message for the modern world struggling to balance economic growth with the human costs of globalisation, Small Is Beautiful puts forward the revolutionary yet viable case for building our economies around the needs of communities, not corporations.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the 100 most influential books published since World War II&#8217; The Times Literary Supplement</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/">Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Feral : Rewilding the Land, Sea and Human Life &#8211; George Monbiot (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/feral-rewilding-the-land-sea-and-human-life-george-monbiot-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of The Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of Wildlife & Habitats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/feral-rewilding-the-land-sea-and-human-life-george-monbiot-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Captivating. Will change the way you think about the natural world, and your place in it&#8217; Hugh Fearnley-Whittingstall In Feral, George Monbiot, one of the world&#8217;s most celebrated radical thinkers offers a riveting tale of possibility and travel in the wild How many of us sometimes feel that we are scratching at the walls of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feral-rewilding-the-land-sea-and-human-life-george-monbiot-abridged/">Feral : Rewilding the Land, Sea and Human Life &#8211; George Monbiot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Captivating. Will change the way you think about the natural world, and your place in it&#8217;  Hugh Fearnley-Whittingstall    </p>
<p>                    In Feral,  George Monbiot, one of the world&#8217;s most celebrated radical thinkers  offers a riveting tale of possibility and travel in the wild    </p>
<p>                    How  many of us sometimes feel that we are scratching at the walls of this  life, seeking to find our way into a wider space beyond? That our mild,  polite existence sometimes seems to crush the breath out of us? Feral  is the lyrical and gripping story of George Monbiot&#8217;s efforts to  re-engage with nature and discover a new way of living. He shows how, by  restoring and rewilding our damaged ecosystems on land and at sea, we  can bring wonder back into our lives. Making use of some remarkable  scientific discoveries, Feral lays out a new, positive environmentalism, in which nature is allowed to find its own way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/feral-rewilding-the-land-sea-and-human-life-george-monbiot-abridged/">Feral : Rewilding the Land, Sea and Human Life &#8211; George Monbiot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Braiding Sweetgrass : Indigenous Wisdom, Scientific Knowledge and the Teachings of Plants &#8211; Robin Wall Kimmerer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/braiding-sweetgrass-indigenous-wisdom-scientific-knowledge-and-the-teachings-of-plants-robin-wall-kimmerer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Ecology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Botany & Plant Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural History Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Trees, Wildflowers & Plants]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/braiding-sweetgrass-indigenous-wisdom-scientific-knowledge-and-the-teachings-of-plants-robin-wall-kimmerer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A hymn of love to the world &#8230; A journey that is every bit as mythic as it is scientific, as sacred as it is historical, as clever as it is wise&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert, author of Eat, Pray, Love As a botanist, Robin Wall Kimmerer has been trained to ask questions of nature with the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/braiding-sweetgrass-indigenous-wisdom-scientific-knowledge-and-the-teachings-of-plants-robin-wall-kimmerer-abridged/">Braiding Sweetgrass : Indigenous Wisdom, Scientific Knowledge and the Teachings of Plants &#8211; Robin Wall Kimmerer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A hymn of love to the world &#8230; A journey that is every bit as mythic as it is scientific, as sacred as  it is historical, as clever as it is wise&#8217; Elizabeth Gilbert, author of Eat, Pray, Love    </p>
<p>                    As a botanist, Robin Wall Kimmerer has been trained to ask questions of nature with the tools of science. As a member of the Citizen Potawatomi Nation, she embraces the notion that plants and animals are our oldest teachers. In Braiding Sweetgrass, Kimmerer brings these two ways of knowledge together.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on her life as an indigenous scientist, a mother, and a woman, Kimmerer shows how other living beings &#8211; asters and goldenrod, strawberries and squash, salamanders, algae, and sweetgrass &#8211; offer us gifts and lessons, even if we&#8217;ve forgotten how to hear their voices. In a rich braid of reflections that range from the creation of Turtle Island to the forces that threaten its flourishing today, she circles toward a central argument: that the awakening of a wider ecological consciousness requires the acknowledgment and celebration of our reciprocal relationship with the rest of the living world. For only when we can hear the languages of other beings will we be capable of understanding the generosity of the earth, and learn to give our own gifts in return.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/braiding-sweetgrass-indigenous-wisdom-scientific-knowledge-and-the-teachings-of-plants-robin-wall-kimmerer-abridged/">Braiding Sweetgrass : Indigenous Wisdom, Scientific Knowledge and the Teachings of Plants &#8211; Robin Wall Kimmerer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Global Warming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER The creator of the Gaia hypothesis and the greatest environmental thinker of our time has produced an astounding new theory about the future of life on Earth. James Lovelock argues that the anthropocene &#8211; the age in which humans acquired planetary-scale technologies &#8211; is, after three centuries, coming to an end. A [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/">Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    The creator of the Gaia hypothesis and the greatest environmental thinker of our time has produced an astounding new theory about the future of life on Earth. James Lovelock argues that the anthropocene &#8211; the age in which humans acquired planetary-scale technologies &#8211; is, after three centuries, coming to an end. A new age &#8211; the novacene &#8211; has already begun.    </p>
<p>                    New beings will emerge from existing artificial intelligence systems. They will think 10,000 times faster than we do and will regard us as we now regard plants. The cruel, violent machine takeover imagined by sci-fi writers will not happen: these hyper-intelligent beings will be as dependent on the health of the planet as we are. They will need the planetary cooling system of Gaia to defend from the increasing heat of the sun. Gaia depends on organic life. We will be partners in this project. It is crucial, Lovelock argues, that the intelligence of Earth survives and prospers. We are at present the only beings capable of understanding the cosmos, but he speculates that the novacene could be the beginning of a process that will see intelligence suffusing the entire cosmos. At the age 100, Lovelock has produced the most compelling work of his life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/novacene-the-coming-age-of-hyperintelligence-james-lovelock-abridged/">Novacene : The Coming Age of Hyperintelligence &#8211; James Lovelock (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
