<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hoaxes &amp; Deceptions Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/hoaxes-deceptions/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/hoaxes-deceptions/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Hoaxes &amp; Deceptions Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/hoaxes-deceptions/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Billion Dollar Whale : the bestselling investigation into the financial fraud of the century &#8211; Tom Wright, Bradley Hope (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hoaxes & Deceptions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A BOOK OF THE YEAR FOR THE FINANCIAL TIMES AND FORTUNE MAGAZINE. The epic story of how a young social climber from Malaysia pulled off one of the biggest financial heists in history. In 2015, rumours began circulating that billions of dollars had been stolen from a Malaysian investment fund. The mastermind of the heist [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/">Billion Dollar Whale : the bestselling investigation into the financial fraud of the century &#8211; Tom Wright, Bradley Hope (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A BOOK OF THE YEAR FOR THE FINANCIAL TIMES AND FORTUNE MAGAZINE.    </p>
<p>                    The epic story of how a young social climber from Malaysia pulled off one of the biggest financial heists in history.    </p>
<p>                    In 2015, rumours began circulating that billions of dollars had been stolen from a Malaysian investment fund. The mastermind of the heist was twenty-seven-year-old Jho Low, a serial fabulist from an upper-middle-class Malaysian family, who had carefully built his reputation as a member of the jet-setting elite by arranging and financing elaborate parties for Wall Street bankers, celebrities, and even royalty.    </p>
<p>                    With the aid of Goldman Sachs and others, Low stole billions of dollars, right under the nose of global financial industry watchdogs. He used the money to finance elections, purchase luxury real estate, throw champagne-drenched parties, and bankroll Hollywood films like The Wolf of Wall Street.     </p>
<p>                    Billion Dollar Whale reveals how this silver-tongued con man, a &#8216;modern Gatsby&#8217;, emerged from obscurity to pull off one of the most audacious financial heists the world has ever seen, and how the financial industry let him. It is a classic harrowing parable of hubris and greed in the financial world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/">Billion Dollar Whale : the bestselling investigation into the financial fraud of the century &#8211; Tom Wright, Bradley Hope (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bunk : The Rise of Hoaxes, Humbug, Plagiarists, Phonies, Post-Facts &#8211; Kevin Young (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bunk-the-rise-of-hoaxes-humbug-plagiarists-phonies-post-facts-kevin-young-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hoaxes & Deceptions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bunk-the-rise-of-hoaxes-humbug-plagiarists-phonies-post-facts-kevin-young-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the National Book Award for Nonfiction &#8220;There Kevin Young goes again, giving us books we greatly need, cleverly disguised as books we merely want. Unexpectedly essential.&#8221;&#8211;Marlon James Award-winning poet and critic Kevin Young tours us through a rogue&#8217;s gallery of hoaxers, plagiarists, forgers, and fakers&#8211;from the humbug of P. T. Barnum and Edgar [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bunk-the-rise-of-hoaxes-humbug-plagiarists-phonies-post-facts-kevin-young-abridged/">Bunk : The Rise of Hoaxes, Humbug, Plagiarists, Phonies, Post-Facts &#8211; Kevin Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the National Book Award for Nonfiction    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;There Kevin Young goes again, giving us books we greatly need, cleverly disguised as books we merely want. Unexpectedly essential.&#8221;&#8211;Marlon James     </p>
<p>                    Award-winning poet and critic Kevin Young tours us through a rogue&#8217;s gallery of hoaxers, plagiarists, forgers, and fakers&#8211;from the humbug of P. T. Barnum and Edgar Allan Poe to the unrepentant bunk of JT LeRoy and Donald J. Trump. Bunk traces the history of the hoax as a peculiarly American phenomenon, examining what motivates hucksters and makes the rest of us so gullible. Disturbingly, Young finds that fakery is woven from stereotype and suspicion, race being the most insidious American hoax of all. He chronicles how Barnum came to fame by displaying figures like Joice Heth, a black woman whom he pretended was the 161-year-old nursemaid to George Washington, and What Is It?, an African American man Barnum professed was a newly discovered missing link in evolution.    </p>
<p>                    Bunk then turns to the hoaxing of history and the ways that forgers, plagiarists, and journalistic fakers invent backstories and falsehoods to sell us lies about themselves and about the world in our own time, from pretend Native Americans Grey Owl and Nasdijj to the deadly imposture of Clark Rockefeller, from the made-up memoirs of James Frey to the identity theft of Rachel Dolezal. In this brilliant and timely work, Young asks what it means to live in a post-factual world of &#8220;truthiness&#8221; where everything is up for interpretation and everyone is subject to a pervasive cynicism that damages our ideas of reality, fact, and art.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bunk-the-rise-of-hoaxes-humbug-plagiarists-phonies-post-facts-kevin-young-abridged/">Bunk : The Rise of Hoaxes, Humbug, Plagiarists, Phonies, Post-Facts &#8211; Kevin Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
