<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Fascism &amp; Nazism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/fascism-nazism/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/fascism-nazism/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Fascism &amp; Nazism Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/fascism-nazism/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>A Long Petal of the Sea : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Isabel Allende</title>
		<link>/a-long-petal-of-the-sea-the-sunday-times-bestseller-isabel-allende/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sagas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spanish Civil War]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Fiction]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-long-petal-of-the-sea-the-sunday-times-bestseller-isabel-allende/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller &#8216;One of the strongest and most affecting works in Allende&#8217;s long career&#8217; New York Times Book Review &#8216;A defiantly warm and funny novel, by somebody who has earned the right to argue that love and optimism can survive whatever history might throw at us&#8217; Daily Telegraph September 3, 1939, the day [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-long-petal-of-the-sea-the-sunday-times-bestseller-isabel-allende/">A Long Petal of the Sea : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Isabel Allende</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller</p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the strongest and most affecting works in Allende&#8217;s long career&#8217; New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A defiantly warm and funny novel, by somebody who has earned the right to argue that love and optimism can survive whatever history might throw at us&#8217; Daily Telegraph</p>
<p>                    September 3, 1939, the day of the Spanish exiles&#8217; splendid arrival in Chile, the Second World War broke out in Europe.</p>
<p>                    Victor Dalmau is a young doctor when he is caught up in the Spanish Civil War, a tragedy that leaves his life &#8211; and the fate of his country &#8211; forever changed. Together with his sister-in-law, the pianist Roser, he is forced out of his beloved Barcelona and into exile. </p>
<p>                    When opportunity to seek refuge arises, they board a ship chartered by the poet Pablo Neruda to Chile, the promised &#8216;long petal of sea and wine and snow&#8217;. There, they find themselves enmeshed in a rich web of characters who come together in love and tragedy over the course of four generations, destined to witness the battle between freedom and repression as it plays out across the world.</p>
<p>                    A masterful work of historical fiction that soars from the Spanish Civil War to the rise and fall of Pinochet, A Long Petal of the Sea is Isabel Allende at the height of her powers.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An epic that starts in 1939 and spans decades and continents . . . A masterful work of historical fiction about hope, exile and belonging, and one that sheds light on the way we live now&#8217; Independent.co.uk</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Full of ambition and humanity&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Allende knows that all stories are love stories, and the greatest love stories are told by time&#8217; Colum McCann</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Allende&#8217;s style is impressively Olympian and the payoff is remarkable&#8217; Guardian</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Epic in scope, yet intimate in execution&#8217; i</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-long-petal-of-the-sea-the-sunday-times-bestseller-isabel-allende/">A Long Petal of the Sea : The Sunday Times Bestseller &#8211; Isabel Allende</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Born Survivors : The incredible true story of three pregnant mothers and their courage and determination to survive in the concentration camps &#8211; Wendy Holden</title>
		<link>/born-survivors-the-incredible-true-story-of-three-pregnant-mothers-and-their-courage-and-determination-to-survive-in-the-concentration-camps-wendy-holden/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Holocaust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/born-survivors-the-incredible-true-story-of-three-pregnant-mothers-and-their-courage-and-determination-to-survive-in-the-concentration-camps-wendy-holden/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller now updated with a new foreword Among millions of Holocaust victims sent to Auschwitz II-Birkenau in 1944, Priska, Rachel, and Anka each passed through its infamous gates with a secret. Strangers to each other, they were newly pregnant, and facing an uncertain fate without their husbands. Alone, scared, and with so [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/born-survivors-the-incredible-true-story-of-three-pregnant-mothers-and-their-courage-and-determination-to-survive-in-the-concentration-camps-wendy-holden/">Born Survivors : The incredible true story of three pregnant mothers and their courage and determination to survive in the concentration camps &#8211; Wendy Holden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times bestseller now updated with a new foreword</p>
<p>                    Among millions of Holocaust victims sent to Auschwitz II-Birkenau in 1944, Priska, Rachel, and Anka each passed through its infamous gates with a secret. Strangers to each other, they were newly pregnant, and facing an uncertain fate without their husbands. Alone, scared, and with so many loved ones already lost to the Nazis, these young women were privately determined to hold on to all they had left: their lives, and those of their unborn babies.</p>
<p>                    That the gas chambers ran out of Zyklon-B just after the babies were born, before they and their mothers could be exterminated, is just one of several miracles that allowed them all to survive and rebuild their lives after World War II. Born Survivors follows the mothers&#8217; incredible journey &#8211; first to Auschwitz, where they each came under the murderous scrutiny of Dr. Josef Mengele; then to a German slave labour camp where, half-starved and almost worked to death, they struggled to conceal their condition; and finally, as the Allies closed in, their hellish 17-day train journey with thousands of other prisoners to the Mauthausen death camp in Austria. Hundreds died along the way but the courage and kindness of strangers, including guards and civilians, helped save these women and their children.</p>
<p>                    Sixty-five years later, the three &#8216;miracle babies&#8217; met for the first time at Mauthausen for the anniversary of the liberation that ultimately saved them. United by their remarkable experiences of survival against all odds, they now consider each other &#8220;siblings of the heart.&#8221; In Born Survivors, Wendy Holden brings all three stories together for the first time to mark their seventieth birthdays and the seventieth anniversary of the ending of the war.</p>
<p>                    A heart-stopping account of how three mothers and their newborns fought to survive the Holocaust, Born Survivors is also a life-affirming celebration of our capacity to care and to love amid inconceivable cruelty.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/born-survivors-the-incredible-true-story-of-three-pregnant-mothers-and-their-courage-and-determination-to-survive-in-the-concentration-camps-wendy-holden/">Born Survivors : The incredible true story of three pregnant mothers and their courage and determination to survive in the concentration camps &#8211; Wendy Holden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>On Tyranny : Twenty Lessons from the Twentieth Century &#8211; Timothy Snyder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/on-tyranny-twenty-lessons-from-the-twentieth-century-timothy-snyder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/on-tyranny-twenty-lessons-from-the-twentieth-century-timothy-snyder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** &#8216;A sort of survival book, a sort of symptom-diagnosis manual in terms of losing your democracy and what tyranny and authoritarianism look like up close&#8217; Rachel Maddow &#8216;These 128 pages are a brief primer in every important thing we might have learned from the history of the last century, and all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-tyranny-twenty-lessons-from-the-twentieth-century-timothy-snyder-abridged/">On Tyranny : Twenty Lessons from the Twentieth Century &#8211; Timothy Snyder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A sort of survival book, a sort of symptom-diagnosis manual in terms of losing your democracy and what tyranny and authoritarianism look like up close&#8217; Rachel Maddow    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;These 128 pages are a brief primer in every important thing we might have learned from the history of the last century, and all that we appear to have forgotten&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                     History does not repeat, but it does instruct.    </p>
<p>                     In the twentieth century, European democracies collapsed into fascism, Nazism and communism. These were movements in which a leader or a party claimed to give voice to the people, promised to protect them from global existential threats, and rejected reason in favour of myth. European history shows us that societies can break, democracies can fall, ethics can collapse, and ordinary people can find themselves in unimaginable circumstances.    </p>
<p>                     History can familiarise, and it can warn. Today, we are no wiser than the Europeans who saw democracy yield to totalitarianism in the twentieth century. But when the political order seems imperilled, our advantage is that we can learn from their experience to resist the advance of tyranny.    </p>
<p>                     Now is a good time to do so.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/on-tyranny-twenty-lessons-from-the-twentieth-century-timothy-snyder-abridged/">On Tyranny : Twenty Lessons from the Twentieth Century &#8211; Timothy Snyder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Parties]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Totalitarianism & Dictatorship]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Of course, everything [D&#8217;Souza] says here is accurate&#8230; But it&#8217;s not going to sit well with people on the American left who, of course, are portraying themselves as the exact opposite of all of this. &#8211;RUSH LIMBAUGH The explosive new book from Dinesh D&#8217;Souza, author of the #1 New York Times bestsellers Hillary&#8217;s America, America, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/">The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Of course, everything [D&#8217;Souza] says here is accurate&#8230; But it&#8217;s not going to sit well with people on the American left who, of course, are portraying themselves as the exact opposite of all of this. &#8211;RUSH LIMBAUGH     </p>
<p>                    The explosive new book from Dinesh D&#8217;Souza, author of the #1 New York Times bestsellers Hillary&#8217;s America, America, and Obama&#8217;s America.      </p>
<p>                     What is the big lie of the Democratic Party? That conservatives&#8211;and President Donald Trump in particular&#8211;are fascists. Nazis, even. In a typical comment, MSNBC host Rachel Maddow says the Trump era is reminiscent of what it was like when Hitler first became chancellor.     </p>
<p>                     But in fact, this audacious lie is a complete inversion of the truth. Yes, there is a fascist threat in America&#8211;but that threat is from the Left and the Democratic Party. The Democratic left has an ideology virtually identical with fascism and routinely borrows tactics of intimidation and political terror from the Nazi Brownshirts.     </p>
<p>                     To cover up their insidious fascist agenda, Democrats loudly accuse President Trump and other Republicans of being Nazis&#8211;an obvious lie, considering the GOP has been fighting the Democrats over slavery, genocide, racism and fascism from the beginning.     </p>
<p>                     Now, finally, Dinesh D&#8217;Souza explodes the Left&#8217;s big lie. He expertly exonerates President Trump and his supporters, then uncovers the Democratic Left&#8217;s long, cozy relationship with Nazism: how the racist and genocidal acts of early Democrats inspired Adolf Hitler&#8217;s campaign of death; how fascist philosophers influenced the great 20th century lions of the American Left; and how today&#8217;s anti-free speech, anti-capitalist, anti-religious liberty, pro-violence Democratic Party is a frightening simulacrum of the Nazi Party.     </p>
<p>                     Hitler coined the term the big lie to describe a lie that the great masses of the people will fall for precisely because of how bold and monstrous the lie is. In The Big Lie, D&#8217;Souza shows that the Democratic Left&#8217;s orchestrated campaign to paint President Trump and conservatives as Nazis to cover up its own fascism is, in fact, the biggest lie of all.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-lie-exposing-the-nazi-roots-of-the-american-left-dinesh-dsouza-abridged/">The Big Lie : Exposing the Nazi Roots of the American Left &#8211; Dinesh D&#8217;Souza (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future is History : How Totalitarianism Reclaimed Russia &#8211; Masha Gessen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-future-is-history-how-totalitarianism-reclaimed-russia-masha-gessen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-future-is-history-how-totalitarianism-reclaimed-russia-masha-gessen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Future is History Masha Gessen follows the lives of four Russians, born as the Soviet Union crumbled, at what promised to be the dawn of democracy. Each came of age with unprecedented expectations, some as the children or grandchildren of the very architects of the new Russia, each with newfound aspirations of their [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-is-history-how-totalitarianism-reclaimed-russia-masha-gessen-abridged/">The Future is History : How Totalitarianism Reclaimed Russia &#8211; Masha Gessen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Future is History Masha Gessen follows the lives of four Russians, born as the Soviet Union crumbled, at what promised to be the dawn of democracy. Each came of age with unprecedented expectations, some as the children or grandchildren of the very architects of the new Russia, each with newfound aspirations of their own &#8211; as entrepreneurs, activists, thinkers and writers, sexual and social beings. Gessen charts their paths not only against the machinations of the regime that would seek to crush them all (censorship, intimidation, violence) but also against the war it waged on understanding itself, ensuring the unobstructed emergence of the old Soviet order in the form of today&#8217;s terrifying and seemingly unstoppable mafia state. The Future is History is a powerful and urgent cautionary tale by contemporary Russia&#8217;s most fearless inquisitor.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-is-history-how-totalitarianism-reclaimed-russia-masha-gessen-abridged/">The Future is History : How Totalitarianism Reclaimed Russia &#8211; Masha Gessen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations & Safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Burnham has real intellectual courage, and writes about real issues.&#8217; &#8211; George Orwell Burnham&#8217;s claim was that capitalism was dead, but that it was being replaced not by socialism, but a new economic system he called &#8220;managerialism&#8221;; rule by managers. Written in 1941, this is the book that theorised how the world was moving into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/">The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Burnham has real intellectual courage, and writes about real issues.&#8217; &#8211; George Orwell    </p>
<p>                    Burnham&#8217;s claim was that capitalism was dead, but that it was being replaced not by socialism, but a new economic system he called &#8220;managerialism&#8221;; rule by managers.    </p>
<p>                    Written in 1941, this is the book that theorised how the world was moving into the hands of the &#8216;managers&#8217;. Burnham explains how Capitalism had virtually lost its control, and would be displaced not by labour, nor by socialism, but by the rule of administartors in business and in government.    </p>
<p>                    This revolution, he posited, is as broad as the world and as comprehensive as human society, asking &#8220;Why is &#8216;totalitarianism&#8217; not the issue?&#8221; &#8220;Can civilization be destroyed?&#8221; And &#8220;Why is the New Deal something bigger than Roosevelt can handle?&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    In a volume extraordinary for its dispassionate handling of those and other fundamental questions, James Burnham explores fully the implications of the managerial revolution.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/">The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
