<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Rock &amp; Pop Music Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/rock-pop-music/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/rock-pop-music/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Rock &amp; Pop Music Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/rock-pop-music/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Kiss and Make-Up &#8211; Gene Simmons</title>
		<link>/kiss-and-make-up-gene-simmons/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Heavy Metal Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/kiss-and-make-up-gene-simmons/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>KISS has released thirty-seven records and sold 80 million albums worldwide. Gene Simmons has also acted in films and on television, has written and produced albums for other recording artists, has managed the recording career of, among others, Liza Minelli, and was founder and president of his own recording label, Simmons Records/RCA. He also launched [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/kiss-and-make-up-gene-simmons/">Kiss and Make-Up &#8211; Gene Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>KISS has released thirty-seven records and sold 80 million albums worldwide. Gene Simmons has also acted in films and on television, has written and produced albums for other recording artists, has managed the recording career of, among others, Liza Minelli, and was founder and president of his own recording label, Simmons Records/RCA. He also launched his film and TV producing career with Detroit Rock City for New Line Cinema. Gene Simmons lives in Beverley Hills, California, and was recently the rock star teacher on Channel 4&#8217;s Rock School.    </p>
<p>                    Here for the first time Gene Simmons, the notorious mainman of the explosive rock and roll group KISS, tells his story. Delivered in Gene&#8217;s own honest, outrageous and uncensored voice, he tells of his early beginnings in Israel, of his arrival in New York at the age of eight, his first taste of 1950s pop culture and his developing thirst for fame, fun and girls. Undoubtedly one of the most infamous rock and roll legends alive, Gene tells the never before revealed story of KISS&#8217;s reign as the biggest and most popular band in the world. Finally, the real story of the man behind the make-up.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/kiss-and-make-up-gene-simmons/">Kiss and Make-Up &#8211; Gene Simmons</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John</title>
		<link>/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                    &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                    In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is Me &#8211; the joyously funny, honest and moving story of the most enduringly successful singer/songwriter of all time.<br />
                    ______________</p>
<p>                    Christened Reginald Dwight, he was a shy boy with Buddy Holly glasses who grew up in the London suburb of Pinner and dreamed of becoming a pop star.  By the age of twenty-three, he was performing his first gig in America, facing an astonished audience in his bright yellow dungarees, a star-spangled T-shirt and boots with wings. Elton John had arrived and the music world would never be the same again.</p>
<p>                    His life has been full of drama, from the early rejection of his work with songwriting partner Bernie Taupin to spinning out of control as a chart-topping superstar; from half-heartedly trying to drown himself in his LA swimming pool to disco-dancing with the Queen; from friendships with John Lennon, Freddie Mercury and George Michael to setting up his AIDS Foundation. All the while, Elton was hiding a drug addiction that would grip him for over a decade.</p>
<p>                    In Me Elton also writes powerfully about getting clean and changing his life, about finding love with David Furnish and becoming a father.   In a voice that is warm, humble and open, this is Elton on his music and his relationships, his passions and his mistakes.  This is a story that will stay with you, by a living legend.<br />
                    ______________</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Self-deprecating, funny . . . You cannot help but enjoy his company throughout, temper tantrums and all&#8217; The Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Racy, pacy and crammed with scurrilous anecdotes &#8211; what more could you ask from the rocket man&#8217; Guardian (Book of the Week)</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Chatty, gossipy, amusing and at times brutally candid&#8217; Telegraph</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Face the Music : A Life Exposed &#8211; Paul Stanley</title>
		<link>/face-the-music-a-life-exposed-paul-stanley/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/face-the-music-a-life-exposed-paul-stanley/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES and INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER In Face the Music, Paul Stanley-the co-founder and famous &#8220;Starchild&#8221; frontman of KISS-reveals for the first time the incredible highs and equally incredible lows in his life both inside and outside the band. Face the Music is the shocking, funny, smart, inspirational story of one of rock&#8217;s most enduring [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/face-the-music-a-life-exposed-paul-stanley/">Face the Music : A Life Exposed &#8211; Paul Stanley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES and INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER  In Face the Music, Paul Stanley-the co-founder and famous &#8220;Starchild&#8221; frontman of KISS-reveals for the first time the incredible highs and equally incredible lows in his life both inside and outside the band. Face the Music is the shocking, funny, smart, inspirational story of one of rock&#8217;s most enduring icons and the group he helped create, define, and immortalize.  Stanley mixes compelling personal revelations and gripping, gritty war stories that will surprise even the most steadfast member of the KISS Army. He takes us back to his childhood in the 1950s and &#8217;60s, a traumatic time made more painful thanks to a physical deformity. Born with a condition called microtia, he grew up partially deaf, with only one ear. But this instilled in him an inner drive to succeed in the most unlikely of pursuits: music.  With never-before-seen photos and images throughout, Stanley&#8217;s memoir is a fully realized and unflinching portrait of a rock star, a chronicle of the stories behind the famous anthems, the many brawls and betrayals, and all the drama and pyrotechnics on and off the stage.<br />
                    Raw and confessional, Stanley offers candid insights into his personal relationships, and the turbulent dynamics with his bandmates over the past four decades. And no one comes out unscathed-including Stanley himself.  &#8220;People say I was brave to write such a revealing book, but I wrote it because I needed to personally reflect on my own life. I know everyone will see themselves somewhere in this book, and where my story might take them is why I&#8217;m sharing it.&#8221; -Paul Stanley    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/face-the-music-a-life-exposed-paul-stanley/">Face the Music : A Life Exposed &#8211; Paul Stanley</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Let Love Rule &#8211; Lenny Kravitz</title>
		<link>/let-love-rule-lenny-kravitz/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/let-love-rule-lenny-kravitz/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I see my story as a suite of songs that have a magical connection. I never understood that connection until I sat down to write. It was then that the magic started to flow.&#8217; Let Love Rule is a work of deep reflection. Lenny Kravitz looks back at his life with candor, self-scrutiny, and humour. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-love-rule-lenny-kravitz/">Let Love Rule &#8211; Lenny Kravitz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I see my story as a suite of songs that have a magical connection. I never understood that connection until I sat down to write. It was then that the magic started to flow.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    Let Love Rule is a work of deep reflection. Lenny Kravitz looks back at his life with candor, self-scrutiny, and humour. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;My life is all about opposites,&#8217; he writes. &#8216;Black and white. Jewish and Christian. The Jackson 5 and Led Zeppelin. I accepted my Gemini soul. I owned it. I adored it. Yins and yangs mingled in various parts of my heart and mind, giving me balance and fueling my curiosity and comfort.&#8217;</p>
<p>                    Let Love Rule covers a vast canvas stretching from Manhattan&#8217;s Upper East Side, Brooklyn&#8217;s Bedford-Stuyvesant, Los Angeles&#8217;s Baldwin Hills, Beverly Hills, and finally to France, England and Germany. It&#8217;s the story of a wildly creative kid who, despite tough struggles at school and extreme tension at home, finds salvation in music. We see him grow as a musician and ultimately a master songwriter, producer, and performer. </p>
<p>                    We also see Lenny&#8217;s spiritual growth-and the powerful way in which spirit informs his music. The cast of characters surrounding Lenny is extraordinary: his father, Sy, a high-powered news executive; his mother, Roxie Roker, a television star; and Lisa Bonet, the young actress who becomes his muse.</p>
<p>                    The central character, of course, is Lenny, who, despite his great aspirational energy, turns down record deal after record deal until he finds his true voice.The creation of that voice, the same voice that is able to declare &#8216;Let Love Rule&#8217; to an international audience, is the very heart of this story.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Whether recording, performing, or writing a book,&#8217; says Lenny, &#8216;my art is about listening to the inspiration inside and then sharing it with people. Art must bring the world closer together.&#8217;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/let-love-rule-lenny-kravitz/">Let Love Rule &#8211; Lenny Kravitz</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>More Myself : A Journey &#8211; Alicia Keys</title>
		<link>/more-myself-a-journey-alicia-keys/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/more-myself-a-journey-alicia-keys/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In her intimate memoir, More Myself, Alicia Keys shares her quest for truth: about herself, her past, and her shift from sacrificing her spirit to celebrating her worth. One of the most celebrated musicians of our time, Alicia Keys has enraptured the nation with her heartfelt lyrics, extraordinary vocal range, and soul-stirring piano compositions. Yet [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/more-myself-a-journey-alicia-keys/">More Myself : A Journey &#8211; Alicia Keys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In her intimate memoir, More Myself, Alicia Keys shares her quest for truth: about herself, her past, and her shift from sacrificing her spirit to celebrating her worth.</p>
<p>                    One of the most celebrated musicians of our time, Alicia Keys has enraptured the nation with her heartfelt lyrics, extraordinary vocal range, and soul-stirring piano compositions. Yet away from the spotlight, Alicia has grappled with private heartache over the challenging and complex relationship with her father, the people-pleasing nature that characterized her early career, the loss of privacy surrounding her romantic relationships, and the oppressive expectations of female perfection.</p>
<p>                    Since her rise to fame, Alicia&#8217;s public persona has belied a deep personal truth: she has spent years not fully recognizing or honoring her own worth. After withholding parts of herself for so long, she is at last exploring the questions that live at the heart of her story: Who am I, really? And once I discover that truth, how can I become brave enough to embrace it?</p>
<p>                    More Myself is part autobiography, part narrative documentary. Alicia&#8217;s journey is revealed not only through her own candid recounting, but also through vivid recollections from those who have walked alongside her. The result is a 360-degree perspective on Alicia&#8217;s path: from her girlhood in Hell&#8217;s Kitchen and Harlem, to the process of self-discovery she&#8217;s still navigating.</p>
<p>                    With the raw honesty that epitomizes Alicia&#8217;s artistry, More Myself is at once a riveting account and a clarion call to readers: to define themselves in a world that rarely encourages a true and unique identity.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/more-myself-a-journey-alicia-keys/">More Myself : A Journey &#8211; Alicia Keys</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trips : Rock Life in the Sixties &#8211; Augmented Edition &#8211; Ellen Sander, Read by Dina Pearlman</title>
		<link>/trips-rock-life-in-the-sixties-augmented-edition-ellen-sander-read-by-dina-pearlman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music Reviews & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Music & Musicology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trips-rock-life-in-the-sixties-augmented-edition-ellen-sander-read-by-dina-pearlman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Simply one of the best pieces of rock reportage ever written.&#8221; (Los Angeles Review of Books) As a pioneering rock journalist for Hit Parader, Vogue, Saturday Review, and other publications, Ellen Sander had a backstage pass to the hottest music scenes of the 1960s. In this feast of juicy anecdotes and keen social commentary, she [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trips-rock-life-in-the-sixties-augmented-edition-ellen-sander-read-by-dina-pearlman/">Trips : Rock Life in the Sixties &#8211; Augmented Edition &#8211; Ellen Sander, Read by Dina Pearlman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Simply one of the best pieces of rock reportage ever written.&#8221; (Los Angeles Review of Books)    </p>
<p>                    As a pioneering rock journalist for Hit Parader, Vogue, Saturday Review, and other publications, Ellen Sander had a backstage pass to the hottest music scenes of the 1960s. In this feast of juicy anecdotes and keen social commentary, she draws upon her professional and personal experiences to chronicle pop culture&#8217;s highs and lows during the turbulent decade. Join her for weird and wild road trips with companions ranging from Yippies to the members of Led Zeppelin. Stops along the way include the folk-music clubs of Greenwich Village, Haight-Ashbury in its riotous heyday, and the euphoric festivals at Monterey and Woodstock.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;It is a memoir, a sourcebook, and a love letter,&#8221; Sander writes, &#8220;a recollection of a time, parenthesized by ambivalence and apathy, a search for the ultimate high, a generation with an irrepressible vision, its art, artists, its audience, and the substance of its statement.&#8221; This expanded edition of Trips adds &#8220;The Plaster Casters of Chicago&#8221;, Sander&#8217;s seminal piece on groupie culture, the lengthy &#8220;Concerts and Conversations&#8221;, as well as a new preface and chapter postscripts.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trips-rock-life-in-the-sixties-augmented-edition-ellen-sander-read-by-dina-pearlman/">Trips : Rock Life in the Sixties &#8211; Augmented Edition &#8211; Ellen Sander, Read by Dina Pearlman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Individual Composers & Musicians, Specific Bands & Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john-abridged/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The rock memoir of the decade&#8217; Daily Mail    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The rock star&#8217;s gloriously entertaining and candid memoir is a gift to the reader&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    In his first and only official autobiography, music icon Elton John reveals the truth about his extraordinary life, which is also the subject of the smash-hit film Rocketman. The result is Me &#8211; the joyously funny, honest and moving story of the most enduringly successful singer/songwriter of all time.<br />
                    ______________    </p>
<p>                    Christened Reginald Dwight, he was a shy boy with Buddy Holly glasses who grew up in the London suburb of Pinner and dreamed of becoming a pop star.  By the age of twenty-three, he was performing his first gig in America, facing an astonished audience in his bright yellow dungarees, a star-spangled T-shirt and boots with wings. Elton John had arrived and the music world would never be the same again.    </p>
<p>                    His life has been full of drama, from the early rejection of his work with songwriting partner Bernie Taupin to spinning out of control as a chart-topping superstar; from half-heartedly trying to drown himself in his LA swimming pool to disco-dancing with the Queen; from friendships with John Lennon, Freddie Mercury and George Michael to setting up his AIDS Foundation. All the while, Elton was hiding a drug addiction that would grip him for over a decade.    </p>
<p>                    In Me Elton also writes powerfully about getting clean and changing his life, about finding love with David Furnish and becoming a father.   In a voice that is warm, humble and open, this is Elton on his music and his relationships, his passions and his mistakes.  This is a story that will stay with you, by a living legend.<br />
                    ______________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Self-deprecating, funny . . . You cannot help but enjoy his company throughout, temper tantrums and all&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Racy, pacy and crammed with scurrilous anecdotes &#8211; what more could you ask from the rocket man&#8217; Guardian (Book of the Week)    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Chatty, gossipy, amusing and at times brutally candid&#8217; Telegraph</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/me-elton-john-official-autobiography-elton-john-abridged/">Me : Elton John Official Autobiography &#8211; Elton John (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>No One Gets out of Here Alive &#8211; Jerry Hopkins</title>
		<link>/no-one-gets-out-of-here-alive-jerry-hopkins/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rock & Pop Music]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/no-one-gets-out-of-here-alive-jerry-hopkins/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is Jim Morrison in all his complexity-singer, philosopher, poet, delinquent-the brilliant, charismatic, and obsessed seeker who rejected authority in any form, the explorer who probed the bounds of reality to see what would happen&#8230; Seven years in the writing, this definitive biography is the work of two men whose empathy and experience with Jim [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-one-gets-out-of-here-alive-jerry-hopkins/">No One Gets out of Here Alive &#8211; Jerry Hopkins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here is Jim Morrison in all his complexity-singer, philosopher, poet, delinquent-the brilliant, charismatic, and obsessed seeker who rejected authority in any form, the explorer who probed the bounds of reality to see what would happen&#8230; Seven years in the writing, this definitive biography is the work of two men whose empathy and experience with Jim Morrison uniquely prepared them to recount this modern tragedy: Jerry Hopkins, whose famous Presley biography, Elvis, was inspired by Morrison&#8217;s suggestion, and Danny Sugerman, confidant of and aide to the Doors. With an afterword by Michael McClure.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/no-one-gets-out-of-here-alive-jerry-hopkins/">No One Gets out of Here Alive &#8211; Jerry Hopkins</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
