<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>True Crime Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/true-crime-books/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/true-crime-books/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>True Crime Books Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/true-crime-books/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The House of Kennedy &#8211; James Patterson</title>
		<link>/the-house-of-kennedy-james-patterson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-house-of-kennedy-james-patterson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Now with an all-new bonus chapter&#8211;in the bestselling The House of Kennedy, &#8220;James Patterson applies his writerly skills to real-life history . . . re-telling the political clan&#8217;s rise and fall and rise again (and fall again) with novelistic style&#8221; (People). The Kennedys have always been a family of charismatic adventurers, raised to take risks [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-house-of-kennedy-james-patterson/">The House of Kennedy &#8211; James Patterson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Now with an all-new bonus chapter&#8211;in the bestselling The House of Kennedy, &#8220;James Patterson applies his writerly skills to real-life history . . . re-telling the political clan&#8217;s rise and fall and rise again (and fall again) with novelistic style&#8221; (People).      </p>
<p>                    The Kennedys have always been a family of charismatic adventurers, raised to take risks and excel, living by the dual family mottos: &#8220;To whom much is given, much is expected&#8221; and &#8220;Win at all costs.&#8221; And they do&#8211;but at a price.     </p>
<p>                    Across decades and generations, the Kennedys have occupied a unique place in the American imagination: charmed, cursed, at once familiar and unknowable. The House of Kennedy is a revealing, fascinating account of America&#8217;s most storied family, as told by America&#8217;s most trusted storyteller.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-house-of-kennedy-james-patterson/">The House of Kennedy &#8211; James Patterson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sleepers &#8211; Lorenzo Carcaterra</title>
		<link>/sleepers-lorenzo-carcaterra/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Endurance & Survival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Stories Of Heroism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sleepers-lorenzo-carcaterra/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An unforgettable true story of friendship, loyalty and revenge, set against the unmistakable backdrop of New York City They were four boys who shared everything &#8211; the laughter and bruises of an impoverished upbringing in New York&#8217;s West Side. Then one of their pranks misfired &#8211; a man nearly died and they were sent away [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sleepers-lorenzo-carcaterra/">Sleepers &#8211; Lorenzo Carcaterra</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An unforgettable true story of friendship, loyalty and revenge, set against the unmistakable backdrop of New York City</p>
<p>                    They  were four boys who shared everything &#8211; the laughter and bruises of an  impoverished upbringing in New York&#8217;s West Side. Then one of their  pranks misfired &#8211; a man nearly died and they were sent away to a  reformatory school. There they suffered the worst abuse the guards could  inflict on them. They were forever scarred by their experiences. Eleven  years later two of them became killers for the mob. They met the  ringleader of the guards who abused them &#8211; and shot him dead in front of  several witnesses. No one thought they would see the outside of a  prison again &#8211; but the four friends banded together once more and in one  last, audacious stand brought their own vengeance to the courtroom.</p>
<p>                    Sleepers was  adapted into an award-winning film, featuring Hollywood stars Dustin  Hoffman, Brad Pitt, Robert de Niro and Kevin Bacon. A moving and  shocking coming-of-age story that is a must read for fans of the cult  film, Stand by Me.</p>
<p>                    Lorenzo Carcaterra was born in New York where he still lives. He was a reporter on the New York Daily News before he wrote A Safe Place. His second book, Sleepers, became a bestseller on both sides of the Atlantic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sleepers-lorenzo-carcaterra/">Sleepers &#8211; Lorenzo Carcaterra</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow</title>
		<link>/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a dramatic account of violence and espionage, Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter Ronan Farrow exposes serial abusers and a cabal of powerful interests hell-bent on covering up the truth, at any cost. In 2017, a routine network television investigation led Ronan Farrow to a story only whispered about: one of Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful producers was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow/">Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a dramatic account of violence and espionage, Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter Ronan Farrow exposes serial abusers and a cabal of powerful interests hell-bent on covering up the truth, at any cost.</p>
<p>                    In 2017, a routine network television investigation led Ronan Farrow to a story only whispered about: one of Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful producers was a predator, protected by fear, wealth, and a conspiracy of silence. As Farrow drew closer to the truth, shadowy operatives, from high-priced lawyers to elite war-hardened spies, mounted a secret campaign of intimidation, threatening his career, following his every move and weaponizing an account of abuse in his own family. </p>
<p>                    All the while, Farrow and his producer faced a degree of resistance that could not be explained &#8211; until now. And a trail of clues revealed corruption and cover-ups from Hollywood, to Washington, and beyond. </p>
<p>                    This is the untold story of the exotic tactics of surveillance and intimidation deployed by wealthy and connected men to threaten journalists, evade accountability and silence victims of abuse &#8211; and it&#8217;s the story of the women who risked everything to expose the truth and spark a global movement.</p>
<p>                    Both a spy thriller and a meticulous work of investigative journalism, Catch and Kill breaks devastating new stories about the rampant abuse of power &#8211; and sheds far-reaching light on investigations that shook the culture.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow/">Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden</title>
		<link>/permanent-record-edward-snowden/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Privacy & Data Protection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/permanent-record-edward-snowden/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER Edward Snowden, the man who risked everything to expose the US government&#8217;s system of mass surveillance, reveals for the first time the story of his life, including how he helped to build that system and what motivated him to try to bring it down. In 2013, twenty-nine-year-old Edward Snowden [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/permanent-record-edward-snowden/">Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    Edward Snowden, the man who risked everything to expose the US government&#8217;s system of mass surveillance, reveals for the first time the story of his life, including how he helped to build that system and what motivated him to try to bring it down.</p>
<p>                    In 2013, twenty-nine-year-old Edward Snowden shocked the world when he broke with the American intelligence establishment and revealed that the United States government was secretly pursuing the means to collect every single phone call, text message, and email. The result would be an unprecedented system of mass surveillance with the ability to pry into the private lives of every person on earth. Six years later, Snowden reveals for the very first time how he helped to build this system and why he was moved to expose it.</p>
<p>                    Spanning the bucolic Beltway suburbs of his childhood and the clandestine CIA and NSA postings of his adulthood, Permanent Record is the extraordinary account of a bright young man who grew up online &#8211; a man who became a spy, a whistleblower, and, in exile, the Internet&#8217;s conscience. Written with wit, grace, passion, and an unflinching candor, Permanent Record is a crucial memoir of our digital age and destined to be a classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/permanent-record-edward-snowden/">Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Innocent Man : Murder and Injustice in a Small Town &#8211; John Grisham</title>
		<link>/the-innocent-man-murder-and-injustice-in-a-small-town-john-grisham/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Law & Procedure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Penology & Punishment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Police & Security Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-innocent-man-murder-and-injustice-in-a-small-town-john-grisham/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the town of Ada, Oklahoma, Ron Williamson was going to be the next Mickey Mantle. But on his way to the Big Leagues, Ron stumbled, his dreams broken by drinking, drugs, and women. Then, on a winter night in 1982, not far from Ron&#8217;s home, a young cocktail waitress named Debra Sue Carter was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innocent-man-murder-and-injustice-in-a-small-town-john-grisham/">The Innocent Man : Murder and Injustice in a Small Town &#8211; John Grisham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the town of Ada, Oklahoma, Ron Williamson was going to be the next Mickey Mantle. But on his way to the Big Leagues, Ron stumbled, his dreams broken by drinking, drugs, and women. Then, on a winter night in 1982, not far from Ron&#8217;s home, a young cocktail waitress named Debra Sue Carter was savagely murdered. The investigation led nowhere. Until, on the flimsiest evidence, it led to Ron Williamson. The washed-up small-town hero was charged, tried, and sentenced to death&#8211;in a trial littered with lying witnesses and tainted evidence that would shatter a man&#8217;s already broken life&#8230;and let a true killer go free. Impeccably researched, grippingly told, filled with eleventh-hour drama, John Grisham&#8217;s first work of nonfiction reads like a page-turning legal thriller. It is a book that will terrify anyone who believes in the presumption of innocence&#8211;a book no American can afford to miss.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-innocent-man-murder-and-injustice-in-a-small-town-john-grisham/">The Innocent Man : Murder and Injustice in a Small Town &#8211; John Grisham</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Amityville Horror &#8211; Jay Anson</title>
		<link>/the-amityville-horror-jay-anson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ghosts & Poltergeists]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Parapsychological Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Satanism & Demonology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Unexplained Phenomena / The Paranormal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-amityville-horror-jay-anson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A fascinating and frightening book&#8221; (Los Angeles Times)&#8211;the bestselling true story about a house possessed by evil spirits, haunted by psychic phenomena almost too terrible to describe. In December 1975, the Lutz family moved into their new home on suburban Long Island. George and Kathleen Lutz knew that, one year earlier, Ronald DeFeo had murdered [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-amityville-horror-jay-anson/">The Amityville Horror &#8211; Jay Anson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A fascinating and frightening book&#8221; (Los Angeles Times)&#8211;the bestselling true story about a house possessed by evil spirits, haunted by psychic phenomena almost too terrible to describe.     </p>
<p>                    In December 1975, the Lutz family moved into their new home on suburban Long Island. George and Kathleen Lutz knew that, one year earlier, Ronald DeFeo had murdered his parents, brothers, and sisters in the house, but the property&#8211;complete with boathouse and swimming pool&#8211;and the price had been too good to pass up.     </p>
<p>                    Twenty-eight days later, the entire Lutz family fled in terror.     </p>
<p>                    This is the spellbinding, shocking true story that gripped the nation about an American dream that turned into a nightmare beyond imagining&#8211;&#8220;this book will scare the hell out of you&#8221; (Kansas City Star).    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-amityville-horror-jay-anson/">The Amityville Horror &#8211; Jay Anson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Soldier Spy &#8211; Tom Marcus</title>
		<link>/soldier-spy-tom-marcus/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/soldier-spy-tom-marcus/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The explosive, shocking and honest account from an MI5 officer, revealing never-before-seen detail into MI5&#8217;s operation &#8216;I do it because it is all I know. I&#8217;m a hunter of people and I&#8217;m damn good at it.&#8217; Recruited after the 7/7 attacks on London, Tom quickly found himself immersed in the tense world of watching, following [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/soldier-spy-tom-marcus/">Soldier Spy &#8211; Tom Marcus</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The explosive, shocking and honest account from an MI5 officer, revealing never-before-seen detail into MI5&#8217;s operation</p>
<p>                     &#8216;I do it because it is all I know. I&#8217;m a hunter of people and I&#8217;m damn good at it.&#8217;</p>
<p>                     Recruited after the 7/7 attacks on London, Tom quickly found himself immersed in the tense world of watching, following and infiltrating networks of terrorists, spies and foreign agents.</p>
<p>                     It was a job that took over his life and cost him dear, taking him to the limit of physical and mental endurance.</p>
<p>                     Filled with extraordinary accounts of operations that saved countless lives, Soldier Spy is the only authentic account by an ex-MI5 officer of the round-the-clock battle to keep this country safe.<br />
                     ________</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Very well written, gives a startling amount of operational detail, the biggest shock of all &#8211; MI5 agreed to its publication&#8217; Sunday Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;A blistering, visceral insight into life on the front line against terror, revealed in remarkable detail&#8217; Daily Telegraph</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Startling, absolutely fascinating. A footsoldier&#8217;s account out on the street.&#8217; Radio 4</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Gripping. One of the most successful MI5 undercover surveillance officers of his time&#8217; Sun</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/soldier-spy-tom-marcus/">Soldier Spy &#8211; Tom Marcus</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Family Next Door : The Heartbreaking Imprisonment of the Thirteen Turpin Siblings and Their Extraordinary Rescue &#8211; John Glatt</title>
		<link>/the-family-next-door-the-heartbreaking-imprisonment-of-the-thirteen-turpin-siblings-and-their-extraordinary-rescue-john-glatt/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Personal Problems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-family-next-door-the-heartbreaking-imprisonment-of-the-thirteen-turpin-siblings-and-their-extraordinary-rescue-john-glatt/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times bestselling true crime author John Glatt comes the devastating story of the Turpins: a seemingly normal family whose dark secrets would shock and captivate the world. On January 14, 2018, a seventeen-year-old girl climbed out of the window of her Perris, California home and dialed 911 on a borrowed cell phone. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-family-next-door-the-heartbreaking-imprisonment-of-the-thirteen-turpin-siblings-and-their-extraordinary-rescue-john-glatt/">The Family Next Door : The Heartbreaking Imprisonment of the Thirteen Turpin Siblings and Their Extraordinary Rescue &#8211; John Glatt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From New York Times bestselling true crime author John Glatt comes the devastating story of the Turpins: a seemingly normal family whose dark secrets would shock and captivate the world.  </p>
<p>                    On January 14, 2018, a seventeen-year-old girl climbed out of the window of her Perris, California home and dialed 911 on a borrowed cell phone. Struggling to stay calm, she told the operator that she and her 12 siblings&#8211;ranging in age from 2 to 29&#8211;were being abused by their parents. When the dispatcher asked for her address, the girl hesitated. &#8220;I&#8217;ve never been out,&#8221; she stammered. </p>
<p>                    To their family, neighbors, and online friends, Louise and David Turpin presented a picture of domestic bliss: dressing their thirteen children in matching outfits and buying them expensive gifts. But what police discovered when they entered the Turpin family home would eclipse the most shocking child abuse cases in history. For years, David and Louise had kept their children in increasing isolation, trapping them in a sinister world of torture, fear, and near starvation. </p>
<p>                    In the first major account of the case, investigative journalist John Glatt delves into the disturbing details and recounts the bravery of the thirteen siblings in the face of unimaginable horror.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-family-next-door-the-heartbreaking-imprisonment-of-the-thirteen-turpin-siblings-and-their-extraordinary-rescue-john-glatt/">The Family Next Door : The Heartbreaking Imprisonment of the Thirteen Turpin Siblings and Their Extraordinary Rescue &#8211; John Glatt</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Sacrifices : A True Story of Passion And Murder &#8211; Ann Rule</title>
		<link>/small-sacrifices-a-true-story-of-passion-and-murder-ann-rule/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/small-sacrifices-a-true-story-of-passion-and-murder-ann-rule/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the #1 New York Times bestselling author of The Stranger Beside Me comes a shocking true crime account of the destructive forces that drove a beautiful young mother to shoot her three young children in cold blood. &#8220;Somebody just shot my kids!&#8221; Diane Downs brought her car to a halt in front of a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-sacrifices-a-true-story-of-passion-and-murder-ann-rule/">Small Sacrifices : A True Story of Passion And Murder &#8211; Ann Rule</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the #1 New York Times bestselling author of The Stranger Beside Me comes a shocking true crime account of the destructive forces that drove a beautiful young mother to shoot her three young children in cold blood. &#8220;Somebody just shot my kids!&#8221; Diane Downs brought her car to a halt in front of a Springfield, Oregon, hospital, her three gravely wounded children beside her. Thus begins the tale of a truly unthinkable crime that shattered the tranquility of a tight-knit community. As police searched for the &#8220;shaggy-haired stranger&#8221; Diane accused of shooting 8-year-old Christie, 7-year-old Cheryl, and 3-year-old Danny, a suspicion grew that was even more horrifying than the crime itself: Did Diane shoot her own children? Haunted by this question, a dedicated district attorney searched for the answer and uncovered a chronology of incest, psychological wounding, desperate affairs, and surrogate motherhood. Ann Rule&#8217;s gripping, powerful, and ultimately terrifying true story of passion and murder will hold you in thrall as it plumbs the unimagined depths of darkness concealed within a human being.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-sacrifices-a-true-story-of-passion-and-murder-ann-rule/">Small Sacrifices : A True Story of Passion And Murder &#8211; Ann Rule</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret Barrister : Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken &#8211; The Secret Barrister</title>
		<link>/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Law & Procedure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Ethics & Professional Conduct]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times number one bestseller. Winner of the Books are My Bag Non-Fiction Award. Shortlisted for Waterstones Book of the Year. Shortlisted for Specsavers Non-Fiction Book of the Year. You may not wish to think about it, but one day you or someone you love will almost certainly appear in a criminal courtroom. You [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister/">The Secret Barrister : Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken &#8211; The Secret Barrister</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times number one bestseller.<br />
                    Winner of the Books are My Bag Non-Fiction Award.<br />
                    Shortlisted for Waterstones Book of the Year.<br />
                    Shortlisted for Specsavers Non-Fiction Book of the Year.</p>
<p>                    You may not wish to think about it, but one day you or someone you love will almost certainly appear in a criminal courtroom. You might be a juror, a victim, a witness or &#8211; perhaps through no fault of your own &#8211; a defendant. Whatever your role, you&#8217;d expect a fair trial.</p>
<p>                      I&#8217;m a barrister. I work in the criminal justice system, and every day I see how fairness is not guaranteed. Too often the system fails those it is meant to protect. The innocent are wronged and the guilty allowed to walk free.</p>
<p>                    In The Secret Barrister: Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken I want to share some stories from my daily life to show you how the system is broken, who broke it and why we should start caring before it&#8217;s too late.</p>
<p>                    A Sunday Times top ten bestseller for twenty-four weeks.<br />
                    &#8216;Eye-opening, funny and horrifying&#8217; &#8211; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Everyone who has any interest in public life should read it&#8217; &#8211; Daily Mail</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister/">The Secret Barrister : Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken &#8211; The Secret Barrister</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Future Crimes : Inside The Digital Underground and the Battle For Our Connected World &#8211; Marc Goodman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/future-crimes-inside-the-digital-underground-and-the-battle-for-our-connected-world-marc-goodman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/future-crimes-inside-the-digital-underground-and-the-battle-for-our-connected-world-marc-goodman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER * * Future-proof yourself and your business by reading this book * Technological advances have benefited our world in immeasurable ways, but there is an ominous flipside. Criminals are often the earliest, and most innovative, adopters of technology and modern times have led to modern crimes. Today&#8217;s criminals are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/future-crimes-inside-the-digital-underground-and-the-battle-for-our-connected-world-marc-goodman-abridged/">Future Crimes : Inside The Digital Underground and the Battle For Our Connected World &#8211; Marc Goodman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER *    </p>
<p>                    * Future-proof yourself and your business by reading this book *     </p>
<p>                    Technological advances have benefited our world in immeasurable ways, but there is an ominous flipside. Criminals are often the earliest, and most innovative, adopters of technology and modern times have led to modern crimes. Today&#8217;s criminals are stealing identities, draining online bank-accounts and wiping out computer servers.  It&#8217;s disturbingly easy to activate baby cam monitors to spy on families, pacemakers can be hacked to deliver a lethal jolt, and thieves are analyzing your social media in order to determine the best time for a home invasion.    </p>
<p>                    Meanwhile, 3D printers produce AK-47s, terrorists can download the recipe for the Ebola virus, and drug cartels are building drones. This is just the beginning of the tsunami of technological threats coming our way.  In Future Crimes, Marc Goodman rips open his database of hundreds of real cases to give us front-row access to these impending perils. Reading like a sci-fi thriller, but based in startling fact, Goodman raises tough questions about the expanding role of technology in our lives. Future Crimes is a call to action for better security measures worldwide, but most importantly, will empower readers to protect themselves against these looming technological threats &#8211; before it&#8217;s too late.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/future-crimes-inside-the-digital-underground-and-the-battle-for-our-connected-world-marc-goodman-abridged/">Future Crimes : Inside The Digital Underground and the Battle For Our Connected World &#8211; Marc Goodman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black Edge : Inside Information, Dirty Money, and the Quest to Bring Down the Most Wanted Man on Wall Street &#8211; Sheelah Kolhatkar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Investment & Securities]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Nominated for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year Nominated for the Carnegie Medal for Excellence in Nonfiction Amazon Top 5 Business Books of 2017 &#8216;A prodigious feat of reporting&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell &#8216;Black Edge has the grip of a thriller &#8230; Everyone should read this book&#8217; &#8211; David Grann, New York Times bestselling author [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/">Black Edge : Inside Information, Dirty Money, and the Quest to Bring Down the Most Wanted Man on Wall Street &#8211; Sheelah Kolhatkar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nominated for the FT/McKinsey Business Book of the Year<br />
                    Nominated for the Carnegie Medal for Excellence in Nonfiction<br />
                    Amazon Top 5 Business Books of 2017    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A prodigious feat of reporting&#8217; &#8211; Malcolm Gladwell    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Black Edge has the grip of a thriller &#8230; Everyone should read this book&#8217; &#8211; David Grann, New York Times bestselling author of THE LOST CITY OF Z     </p>
<p>                    How do super-rich bankers get away with it?    </p>
<p>                    There is a powerful new class of billionaire financiers in the world, who use their phenomenal wealth to write their own rules and laws.  Chief among them is Steven Cohen, a Wall Street legend, and the basis for Damian Lewis&#8217;s character in BILLIONS, who built his hedge fund into a $15 billion empire on the basis of wizard-like stock trading, and who flies to work by helicopter and owns one of the largest private art collections in the world.  But his iconic status was shattered when his fund became the target of a sprawling FBI investigation into insider trading, charged with using illegal inside information &#8211; or &#8216;black edge&#8217; &#8211; to beat the market.  His firm, SAC Capital, was ultimately indicted and pled guilty to charges of securities and wire fraud, and paid record criminal and civil fines of nearly $2 billion.  But even as the company bearing his name pled guilty, Cohen himself was never charged, and is free to start trading publicly again from January 2018.    </p>
<p>                    Black Edge offers a revelatory look at the grey zone in which so much of Wall Street functions, and a window into the transformation of the worldwide economy. With meticulous reporting and powerful storytelling, this is a riveting, true-life legal thriller that takes readers inside the US government&#8217;s pursuit of Cohen and his employees, and raises urgent questions about the power and wealth of those who sit at the pinnacle of the financial world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/black-edge-inside-information-dirty-money-and-the-quest-to-bring-down-the-most-wanted-man-on-wall-street-sheelah-kolhatkar-abridged/">Black Edge : Inside Information, Dirty Money, and the Quest to Bring Down the Most Wanted Man on Wall Street &#8211; Sheelah Kolhatkar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Spider Network : The Wild Story of a Maths Genius and One of the Greatest Scams in Financial History &#8211; David Enrich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fraud]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times Business Book of the Year! &#8216;Will snare you in its web of deceit &#8230; A brilliant investigative expose&#8217; &#8211; Harlan Coben, bestselling thriller author &#8216;Reads like a fast-paced John le Carre thriller, and never lets up&#8217; &#8211; New York Times book review The Spider Network is the almost-unbelievable and darkly [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/">The Spider Network : The Wild Story of a Maths Genius and One of the Greatest Scams in Financial History &#8211; David Enrich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Shortlisted for the Financial Times Business Book of the Year!    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Will snare you in its web of deceit &#8230; A brilliant investigative expose&#8217; &#8211; Harlan Coben, bestselling thriller author     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Reads like a fast-paced John le Carre thriller, and never lets up&#8217; &#8211; New York Times book review     </p>
<p>                    The Spider Network is the almost-unbelievable and darkly entertaining inside account of the Libor scandal &#8211; one of the biggest, farthest-reaching financial scams since the global financial crisis &#8211; written by the only journalist with access to Tom Hayes before he was sentenced to fourteen years in prison.   Full of exclusive details, and with ramifications that stretch right across the British establishment, this is a gripping, real-life story of outlandish characters and reckless greed in the City of London.     </p>
<p>                    By turns a rollicking account of the scandal and also a provocative examination of a financial system that was crooked throughout, The Spider Network is a perfect read for fans of The Wolf of Wall Street and The Big Short.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-spider-network-the-wild-story-of-a-maths-genius-and-one-of-the-greatest-scams-in-financial-history-david-enrich-abridged/">The Spider Network : The Wild Story of a Maths Genius and One of the Greatest Scams in Financial History &#8211; David Enrich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Very English Scandal : Now a Major BBC Series Starring Hugh Grant &#8211; John Preston (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-very-english-scandal-now-a-major-bbc-series-starring-hugh-grant-john-preston-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-very-english-scandal-now-a-major-bbc-series-starring-hugh-grant-john-preston-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling book that inspired the Bafta-winning BBC drama Corruption. Blackmail. Conspiracy to murder. A Very English Scandal has all the hallmarks of a classic thriller with one difference. It&#8217;s all true. In the late 1960s Jeremy Thorp, the charismatic leader of the Liberal Party, was at the height of his political career. But homosexuality [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-english-scandal-now-a-major-bbc-series-starring-hugh-grant-john-preston-abridged/">A Very English Scandal : Now a Major BBC Series Starring Hugh Grant &#8211; John Preston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The bestselling book that inspired the Bafta-winning BBC drama    </p>
<p>                    Corruption. Blackmail. Conspiracy to murder. A Very English Scandal has all the hallmarks of a classic thriller with one difference. It&#8217;s all true.    </p>
<p>                    In the late 1960s Jeremy Thorp, the charismatic leader of the Liberal Party, was at the height of his political career. But homosexuality had only just been legalized, and a former relationship with a younger man named Norman Scott threatened to destroy Thorp&#8217;s carefully curated facade. Helped by fellow politicians, Thorpe schemed, deceived and embezzled until he saw only one way to silence his ex-lover for good.    </p>
<p>                    Meticulously researched and endlessly extraordinary, Thorp&#8217;s trial captured the moment that British society discovered the truth about its political class &#8211; and learned just how far the Establishment will go to protect its own.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Gripping. A story of cack-handed assassins, buffoonish policemen, dodgy Home Secretaries&#8217; Daily Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I loved it; eccentric, dark, humane and English in the very best sense&#8217; Alain de Botton    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Retold with masterful skill . . . It grips like a detective story&#8217; Daily Mail, Book of the Week    </p>
<p>                    JOHN PRESTON&#8217;S NEXT BOOK, FALL: THE MYSTERY OF ROBERT MAXWELL, IS AVAILABLE FOR PRE-ORDER NOW</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-very-english-scandal-now-a-major-bbc-series-starring-hugh-grant-john-preston-abridged/">A Very English Scandal : Now a Major BBC Series Starring Hugh Grant &#8211; John Preston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Doing Justice : A Prosecutor&#8217;s Thoughts on Crime, Punishment and the Rule of Law &#8211; Preet Bharara (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/doing-justice-a-prosecutors-thoughts-on-crime-punishment-and-the-rule-of-law-preet-bharara-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sentencing & Punishment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/doing-justice-a-prosecutors-thoughts-on-crime-punishment-and-the-rule-of-law-preet-bharara-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller &#8216;Simply, utterly brilliant. Bursting with humility and humanity&#8217; The Secret Barrister &#8216;An elegant, philosophical and, at times, moving memoir of what it is like to serve as America&#8217;s most high-profile legal official&#8217; Financial Times Multi-million-dollar fraud. Terrorism. Mafia criminality. Russian espionage. As United States Attorney for the Southern District of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/doing-justice-a-prosecutors-thoughts-on-crime-punishment-and-the-rule-of-law-preet-bharara-abridged/">Doing Justice : A Prosecutor&#8217;s Thoughts on Crime, Punishment and the Rule of Law &#8211; Preet Bharara (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Simply, utterly brilliant. Bursting with humility and humanity&#8217; The Secret Barrister    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An elegant, philosophical and, at times, moving memoir of what it is like to serve as America&#8217;s most high-profile legal official&#8217; Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    Multi-million-dollar fraud. Terrorism. Mafia criminality. Russian espionage.     </p>
<p>                    As United States Attorney for the Southern District of New York, Preet Bharara prosecuted some of the most high-profile cases in America. In Doing Justice he takes us inside America&#8217;s criminal justice system to deliver a powerful meditation on justice  &#8211; what it is, who dispenses it, how it works &#8211; and what the law can teach us about thinking and acting justly in our own lives.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/doing-justice-a-prosecutors-thoughts-on-crime-punishment-and-the-rule-of-law-preet-bharara-abridged/">Doing Justice : A Prosecutor&#8217;s Thoughts on Crime, Punishment and the Rule of Law &#8211; Preet Bharara (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Gang Leader for a Day &#8211; Sudhir Venkatesh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/gang-leader-for-a-day-sudhir-venkatesh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Age Groups: Adolescents]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Street Crime / Gun Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/gang-leader-for-a-day-sudhir-venkatesh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sudhir Venkatesh the young sociologist who became famous in Freakonomics (Why do drug dealers still live with their moms?) describes his time living with the gangs on the Southside of Chicago and answers another question: what&#8217;s it like to live in hell? In the Robert Taylor Homes projects on Chicago&#8217;s South Side, Sudhir befriends J.T., [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gang-leader-for-a-day-sudhir-venkatesh-abridged/">Gang Leader for a Day &#8211; Sudhir Venkatesh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sudhir Venkatesh the young sociologist who became famous in Freakonomics (Why do drug dealers still live with their moms?) describes his time living with the gangs on the Southside of Chicago and answers another question: what&#8217;s it like to live in hell?    </p>
<p>                    In the Robert Taylor Homes projects on Chicago&#8217;s South Side, Sudhir befriends J.T., a gang leader for the Black Kings. As he slowly gains J.T.&#8217;s trust, one day, in order to convince Sudhir of his own CEO-like qualities, J.T. makes him leader of the gang&#8230;     </p>
<p>                    Why does J.T. make his henchmen, the &#8216;shorties&#8217;, stay in school? What is the difference between a &#8216;regular&#8217; hustler and a &#8216;hype&#8217; &#8211; and is Peanut telling him the truth about which she is? And, when the FBI finally starts cracking down on the Black Kings, is it time to get out &#8211; or is it too late?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/gang-leader-for-a-day-sudhir-venkatesh-abridged/">Gang Leader for a Day &#8211; Sudhir Venkatesh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stay Sexy and Don&#8217;t Get Murdered : The Definitive How-To Guide From the My Favorite Murder Podcast &#8211; Georgia Hardstark, Karen Kilgariff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/stay-sexy-and-dont-get-murdered-the-definitive-how-to-guide-from-the-my-favorite-murder-podcast-georgia-hardstark-karen-kilgariff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Eating Disorders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Or Forensic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eating Disorders & Therapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Pornography & Obscenity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/stay-sexy-and-dont-get-murdered-the-definitive-how-to-guide-from-the-my-favorite-murder-podcast-georgia-hardstark-karen-kilgariff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER FROM THE CULT-HIT TRUE CRIME PODCAST, MY FAVORITE MURDER In STAY SEXY &#038; DON&#8217;T GET MURDERED, Karen Kilgariff and Georgia Hardstark, hosts of true crime comedy podcast &#8216;My Favorite Murder,&#8217; open up about their lives more intimately than ever in their confessionally honest and hilarious debut book, titled after their podcast [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stay-sexy-and-dont-get-murdered-the-definitive-how-to-guide-from-the-my-favorite-murder-podcast-georgia-hardstark-karen-kilgariff-abridged/">Stay Sexy and Don&#8217;t Get Murdered : The Definitive How-To Guide From the My Favorite Murder Podcast &#8211; Georgia Hardstark, Karen Kilgariff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER FROM THE CULT-HIT TRUE CRIME PODCAST, MY FAVORITE MURDER    </p>
<p>                    In STAY SEXY &#038; DON&#8217;T GET MURDERED, Karen Kilgariff and Georgia Hardstark, hosts of true crime comedy podcast &#8216;My Favorite Murder,&#8217; open up about their lives more intimately than ever in their confessionally honest and hilarious debut book, titled after their podcast sign-off.    </p>
<p>                    Sharing never-before-heard stories ranging from their struggles with depression, eating disorders, and addiction, Karen and Georgia irreverently recount their biggest mistakes and deepest fears, reflecting on the formative life events that shaped them into two of the most followed voices in the podcasting world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stay-sexy-and-dont-get-murdered-the-definitive-how-to-guide-from-the-my-favorite-murder-podcast-georgia-hardstark-karen-kilgariff-abridged/">Stay Sexy and Don&#8217;t Get Murdered : The Definitive How-To Guide From the My Favorite Murder Podcast &#8211; Georgia Hardstark, Karen Kilgariff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Legal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An unburdening, a witness statement and a thriller all at the same time &#8230; electrifying.&#8217; The Times I have to assume that there is a very real chance that Putin or members of his regime will have me killed some day. If I&#8217;m killed, you will know who did it. When my enemies read this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/">Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An unburdening, a witness statement and a thriller all at the same time &#8230; electrifying.&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                    I have to assume that there is a very real chance that Putin or members of his regime will have me killed some day. If I&#8217;m killed, you will know who did it. When my enemies read this book, they will know that you know.    </p>
<p>                    A Sunday Times and New York Times bestseller. A true-life thriller by one of Putin&#8217;s Most Wanted.    </p>
<p>                    In November 2009, the young lawyer Sergei Magnitsky was beaten to death by eight police officers in a freezing cell in a Moscow prison. His crime? Testifying against Russian officials who were involved in a conspiracy to steal $230 million of taxes.    </p>
<p>                    Red Notice is a searing expose of the whitewash of this imprisonment and murder. The killing hasn&#8217;t been investigated. It hasn&#8217;t been punished. Bill Browder is still campaigning for justice for his late lawyer and friend. This is his explosive journey from the heady world of finance in New York and London in the 1990s, through battles with ruthless oligarchs in turbulent post-Soviet Union Moscow, to the shadowy heart of the Kremlin.    </p>
<p>                    With fraud, bribery, corruption and torture exposed at every turn, Red Notice is a shocking political roller-coaster.<br />
                    __________________    </p>
<p>                    Reads like a classic thriller, with an everyman hero alone and in danger in a hostile foreign city &#8230; but it&#8217;s all true, and it&#8217;s a story that needs to be told.&#8217; Lee Child    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A shocking true-life thriller.&#8217; Tom Stoppard    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A riveting account&#8230; it is a powerful story and Browder tells it skilfully.&#8217; The Washington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/red-notice-a-true-story-of-corruption-murder-and-how-i-became-putins-no-1-enemy-bill-browder-abridged/">Red Notice : A True Story of Corruption, Murder and how I became Putin&#8217;s no. 1 enemy &#8211; Bill Browder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Devil in the White City : Murder, Magic, and Madness at the Fair that Changed America &#8211; Erik Larson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Local History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Urban Communities]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The true tale of the 1893 World&#8217;s Fair in Chicago and the cunning serial killer who used the magic and majesty of the fair to lure his victims to their death. &#8220;Relentlessly fuses history and entertainment to give this nonfiction book the dramatic effect of a novel &#8230;. It doesn&#8217;t [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/">The Devil in the White City : Murder, Magic, and Madness at the Fair that Changed America &#8211; Erik Larson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The true tale of the 1893 World&#8217;s Fair in Chicago and the cunning serial killer who used the magic and majesty of the fair to lure his victims to their death.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Relentlessly fuses history and entertainment to give this nonfiction book the dramatic effect of a novel &#8230;. It doesn&#8217;t hurt that this truth is stranger than fiction.&#8221; &#8211;The New York Times     </p>
<p>                    Combining meticulous research with nail-biting storytelling, Erik Larson has crafted a narrative with all the wonder of newly discovered history and the thrills of the best fiction.    </p>
<p>                    Two men, each handsome and unusually adept at his chosen work, embodied an element of the great dynamic that characterized America&#8217;s rush toward the twentieth century. The architect was Daniel Hudson Burnham, the fair&#8217;s brilliant director of works and the builder of many of the country&#8217;s most important structures, including the Flatiron Building in New York and Union Station in Washington, D.C. The murderer was Henry H. Holmes, a young doctor who, in a malign parody of the White City, built his &#8220;World&#8217;s Fair Hotel&#8221; just west of the fairgrounds&#8211;a torture palace complete with dissection table, gas chamber, and 3,000-degree crematorium.     </p>
<p>                    Burnham overcame tremendous obstacles and tragedies as he organized the talents of Frederick Law Olmsted, Charles McKim, Louis Sullivan, and others to transform swampy Jackson Park into the White City, while Holmes used the attraction of the great fair and his own satanic charms to lure scores of young women to their deaths. What makes the story all the more chilling is that Holmes really lived, walking the grounds of that dream city by the lake.     </p>
<p>                    The Devil in the White City draws the reader into the enchantment of the Guilded Age, made all the more appealing by a supporting cast of real-life characters, including Buffalo Bill, Theodore Dreiser, Susan B. Anthony, Thomas Edison, Archduke Francis Ferdinand, and others. Erik Larson&#8217;s gifts as a storyteller are magnificently displayed in this rich narrative of the master builder, the killer, and the great fair that obsessed them both.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-devil-in-the-white-city-murder-magic-and-madness-at-the-fair-that-changed-america-erik-larson-abridged/">The Devil in the White City : Murder, Magic, and Madness at the Fair that Changed America &#8211; Erik Larson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Billion Dollar Whale : the bestselling investigation into the financial fraud of the century &#8211; Tom Wright, Bradley Hope (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Banking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hoaxes & Deceptions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A BOOK OF THE YEAR FOR THE FINANCIAL TIMES AND FORTUNE MAGAZINE. The epic story of how a young social climber from Malaysia pulled off one of the biggest financial heists in history. In 2015, rumours began circulating that billions of dollars had been stolen from a Malaysian investment fund. The mastermind of the heist [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/">Billion Dollar Whale : the bestselling investigation into the financial fraud of the century &#8211; Tom Wright, Bradley Hope (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A BOOK OF THE YEAR FOR THE FINANCIAL TIMES AND FORTUNE MAGAZINE.    </p>
<p>                    The epic story of how a young social climber from Malaysia pulled off one of the biggest financial heists in history.    </p>
<p>                    In 2015, rumours began circulating that billions of dollars had been stolen from a Malaysian investment fund. The mastermind of the heist was twenty-seven-year-old Jho Low, a serial fabulist from an upper-middle-class Malaysian family, who had carefully built his reputation as a member of the jet-setting elite by arranging and financing elaborate parties for Wall Street bankers, celebrities, and even royalty.    </p>
<p>                    With the aid of Goldman Sachs and others, Low stole billions of dollars, right under the nose of global financial industry watchdogs. He used the money to finance elections, purchase luxury real estate, throw champagne-drenched parties, and bankroll Hollywood films like The Wolf of Wall Street.     </p>
<p>                    Billion Dollar Whale reveals how this silver-tongued con man, a &#8216;modern Gatsby&#8217;, emerged from obscurity to pull off one of the most audacious financial heists the world has ever seen, and how the financial industry let him. It is a classic harrowing parable of hubris and greed in the financial world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/billion-dollar-whale-the-bestselling-investigation-into-the-financial-fraud-of-the-century-tom-wright-bradley-hope-abridged/">Billion Dollar Whale : the bestselling investigation into the financial fraud of the century &#8211; Tom Wright, Bradley Hope (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dreamland : The True Tale of America&#8217;s Opiate Epidemic &#8211; Sam Quinones (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dreamland-the-true-tale-of-americas-opiate-epidemic-sam-quinones-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drug & Substance Abuse: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drugs Trade / Drug Trafficking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dreamland-the-true-tale-of-americas-opiate-epidemic-sam-quinones-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the NBCC Award for General Nonfiction Named on Amazon&#8217;s Best Books of the Year 2015&#8211;Michael Botticelli, U.S. Drug Czar (Politico) Favorite Book of the Year&#8211;Angus Deaton, Nobel Prize Economics (Bloomberg/WSJ) Best Books of 2015&#8211;Matt Bevin, Governor of Kentucky (WSJ) Books of the Year&#8211;Slate.com&#8217;s 10 Best Books of 2015&#8211;Entertainment Weekly&#8217;s 10 Best Books of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dreamland-the-true-tale-of-americas-opiate-epidemic-sam-quinones-abridged/">Dreamland : The True Tale of America&#8217;s Opiate Epidemic &#8211; Sam Quinones (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the NBCC Award for General Nonfiction    </p>
<p>                    Named on Amazon&#8217;s Best Books of the Year 2015&#8211;Michael Botticelli, U.S. Drug Czar (Politico) Favorite Book of the Year&#8211;Angus Deaton, Nobel Prize Economics (Bloomberg/WSJ) Best Books of 2015&#8211;Matt Bevin, Governor of Kentucky (WSJ) Books of the Year&#8211;Slate.com&#8217;s 10 Best Books of 2015&#8211;Entertainment Weekly&#8217;s 10 Best Books of 2015 &#8211;Buzzfeed&#8217;s 19 Best Nonfiction Books of 2015&#8211;The Daily Beast&#8217;s Best Big Idea Books of 2015&#8211;Seattle Times&#8217; Best Books of 2015&#8211;Boston Globe&#8217;s Best Books of 2015&#8211;St. Louis Post-Dispatch&#8217;s Best Books of 2015&#8211;The Guardian&#8217;s The Best Book We Read All Year&#8211;Audible&#8217;s Best Books of 2015&#8211;Texas Observer&#8217;s Five Books We Loved in 2015&#8211;Chicago Public Library&#8217;s Best Nonfiction Books of 2015     </p>
<p>                    From a small town in Mexico to the boardrooms of Big Pharma to main streets nationwide, an explosive and shocking account of addiction in the heartland of America.     </p>
<p>                    In 1929, in the blue-collar city of Portsmouth, Ohio, a company built a swimming pool the size of a football field; named Dreamland, it became the vital center of the community. Now, addiction has devastated Portsmouth, as it has hundreds of small rural towns and suburbs across America&#8211;addiction like no other the country has ever faced. How that happened is the riveting story of Dreamland.     </p>
<p>                    With a great reporter&#8217;s narrative skill and the storytelling ability of a novelist, acclaimed journalist Sam Quinones weaves together two classic tales of capitalism run amok whose unintentional collision has been catastrophic. The unfettered prescribing of pain medications during the 1990s reached its peak in Purdue Pharma&#8217;s campaign to market OxyContin, its new, expensive&#8211;extremely addictive&#8211;miracle painkiller. Meanwhile, a massive influx of black tar heroin&#8211;cheap, potent, and originating from one small county on Mexico&#8217;s west coast, independent of any drug cartel&#8211;assaulted small town and mid-sized cities across the country, driven by a brilliant, almost unbeatable marketing and distribution system. Together these phenomena continue to lay waste to communities from Tennessee to Oregon, Indiana to New Mexico.     </p>
<p>                    Introducing a memorable cast of characters&#8211;pharma pioneers, young Mexican entrepreneurs, narcotics investigators, survivors, and parents&#8211;Quinones shows how these tales fit together. Dreamland is a revelatory account of the corrosive threat facing America and its heartland.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dreamland-the-true-tale-of-americas-opiate-epidemic-sam-quinones-abridged/">Dreamland : The True Tale of America&#8217;s Opiate Epidemic &#8211; Sam Quinones (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ghettoside : Investigating a Homicide Epidemic &#8211; Jill Leovy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ghettoside-investigating-a-homicide-epidemic-jill-leovy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ghettoside-investigating-a-homicide-epidemic-jill-leovy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE MULTI-AWARD WINNING INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; AS READ ON BBC RADIO 4 Why would you kill your neighbour? Based on the best part of a decade embedded with the homicide units of the LAPD, this groundbreaking work of reportage takes us onto the streets, inside the homes and into the lives of a community wracked [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ghettoside-investigating-a-homicide-epidemic-jill-leovy-abridged/">Ghettoside : Investigating a Homicide Epidemic &#8211; Jill Leovy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE MULTI-AWARD WINNING INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; AS READ ON BBC RADIO 4    </p>
<p>                    Why would you kill your neighbour?    </p>
<p>                    Based on the best part of a decade embedded with the homicide units of the LAPD, this groundbreaking work of reportage takes us onto the streets, inside the homes and into the lives of a community wracked by a homicide epidemic.    </p>
<p>                    Through the gripping story of one particular murder &#8211; of an eighteen-year-old boy named Bryant Tennelle, gunned down one evening in spring for no apparent reason &#8211; and of its investigation by a brilliant, ferociously driven detective &#8211; a blond, surfer-turned-cop named John Skaggs &#8211; it reveals the true origins of such violence, explodes the myths surrounding policing and race and shows that the only way to reverse the cycle of violence is with justice.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ghettoside-investigating-a-homicide-epidemic-jill-leovy-abridged/">Ghettoside : Investigating a Homicide Epidemic &#8211; Jill Leovy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Say Nothing : A True Story of Murder and Memory in Northern Ireland &#8211; Patrick Radden Keefe (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/say-nothing-a-true-story-of-murder-and-memory-in-northern-ireland-patrick-radden-keefe-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True War & Combat Stories]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/say-nothing-a-true-story-of-murder-and-memory-in-northern-ireland-patrick-radden-keefe-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE ORWELL PRIZE FOR POLITICAL WRITING 2019 A BARACK OBAMA BEST BOOK OF 2019 SHORTLISTED FOR THE NATIONAL BOOK AWARD FOR NONFICTION 2019 TIME&#8217;s #1 Best Nonfiction Book of 2019 A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;A must read&#8217; Gillian Flynn One night in December 1972, Jean McConville, a mother of ten, was abducted [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/say-nothing-a-true-story-of-murder-and-memory-in-northern-ireland-patrick-radden-keefe-abridged/">Say Nothing : A True Story of Murder and Memory in Northern Ireland &#8211; Patrick Radden Keefe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>WINNER OF THE ORWELL PRIZE FOR POLITICAL WRITING 2019<br />
                              A BARACK OBAMA BEST BOOK OF 2019<br />
                              SHORTLISTED FOR THE NATIONAL BOOK AWARD FOR NONFICTION 2019<br />
                              TIME&#8217;s #1 Best Nonfiction Book of 2019<br />
                              A NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                              &#8216;A must read&#8217; Gillian Flynn<br />
                              One night in December 1972, Jean McConville, a mother of ten, was abducted from her home in Belfast and never seen alive again. Her disappearance would haunt her orphaned children, the perpetrators of the brutal crime and a whole society in Northern Ireland for decades.    </p>
<p>                              Through the unsolved case of Jean McConville&#8217;s abduction, Patrick Radden Keefe tells the larger story of the Troubles, investigating Dolours Price, the first woman to join the IRA, who bombed the Old Bailey; Gerry Adams, the politician who helped end the fighting but denied his IRA past; and Brendan Hughes, an IRA commander who broke their code of silence. A gripping story forensically reported, Say Nothing explores the extremes people will go to for an ideal, and the way societies mend &#8211; or don&#8217;t &#8211; after long and bloody conflict.    </p>
<p>                                &#8217;10 Best Books of 2019&#8242; &#8211; The New York Times, Washington Post, Chicago Tribune, Slate, NPR&#8217;s Fresh Air    </p>
<p>                                &#8216;Best History Book of 2019&#8242; &#8211; Amazon    </p>
<p>                                &#8217;10 Best Nonfiction Books of 2019&#8242; &#8211; TIME    </p>
<p>                                &#8217;10 Best Nonfiction Books of the Decade&#8217; &#8211; Entertainment Weekly    </p>
<p>                                &#8217;20 Best Nonfiction Books of the Decade&#8217; &#8211; Literary Hub    </p>
<p>                                &#8217;10 Best True Crime Books of the Decade&#8217; &#8211; CrimeReads</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/say-nothing-a-true-story-of-murder-and-memory-in-northern-ireland-patrick-radden-keefe-abridged/">Say Nothing : A True Story of Murder and Memory in Northern Ireland &#8211; Patrick Radden Keefe (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Woman of No Importance : The Untold Story of Virginia Hall, WWII&#8217;s Most Dangerous Spy &#8211; Sonia Purnell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-woman-of-no-importance-the-untold-story-of-virginia-hall-wwiis-most-dangerous-spy-sonia-purnell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[20th Century History: C 1900 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[World War 2 Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-woman-of-no-importance-the-untold-story-of-virginia-hall-wwiis-most-dangerous-spy-sonia-purnell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A METICULOUS HISTORY THAT READS LIKE A THRILLER&#8217; BEN MACINTYRE, TEN BEST BOOKS TO READ ABOUT WORLD WAR II An astounding story of heroism, spycraft, resistance and personal triumph over shocking adversity. &#8216;A rousing tale of derring-do&#8217; THE TIMES * &#8216;Riveting&#8217; MICK HERRON * &#8216;Superb&#8217; IRISH TIMES THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER In September 1941, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-woman-of-no-importance-the-untold-story-of-virginia-hall-wwiis-most-dangerous-spy-sonia-purnell-abridged/">A Woman of No Importance : The Untold Story of Virginia Hall, WWII&#8217;s Most Dangerous Spy &#8211; Sonia Purnell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A METICULOUS HISTORY THAT READS LIKE A THRILLER&#8217; BEN MACINTYRE, TEN BEST BOOKS TO READ ABOUT WORLD WAR II    </p>
<p>                        An astounding story of heroism, spycraft, resistance and personal triumph over shocking adversity.    </p>
<p>                       &#8216;A rousing tale of derring-do&#8217; THE TIMES   *   &#8216;Riveting&#8217; MICK HERRON   *   &#8216;Superb&#8217; IRISH TIMES    </p>
<p>                                                                           THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    In September 1941, a young American woman strides up the steps of a hotel in Lyon, Vichy France. Her papers say she is a journalist. Her wooden leg is disguised by a determined gait and a distracting beauty. She is there to spark the resistance.    </p>
<p>                    By 1942 Virginia Hall was the Gestapo&#8217;s most urgent target, having infiltrated Vichy command, trained civilians in guerrilla warfare and sprung soldiers from Nazi prison camps. The first woman to go undercover for British SOE, her intelligence changed the course of the war &#8211; but her fight was still not over.     </p>
<p>                    This is a spy history like no other, telling the story of the hunting accident that disabled her, the discrimination she fought and the secret life that helped her triumph over shocking adversity.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A cracking story about an extraordinarily brave woman&#8217; TELEGRAPH    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Gripping &#8230; superb &#8230; a rounded portrait of a complicated, resourceful, determined and above all brave woman&#8217; IRISH TIMES    </p>
<p>                    WINNER of the PLUTARCH AWARD FOR BEST BIOGRAPHY</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-woman-of-no-importance-the-untold-story-of-virginia-hall-wwiis-most-dangerous-spy-sonia-purnell-abridged/">A Woman of No Importance : The Untold Story of Virginia Hall, WWII&#8217;s Most Dangerous Spy &#8211; Sonia Purnell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Viruses, Trojans & Worms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award! There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life. In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award!<br />
                    There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life.<br />
                    In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest spam and hacker operations targeting Americans and their bank accounts. Tracing the rise, fall, and alarming resurrection of the digital mafia behind the two largest spam pharmacies-and countless viruses, phishing, and spyware attacks-he delivers the first definitive narrative of the global spam problem and its threat to consumers everywhere.<br />
                    Blending cutting-edge research, investigative reporting, and firsthand interviews, this terrifying true story reveals how we unwittingly invite these digital thieves into our lives every day. From unassuming computer programmers right next door to digital mobsters like &#8220;Cosma&#8221;-who unleashed a massive malware attack that has stolen thousands of Americans&#8217; logins and passwords-Krebs uncovers the shocking lengths to which these people will go to profit from our data and our wallets.<br />
                    Not only are hundreds of thousands of Americans exposing themselves to fraud and dangerously toxic products from rogue online pharmacies, but even those who never open junk messages are at risk. As Krebs notes, spammers can-and do-hack into accounts through these emails, harvest personal information like usernames and passwords, and sell them on the digital black market. The fallout from this global epidemic doesn&#8217;t just cost consumers and companies billions, it costs lives too.<br />
                    Fast-paced and utterly gripping, Spam Nation ultimately proposes concrete solutions for protecting ourselves online and stemming this tidal wave of cybercrime-before it&#8217;s too late.<br />
                    &#8220;Krebs&#8217;s talent for exposing the weaknesses in online security has earned him respect in the IT business and loathing among cybercriminals&#8230; His track record of scoops&#8230;has helped him become the rare blogger who supports himself on the strength of his reputation for hard-nosed reporting.&#8221; -Bloomberg Businessweek</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Furious Hours : Murder, Fraud and the Last Trial of Harper Lee &#8211; Casey Cep (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/furious-hours-murder-fraud-and-the-last-trial-of-harper-lee-casey-cep-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/furious-hours-murder-fraud-and-the-last-trial-of-harper-lee-casey-cep-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A BARACK OBAMA BOOK OF THE YEAR WINNER OF THE 2020 CRIME WRITERS&#8217; ASSOCIATION ALCS GOLD DAGGER FOR NON-FICTION SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2019 BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION A SUNDAY TIMES, ECONOMIST AND SPECTATOR BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8216;A triumph on every level. One of the losses to literature is that Harper Lee never found [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/furious-hours-murder-fraud-and-the-last-trial-of-harper-lee-casey-cep-abridged/">Furious Hours : Murder, Fraud and the Last Trial of Harper Lee &#8211; Casey Cep (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A BARACK OBAMA BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    WINNER OF THE 2020 CRIME WRITERS&#8217; ASSOCIATION ALCS GOLD DAGGER FOR NON-FICTION<br />
                    SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2019 BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION<br />
                    A SUNDAY TIMES, ECONOMIST AND SPECTATOR BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A triumph on every level. One of the losses to literature is that Harper Lee never found a way to tell a gothic true-crime story she&#8217;d spent years researching. Casey Cep has excavated this mesmerizing story and tells it with grace and insight and a fierce fidelity to the truth.&#8217;<br />
                    DAVID GRANN, author of Killers of the Flower Moon<br />
                    _____________________________<br />
                    The stunning story of an Alabama serial killer and the true-crime book that Harper Lee worked on obsessively in the years after To Kill a Mockingbird    </p>
<p>                    Reverend Willie Maxwell was a rural preacher accused of murdering five of his family members for insurance money in the 1970s. With the help of a savvy lawyer, he escaped justice for years until a relative shot him dead at the funeral of his last victim. Despite hundreds of witnesses, Maxwell&#8217;s murderer was acquitted &#8211; thanks to the same attorney who had previously defended the Reverend.    </p>
<p>                    As Alabama is consumed by these gripping events, it&#8217;s not long until news of the case reaches Alabama&#8217;s &#8211; and America&#8217;s &#8211; most famous writer. Intrigued by the story, Harper Lee makes a journey back to her home state to witness the Reverend&#8217;s killer face trial. Harper had the idea of writing her own In Cold Blood, the true-crime classic she had helped her friend Truman Capote research. Lee spent a year in town reporting on the Maxwell case and many more years trying to finish the book she called The Reverend.    </p>
<p>                    Now Casey Cep brings this story to life, from the shocking murders to the courtroom drama to the racial politics of the Deep South. At the same time, she offers a deeply moving portrait of one of the country&#8217;s most beloved writers and her struggle with fame, success, and the mystery of artistic creativity.    </p>
<p>                    This is the story Harper Lee wanted to write. This is the story of why she couldn&#8217;t.<br />
                    _____________________________<br />
                    &#8216;Fascinating &#8230; Cep has spliced together a Southern-gothic tale  of multiple murder and the unhappy story of Lee&#8217;s literary career, to produce a tale that is engrossing in its detail and deeply poignant&#8230; [Cep] spends the first third of Furious Hours following the jaw-dropping trail of murders &#8230; Engrossing &#8230; Cep writes about all this with great skill, sensitivity and attention to detail.&#8217;<br />
                    SUNDAY TIMES    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It&#8217;s been a long time since I picked up a book so impossible to put down. Furious Hours made me forget dinner, ignore incoming calls, and stay up reading into the small hours. It&#8217;s a work of literary and legal detection as gripping as a thriller. But it&#8217;s also a meditation on motive and mystery, the curious workings of history, hope, and ambition, justice, and the darkest matters of life and death. Casey Cep&#8217;s investigation into an infamous Southern murder trial and Harper Lee&#8217;s quest to write about it is a beautiful, sobering, and sometimes chilling triumph.&#8217;<br />
                    HELEN MACDONALD, author of H is for Hawk    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This story is just too good &#8230; Furious Hours builds and builds until it collides with the writer who saw the power of Maxwell&#8217;s story, but for some reason was unable to harness it. It lays bare the inner life of a woman who had a world-class gift for hiding &#8230; [this] book makes a magical leap, and it goes from being a superbly written true-crime story to the sort of story that even Lee would have been proud to write.&#8217;<br />
                    MICHAEL LEWIS, author of Moneyball and The Big Short</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/furious-hours-murder-fraud-and-the-last-trial-of-harper-lee-casey-cep-abridged/">Furious Hours : Murder, Fraud and the Last Trial of Harper Lee &#8211; Casey Cep (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Abuse & Harassment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a dramatic account of violence and espionage, Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter Ronan Farrow exposes serial abusers and a cabal of powerful interests hell-bent on covering up the truth, at any cost. In 2017, a routine network television investigation led Ronan Farrow to a story only whispered about: one of Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful producers was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow-abridged/">Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a dramatic account of violence and espionage, Pulitzer Prize-winning investigative reporter Ronan Farrow exposes serial abusers and a cabal of powerful interests hell-bent on covering up the truth, at any cost.    </p>
<p>                    In 2017, a routine network television investigation led Ronan Farrow to a story only whispered about: one of Hollywood&#8217;s most powerful producers was a predator, protected by fear, wealth, and a conspiracy of silence. As Farrow drew closer to the truth, shadowy operatives, from high-priced lawyers to elite war-hardened spies, mounted a secret campaign of intimidation, threatening his career, following his every move and weaponizing an account of abuse in his own family.     </p>
<p>                    All the while, Farrow and his producer faced a degree of resistance that could not be explained &#8211; until now. And a trail of clues revealed corruption and cover-ups from Hollywood, to Washington, and beyond.     </p>
<p>                    This is the untold story of the exotic tactics of surveillance and intimidation deployed by wealthy and connected men to threaten journalists, evade accountability and silence victims of abuse &#8211; and it&#8217;s the story of the women who risked everything to expose the truth and spark a global movement.    </p>
<p>                    Both a spy thriller and a meticulous work of investigative journalism, Catch and Kill breaks devastating new stories about the rampant abuse of power &#8211; and sheds far-reaching light on investigations that shook the culture.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/catch-and-kill-lies-spies-and-a-conspiracy-to-protect-predators-ronan-farrow-abridged/">Catch and Kill : Lies, Spies and a Conspiracy to Protect Predators &#8211; Ronan Farrow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bunk : The Rise of Hoaxes, Humbug, Plagiarists, Phonies, Post-Facts &#8211; Kevin Young (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/bunk-the-rise-of-hoaxes-humbug-plagiarists-phonies-post-facts-kevin-young-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hoaxes & Deceptions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literature: History & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reportage & Collected Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/bunk-the-rise-of-hoaxes-humbug-plagiarists-phonies-post-facts-kevin-young-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the National Book Award for Nonfiction &#8220;There Kevin Young goes again, giving us books we greatly need, cleverly disguised as books we merely want. Unexpectedly essential.&#8221;&#8211;Marlon James Award-winning poet and critic Kevin Young tours us through a rogue&#8217;s gallery of hoaxers, plagiarists, forgers, and fakers&#8211;from the humbug of P. T. Barnum and Edgar [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bunk-the-rise-of-hoaxes-humbug-plagiarists-phonies-post-facts-kevin-young-abridged/">Bunk : The Rise of Hoaxes, Humbug, Plagiarists, Phonies, Post-Facts &#8211; Kevin Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Longlisted for the National Book Award for Nonfiction    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;There Kevin Young goes again, giving us books we greatly need, cleverly disguised as books we merely want. Unexpectedly essential.&#8221;&#8211;Marlon James     </p>
<p>                    Award-winning poet and critic Kevin Young tours us through a rogue&#8217;s gallery of hoaxers, plagiarists, forgers, and fakers&#8211;from the humbug of P. T. Barnum and Edgar Allan Poe to the unrepentant bunk of JT LeRoy and Donald J. Trump. Bunk traces the history of the hoax as a peculiarly American phenomenon, examining what motivates hucksters and makes the rest of us so gullible. Disturbingly, Young finds that fakery is woven from stereotype and suspicion, race being the most insidious American hoax of all. He chronicles how Barnum came to fame by displaying figures like Joice Heth, a black woman whom he pretended was the 161-year-old nursemaid to George Washington, and What Is It?, an African American man Barnum professed was a newly discovered missing link in evolution.    </p>
<p>                    Bunk then turns to the hoaxing of history and the ways that forgers, plagiarists, and journalistic fakers invent backstories and falsehoods to sell us lies about themselves and about the world in our own time, from pretend Native Americans Grey Owl and Nasdijj to the deadly imposture of Clark Rockefeller, from the made-up memoirs of James Frey to the identity theft of Rachel Dolezal. In this brilliant and timely work, Young asks what it means to live in a post-factual world of &#8220;truthiness&#8221; where everything is up for interpretation and everyone is subject to a pervasive cynicism that damages our ideas of reality, fact, and art.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bunk-the-rise-of-hoaxes-humbug-plagiarists-phonies-post-facts-kevin-young-abridged/">Bunk : The Rise of Hoaxes, Humbug, Plagiarists, Phonies, Post-Facts &#8211; Kevin Young (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Blood of Emmett Till &#8211; Timothy B. Tyson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-blood-of-emmett-till-timothy-b-tyson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-blood-of-emmett-till-timothy-b-tyson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>* Longlisted for the National Book Award * Winner of the Robert F. Kennedy Book Award * A New York Times Notable Book * A Washington Post Notable Book * An NPR Best Book of 2017 * A Los Angeles Times Best Book of 2017 * An Atlanta Journal-Constitution Best Southern Book of 2017 * [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-blood-of-emmett-till-timothy-b-tyson-abridged/">The Blood of Emmett Till &#8211; Timothy B. Tyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>* Longlisted for the National Book Award * Winner of the Robert F. Kennedy Book Award * A New York Times Notable Book * A Washington Post Notable Book * An NPR Best Book of 2017 * A Los Angeles Times Best Book of 2017 * An Atlanta Journal-Constitution Best Southern Book of 2017 *    </p>
<p>                     This extraordinary New York Times bestseller reexamines a pivotal event of the civil rights movement-the 1955 lynching of Emmett Till-&#8220;and demands that we do the one vital thing we aren&#8217;t often enough asked to do with history: learn from it&#8221; (The Atlantic).    </p>
<p>                    In 1955, white men in the Mississippi Delta lynched a fourteen-year-old from Chicago named Emmett Till. His murder was part of a wave of white terrorism in the wake of the 1954 Supreme Court decision that declared public school segregation unconstitutional. Only weeks later, Rosa Parks thought about young Emmett as she refused to move to the back of a city bus in Montgomery, Alabama. Five years later, Black students who called themselves &#8220;the Emmett Till generation&#8221; launched sit-in campaigns that turned the struggle for civil rights into a mass movement. Till&#8217;s lynching became the most notorious hate crime in American history.    </p>
<p>                    But what actually happened to Emmett Till-not the icon of injustice, but the flesh-and-blood boy? Part detective story, part political history, The Blood of Emmett Till &#8220;unfolds like a movie&#8221; (The Atlanta Journal-Constitution), drawing on a wealth of new evidence, including a shocking admission of Till&#8217;s innocence from the woman in whose name he was killed. &#8220;Jolting and powerful&#8221; (The Washington Post), the book &#8220;provides fresh insight into the way race has informed and deformed our democratic institutions&#8221; (Diane McWhorter, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of Carry Me Home) and &#8220;calls us to the cause of justice today&#8221; (Rev. Dr. William J. Barber, II, president of the North Carolina NAACP).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-blood-of-emmett-till-timothy-b-tyson-abridged/">The Blood of Emmett Till &#8211; Timothy B. Tyson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In the Name of Identity : Violence and the Need to Belong &#8211; Amin Maalouf, Translated byProfessor Barbara Bray (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-the-name-of-identity-violence-and-the-need-to-belong-amin-maalouf-translated-by-professor-barbara-bray-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-the-name-of-identity-violence-and-the-need-to-belong-amin-maalouf-translated-by-professor-barbara-bray-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Makes for compelling reading in America today.&#8221;&#8211;New York Times Book Review. &#8220;I want to try and understand why so many people commit crimes in the name of identity,&#8221; writes Amin Maalouf. Identity is the crucible out of which we come: our background, our race, our gender, our tribal affiliations, our religion (or lack thereof), all [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-the-name-of-identity-violence-and-the-need-to-belong-amin-maalouf-translated-by-professor-barbara-bray-abridged/">In the Name of Identity : Violence and the Need to Belong &#8211; Amin Maalouf, Translated byProfessor Barbara Bray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Makes for compelling reading in America today.&#8221;&#8211;New York Times Book Review.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;I want to try and understand why so many people commit crimes in the name of identity,&#8221; writes Amin Maalouf. Identity is the crucible out of which we come: our background, our race, our gender, our tribal affiliations, our religion (or lack thereof), all go into making up who we are. All too often, however, the notion of identity&#8211;personal, religious, ethnic, or national&#8211;has given rise to heated passions and even massive crimes.     </p>
<p>                    Moving across the world&#8217;s history, faiths, and politics, he argues against an oversimplified and hostile interpretation of the concept. He cogently and persuasively examines identity in the context of the modern world, where it can be viewed as both glory and poison. Evident here are the dangers of using identity as a protective&#8211;and therefore aggressive&#8211;mechanism, the root of racial, geographical, and colonialist subjugation throughout history.     </p>
<p>                    Maalouf contends that many of us would reject our inherited conceptions of identity, to which we cling through habit, if only we examined them more closely. The future of society depends on accepting all identities, while recognizing our individualism.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-the-name-of-identity-violence-and-the-need-to-belong-amin-maalouf-translated-by-professor-barbara-bray-abridged/">In the Name of Identity : Violence and the Need to Belong &#8211; Amin Maalouf, Translated byProfessor Barbara Bray (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/permanent-record-edward-snowden-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Freedom Of Information & Freedom Of Speech]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Network Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Privacy & Data Protection]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/permanent-record-edward-snowden-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER Edward Snowden, the man who risked everything to expose the US government&#8217;s system of mass surveillance, reveals for the first time the story of his life, including how he helped to build that system and what motivated him to try to bring it down. In 2013, twenty-nine-year-old Edward Snowden [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/permanent-record-edward-snowden-abridged/">Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    Edward Snowden, the man who risked everything to expose the US government&#8217;s system of mass surveillance, reveals for the first time the story of his life, including how he helped to build that system and what motivated him to try to bring it down.    </p>
<p>                    In 2013, twenty-nine-year-old Edward Snowden shocked the world when he broke with the American intelligence establishment and revealed that the United States government was secretly pursuing the means to collect every single phone call, text message, and email. The result would be an unprecedented system of mass surveillance with the ability to pry into the private lives of every person on earth. Six years later, Snowden reveals for the very first time how he helped to build this system and why he was moved to expose it.    </p>
<p>                    Spanning the bucolic Beltway suburbs of his childhood and the clandestine CIA and NSA postings of his adulthood, Permanent Record is the extraordinary account of a bright young man who grew up online &#8211; a man who became a spy, a whistleblower, and, in exile, the Internet&#8217;s conscience. Written with wit, grace, passion, and an unflinching candor, Permanent Record is a crucial memoir of our digital age and destined to be a classic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/permanent-record-edward-snowden-abridged/">Permanent Record &#8211; Edward Snowden (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Run of His Life : The People v. O. J. Simpson &#8211; Jeffrey Toobin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-run-of-his-life-the-people-v-o-j-simpson-jeffrey-toobin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Law & Procedure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-run-of-his-life-the-people-v-o-j-simpson-jeffrey-toobin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The inspiration for American Crime Story: The People v. O. J. Simpson on FX, starring Cuba Gooding, Jr., John Travolta, David Schwimmer, and Connie Britton The definitive account of the O. J. Simpson trial, The Run of His Life is a prodigious feat of reporting that could have been written [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-run-of-his-life-the-people-v-o-j-simpson-jeffrey-toobin-abridged/">The Run of His Life : The People v. O. J. Simpson &#8211; Jeffrey Toobin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; The inspiration for American Crime Story: The People v. O. J. Simpson on FX, starring Cuba Gooding, Jr., John Travolta, David Schwimmer, and Connie Britton     </p>
<p>                     The definitive account of the O. J. Simpson trial, The Run of His Life is a prodigious feat of reporting that could have been written only by the foremost legal journalist of our time. First published less than a year after the infamous verdict, Jeffrey Toobin&#8217;s nonfiction masterpiece tells the whole story, from the murders of Nicole Brown Simpson and Ronald Goldman to the ruthless gamesmanship behind the scenes of &#8220;the trial of the century.&#8221; Rich in character, as propulsive as a legal thriller, this enduring narrative continues to shock and fascinate with its candid depiction of the human drama that upended American life.    </p>
<p>                     Praise for The Run of His Life    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This is the book to read.&#8221;&#8211;Michiko Kakutani, The New York Times      </p>
<p>                     &#8220;This book stands out as a gripping and colorful account of the crime and trial that captured the world&#8217;s attention.&#8221;&#8211;Boston Sunday Globe    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A real page-turner . . . strips away the months of circuslike televised proceedings and the sordid tell-all books and lays out a simple, but devastating, synopsis of the case.&#8221;&#8211;Entertainment Weekly    </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A well-written, profoundly rational analysis of the trial and, more specifically, the lawyers who conducted it.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Engrossing . . . Toobin&#8217;s insight into the motives and mind-set of key players sets this Simpson book apart from the pack.&#8221;&#8211;People (one of the top ten books of the year)</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-run-of-his-life-the-people-v-o-j-simpson-jeffrey-toobin-abridged/">The Run of His Life : The People v. O. J. Simpson &#8211; Jeffrey Toobin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Secret Barrister : Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken &#8211; The Secret Barrister (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Criminal Law & Procedure]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Ethics & Professional Conduct]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Legal Profession: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times number one bestseller. Winner of the Books are My Bag Non-Fiction Award. Shortlisted for Waterstones Book of the Year. Shortlisted for Specsavers Non-Fiction Book of the Year. You may not wish to think about it, but one day you or someone you love will almost certainly appear in a criminal courtroom. You [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister-abridged/">The Secret Barrister : Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken &#8211; The Secret Barrister (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Sunday Times number one bestseller.<br />
                    Winner of the Books are My Bag Non-Fiction Award.<br />
                    Shortlisted for Waterstones Book of the Year.<br />
                    Shortlisted for Specsavers Non-Fiction Book of the Year.    </p>
<p>                    You may not wish to think about it, but one day you or someone you love will almost certainly appear in a criminal courtroom. You might be a juror, a victim, a witness or &#8211; perhaps through no fault of your own &#8211; a defendant. Whatever your role, you&#8217;d expect a fair trial.    </p>
<p>                      I&#8217;m a barrister. I work in the criminal justice system, and every day I see how fairness is not guaranteed. Too often the system fails those it is meant to protect. The innocent are wronged and the guilty allowed to walk free.    </p>
<p>                    In The Secret Barrister: Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken I want to share some stories from my daily life to show you how the system is broken, who broke it and why we should start caring before it&#8217;s too late.    </p>
<p>                    A Sunday Times top ten bestseller for twenty-four weeks.<br />
                    &#8216;Eye-opening, funny and horrifying&#8217; &#8211; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Everyone who has any interest in public life should read it&#8217; &#8211; Daily Mail</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-secret-barrister-stories-of-the-law-and-how-its-broken-the-secret-barrister-abridged/">The Secret Barrister : Stories of the Law and How It&#8217;s Broken &#8211; The Secret Barrister (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Drug & Alcohol Abuse]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drugs Trade / Drug Trafficking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organized Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Everything drug cartels do to survive and prosper they&#8217;ve learnt from big business &#8211; brand value and franchising from McDonald&#8217;s, supply chain management from Walmart, diversification from Coca-Cola. Whether it&#8217;s human resourcing, R&#038;D, corporate social responsibility, off-shoring, problems with e-commerce or troublesome changes in legislation, the drug lords face the same strategic concerns companies like [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/">Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Everything drug cartels do to survive and prosper they&#8217;ve learnt from big business &#8211; brand value and franchising from McDonald&#8217;s, supply chain management from Walmart, diversification from Coca-Cola. Whether it&#8217;s human resourcing, R&#038;D, corporate social responsibility, off-shoring, problems with e-commerce or troublesome changes in legislation, the drug lords face the same strategic concerns companies like Ryanair or Apple. So when the drug cartels start to think like big business, the only way to understand them is using economics.     </p>
<p>                    In Narconomics, Tom Wainwright meets everyone from coca farmers in secret Andean locations, deluded heads of state in presidential palaces, journalists with a price on their head, gang leaders who run their empires from dangerous prisons and teenage hitmen on city streets &#8211; all in search of the economic truth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/narconomics-how-to-run-a-drug-cartel-tom-wainwright-abridged/">Narconomics : How To Run a Drug Cartel &#8211; Tom Wainwright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
