<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Budgeting &amp; Financial Management Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/budgeting-financial-management/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/budgeting-financial-management/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Budgeting &amp; Financial Management Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/budgeting-financial-management/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Financial Diet : A Total Beginner&#8217;s Guide to Getting Good with Money &#8211; Chelsea Fagan, Lauren Ver Hage (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-financial-diet-a-total-beginners-guide-to-getting-good-with-money-chelsea-fagan-lauren-ver-hage-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Financial Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-financial-diet-a-total-beginners-guide-to-getting-good-with-money-chelsea-fagan-lauren-ver-hage-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*A Refinery29 Best Book of 2018* *One of Real Simple&#8217;s Most Inspiring Books for Graduates* *Indie Personal Finance Bestseller* How to get good with money, even if you have no idea where to start. The Financial Diet is the personal finance book for people who don&#8217;t care about personal finance. Whether you&#8217;re in need of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-financial-diet-a-total-beginners-guide-to-getting-good-with-money-chelsea-fagan-lauren-ver-hage-abridged/">The Financial Diet : A Total Beginner&#8217;s Guide to Getting Good with Money &#8211; Chelsea Fagan, Lauren Ver Hage (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*A Refinery29 Best Book of 2018*<br />
                    *One of Real Simple&#8217;s Most Inspiring Books for Graduates*<br />
                    *Indie Personal Finance Bestseller*     </p>
<p>                    How to get good with money, even if you have no idea where to start.     </p>
<p>                    The Financial Diet is the personal finance book for people who don&#8217;t care about personal finance. Whether you&#8217;re in need of an overspending detox, buried under student debt, or just trying to figure out how to live on an entry-level salary, The Financial Diet gives you tools to make a budget, understand investments, and deal with your credit. Chelsea Fagan has tapped a range of experts to help you make the best choices for you, but she also knows that being smarter with money isn&#8217;t just about what you put in the bank. It&#8217;s about everything&#8211;from the clothes you put in your closet, to your financial relationship habits, to the food you put in your kitchen (instead of ordering in again). So The Financial Diet gives you the tools to negotiate a raise and the perfect cocktail recipe to celebrate your new salary.     </p>
<p>                    The Financial Diet will teach you:<br />
                    &#8211; how to get good with money in a year.<br />
                    &#8211; the ingredients everyone needs to have a budget-friendly kitchen.<br />
                    &#8211; how to talk about awkward money stuff with your friends.<br />
                    &#8211; the best way to make (and stick to!) a budget.<br />
                    &#8211; how to take care of your house like a grown-up.<br />
                    &#8211; what the hell it means to invest (and how you can do it).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-financial-diet-a-total-beginners-guide-to-getting-good-with-money-chelsea-fagan-lauren-ver-hage-abridged/">The Financial Diet : A Total Beginner&#8217;s Guide to Getting Good with Money &#8211; Chelsea Fagan, Lauren Ver Hage (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fit for Growth : A Guide to Strategic Cost Cutting, Restructuring, and Renewal &#8211; Vinay Couto, John Plansky, Deniz Caglar (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fit-for-growth-a-guide-to-strategic-cost-cutting-restructuring-and-renewal-vinay-couto-john-plansky-deniz-caglar-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Production & Quality Control Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fit-for-growth-a-guide-to-strategic-cost-cutting-restructuring-and-renewal-vinay-couto-john-plansky-deniz-caglar-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A practical approach to business transformation Fit for Growth* is a unique approach to business transformation that explicitly connects growth strategy with cost management and organization restructuring. Drawing on 70-plus years of strategy consulting experience and in-depth research, the experts at PwC s Strategy&#038; lay out a winning framework that helps CEOs and senior executives [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fit-for-growth-a-guide-to-strategic-cost-cutting-restructuring-and-renewal-vinay-couto-john-plansky-deniz-caglar-abridged/">Fit for Growth : A Guide to Strategic Cost Cutting, Restructuring, and Renewal &#8211; Vinay Couto, John Plansky, Deniz Caglar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A practical approach to business transformation Fit for Growth* is a unique approach to business transformation that explicitly connects growth strategy with cost management and organization restructuring. Drawing on 70-plus years of strategy consulting experience and in-depth research, the experts at PwC s Strategy&#038; lay out a winning framework that helps CEOs and senior executives transform their organizations for sustainable, profitable growth. This approach gives structure to strategy while promoting lasting change. Examples from Strategy&#038; s hundreds of clients illustrate successful transformation on the ground, and illuminate how senior and middle managers are able to take ownership and even thrive during difficult periods of transition. Throughout the Fit for Growth process, the focus is on maintaining consistent high-value performance while enabling fundamental change. Strategy&#038; has helped major clients around the globe achieve significant and sustained results with its research-backed approach to restructuring and cost reduction.<br />
                    This book provides practical guidance for leveraging that expertise to make the choices that allow companies to: * Achieve growth while reducing costs * Manage transformation and transition productively * Create lasting competitive advantage * Deliver reliable, high-value performance Sustainable success is founded on efficiency and high performance. Companies are always looking to do more with less, but their efforts often work against them in the long run. Total business transformation requires total buy-in, and it entails a series of decisions that must not be made lightly. The Fit for Growth approach provides a clear strategy and practical framework for growth-oriented change, with expert guidance on getting it right.  * Fit for Growth is a registered service mark of PwC Strategy&#038; Inc. in the United States</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fit-for-growth-a-guide-to-strategic-cost-cutting-restructuring-and-renewal-vinay-couto-john-plansky-deniz-caglar-abridged/">Fit for Growth : A Guide to Strategic Cost Cutting, Restructuring, and Renewal &#8211; Vinay Couto, John Plansky, Deniz Caglar (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Be a Power Connector: The 5+50+100 Rule for Turning Your Business Network into Profits &#8211; Judy Robinett (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Create a personal &#8220;power grid&#8221; of influence to spark professional and personal success&#8221;Other people have the answers, deals, money, access, power, and influence you need to get what you want in this world. To achieve any goal, you need other people to help you do it.&#8221; &#8212; JUDY ROBINETT As anyone in business knows, strategic [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/">How to Be a Power Connector: The 5+50+100 Rule for Turning Your Business Network into Profits &#8211; Judy Robinett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Create a personal &#8220;power grid&#8221; of influence to spark professional and personal success&#8221;Other people have the answers, deals, money, access, power, and influence you need to get what you want in this world. To achieve any goal, you need other people to help you do it.&#8221; &#8212; JUDY ROBINETT    </p>
<p>                    As anyone in business knows, strategic planning iscritical to achieving long-term success. In How to Be a Power Connector, super-networker Judy Robinett argues that strategic relationship planning should be your top priority.    </p>
<p>                    When you combine your specific skills and talents with a clear, workable path for creating and managing your relationships, nothing will stop you from meeting your goals. With high-value connections, you&#8217;ll tap into a dynamic &#8220;power grid&#8221; of influence guaranteed to accelerate your personal and professional success.    </p>
<p>                    Robinett uses her decades of experience connecting the world&#8217;s highest achievers with one another to help you build high-value relationships. She reveals all the secrets of her trade, including proven ways to:    </p>
<p>                    Find and enter the best network &#8220;ecosystem&#8221; to meet your goalsReach even the most unreachable people quickly and effectivelyGet anyone&#8217;s contact information within 30 secondsCreate a &#8220;3-D connection&#8221; that adds value to multiple people at the same timeAccess key infl uencers through industry and community eventsSubtly seed conversation with information about interests and needsUse social media to your best advantage    </p>
<p>                    Robinett has based her methods on solid researchproving that social groups begin to break up when they become larger than 150 people, and that 50 members is the optimal size for group communication. As such, she has developed what she calls the &#8220;5+50+100&#8243; method: contact your top 5 connections daily, your Key 50 weekly, and your Vital 100 monthly. this is your power grid, and it will work wonders for your career.    </p>
<p>                    Nothing will stop you when you learn How to Be aPower Connector.    </p>
<p>                    PRAISE FOR HOW TO BE A POWER CONNECTOR:&#8221;Unlike many books in this genre, this one is written by a woman who has lived it.. . . Judy Robinett offers guidance on how to form authentic relationships thatbring mutual benefits.&#8221; &#8212; ADAM GRANT, Wharton professor and New York Times bestselling author of Give and Take    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;How to Be a Power Connector is like an MBA in networking: an advanced course in finding and developing quality relationships with the people who can make the biggest difference in your professional success.&#8221; &#8212; IVAN MISNER, founder and chairman of BNI    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Talk about power! Follow Judy Robinett&#8217;s logical, straightforward, and helpfully detailed advice, and you can be a &#8216;Power Connector&#8217; yourself! Great ideas, wellpresented, with no &#8216;wasted space&#8217; in her argument!&#8221; &#8212; DON PEPPERS, coauthor of Extreme Trust: Honesty as a Competitive Advantage    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Absolutely brilliant. A step-by-step guide to building a network that will be both invaluable to you and just as valuable to those whose lives you will now have theopportunity to touch. I can&#8217;t imagine a more powerful book for one who truly desires to be a Power Connector.&#8221; &#8212; BOB BURG, coauthor of The Go-Giver and author of Adversaries into Allies    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;In the C-Suite or in your personal life everything comes down to the quality of your relationships. Judy&#8217;s book helps you attract and maintain the relationships that will get you what you want most. Be a super connector now!&#8221; &#8212; JEFFREY HAYZLETT, TV host and bestselling author of Running the Gauntlet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-a-power-connector-the-550100-rule-for-turning-your-business-network-into-profits-judy-robinett-abridged/">How to Be a Power Connector: The 5+50+100 Rule for Turning Your Business Network into Profits &#8211; Judy Robinett (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Revenue Growth Habit : The Simple Art of Growing Your Business by 15% in 15 Minutes Per Day &#8211; Alex Goldfayn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-revenue-growth-habit-the-simple-art-of-growing-your-business-by-15-in-15-minutes-per-day-alex-goldfayn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corporate Finance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-revenue-growth-habit-the-simple-art-of-growing-your-business-by-15-in-15-minutes-per-day-alex-goldfayn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>800-CEO-Read Sales Book Of The Year for 2015 &#124; Forbes 15 Best Business Books of 2015 &#124; The chapters, (46 of them in this 256 page book) are quick and concise, and it is easy to pick it up anywhere and find a nugget of easily actionable advice, but the kicker is that the actions [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-revenue-growth-habit-the-simple-art-of-growing-your-business-by-15-in-15-minutes-per-day-alex-goldfayn-abridged/">The Revenue Growth Habit : The Simple Art of Growing Your Business by 15% in 15 Minutes Per Day &#8211; Alex Goldfayn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>800-CEO-Read Sales Book Of The Year for 2015 | Forbes 15 Best Business Books of 2015 | The chapters, (46 of them in this 256 page book) are quick and concise, and it is easy to pick it up anywhere and find a nugget of easily actionable advice, but the kicker is that the actions he recommends are also quick and concise, so that we can accomplish them in the few bursts of spare time we all have left. 800CEORead.com Follow Goldfayn&#8217;s brilliant advice and you will have an endless supply of customer testimonials, spontaneous referrals, and new business, and it will compel you to buy a beautiful fountain pen and stop obsessing over social media. His advice simply works. Inc.com  Grow your business by 15% with these proven daily growth actions Do you have trouble finding time during your hectic day to grow your business? Is your company stalled because you are too busy reacting to customer problems? Do you lack the funds to jumpstart an effective marketing plan? The Revenue Growth Habit gives business owners, leaders, and all customer facing staff a hands-on resource for increasing revenue that is fast, easy, and requires no financial investment.<br />
                    Alex Goldfayn, CEO of the Evangelist Marketing Institute, shows how to grow your organization by 15% or more in 15 minutes or less per day without spending a penny of your money. Forget about relying on social media. Posting on Twitter, Facebook, and LinkedIn doesn&#8217;t grow revenue, especially for business-to-business companies. The Revenue Growth Habit shows how to request and collect testimonials and how to communicate these testimonials to grow your business. You will discover how to write powerful case studies, ask for (and get!) referrals, grow your lists, and send a revenue-growing newsletter. Goldfayn also includes information for teaching your customer service people how to inform your current clients about what else they can buy from you. This proven approach revolves around letting your customers tell your story. There is nothing you can say about your products and services that is more effective than what your paying customers say. How does it work? Each day, take one quick, proactive communication action that tells someone about how they&#8217;ll be improved after buying from you. Choose from the 22 actions Goldfayn details in The Revenue Growth Habit.<br />
                    Each technique is fast, simple, and free. It only requires your personal effort to communicate the value of your product or service to someone who can buy from you. Personal communication the key to the 22 action steps will make your company stand head-and-shoulders above the competition.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-revenue-growth-habit-the-simple-art-of-growing-your-business-by-15-in-15-minutes-per-day-alex-goldfayn-abridged/">The Revenue Growth Habit : The Simple Art of Growing Your Business by 15% in 15 Minutes Per Day &#8211; Alex Goldfayn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management: Leadership & Motivation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Working Patterns & Practices]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A refreshing approach to entrepreneurship centered on staying small and avoiding growth &#8211; maximizing happiness, sustainability and profitability. Paul Jarvis left the corporate world when he realized that working in a high-pressure, high-profile world was not his idea of success. Instead, he now works for himself out of his home, and lives a much more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/">Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A refreshing approach to entrepreneurship centered on staying small and avoiding growth &#8211; maximizing happiness, sustainability and profitability.    </p>
<p>                    Paul Jarvis left the corporate world when he realized that working in a high-pressure, high-profile world was not his idea of success. Instead, he now works for himself out of his home, and lives a much more rewarding and productive life. He no longer has to contend with an environment that constantly demands more productivity, more output and more growth.    </p>
<p>                    In Company of One, Jarvis explains how you can do the same, including:    </p>
<p>                    *         Planning to set up<br />
                    *         Determining desired revenues<br />
                    *         Keeping clients happy<br />
                    *         And, of course, doing all this on your own.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Jarvis makes a compelling case for making your business better instead of bigger. A must-read for any entrepreneur who prioritizes a rich life over riches.&#8221;<br />
                     -CAL NEWPORT, bestselling author of DEEP WORK and DIGITAL MINIMALISM    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You&#8217;re not a machine, so why would you run your business like one? Company of One shows you another way. If you&#8217;ve ever wondered how to have a business that works for you-instead of the other way around-you need this book.&#8221;<br />
                    -CHRIS GUILLEBEAU, bestselling author of SIDE HUSTLE and THE $100 STARTUP</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/company-of-one-why-staying-small-is-the-next-big-thing-for-business-paul-jarvis-abridged/">Company of One : Why Staying Small is the Next Big Thing for Business &#8211; Paul Jarvis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Write Your Business Plan : Get Your Plan in Place and Your Business off the Ground &#8211; The Staff of Entrepreneur Media (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/write-your-business-plan-get-your-plan-in-place-and-your-business-off-the-ground-the-staff-of-entrepreneur-media-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/write-your-business-plan-get-your-plan-in-place-and-your-business-off-the-ground-the-staff-of-entrepreneur-media-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A comprehensive companion to Entrepreneur&#8217;s long-time bestseller Start Your Own Business, this essential guide leads you through the most critical startup step next to committing to your business vision&#8211;defining how to achieve it. Coached by a diverse group of experts and successful business owners, gain an in-depth understanding of what&#8217;s essential to any business plan, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/write-your-business-plan-get-your-plan-in-place-and-your-business-off-the-ground-the-staff-of-entrepreneur-media-abridged/">Write Your Business Plan : Get Your Plan in Place and Your Business off the Ground &#8211; The Staff of Entrepreneur Media (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A comprehensive companion to Entrepreneur&#8217;s long-time bestseller Start Your Own Business, this essential guide leads you through the most critical startup step next to committing to your business vision&#8211;defining how to achieve it.  Coached by a diverse group of experts and successful business owners, gain an in-depth understanding of what&#8217;s essential to any business plan, what&#8217;s appropriate for your venture, and what it takes ensure success. Plus, learn from real-world examples of plans that worked, helping to raise money, hone strategy, and build a solid business.  Whether you&#8217;re just starting out or already running a business, to successfully build a company, you need a plan. One that lays out your product, your strategy, your market, your team, and your opportunity. It is the blueprint for your business. The experts at Entrepreneur show you how to create it.  Includes sample business plans, resources and worksheets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/write-your-business-plan-get-your-plan-in-place-and-your-business-off-the-ground-the-staff-of-entrepreneur-media-abridged/">Write Your Business Plan : Get Your Plan in Place and Your Business off the Ground &#8211; The Staff of Entrepreneur Media (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cut Costs Not Corners : A Practical Guide to Staying Competitive and Improving Profits &#8211; Colin Barrow (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cut-costs-not-corners-a-practical-guide-to-staying-competitive-and-improving-profits-colin-barrow-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Budgeting & Financial Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Finance & Accounting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cut-costs-not-corners-a-practical-guide-to-staying-competitive-and-improving-profits-colin-barrow-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Cost cutting is an issue for every manager and executive at every level in every company, large or small, public or private sector. Junior managers who are proactively tight on cost are learning good habits for the future, ones that will bring them recognition and advance their climb up the organizational chart. The HR department [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cut-costs-not-corners-a-practical-guide-to-staying-competitive-and-improving-profits-colin-barrow-abridged/">Cut Costs Not Corners : A Practical Guide to Staying Competitive and Improving Profits &#8211; Colin Barrow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Cost cutting is an issue for every manager and executive at every level in every company, large or small, public or private sector. Junior managers who are proactively tight on cost are learning good habits for the future, ones that will bring them recognition and advance their climb up the organizational chart. The HR department is now staffed with tough cost managers dealing with the most difficult cost category, people. Marketing departments now focus on how to get higher returns from less spend.    </p>
<p>                    Cut Costs Not Corners has a coherent and structured approach to cost cutting as a permanent activity, combined with guidance on the practical steps to take and powerful international case studies. It covers strategic and tactical cost cutting options such as analysing space needs, buying technology for less, selling off redundant assets, reducing credit risk, reviewing distribution methods, sourcing new suppliers or consolidating existing ones, advertising for less, changing the route to market, travel and utility savings, minimising finance and tax costs, crisis measures &#8211; freezing recruitment, delaying pay rises, sell and lease back assets &#8211; keeping budgets rolling and using a daily cash flow model.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cut-costs-not-corners-a-practical-guide-to-staying-competitive-and-improving-profits-colin-barrow-abridged/">Cut Costs Not Corners : A Practical Guide to Staying Competitive and Improving Profits &#8211; Colin Barrow (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
