<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Palaeontology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/palaeontology/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/palaeontology/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:58:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Palaeontology Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/palaeontology/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Story of the Human Body : Evolution, Health and Disease &#8211; Daniel Lieberman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-story-of-the-human-body-evolution-health-and-disease-daniel-lieberman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Palaeontology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-story-of-the-human-body-evolution-health-and-disease-daniel-lieberman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In The Story of the Human Body, Daniel Lieberman, Professor of human evolutionary biology at Harvard, shows how we need to change our world to fit our hunter-gatherer bodies This ground-breaking book of popular science explores how the way we use our bodies is all wrong. From an evolutionary perspective, if normal is defined as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-the-human-body-evolution-health-and-disease-daniel-lieberman-abridged/">The Story of the Human Body : Evolution, Health and Disease &#8211; Daniel Lieberman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In The Story of the Human Body, Daniel Lieberman, Professor of human evolutionary biology at Harvard, shows how we need to change our world to fit our hunter-gatherer bodies    </p>
<p>                    This ground-breaking book of popular science explores how the way we use our bodies is all wrong. From an evolutionary perspective, if normal is defined as what most people have done for millions of years, then it&#8217;s normal to walk and run 9 -15 kilometres a day to hunt and gather fresh food which is high in fibre, low in sugar, and barely processed. It&#8217;s also normal to spend much of your time nursing, napping, making stone tools, and gossiping with a small band of people.     </p>
<p>                    Our 21st-century lifestyles, argues Daniel Lieberman, are out of synch with our stone-age bodies. Never have we been so healthy and long-lived &#8211; but never, too, have we been so prone to a slew of problems that were, until recently, rare or unknown, from asthma, to diabetes, to &#8211; scariest of all &#8211; overpopulation.    </p>
<p>                    The Story of the Human Body asks how our bodies got to be the way they are, and considers how that evolutionary history &#8211; both ancient and recent &#8211; can help us evaluate how we use our bodies. How is the present-day state of the human body related to the past? And what is the human body&#8217;s future?<br />
                    &#8216;Monumental. The Story of the Human Body, by one of our leading experts, takes us on an epic voyage&#8217; &#8211; Neil Shubin, author of Your Inner Fish    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Riveting, enlightening, and more than a little frightening&#8217; &#8211; Christopher McDougall, author of Born to Run    </p>
<p>                    Daniel Lieberman is the Chair of the Department of Human Evolutionary Biology at Harvard and a leader in the field. He has written nearly 100 articles, many appearing in the journals Nature and Science, and his cover story on barefoot running in Nature was picked up by major media the world over. His research and discoveries have been highlighted in newspapers and magazines, including The New York Times, Boston Globe, Discover, and National Geographic.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-story-of-the-human-body-evolution-health-and-disease-daniel-lieberman-abridged/">The Story of the Human Body : Evolution, Health and Disease &#8211; Daniel Lieberman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs : The Untold Story of a Lost World &#8211; Steve Brusatte (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dinosaurs & The Prehistoric World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Palaeontology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Times Science Book of the Year. A Sunday Times Bestseller. 66 million years ago the dinosaurs were wiped from the face of the earth. Today, Dr. Steve Brusatte, one of the leading scientists of a new generation of dinosaur hunters, armed with cutting edge technology, is piecing together the complete story of how the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/">The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs : The Untold Story of a Lost World &#8211; Steve Brusatte (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Times Science Book of the Year.<br />
                    A Sunday Times Bestseller.    </p>
<p>                    66 million years ago the dinosaurs were wiped from the face of the earth. Today, Dr. Steve Brusatte, one of the leading scientists of a new generation of dinosaur hunters, armed with cutting edge technology, is piecing together the complete story of how the dinosaurs ruled the earth for 150 million years.    </p>
<p>                    The world of the dinosaurs has fascinated on book and screen for decades &#8211; from early science fiction classics like The Lost World, to Godzilla terrorizing the streets of Tokyo, and the monsters of Jurassic Park. But what if we got it wrong? In The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs, top dinosaur expert Brusatte, tells the real story of how dinosaurs rose to dominate the planet. Using the fossil clues that have been gathered using state of the art technology, Brusatte follows these magnificent creatures from their beginnings in the Early Triassic period, through the Jurassic period to their final days in the Cretaceous and the legacy that they left behind.    </p>
<p>                    Along the way, Brusatte introduces us to modern day dinosaur hunters and gives an insight into what it&#8217;s like to be a paleontologist. The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs is full of thrilling accounts of some of his personal discoveries, including primitive human-sized tyrannosaurs, monstrous carnivores even larger than T. rex, and feathered raptor dinosaurs preserved in lava from China.     </p>
<p>                    At a time when Homo sapiens has existed for less than 200,000 years and we are already talking about planetary extinction, The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs is a timely reminder of what humans can learn from the magnificent creatures who ruled the earth before us.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Thrilling . . . the best book on the subject written for the general reader since the 1980s.&#8217; &#8211;  The Sunday Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-and-fall-of-the-dinosaurs-the-untold-story-of-a-lost-world-steve-brusatte-abridged/">The Rise and Fall of the Dinosaurs : The Untold Story of a Lost World &#8211; Steve Brusatte (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
