<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Computing Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/computing/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/computing/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:59:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Computing Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/computing/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Life After Google : The Fall of Big Data and the Rise of the Blockchain Economy &#8211; George Gilder (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Monetary Economics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE MONTH FROM THE WALL STREET JOURNAL: &#8220;Nothing Mr. Gilder says or writes is ever delivered at anything less than the fullest philosophical decibel&#8230; Mr. Gilder sounds less like a tech guru than a poet, and his words tumble out in a romantic cascade.&#8221; &#8220;Google&#8217;s algorithms assume the world&#8217;s future [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/">Life After Google : The Fall of Big Data and the Rise of the Blockchain Economy &#8211; George Gilder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A FINANCIAL TIMES BOOK OF THE MONTH      </p>
<p>                     FROM THE WALL STREET JOURNAL: &#8220;Nothing Mr. Gilder says or writes is ever delivered at anything less than the fullest philosophical decibel&#8230; Mr. Gilder sounds less like a tech guru than a poet, and his words tumble out in a romantic cascade.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Google&#8217;s algorithms assume the world&#8217;s future is nothing more than the next moment in a random process. George Gilder shows how deep this assumption goes, what motivates people to make it, and why it&#8217;s wrong: the future depends on human action.&#8221; &#8212; Peter Thiel, founder of PayPal and Palantir Technologies and author of Zero to One: Notes on Startups, or How to Build the Future     </p>
<p>                     The Age of Google, built on big data and machine intelligence, has been an awesome era. But it&#8217;s coming to an end. In Life after Google, George Gilder&#8211;the peerless visionary of technology and culture&#8211;explains why Silicon Valley is suffering a nervous breakdown and what to expect as the post-Google age dawns.     </p>
<p>                     Google&#8217;s astonishing ability to &#8220;search and sort&#8221; attracts the entire world to its search engine and countless other goodies&#8211;videos, maps, email, calendars&#8230;.And everything it offers is free, or so it seems. Instead of paying directly, users submit to advertising. The system of &#8220;aggregate and advertise&#8221; works&#8211;for a while&#8211;if you control an empire of data centers, but a market without prices strangles entrepreneurship and turns the Internet into a wasteland of ads.     </p>
<p>                     The crisis is not just economic. Even as advances in artificial intelligence induce delusions of omnipotence and transcendence, Silicon Valley has pretty much given up on security. The Internet firewalls supposedly protecting all those passwords and personal information have proved hopelessly permeable.     </p>
<p>                     The crisis cannot be solved within the current computer and network architecture. The future lies with the &#8220;cryptocosm&#8221;&#8211;the new architecture of the blockchain and its derivatives. Enabling cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin and ether, NEO and Hashgraph, it will provide the Internet a secure global payments system, ending the aggregate-and-advertise Age of Google.     </p>
<p>                     Silicon Valley, long dominated by a few giants, faces a &#8220;great unbundling,&#8221; which will disperse computer power and commerce and transform the economy and the Internet.     </p>
<p>                     Life after Google is almost here.     </p>
<p>                     For fans of &#8220;Wealth and Poverty,&#8221; &#8220;Knowledge and Power,&#8221; and &#8220;The Scandal of Money.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-after-google-the-fall-of-big-data-and-the-rise-of-the-blockchain-economy-george-gilder-abridged/">Life After Google : The Fall of Big Data and the Rise of the Blockchain Economy &#8211; George Gilder (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Consultant&#8217;s Handbook : A Practical Guide to Delivering High-value and Differentiated Services in a Competitive Marketplace &#8211; Samir Parikh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-consultants-handbook-a-practical-guide-to-delivering-high-value-and-differentiated-services-in-a-competitive-marketplace-samir-parikh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consultancy & Grants For Businesses]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Encyclopaedias & Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-consultants-handbook-a-practical-guide-to-delivering-high-value-and-differentiated-services-in-a-competitive-marketplace-samir-parikh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Delivers the essential practical skills needed to consult and make sharp, well prepared interactions in a wide range of business situations This comprehensive handbook covers the fundamental skills and attitudes required by successful consultants from novice to practitioner level, irrespective of their specialist area. It untangles the key variables present in any consulting service and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-consultants-handbook-a-practical-guide-to-delivering-high-value-and-differentiated-services-in-a-competitive-marketplace-samir-parikh-abridged/">The Consultant&#8217;s Handbook : A Practical Guide to Delivering High-value and Differentiated Services in a Competitive Marketplace &#8211; Samir Parikh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Delivers the essential practical skills needed to consult and make sharp, well prepared interactions in a wide range of business situations This comprehensive handbook covers the fundamental skills and attitudes required by successful consultants from novice to practitioner level, irrespective of their specialist area. It untangles the key variables present in any consulting service and introduces practical ways to improve their effectiveness based upon the author&#8217;s experience of helping consulting organisations to develop and excel in the marketplace. The book explores consulting from the ground up&#8217; steering away from theory and focusing instead on practical application, providing a solid platform upon which to build further domain-specific competence. The Consultant&#8217;s Handbook provides: * An understanding of the key variables that can be addressed in order to improve one&#8217;s own consulting performance * A set of simple practices that can be implemented with immediate benefit to the reader * Practical insight into day-to-day real life consulting interactions * Confidence to implement the new ideas and approaches</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-consultants-handbook-a-practical-guide-to-delivering-high-value-and-differentiated-services-in-a-competitive-marketplace-samir-parikh-abridged/">The Consultant&#8217;s Handbook : A Practical Guide to Delivering High-value and Differentiated Services in a Competitive Marketplace &#8211; Samir Parikh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ownership & Organization Of Enterprises]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Finance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Facebook, PayPal, Alibaba, Uber-these companies have upended entire industries by harnessing a single phenomenon: the platform business model. Platform Revolution delivers the first comprehensive analysis of how platforms match producers and consumers in a multi-sided marketplace, unlocking hidden resources and creating new forms of value. Platform Revolution explores the what, how and why of this [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/">Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Facebook, PayPal, Alibaba, Uber-these companies have upended entire industries by harnessing a single phenomenon: the platform business model. Platform Revolution delivers the first comprehensive analysis of how platforms match producers and consumers in a multi-sided marketplace, unlocking hidden resources and creating new forms of value.    </p>
<p>                     Platform Revolution explores the what, how and why of this revolution and provides the first &#8220;owner&#8217;s manual&#8221; for creating a platform marketplace. It provides the essential guide to unlocking the potential of an economic landscape transformed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/platform-revolution-how-networked-markets-are-transforming-the-economy-and-how-to-make-them-work-for-you-geoffrey-g-parker-marshall-w-van-alstyne-sangeet-paul-choudary-abridged/">Platform Revolution : How Networked Markets Are Transforming the Economy and How to Make Them Work for You &#8211; Geoffrey G. Parker, Marshall W. Van Alstyne, Sangeet Paul Choudary (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Everybody Lies : The New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Seth Stephens-Davidowitz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Analysis: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Prose: Non-fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AN ECONOMIST BOOK OF THE YEAR A NEW STATESMAN BOOK OF THE YEAR &#8216;This book is about a whole new way of studying the mind &#8230; Endlessly fascinating&#8217; Steven Pinker &#8216;A whirlwind tour of the modern human psyche&#8217; Economist Everybody lies, to friends, lovers, doctors, pollsters &#8211; and to themselves. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/">Everybody Lies : The New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Seth Stephens-Davidowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    AN ECONOMIST BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    A NEW STATESMAN BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book is about a whole new way of studying the mind &#8230; Endlessly fascinating&#8217; Steven Pinker    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A whirlwind tour of the modern human psyche&#8217; Economist    </p>
<p>                    Everybody lies, to friends, lovers, doctors, pollsters &#8211; and to themselves. In Internet searches, however, people confess the truth.    </p>
<p>                    Insightful, funny and always surprising, Everybody Lies explores how this huge collection of data, unprecedented in human history, could just be the most important ever collected. It offers astonishing insights into the human psyche, revealing the biases deeply embedded within us, the questions we&#8217;re afraid to ask that might be essential to our well-being, and the information we can use to change our culture for the better.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/everybody-lies-the-new-york-times-bestseller-seth-stephens-davidowitz-abridged/">Everybody Lies : The New York Times Bestseller &#8211; Seth Stephens-Davidowitz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zucked : Waking Up to the Facebook Catastrophe &#8211; Roger McNamee (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zucked-waking-up-to-the-facebook-catastrophe-roger-mcnamee-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zucked-waking-up-to-the-facebook-catastrophe-roger-mcnamee-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This is the dramatic story of how a noted tech venture capitalist, an early mentor to Mark Zuckerberg and investor in his company, woke up to the serious damage Facebook was doing to our society and set out to try to stop it. If you had told Roger McNamee three years ago that he would [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zucked-waking-up-to-the-facebook-catastrophe-roger-mcnamee-abridged/">Zucked : Waking Up to the Facebook Catastrophe &#8211; Roger McNamee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is the dramatic story of how a noted tech venture capitalist, an early mentor to Mark Zuckerberg and investor in his company, woke up to the serious damage Facebook was doing to our society and set out to try to stop it.    </p>
<p>                              If you had told Roger McNamee three years ago that he would soon be devoting himself to stopping Facebook from destroying democracy, he would have howled with laughter. He had mentored many tech leaders in his illustrious career as an investor, but few things had made him prouder, or been better for his fund&#8217;s bottom line, than his early service to Mark Zuckerberg. Still a large shareholder in Facebook, he had every good reason to stay on the bright side. Until he simply couldn&#8217;t.     </p>
<p>                              Zucked is McNamee&#8217;s intimate reckoning with the catastrophic failure of the head of one of the world&#8217;s most powerful companies to face up to the damage he is doing. It&#8217;s a story that begins with a series of rude awakenings. First there is the author&#8217;s dawning realization that the platform is being manipulated by some very bad actors. Then there is the even more unsettling realization that Zuckerberg and Sheryl Sandberg are unable or unwilling to share his concerns, polite as they may be to his face.     </p>
<p>                              And then comes Brexit and the election of Donald Trump, and the emergence of one horrific piece of news after another about the malign ends to which the Facebook platform has been put. To McNamee&#8217;s shock, Facebook&#8217;s leaders still duck and dissemble, viewing the matter as a public relations problem. Now thoroughly alienated, McNamee digs into the issue, and fortuitously meets up with some fellow travellers who share his concerns, and help him sharpen its focus. Soon he and a dream team of Silicon Valley technologists are charging into the fray, to raise consciousness about the existential threat of Facebook, and the persuasion architecture of the attention economy more broadly &#8211; to our public health and to our political order.     </p>
<p>                              Zucked is both an enthralling personal narrative and a masterful explication of the forces that have conspired to place us all on the horns of this dilemma. This is the story of a company and its leadership, but it&#8217;s also a larger tale of a business sector unmoored from normal constraints, at a moment of political and cultural crisis, the worst possible time to be given new tools for summoning the darker angels of our nature and whipping them into a frenzy. This is a wise, hard-hitting, and urgently necessary account that crystallizes the issue definitively for the rest of us.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zucked-waking-up-to-the-facebook-catastrophe-roger-mcnamee-abridged/">Zucked : Waking Up to the Facebook Catastrophe &#8211; Roger McNamee (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tools and Weapons : The Promise and the Peril of the Digital Age &#8211; Brad Smith, Carol Ann Browne (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Certification: Microsoft (eg MCSE)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft Windows]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>*THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AND WORLD ECONOMIC FORUM BOOK CLUB PICK* &#8216;A clear, compelling guide to some of the most pressing debates in technology today.&#8217; Bill Gates &#8216;A colourful and insightful insiders&#8217; view of how technology is both empowering us and threatening us. From privacy to cyberattacks, this timely book is a useful [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/">Tools and Weapons : The Promise and the Peril of the Digital Age &#8211; Brad Smith, Carol Ann Browne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>*THE INSTANT NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER AND WORLD ECONOMIC FORUM BOOK CLUB PICK*    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A clear, compelling guide to some of the most pressing debates in technology today.&#8217; Bill Gates    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A colourful and insightful insiders&#8217; view of how technology is both empowering us and threatening us. From privacy to cyberattacks, this timely book is a useful guide for how to navigate the digital future.&#8217;  Walter Isaacson, bestselling author of Steve Jobs    </p>
<p>                    From Microsoft&#8217;s President and one of the tech industry&#8217;s wisest thinkers, a frank and thoughtful reckoning with how to balance enormous promise and existential risk as the digitization of everything accelerates. With new chapters on the pandemic and beyond.<br />
                    __________    </p>
<p>                    Microsoft President Brad Smith operates by a simple core belief: when your technology changes the world, you bear a responsibility to help address the world you have helped create.     </p>
<p>                    This might seem uncontroversial, but it flies in the face of a tech sector long obsessed with rapid growth and sometimes on disruption as an end in itself. While sweeping digital transformation holds great promise, we have reached an inflection point. The world has turned information technology into both a powerful tool and a formidable weapon, and new approaches are needed to manage an era defined by even more powerful inventions like artificial intelligence. Companies that create technology must accept greater responsibility for the future, and governments will need to regulate technology by moving faster and catching up with the pace of innovation.    </p>
<p>                    In Tools and Weapons, Brad Smith and Carol Ann Browne bring us a captivating narrative from the cockpit of one of the world&#8217;s largest and most powerful tech companies as it finds itself in the middle of some of the thorniest emerging issues of our time. These are challenges that come with no pre-existing playbook, including privacy, cybercrime and cyberwar, social media, the moral conundrums of artificial intelligence, big tech&#8217;s relationship to inequality, and the challenges for democracy, far and near. While in no way a self-glorifying &#8220;Microsoft memoir,&#8221; the book pulls back the curtain remarkably wide onto some of the company&#8217;s most crucial recent decision points as it strives to protect the hopes technology offers against the very real threats it also presents. There are huge ramifications for communities and countries, and Brad Smith provides a thoughtful and urgent contribution to that effort.    </p>
<p>                    __________    </p>
<p>                    In Tools and Weapons, Brad Smith takes us behind the scenes on some of the biggest stories to hit the tech industry in the past decade and some of the biggest threats we face. From Edward Snowden&#8217;s NSA leak to the NHS WannaCry ransomware attack, this book is essential reading to understand what&#8217;s happening in the world around us.    </p>
<p>                    Praise for Tools and Weapons:     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The de facto ambassador for the technology industry at large.&#8217; The New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;In Tools and Weapons, Brad and Carol Ann Browne wrestle with some of the world&#8217;s toughest technology challenges with common sense and valuable insight reflecting their inside experience. The ideas in Tools and Weapons won&#8217;t solve all our problems, but they&#8217;re a very good place to start.&#8217; &#8211; Reed Hastings, CEO, Netflix    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Tools and Weapons is a glimpse behind the curtain as Microsoft reckoned with the Snowden revelations, defended against the vicious cyberattacks, and took both the Obama and Trump administrations to court.&#8217; &#8211; Rolling Stone</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tools-and-weapons-the-promise-and-the-peril-of-the-digital-age-brad-smith-carol-ann-browne-abridged/">Tools and Weapons : The Promise and the Peril of the Digital Age &#8211; Brad Smith, Carol Ann Browne (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of Jobs : Money, Meaning and Freedom Without the 9-to-5 &#8211; Taylor Pearson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-jobs-money-meaning-and-freedom-without-the-9-to-5-taylor-pearson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Entrepreneurship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Small Businesses & Self-employed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-end-of-jobs-money-meaning-and-freedom-without-the-9-to-5-taylor-pearson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 Amazon Bestseller in Business and Money, Small Business, Entrepreneurship, and International Economics A Top 3 &#8216;Start Your Own Business&#8217; Book -Inc Magazine The rapid development of technology and globalization has changed the leverage points in accumulating wealth: money, meaning and freedom. Those that don&#8217;t adapt are becoming trapped in the downward spiral of a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-jobs-money-meaning-and-freedom-without-the-9-to-5-taylor-pearson-abridged/">The End of Jobs : Money, Meaning and Freedom Without the 9-to-5 &#8211; Taylor Pearson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 Amazon Bestseller in Business and Money, Small Business, Entrepreneurship, and International Economics    </p>
<p>                    A Top 3 &#8216;Start Your Own Business&#8217; Book -Inc Magazine    </p>
<p>                    The rapid development of technology and globalization has changed the leverage points in accumulating wealth: money, meaning and freedom. Those that don&#8217;t adapt are becoming trapped in the downward spiral of a dying middle class &#8211; working harder and earning less. Entrepreneurs that understand the new paradigm, have created unprecedented wealth in their lives and the lives of those they love.    </p>
<p>                    In This Book You&#8217;ll Learn:     </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why the century-long growth in wages came to a halt in 2000.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why MBAs and JDs can&#8217;t get jobs and what that means for the future of work and your job.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why The Theory of Constraints and a shift into the Fourth Economy has made entrepreneurship the highest-leveraged career path for the young and ambitious.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why The Turkey Problem means accounting may be the riskiest profession in the 21st century while entrepreneurship may be the safest.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; How entrepreneurs with second-rate degrees are leveraging the radical democracy of the Long Tail to get rich.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; How the Stair Step Method and return of apprenticeships have transformed the &#8220;entrepreneurial leap&#8221; to make entrepreneurship at large, and small business entrepreneurship in particular, more accessible than ever.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; The scientific research on how giving up balanced living and embracing integrated living leads to more money, more meaning, and more freedom.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Why a 20th century world view to career search questions like &#8220;What career is right for me?&#8221; and &#8220;How do I find a career?&#8221; could be the source of your frustration (and a better way to think about it)    </p>
<p>                    Included (Free) Resources:     </p>
<p>                    Get access by visiting http: //taylorpearson.me/eoj    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Full Recorded Interviews with the Ten Entrepreneurs featured in The End of Jobs detailing how they launched their own successful businesses.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Taylor&#8217;s 67 must-read business books and the best entrepreneur books to fuel your entrepreneurial career.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; 49 tools and templates to save you hundreds of hours when launching and growing a business.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; A Ninety-Day goal setting template to translate the book into actionable steps    </p>
<p>                    &#8212; Access to a private community to discuss the book and get support from a community of like-minded individuals to inspire, motivate, and assist each other in seeking out apprenticeships, your career search and other elements around &#8220;how to find a career&#8221; and other career guidance questions like &#8220;what career is right for me</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-jobs-money-meaning-and-freedom-without-the-9-to-5-taylor-pearson-abridged/">The End of Jobs : Money, Meaning and Freedom Without the 9-to-5 &#8211; Taylor Pearson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Becoming Steve Jobs : The evolution of a reckless upstart into a visionary leader &#8211; Brent Schlender, Rick Tetzeli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/becoming-steve-jobs-the-evolution-of-a-reckless-upstart-into-a-visionary-leader-brent-schlender-rick-tetzeli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macintosh]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/becoming-steve-jobs-the-evolution-of-a-reckless-upstart-into-a-visionary-leader-brent-schlender-rick-tetzeli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES AND #1 INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; with a new foreword by Silicon Valley legend Marc Andreessen. &#8216;For my money, a better book about Jobs than Walter Isaacson&#8217;s biography&#8217; New Yorker &#8216;A fascinating reinterpretation of the Steve Jobs story&#8217; Sunday Times We all think we know who Steve Jobs was, what made him tick, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-steve-jobs-the-evolution-of-a-reckless-upstart-into-a-visionary-leader-brent-schlender-rick-tetzeli-abridged/">Becoming Steve Jobs : The evolution of a reckless upstart into a visionary leader &#8211; Brent Schlender, Rick Tetzeli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES AND #1 INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER &#8211; with a new foreword by Silicon Valley legend Marc Andreessen.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;For my money, a better book about Jobs than Walter Isaacson&#8217;s biography&#8217; New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A fascinating reinterpretation of the Steve Jobs story&#8217; Sunday Times    </p>
<p>                    We all think we know who Steve Jobs was, what made him tick, and what made him succeed.     </p>
<p>                    Yet the single most important question about him has never been answered.     </p>
<p>                    The young, impulsive, egotistical genius was ousted in the mid-80s from the company he founded, exiled from his own kingdom and cast into the wilderness. Yet he returned a decade later to transform the ailing Apple into the most successful company the world had ever seen.     </p>
<p>                    How did this reckless upstart transform himself into a visionary business leader?     </p>
<p>                    The first comprehensive study of Jobs&#8217; career following his dismissal from Apple, written with unparalleled access and insight, BECOMING STEVE JOBS offers a startling new portrait of the most important business figure in modern history. The most intimate biography yet of Jobs, written by the journalist who knew him better than any other, BECOMING STEVE JOBS draws on recently discovered interviews that have never before seen the light of day, and answers for the first time the most pressing questions about what made this legendary business leader such a success.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/becoming-steve-jobs-the-evolution-of-a-reckless-upstart-into-a-visionary-leader-brent-schlender-rick-tetzeli-abridged/">Becoming Steve Jobs : The evolution of a reckless upstart into a visionary leader &#8211; Brent Schlender, Rick Tetzeli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Data : The Tiny Clues That Uncover Huge Trends &#8211; Martin Lindstrom Company (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/small-data-the-tiny-clues-that-uncover-huge-trends-martin-lindstrom-company-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Occupational & Industrial Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/small-data-the-tiny-clues-that-uncover-huge-trends-martin-lindstrom-company-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller named one of the &#8220;Most Important Books of 2016&#8221; by Inc, and a Forbes 2016 &#8220;Must Read Business Book&#8221; &#8216;If you love &#8216;Bones&#8217; and &#8216;CSI&#8217;, this book is your kind of candy&#8217; Paco Underhill, author of Why We Buy &#8216;Martin&#8217;s best book to date. A personal, intuitive, powerful way to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-data-the-tiny-clues-that-uncover-huge-trends-martin-lindstrom-company-abridged/">Small Data : The Tiny Clues That Uncover Huge Trends &#8211; Martin Lindstrom Company (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller named one of the &#8220;Most Important Books of 2016&#8221; by Inc, and a Forbes 2016 &#8220;Must Read Business Book&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;If you love &#8216;Bones&#8217; and &#8216;CSI&#8217;, this book is your kind of candy&#8217; Paco Underhill, author of Why We Buy    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Martin&#8217;s best book to date. A personal, intuitive, powerful way to look at making an impact with your work&#8217; Seth Godin, author of Purple Cow    </p>
<p>                    Martin Lindstrom, one of Time Magazine&#8217;s 100 Most Influential People in The World and a modern-day Sherlock Holmes, harnesses the power of &#8220;small data&#8221; in his quest to discover the next big thing.    </p>
<p>                    In an era where many believe Big Data has rendered human perception and observation &#8216;old-school&#8217; or passe, Martin Lindstrom shows that mining and matching technological data with up-close psychological insight creates the ultimate snapshot of who we really are and what we really want. He works like a modern-day Sherlock Holmes, accumulating small clues &#8211; the progressively weaker handshakes of Millenials, a notable global decrease in the use of facial powder, a change in how younger consumers approach eating ice cream cones &#8211; to help solve a stunningly diverse array of challenges. In Switzerland, a stuffed teddy bear in a teenage girl&#8217;s bedroom helped revolutionise 1,000 stores &#8211; spread across twenty countries &#8211; for one of Europe&#8217;s largest fashion retailers. In Dubai, a distinctive bracelet strung with pearls helped Jenny Craig offset its declining membership in the United States and increase loyalty by 159% in only one year. In China, the look of a car dashboard led to the design of the iRobot, or Roomba, floor cleaner &#8211; a great success story.    </p>
<p>                    SMALL DATA combines armchair travel with forensic psychology in an interlocking series of international clue-gathering detective stories. It shows Lindstrom using his proprietary CLUES Framework &#8211; where big data is merely one part of the overall puzzle &#8211; to get radically close to consumers and come up with the counter-intuitive insights that have in some cases helped transform entire industries.     </p>
<p>                    SMALL DATA presents a rare behind-the-scenes look at what it takes to create global brands, and reveals surprising and counter-intuitive truths about what connects us all as humans.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-data-the-tiny-clues-that-uncover-huge-trends-martin-lindstrom-company-abridged/">Small Data : The Tiny Clues That Uncover Huge Trends &#8211; Martin Lindstrom Company (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
