<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Social &amp; Political Philosophy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/social-political-philosophy/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/social-political-philosophy/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Social &amp; Political Philosophy Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/social-political-philosophy/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Fear : Trump in the White House &#8211; Bob Woodward</title>
		<link>/fear-trump-in-the-white-house-bob-woodward/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fear-trump-in-the-white-house-bob-woodward/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER THE OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR THE INSIDE STORY ON PRESIDENT TRUMP, AS ONLY BOB WOODWARD CAN TELL IT. &#8216;Fear is a meticulously researched account of a White House and a president in financial, legal and personal disorder&#8230;essential reading&#8230;&#8217; Daily Mail &#8216;I think you&#8217;ve always been fair.&#8217; &#8211; President [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-trump-in-the-white-house-bob-woodward/">Fear : Trump in the White House &#8211; Bob Woodward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES NUMBER ONE BESTSELLER<br />
                    THE OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR</p>
<p>                     THE INSIDE STORY ON PRESIDENT TRUMP, AS ONLY BOB WOODWARD CAN TELL IT.</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fear is a meticulously researched account of a White House and a president in financial, legal and personal disorder&#8230;essential reading&#8230;&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                     &#8216;I think you&#8217;ve always been fair.&#8217; &#8211; President Donald J. Trump, in a call to Bob Woodward, August 14, 2018</p>
<p>                     &#8216;The sheer weight of anecdotes depicts a man with no empathy and a pathological capacity for lying.&#8217; &#8211; The Financial Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fuelling his narrative is an astonishing cast of rogues, ideologues, self-made millionaires and men in uniform who have spent the past two years in and out of Trump&#8217;s administration.&#8217; &#8211; The Sunday Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Woodward&#8217;s meticulous account of office intrigues, the president&#8217;s men don&#8217;t seem to be trembling with fright.  What they mostly feel is contempt for Trump or pity for his ignorance and the &#8220;teenage logic&#8221; of his obsessively vented grievances.&#8217; &#8211; The Observer</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Horribly fascinating. Strongly recommended. If you can bear it.&#8217; Richard Dawkins</p>
<p>                     &#8216;To me the standout message from the book&#8230;is that the president is a bit clueless, a bit vain, a bit dangerous even; but his people are utterly at sea&#8230;&#8217; &#8211; Justin Webb, The Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;He is the master and I&#8217;d trust him over politicians of either party any day of the week.&#8217; -Peter Baker, New York Times</p>
<p>                     &#8216;His work has been factually unassailable . . . In an age of &#8216;alternative facts&#8217; and corrosive tweets about &#8216;fake news,&#8217; Woodward is truth&#8217;s gold standard.&#8217; &#8211; Jill Abramson, The Washington Post</p>
<p>                     &#8216;Fear depicts a White House awash in dysfunction, where the Lord of the Flies is the closest thing to an owner&#8217;s manual.&#8217; The Guardian</p>
<p>                     &#8216;I wonder how many journalists have arrived in Washington over the years dreaming of becoming the next Bob Woodward . . . Though his books are often sensational, he is the opposite of sensationalist. He&#8217;s diligent, rigorous, fastidious about the facts, and studiously ethical. There&#8217;s something almost monastic about his method . . . He&#8217;s Washington&#8217;s chronicler in chief.&#8217; &#8211;  Nick Bryant, BBC</p>
<p>                     &#8216;I&#8217;ve been on the receiving end of a Bob Woodward book. There were quotes in it I didn&#8217;t like. But never once-never-did I think Woodward made it up. Anonymous sources have looser lips and may take liberties. But Woodward always plays is straight. Someone told it to him.&#8217; &#8211; Ari Fleisher, White House Press Secretary for George W. Bush</p>
<p>                     With authoritative reporting honed through eight presidencies from Nixon to Obama, author Bob Woodward reveals in unprecedented detail the harrowing life inside President Donald Trump&#8217;s White House and precisely how he makes decisions on major foreign and domestic policies. Woodward draws from hundreds of hours of interviews with firsthand sources, meeting notes, personal diaries, files and documents. The focus is on the explosive debates and the decision-making in the Oval Office, the Situation Room, Air Force One and the White House residence.</p>
<p>                    Fear is the most intimate portrait of a sitting president ever published during the president&#8217;s first years in office.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fear-trump-in-the-white-house-bob-woodward/">Fear : Trump in the White House &#8211; Bob Woodward</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Utopia Experiment &#8211; Dylan Evans</title>
		<link>/the-utopia-experiment-dylan-evans/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-utopia-experiment-dylan-evans/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As read on BBC Radio 4&#8217;s Book of the Week. Imagine you have survived an apocalypse. Civilization as you knew it is no more. What will life be like and how will you cope? In 2006, Dylan Evans set out to answer these questions. He left his job in a high-tech robotics lab, moved to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-utopia-experiment-dylan-evans/">The Utopia Experiment &#8211; Dylan Evans</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As read on BBC Radio 4&#8217;s Book of the Week.</p>
<p>                    Imagine you have survived an apocalypse. Civilization as you knew it is no more. What will life be like and how will you cope?</p>
<p>                    In 2006, Dylan Evans set out to answer these questions. He left his job in a high-tech robotics lab, moved to the Scottish Highlands and founded a community called The Utopia Experiment. There, together with an eclectic assortment of volunteers, he tried to live out a scenario of global collapse, free from modern technology and comforts. </p>
<p>                    Within a year, Evans found himself detained in a psychiatric hospital, shattered and depressed, trying to figure out what had gone wrong. In The Utopia Experiment he tells his own extraordinary story: his frenzied early enthusiasm for this unusual project, the many challenges of post-apocalyptic living, his descent into madness and his gradual recovery. In the process, he learns some hard lessons about himself and about life, and comes to see the modern world he abandoned in a new light.</p>
<p>                    &#8216;A gripping, slow-motion car crash. You can&#8217;t take your eyes off it&#8217; Julian Baggini, Financial Times</p>
<p>                    &#8216;It radiates an intense intelligence and a candour that is never less than touching and, sometimes, downright heartrending&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Extraordinary . . . both frightening and compelling&#8217; GQ</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-utopia-experiment-dylan-evans/">The Utopia Experiment &#8211; Dylan Evans</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>12 Rules for Life : An Antidote to Chaos &#8211; Jordan B. Peterson</title>
		<link>/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 Sunday Times bestseller from &#8216;the most influential public intellectual in the Western world right now&#8217; (New York Times) &#8211; now in paperback. How should we live properly in a world of chaos and uncertainty? Jordan Peterson has helped millions of people, young and old, men and women, aim at a life of responsibility [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson/">12 Rules for Life : An Antidote to Chaos &#8211; Jordan B. Peterson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 Sunday Times bestseller from &#8216;the most influential public intellectual in the Western world right now&#8217; (New York Times) &#8211; now in paperback.    </p>
<p>                    How should we live properly in a world of chaos and uncertainty?    </p>
<p>                    Jordan Peterson has helped millions of people, young and old, men and women, aim at a life of responsibility and meaning. Now he can help you.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his own work as a clinical psychologist and on lessons from humanity&#8217;s oldest myths and stories, Peterson offers twelve profound and realistic principles to live by. After all, as he reminds us, we each have a vital role to play in the unfolding destiny of the world.    </p>
<p>                    Deep, rewarding and enlightening, 12 Rules for Life is a lifeboat built solidly for stormy seas: ancient wisdom applied to our contemporary problems.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson/">12 Rules for Life : An Antidote to Chaos &#8211; Jordan B. Peterson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enlightenment Now : The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress &#8211; Steven Pinker</title>
		<link>/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Enlightenment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP TEN SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Bristles with pure, crystalline intelligence, deep knowledge and human sympathy&#8217; Richard Dawkins Is modernity really failing? Or have we failed to appreciate progress and the ideals that make it possible? If you follow the headlines, the world in the 21st century appears to be sinking into chaos, hatred, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/">Enlightenment Now : The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP TEN SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Bristles with pure, crystalline intelligence, deep knowledge and human sympathy&#8217; Richard Dawkins  </p>
<p>                    Is modernity really failing? Or have we failed to appreciate progress and the ideals that make it possible?</p>
<p>                    If  you follow the headlines, the world in the 21st century appears to be  sinking into chaos, hatred, and irrationality. Yet Steven Pinker shows  that this is an illusion &#8211; a symptom of historical amnesia and  statistical fallacies. If you follow the trendlines rather than the  headlines, you discover that our lives have become longer, healthier,  safer, happier, more peaceful, more stimulating and more prosperous &#8211;  not just in the West, but worldwide. Such progress is no accident: it&#8217;s  the gift of a coherent and inspiring value system that many of us  embrace without even realizing it. These are the values of the  Enlightenment: of reason, science, humanism and progress.</p>
<p>                    The  challenges we face today are formidable, including inequality, climate  change, Artificial Intelligence and nuclear weapons. But the way to deal  with them is not to sink into despair or try to lurch back to a  mythical idyllic past; it&#8217;s to treat them as problems we can solve, as  we have solved other problems in the past. In making the case for an  Enlightenment newly recharged for the 21st century, Pinker shows how we  can use our faculties of reason and sympathy to solve the problems that  inevitably come with being products of evolution in an indifferent  universe. We will never have a perfect world, but &#8211; defying the chorus  of fatalism and reaction &#8211; we can continue to make it a better one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/">Enlightenment Now : The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Years of Rice and Salt : A Novel &#8211; Kim Stanley Robinson</title>
		<link>/the-years-of-rice-and-salt-a-novel-kim-stanley-robinson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Adventure Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Contemporary Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Fiction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-years-of-rice-and-salt-a-novel-kim-stanley-robinson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With the same unique vision that brought his now classic Mars trilogy to vivid life, bestselling author Kim Stanley Robinson boldly imagines an alternate history of the last seven hundred years. In his grandest work yet, the acclaimed storyteller constructs a world vastly different from the one we know. . . . &#8220;A thoughtful, magisterial [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-years-of-rice-and-salt-a-novel-kim-stanley-robinson/">The Years of Rice and Salt : A Novel &#8211; Kim Stanley Robinson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the same unique vision that brought his now classic Mars trilogy to vivid life, bestselling author Kim Stanley Robinson boldly imagines an alternate history of the last seven hundred years. In his grandest work yet, the acclaimed storyteller constructs a world vastly different from the one we know. . . . </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A thoughtful, magisterial alternate history from one of science fiction&#8217;s most important writers.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review  </p>
<p>                    It is the fourteenth century and one of the most apocalyptic events in human history is set to occur&#8211;the coming of the Black Death. History teaches us that a third of Europe&#8217;s population was destroyed. But what if the plague had killed 99 percent of the population instead? How would the world have changed? This is a look at the history that could have been&#8211;one that stretches across centuries, sees dynasties and nations rise and crumble, and spans horrible famine and magnificent innovation. </p>
<p>                    Through the eyes of soldiers and kings, explorers and philosophers, slaves and scholars, Robinson navigates a world where Buddhism and Islam are the most influential and practiced religions, while Christianity is merely a historical footnote. Probing the most profound questions as only he can, Robinson shines his extraordinary light on the place of religion, culture, power&#8211;and even love&#8211;in this bold New World.</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Exceptional and engrossing.&#8221;&#8211;New York Post</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Ambitious . . . ingenious.&#8221;&#8211;Newsday</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-years-of-rice-and-salt-a-novel-kim-stanley-robinson/">The Years of Rice and Salt : A Novel &#8211; Kim Stanley Robinson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</title>
		<link>/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>As President Trump&#8217;s National Security Advisor, John Bolton spent many of his 453 days in the room where it happened, and the facts speak for themselves. The result is a White House memoir that is the most comprehensive and substantial account of the Trump Administration, and one of the few to date by a top-level [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/">The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As President Trump&#8217;s National Security Advisor, John Bolton spent many of his 453 days in the room where it happened, and the facts speak for themselves. </p>
<p>                    The result is a White House memoir that is the most comprehensive and substantial account of the Trump Administration, and one of the few to date by a top-level official. With almost daily access to the President, John Bolton has produced a precise rendering of his days in and around the Oval Office. What Bolton saw astonished him: a President for whom getting reelected was the only thing that mattered, even if it meant endangering or weakening the nation. &#8220;I am hard-pressed to identify any significant Trump decision during my tenure that wasn&#8217;t driven by reelection calculations,&#8221; he writes. In fact, he argues that the House committed impeachment malpractice by keeping their prosecution focused narrowly on Ukraine when Trump&#8217;s Ukraine-like transgressions existed across the full range of his foreign policy-and Bolton documents exactly what those were, and attempts by him and others in the Administration to raise alarms about them.</p>
<p>                    He shows a President addicted to chaos, who embraced our enemies and spurned our friends, and was deeply suspicious of his own government. In Bolton&#8217;s telling, all this helped put Trump on the bizarre road to impeachment. &#8220;The differences between this presidency and previous ones I had served were stunning,&#8221; writes Bolton, who worked for Reagan, Bush 41, and Bush 43. He discovered a President who thought foreign policy is like closing a real estate deal-about personal relationships, made-for-TV showmanship, and advancing his own interests. As a result, the US lost an opportunity to confront its deepening threats, and in cases like China, Russia, Iran, and North Korea ended up in a more vulnerable place. </p>
<p>                    Bolton&#8217;s account starts with his long march to the West Wing as Trump and others woo him for the National Security job. The minute he lands, he has to deal with Syria&#8217;s chemical attack on the city of Douma, and the crises after that never stop. As he writes in the opening pages, &#8220;If you don&#8217;t like turmoil, uncertainty, and risk-all the while being constantly overwhelmed with information, decisions to be made, and sheer amount of work-and enlivened by international and domestic personality and ego conflicts beyond description, try something else.&#8221; </p>
<p>                    The turmoil, conflicts, and egos are all there-from the upheaval in Venezuela, to the erratic and manipulative moves of North Korea&#8217;s Kim Jong Un, to the showdowns at the G7 summits, the calculated warmongering by Iran, the crazy plan to bring the Taliban to Camp David, and the placating of an authoritarian China that ultimately exposed the world to its lethal lies. But this seasoned public servant also has a great eye for the Washington inside game, and his story is full of wit and wry humor about how he saw it played.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-room-where-it-happened-a-white-house-memoir-john-bolton/">The Room Where It Happened : A White House Memoir &#8211; John Bolton</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teaching Resources & Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Times book of the year A Guardian book of the year &#8216;Magnificent&#8217;The Times &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; New Statesman &#8216;It filled me with hope&#8217; Zadie Smith What happens to our behaviour when we live most of our lives online? What does it mean to &#8216;always be optimising&#8217;? And what is it about scams and the millennial generation? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/">Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Times book of the year<br />
                              A Guardian book of the year<br />
                              &#8216;Magnificent&#8217;The Times<br />
                              &#8216;Dazzling&#8217; New Statesman<br />
                              &#8216;It filled me with hope&#8217; Zadie Smith<br />
                              What happens to our behaviour when we live most of our lives online? What does it mean to &#8216;always be optimising&#8217;? And what is it about scams and the millennial generation?    </p>
<p>                              Offering nuanced and witty reflections on feminism, reality TV, the internet, drugs, identity and more, Trick Mirror is a multifaceted, thought-provoking and entertaining response to our zeitgeist &#8211; a must-read for anyone interested in the way we live and think today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trick-mirror-reflections-on-self-delusion-jia-tolentino-abridged/">Trick Mirror : Reflections on Self-Delusion &#8211; Jia Tolentino (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Philosophy for Life : And other dangerous situations &#8211; Jules Evans (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/philosophy-for-life-and-other-dangerous-situations-jules-evans-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/philosophy-for-life-and-other-dangerous-situations-jules-evans-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his engaging book, Jules Evans explains how ancient philosophy saved his life, and how we can all use it to become happier, wiser and more resilient. Jules imagines a dream school, which includes 12 of the greatest and most colourful thinkers the world has ever known. Each of these ancient philosophers teaches a technique [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/philosophy-for-life-and-other-dangerous-situations-jules-evans-abridged/">Philosophy for Life : And other dangerous situations &#8211; Jules Evans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his engaging book, Jules Evans explains how ancient philosophy saved his life, and how we can all use it to become happier, wiser and more resilient. Jules imagines a dream school, which includes 12 of the greatest and most colourful thinkers the world has ever known.      </p>
<p>                    Each of these ancient philosophers teaches a technique we can use to transform ourselves and live better lives. These practical techniques are illustrated by the extraordinary stories of real people who are using them today &#8211; from marines to magicians, from astronauts to anarchists and from CBT psychologists to soldiers. Jules also explores how ancient philosophy is inspiring modern communities &#8211; Socratic cafes, Stoic armies, Platonic sects, Sceptic summer camps &#8211; and even whole nations in their quest for the good life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/philosophy-for-life-and-other-dangerous-situations-jules-evans-abridged/">Philosophy for Life : And other dangerous situations &#8211; Jules Evans (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Justice : What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? &#8211; Michael J. Sandel (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/justice-whats-the-right-thing-to-do-michael-j-sandel-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/justice-whats-the-right-thing-to-do-michael-j-sandel-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michael Sandel&#8217;s Justice: What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? invites readers of all ages and political persuasions on a journey of moral reflection, and shows how reasoned debate can illuminate our lives. Is it always wrong to lie? Should there be limits to personal freedom? Can killing sometimes be justified? Is the free market fair? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/justice-whats-the-right-thing-to-do-michael-j-sandel-abridged/">Justice : What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? &#8211; Michael J. Sandel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michael Sandel&#8217;s Justice: What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? invites readers of all ages and political persuasions on a journey of moral reflection, and shows how reasoned debate can illuminate our lives.    </p>
<p>                    Is it always wrong to lie?<br />
                    Should there be limits to personal freedom?<br />
                    Can killing sometimes be justified?<br />
                    Is the free market fair?<br />
                    What is the right thing to do?    </p>
<p>                    Questions like these are at the heart of our lives. In this acclaimed book Michael Sandel &#8211; BBC Reith Lecturer and the Harvard professor whose &#8216;Justice&#8217; course has become world famous &#8211; gives us a lively and accessible introduction to the intersection of politics and philosophy. He helps us think our way through such hotly contested issues as equal rights, democracy, euthanasia, abortion and same-sex marriage, as well as the ethical dilemmas we face every day.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the most popular teachers in the world&#8217; &#8211; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Enormously refreshing &#8230; Michael Sandel transforms moral philosophy by putting it at the heart of civic debate&#8217; &#8211; New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the world&#8217;s most interesting political philosophers&#8217; &#8211; Guardian    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Spellbinding&#8217; &#8211; The Nation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/justice-whats-the-right-thing-to-do-michael-j-sandel-abridged/">Justice : What&#8217;s the Right Thing to Do? &#8211; Michael J. Sandel (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Distinction : A Social Critique of the Judgement of Taste &#8211; Pierre Bourdieu (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/distinction-a-social-critique-of-the-judgement-of-taste-pierre-bourdieu-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/distinction-a-social-critique-of-the-judgement-of-taste-pierre-bourdieu-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>No judgement of taste is innocent &#8211; we are all snobs. Pierre Bourdieu&#8217;s Distinction brilliantly illuminates the social pretentions of the middle classes in the modern world, focusing on the tastes and preferences of the French bourgeoisie. First published in 1979, the book is at once a vast ethnography of contemporary France and a dissection [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/distinction-a-social-critique-of-the-judgement-of-taste-pierre-bourdieu-abridged/">Distinction : A Social Critique of the Judgement of Taste &#8211; Pierre Bourdieu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>No judgement of taste is innocent &#8211; we are all snobs. Pierre Bourdieu&#8217;s Distinction brilliantly illuminates the social pretentions of the middle classes in the modern world, focusing on the tastes and preferences of the French bourgeoisie. First published in 1979, the book is at once a vast ethnography of contemporary France and a dissection of the bourgeois mind.     </p>
<p>                    In the course of everyday life we constantly choose between what we find aesthetically pleasing, and what we consider tacky, merely trendy, or ugly. Taste is not pure. Bourdieu demonstrates that our different aesthetic choices are all distinctions &#8211; that is, choices made in opposition to those made by other classes. This fascinating work argues that the social world functions simultaneously as a system of power relations and as a symbolic system in which minute distinctions of taste become the basis for social judgement.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/distinction-a-social-critique-of-the-judgement-of-taste-pierre-bourdieu-abridged/">Distinction : A Social Critique of the Judgement of Taste &#8211; Pierre Bourdieu (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asian History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colonialism & Imperialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Historiography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Middle Eastern History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[National Liberation & Independence, Post-colonialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The seminal work that has redefined our understanding of colonialism and empire, with a preface by the author &#8216;Stimulating, elegant and pugnacious&#8217; Observer &#8216;Magisterial&#8217; Terry Eagleton In this highly-acclaimed work, Edward Said surveys the history and nature of Western attitudes towards the East, considering orientalism as a powerful European ideological creation &#8211; a way for [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/">Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The seminal work that has redefined our  understanding of colonialism and empire, with a preface by the author    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Stimulating, elegant and pugnacious&#8217; Observer<br />
                    &#8216;Magisterial&#8217; Terry Eagleton    </p>
<p>                    In this  highly-acclaimed work, Edward Said surveys the history and nature of  Western attitudes towards the East, considering orientalism as a  powerful European ideological creation &#8211; a way for writers, philosophers  and colonial administrators to deal with the &#8216;otherness&#8217; of eastern  culture, customs and beliefs. He traces this view through the writings  of Homer, Nerval and Flaubert, Disraeli and Kipling, whose imaginative  depictions have greatly contributed to the West&#8217;s romantic and exotic  picture of the Orient. Drawing on his own experiences as an Arab  Palestinian living in the West, Said examines how these ideas can be a  reflection of European imperialism and racism.<br />
                    &#8216;Beautifully patterned and passionately argued&#8217;<br />
                    New Statesman    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Very exciting &#8230; his case is not merely persuasive, but conclusive&#8217;<br />
                    John Leonard, New York Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/orientalism-edward-w-said-abridged/">Orientalism &#8211; Edward W. Said (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rebel Ideas : The Power of Thinking Differently &#8211; Matthew Syed, Matthew Syed Consulting Ltd (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rebel-ideas-the-power-of-thinking-differently-matthew-syed-matthew-syed-consulting-ltd-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Ideas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rebel-ideas-the-power-of-thinking-differently-matthew-syed-matthew-syed-consulting-ltd-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>I like listening to people who know things that I don&#8217;t,&#8217; Gareth Southgate told me. &#8216;That&#8217;s how you learn.&#8217; Former Olympian and best-selling author Matthew Syed is one of the advisors Gareth Southgate engaged from outside football in order to find new ways of working as a team. In Rebel Ideas, discover how Southgate &#8216;the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rebel-ideas-the-power-of-thinking-differently-matthew-syed-matthew-syed-consulting-ltd-abridged/">Rebel Ideas : The Power of Thinking Differently &#8211; Matthew Syed, Matthew Syed Consulting Ltd (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I like listening to people who know things that I don&#8217;t,&#8217; Gareth Southgate told me. &#8216;That&#8217;s how you learn.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    Former Olympian and best-selling author Matthew Syed is one of the advisors Gareth Southgate engaged from outside football in order to find new ways of working as a team. In Rebel Ideas, discover how Southgate &#8216;the man with the plan&#8217; replaced 50 years of hurt with two major tournament semi-finals in three years.&#8217;     </p>
<p>                    Matthew Syed&#8217;s phenomenal bestseller will change the way you think about success &#8211; for ever.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Syed is a superb storyteller. I couldn&#8217;t put the book down, and I learned so much. A stunning achievement&#8217; Tim Harford, author of The Undercover Economist    </p>
<p>                    Rebel Ideas examines the power of &#8216;cognitive diversity&#8217; &#8211; the ability to think differently about the world around us.    </p>
<p>                    It explains how to harness our unique perspectives, pool our collective intelligence and tackle the greatest challenges of our age &#8211; from climate change to terrorism. It draws on a dazzling range of case studies, including the catastrophic failings of the CIA before 9/11, a fatal communication breakdown on top of Mount Everest and a moving tale of deradicalisation in America&#8217;s Deep South.    </p>
<p>                    Rebel Ideas will strengthen any team or organisation, but has dozens of individual applications, too: from the art of reinvention to the remarkable benefits of personalised nutrition. It shows us how to become more creative, how to collaborate in a world becoming more interconnected, and how to break free of echo chambers that surround us all.    </p>
<p>                    Now updated with a new chapter on the Covid-19 crisis    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A gripping read, full of intelligence and perspective&#8217; James Dyson    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Will change the way you think about success and even about life&#8217; Judy Murray    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A master of the genre&#8217; The Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rebel-ideas-the-power-of-thinking-differently-matthew-syed-matthew-syed-consulting-ltd-abridged/">Rebel Ideas : The Power of Thinking Differently &#8211; Matthew Syed, Matthew Syed Consulting Ltd (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Man, the State, and War : A Theoretical Analysis &#8211; Kenneth Waltz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Peace Studies & Conflict Resolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What are the causes of war? To answer this question, Professor Waltz examines the ideas of major thinkers throughout the history of Western civilization. He explores works both by classic political philosophers, such as St. Augustine, Hobbes, Kant, and Rousseau, and by modern psychologists and anthropologists to discover ideas intended to explain war among states [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/">Man, the State, and War : A Theoretical Analysis &#8211; Kenneth Waltz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What are the causes of war? To answer this question, Professor Waltz examines the ideas of major thinkers throughout the history of Western civilization. He explores works both by classic political philosophers, such as St. Augustine, Hobbes, Kant, and Rousseau, and by modern psychologists and anthropologists to discover ideas intended to explain war among states and related prescriptions for peace.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/man-the-state-and-war-a-theoretical-analysis-kenneth-waltz-abridged/">Man, the State, and War : A Theoretical Analysis &#8211; Kenneth Waltz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anarchism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Colin Ward (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/anarchism-a-very-short-introduction-colin-ward-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anarchism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/anarchism-a-very-short-introduction-colin-ward-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The word &#8216;anarchism&#8217; tends to conjure up images of aggressive protest against government, and &#8211; recently &#8211; of angry demonstrations against bodies such as the World Bank and the International Monetary Fund. But is anarchism inevitably linked with violent disorder? Do anarchists adhere to a coherent ideology? What exactly is anarchism? In this Very Short [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anarchism-a-very-short-introduction-colin-ward-abridged/">Anarchism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Colin Ward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The word &#8216;anarchism&#8217; tends to conjure up images of aggressive protest against government, and &#8211; recently &#8211; of angry demonstrations against bodies such as the World Bank and the International Monetary Fund. But is anarchism inevitably linked with violent disorder? Do anarchists adhere to a coherent ideology? What exactly is anarchism?    </p>
<p>                    In this Very Short Introduction, Colin Ward considers anarchism from a variety of perspectives: theoretical, historical, and international, and by exploring key anarchist thinkers from Kropotkin to Chomsky. He looks critically at anarchism by evaluating key ideas within it, such as its blanket opposition to incarceration, and policy of &#8216;no compromise&#8217; with the apparatus of political decision-making. Among the questions he ponders are: can anarchy ever function effectively as a political force?<br />
                    Is it more &#8216;organized&#8217; and &#8216;reasonable&#8217; than is currently perceived? Whatever the politics of the reader, Ward&#8217;s argument ensures that anarchism will be much better understood after reading this book.    </p>
<p>                    ABOUT THE SERIES: The Very Short Introductions series from Oxford University Press contains hundreds of titles in almost every subject area. These pocket-sized books are the perfect way to get ahead in a new subject quickly. Our expert authors combine facts, analysis, perspective, new ideas, and enthusiasm to make interesting and challenging topics highly readable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anarchism-a-very-short-introduction-colin-ward-abridged/">Anarchism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Colin Ward (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Vindication of the Rights of Woman (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Mary Wollstonecraft (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Discover Wollstonecraft&#8217;s classic feminist text in an abridged, digestible form. WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY ZOE WILLIAMS The term feminism did not yet exist when Mary Wollstonecraft wrote this book, but it was the first great piece of feminist writing. In these pages you will find the essence of her argument &#8211; for the education of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/">A Vindication of the Rights of Woman (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Mary Wollstonecraft (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Discover Wollstonecraft&#8217;s classic feminist text in an abridged, digestible form.    </p>
<p>                    WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY ZOE WILLIAMS     </p>
<p>                    The term feminism did not yet exist when Mary Wollstonecraft wrote this book, but it was the first great piece of feminist writing. In these pages you will find the essence of her argument &#8211; for the education of women and for an increased female contribution to society. Her work made the first ripples of what would later become the tidal wave of the women&#8217;s rights movement. Rationalist but revolutionary, Wollstonecraft changed the world for women.    </p>
<p>                    Vintage Feminism: classic feminist texts in short form</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/">A Vindication of the Rights of Woman (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Mary Wollstonecraft (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Consumerism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ecological Science, The Biosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmentalist Thought & Ideology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Macroeconomics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology: Work & Labour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How does our economic system impact the way we live? Does it really affect what we truly care about? Oxford economist E. F. Schumacher provides an enlightening study of our economic system and its purpose, challenging the current state of excessive consumption in our society. Offering a crucial message for the modern world struggling to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/">Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How does our economic system impact the way we live? Does it really affect what we truly care about?     </p>
<p>                    Oxford economist E. F. Schumacher provides an enlightening study of our economic system and its purpose, challenging the current state of excessive consumption in our society. Offering a crucial message for the modern world struggling to balance economic growth with the human costs of globalisation, Small Is Beautiful puts forward the revolutionary yet viable case for building our economies around the needs of communities, not corporations.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the 100 most influential books published since World War II&#8217; The Times Literary Supplement</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/small-is-beautiful-a-study-of-economics-as-if-people-mattered-e-f-schumacher-abridged/">Small Is Beautiful : A Study of Economics as if People Mattered &#8211; E F Schumacher (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Discipline and Punish : The Birth of the Prison &#8211; Michel Foucault (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/discipline-and-punish-the-birth-of-the-prison-michel-foucault-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Penology & Punishment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy, From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/discipline-and-punish-the-birth-of-the-prison-michel-foucault-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this brilliant work, the most influential philosopher since Sartre suggests that such vaunted reforms as the abolition of torture and the emergence of the modern penitentiary have merely shifted the focus of punishment from the prisoner&#8217;s body to his soul.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discipline-and-punish-the-birth-of-the-prison-michel-foucault-abridged/">Discipline and Punish : The Birth of the Prison &#8211; Michel Foucault (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this brilliant work, the most influential philosopher since Sartre suggests that such vaunted reforms as the abolition of torture and the emergence of the modern penitentiary have merely shifted the focus of punishment from the prisoner&#8217;s body to his soul.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/discipline-and-punish-the-birth-of-the-prison-michel-foucault-abridged/">Discipline and Punish : The Birth of the Prison &#8211; Michel Foucault (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>12 Rules for Life : An Antidote to Chaos &#8211; Jordan B. Peterson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The #1 Sunday Times bestseller from &#8216;the most influential public intellectual in the Western world right now&#8217; (New York Times) &#8211; now in paperback. How should we live properly in a world of chaos and uncertainty? Jordan Peterson has helped millions of people, young and old, men and women, aim at a life of responsibility [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson-abridged/">12 Rules for Life : An Antidote to Chaos &#8211; Jordan B. Peterson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The #1 Sunday Times bestseller from &#8216;the most influential public intellectual in the Western world right now&#8217; (New York Times) &#8211; now in paperback.    </p>
<p>                    How should we live properly in a world of chaos and uncertainty?    </p>
<p>                    Jordan Peterson has helped millions of people, young and old, men and women, aim at a life of responsibility and meaning. Now he can help you.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his own work as a clinical psychologist and on lessons from humanity&#8217;s oldest myths and stories, Peterson offers twelve profound and realistic principles to live by. After all, as he reminds us, we each have a vital role to play in the unfolding destiny of the world.    </p>
<p>                    Deep, rewarding and enlightening, 12 Rules for Life is a lifeboat built solidly for stormy seas: ancient wisdom applied to our contemporary problems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/12-rules-for-life-an-antidote-to-chaos-jordan-b-peterson-abridged/">12 Rules for Life : An Antidote to Chaos &#8211; Jordan B. Peterson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Be an Antiracist &#8211; Ibram X. Kendi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-an-antiracist-ibram-x-kendi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-an-antiracist-ibram-x-kendi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**THE GLOBAL MILLION-COPY BESTSELLER** NOT BEING RACIST IS NOT ENOUGH. WE HAVE TO BE ANTIRACIST. &#8216;Transformative and revolutionary&#8217; ROBIN DIANGELO, author of White Fragility &#8216;So vital&#8217; IJEOMA OLUO, author of So You Want to Talk About Race In this rousing and deeply empathetic book, Ibram X. Kendi, one of the world&#8217;s most influential scholars of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-an-antiracist-ibram-x-kendi-abridged/">How To Be an Antiracist &#8211; Ibram X. Kendi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**THE GLOBAL MILLION-COPY BESTSELLER**    </p>
<p>                    NOT BEING RACIST IS NOT ENOUGH. WE HAVE TO BE ANTIRACIST.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Transformative and revolutionary&#8217; ROBIN DIANGELO, author of White Fragility    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;So vital&#8217; IJEOMA OLUO, author of So You Want to Talk About Race    </p>
<p>                     In this rousing and deeply empathetic book, Ibram X. Kendi, one of the world&#8217;s most influential scholars of racism, shows that neutrality is not an option: until we become part of the solution, we can only be part of the problem.    </p>
<p>                     Using his extraordinary gifts as a teacher and story-teller, Kendi helps us recognise that everyone is, at times, complicit in racism whether they realise it or not, and by describing with moving humility his own journey from racism to antiracism, he shows us how instead to be a force for good. Along the way, Kendi punctures all the myths and taboos that so often cloud our understanding, from arguments about what race is and whether racial differences exist to the complications that arise when race intersects with ethnicity, class, gender and sexuality.    </p>
<p>                     In the process he demolishes the myth of the post-racial society and builds from the ground up a vital new understanding of racism &#8211; what it is, where it is hidden, how to identify it and what to do about it.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The most courageous book to date on the problem of race&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It feels like a light switch being flicked on&#8217; OWEN JONES</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-an-antiracist-ibram-x-kendi-abridged/">How To Be an Antiracist &#8211; Ibram X. Kendi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Status Anxiety &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/status-anxiety-alain-de-botton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/status-anxiety-alain-de-botton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER From one of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy, Religion for Atheists and The School of Life &#8211; Alain de Botton sets out to understand our universal fear of failure &#8211; and how we might change it &#8216;De Botton&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/status-anxiety-alain-de-botton-abridged/">Status Anxiety &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    From one of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy, Religion for Atheists and The School of Life &#8211; Alain de Botton sets out to understand our universal fear of failure &#8211; and how we might change it    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;De Botton&#8217;s gift is to prompt us to think about how we live and how we might change things&#8217;  The Times     </p>
<p>                    We all worry about what others think of us. We all long to succeed and fear failure. We all suffer &#8211; to a greater or lesser degree, usually privately and with embarrassment &#8211; from status anxiety.     </p>
<p>                    Alain de Botton gives a name to this universal condition and sets out to investigate both its origins and possible solutions. He looks at history, philosophy, economics, art and politics &#8211; and reveals the many ingenious ways that great minds have overcome their worries. The result is a book that is not only entertaining and thought-provoking &#8211; but genuinely wise and helpful as well.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;He analyses modern society with great charm, learning and humour. His remedies come as a welcome relief when most books offering solutions to the stresses of life recommend the lotus position&#8217; Daily Mail</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/status-anxiety-alain-de-botton-abridged/">Status Anxiety &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>First as Tragedy, Then as Farce &#8211; Slavoj Zizek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/first-as-tragedy-then-as-farce-slavoj-zizek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Phenomenology & Existentialism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Issues & Processes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/first-as-tragedy-then-as-farce-slavoj-zizek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Billions of dollars were hastily poured into the global banking system in a frantic attempt at financial stabilisation. So why has it not been possible to bring the same forces to bear in addressing world poverty and environmental crisis? In this take-no-prisoners analysis, Slavoj Zizek frames the moral failures of the modern world in terms [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-as-tragedy-then-as-farce-slavoj-zizek-abridged/">First as Tragedy, Then as Farce &#8211; Slavoj Zizek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Billions of dollars were hastily poured into the global banking system in a frantic attempt at financial stabilisation. So why has it not been possible to bring the same forces to bear in addressing world poverty and environmental crisis? In this take-no-prisoners analysis, Slavoj Zizek frames the moral failures of the modern world in terms of the epoch-making events of the first decade of this century. What he finds is the old one-two punch of history: the jab of tragedy, the right hook of farce. In the attacks of 9/11 and the global credit crunch, liberalism dies twice: as a political doctrine and as an economic theory. The election of Donald Trump only confirms the bankruptcy of a liberal order on its last legs. First as Tragedy, Then as Farce is a call for the left to reinvent itself in the light of our desperate historical situation. The time for liberal, moralistic blackmail is over.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/first-as-tragedy-then-as-farce-slavoj-zizek-abridged/">First as Tragedy, Then as Farce &#8211; Slavoj Zizek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Second Mountain : The Quest for a Moral Life &#8211; David Brooks (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-second-mountain-the-quest-for-a-moral-life-david-brooks-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-second-mountain-the-quest-for-a-moral-life-david-brooks-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DEBUTED AT NO.1 ON THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER LIST NO.1 BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE SOCIAL ANIMAL Are you on your first or second mountain? Is life about you &#8211; or others? About success &#8211; or something deeper? The world tells us that we should pursue our self-interest: career wins, high status, nice things. These [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-second-mountain-the-quest-for-a-moral-life-david-brooks-abridged/">The Second Mountain : The Quest for a Moral Life &#8211; David Brooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>DEBUTED AT NO.1 ON THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER LIST<br />
                    NO.1 BESTSELLING AUTHOR OF THE SOCIAL ANIMAL    </p>
<p>                    Are you on your first or second mountain?<br />
                    Is life about you &#8211; or others?<br />
                    About success &#8211; or something deeper?     </p>
<p>                    The  world tells us that we should pursue our self-interest: career wins,  high status, nice things. These are the goals of our first mountain. But  at some point in our lives we might find that we&#8217;re not interested in  what other people tell us to want. We want the things that are truly  worth wanting.    </p>
<p>                    This is the second mountain.     </p>
<p>                    What does it  mean to look beyond yourself and find a moral cause? To forget about  independence and discover dependence &#8211; to be utterly enmeshed in a web  of warm relationships? What does it mean to value intimacy, devotion,  responsibility and commitment above individual freedom? In The Second Mountain  David Brooks explores the meaning and possibilities that scaling a  second mountain offer us and the four commitments that most commonly  move us there: family, vocation, philosophy and community. Inspiring,  personal and full of joy, this book will help you discover why you were  really put on this earth.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-second-mountain-the-quest-for-a-moral-life-david-brooks-abridged/">The Second Mountain : The Quest for a Moral Life &#8211; David Brooks (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Free Will &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religious Groups: Social & Cultural Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Spirituality & Religious Experience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The physiologist Benjamin Libet famously demonstrated that activity in the brain&#8217;s motor regions can be detected some 300 milliseconds before a person feels that he has decided to move. Another lab recently used fMRI data to show that some &#8220;conscious&#8221; decisions can be predicted up to 10 seconds before they enter awareness (long before the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/">Free Will &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The physiologist Benjamin Libet famously demonstrated that activity in the brain&#8217;s motor regions can be detected some 300 milliseconds before a person feels that he has decided to move. Another lab recently used fMRI data to show that some &#8220;conscious&#8221; decisions can be predicted up to 10 seconds before they enter awareness (long before the preparatory motor activity detected by Libet). Clearly, findings of this kind are difficult to reconcile with the sense that one is the conscious source of one&#8217;s actions.     </p>
<p>                    The question of free will is no mere curio of philosophy seminars. A belief in free will underwrites both the religious notion of &#8220;sin&#8221; and our enduring commitment to retributive justice. The Supreme Court has called free will a &#8220;universal and persistent&#8221; foundation for our system of law. Any scientific developments that threatened our notion of free will would seem to put the ethics of punishing people for their bad behaviour in question.In Free Will Harris debates these ideas and asks whether or not, given what brain science is telling us, we actually have free will?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/free-will-sam-harris-abridged/">Free Will &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Aristotle&#8217;s &#8220;Politics&#8221; : Second Edition &#8211; Aristotle, Translated byCarnes Lord (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/aristotles-politics-second-edition-aristotle-translated-by-carnes-lord-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Ancient, To C 500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/aristotles-politics-second-edition-aristotle-translated-by-carnes-lord-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the fundamental works of Western political thought, Aristotle&#8217;s masterwork is the first systematic treatise on the science of politics. For almost three decades, Carnes Lord&#8217;s justly acclaimed translation has served as the standard English edition. Widely regarded as the most faithful to both the original Greek and Aristotle&#8217;s distinctive style, it is also [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/aristotles-politics-second-edition-aristotle-translated-by-carnes-lord-abridged/">Aristotle&#8217;s &#8220;Politics&#8221; : Second Edition &#8211; Aristotle, Translated byCarnes Lord (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of the fundamental works of Western political thought, Aristotle&#8217;s masterwork is the first systematic treatise on the science of politics. For almost three decades, Carnes Lord&#8217;s justly acclaimed translation has served as the standard English edition. Widely regarded as the most faithful to both the original Greek and Aristotle&#8217;s distinctive style, it is also written in clear, contemporary English. This new edition of the Politics retains and adds to Lord&#8217;s already extensive notes, clarifying the flow of Aristotle&#8217;s argument and identifying literary and historical references. A glossary defines key terms in Aristotle&#8217;s philosophical-political vocabulary. Lord has made revisions to problematic passages throughout the translation in order to enhance both its accuracy and its readability. He has also substantially revised his introduction for the new edition, presenting an account of Aristotle&#8217;s life in relation to political events of his time; the character and history of his writings and of the Politics in particular; his overall conception of political science; and his impact on subsequent political thought from antiquity to the present.<br />
                    Further enhancing this new edition is an up-to-date selected bibliography.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/aristotles-politics-second-edition-aristotle-translated-by-carnes-lord-abridged/">Aristotle&#8217;s &#8220;Politics&#8221; : Second Edition &#8211; Aristotle, Translated byCarnes Lord (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Think More About Sex &#8211; Alain De Botton, The School of Life (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-think-more-about-sex-alain-de-botton-the-school-of-life-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-think-more-about-sex-alain-de-botton-the-school-of-life-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In this rigorous and supremely honest book Alain de Botton helps us navigate the intimate and exciting &#8211; yet often confusing and difficult &#8211; experience that is sex. Few of us tend to feel we&#8217;re entirely normal when it comes to sex, and what we&#8217;re supposed to be feeling rarely matches up with the reality. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-think-more-about-sex-alain-de-botton-the-school-of-life-abridged/">How To Think More About Sex &#8211; Alain De Botton, The School of Life (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In this rigorous and supremely honest book Alain de Botton helps us navigate the intimate and exciting &#8211; yet often confusing and difficult &#8211; experience that is sex. Few of us tend to feel we&#8217;re entirely normal when it comes to sex, and what we&#8217;re supposed to be feeling rarely matches up with the reality. This book argues that 21st-century sex is ultimately fated to be a balancing act between love and desire, and adventure and commitment. Covering topics that include lust, fetishism, adultery and pornography, Alain de Botton frankly articulates the dilemmas of modern sexuality, offering insights and consolation to help us think more deeply and wisely about the sex we are, or aren&#8217;t, having.    </p>
<p>                     One in the new series of books from The School of Life, launched May 2012:    </p>
<p>                     How to Stay Sane by Philippa Perry    </p>
<p>                     How to Find Fulfilling Work by Roman Krznaric    </p>
<p>                     How to Worry Less About Money by John Armstrong    </p>
<p>                     How to Change the World by John-Paul Flintoff    </p>
<p>                     How to Thrive in the Digital Age by Tom Chatfield    </p>
<p>                     How to Think More About Sex by Alain de Botton</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-think-more-about-sex-alain-de-botton-the-school-of-life-abridged/">How To Think More About Sex &#8211; Alain De Botton, The School of Life (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Plato: &#8216;The Republic&#8217; &#8211; Plato, Translated byTom Griffith, Edited byG. R. F. Ferrari (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/plato-the-republic-plato-translated-by-tom-griffith-edited-by-g-r-f-ferrari-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Ancient, To C 500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/plato-the-republic-plato-translated-by-tom-griffith-edited-by-g-r-f-ferrari-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>First published in 2000, this translation of one of the great works of Western political thought is based on the assumption that when Plato chose the dialogue form for his writing, he intended these dialogues to sound like conversations &#8211; although conversations of a philosophical sort. In addition to a vivid, dignified and accurate rendition [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/plato-the-republic-plato-translated-by-tom-griffith-edited-by-g-r-f-ferrari-abridged/">Plato: &#8216;The Republic&#8217; &#8211; Plato, Translated byTom Griffith, Edited byG. R. F. Ferrari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First published in 2000, this translation of one of the great works of Western political thought is based on the assumption that when Plato chose the dialogue form for his writing, he intended these dialogues to sound like conversations &#8211; although conversations of a philosophical sort. In addition to a vivid, dignified and accurate rendition of Plato&#8217;s text, the student and general reader will find many aids to comprehension in this volume: an introduction that assesses the cultural background to the Republic, its place within political philosophy, and its general argument; succinct notes in the body of the text; an analytical summary of the work&#8217;s content; a full glossary of proper names; a chronology of important events; and a guide to further reading. The result is an accomplished and accessible edition of this seminal work, suitable for philosophers and classicists as well as historians of political thought at all levels.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/plato-the-republic-plato-translated-by-tom-griffith-edited-by-g-r-f-ferrari-abridged/">Plato: &#8216;The Republic&#8217; &#8211; Plato, Translated byTom Griffith, Edited byG. R. F. Ferrari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the best-selling author of Americanah and We Should All Be Feminists comes a powerful new statement about feminism today &#8211; written as a letter to a friend. A few years ago, Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie received a letter from a dear friend from childhood, asking her how to raise her baby girl as a feminist. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the best-selling author of Americanah and We Should All Be Feminists comes a powerful new statement about feminism today &#8211; written as a letter to a friend.<br />
                              A few years ago, Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie received a letter from a dear friend from childhood, asking her how to raise her baby girl as a feminist. Dear Ijeawele is Adichie&#8217;s letter of response.    </p>
<p>                              Here are fifteen invaluable suggestions-compelling, direct, wryly funny, and perceptive-for how to empower a daughter to become a strong, independent woman. From encouraging her to choose a helicopter, and not only a doll, as a toy if she so desires; having open conversations with her about clothes, makeup, and sexuality; debunking the myth that women are somehow biologically arranged to be in the kitchen making dinner, and that men can &#8220;allow&#8221; women to have full careers, Dear Ijeawele goes right to the heart of sexual politics in the twenty-first century. It will start a new and urgently needed conversation about what it really means to be a woman today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dear-ijeawele-or-a-feminist-manifesto-in-fifteen-suggestions-chimamanda-ngozi-adichie-abridged/">Dear Ijeawele, or a Feminist Manifesto in Fifteen Suggestions &#8211; Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology, Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In a divided world, empathy is not the solution, it is the problem. We think of empathy &#8211; the ability to feel the suffering of others for ourselves &#8211; as the ultimate source of all good behaviour. But while it inspires care and protection in personal relationships, it has the opposite effect in the wider [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/">Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a divided world, empathy is not the solution, it is the problem.      </p>
<p>                    We think of empathy &#8211; the ability to feel the suffering of others for ourselves &#8211; as the ultimate source of all good behaviour. But while it inspires care and protection in personal relationships, it has the opposite effect in the wider world. As the latest research in psychology and neuroscience shows, we feel empathy most for those we find attractive and who seem similar to us and not at all for those who are different, distant or anonymous. Empathy therefore biases us in favour of individuals we know while numbing us to the plight of thousands. Guiding us expertly through the experiments, case studies and arguments on all sides, Paul Bloom ultimately shows that some of our worst decisions &#8211; in charity, child-raising, criminal justice, climate change and war &#8211; are motivated by this wolf in sheep&#8217;s clothing.     </p>
<p>                    Brilliantly argued, urgent and humane, Against Empathy overturns widely held assumptions to reveal one of the most profound yet overlooked sources of human conflict.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/against-empathy-the-case-for-rational-compassion-paul-bloom-abridged/">Against Empathy : The Case for Rational Compassion &#8211; Paul Bloom (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>To Have or To Be? &#8211; Erich Fromm (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/to-have-or-to-be-erich-fromm-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance, C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/to-have-or-to-be-erich-fromm-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>To Have Or to Be? is one of the seminal books of the second half of the 20th century. Nothing less than a manifesto for a new social and psychological revolution to save our threatened planet, this book is a summary of the penetrating thought of Eric Fromm. His thesis is that two modes of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/to-have-or-to-be-erich-fromm-abridged/">To Have or To Be? &#8211; Erich Fromm (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>To Have Or to Be? is one of the seminal books of the second half of the 20th century. Nothing less than a manifesto for a new social and psychological revolution to save our threatened planet, this book is a summary of the penetrating thought of Eric Fromm. His thesis is that two modes of existence struggle for the spirit of humankind: the having mode, which concentrates on material possessions, power, and aggression, and is the basis of the universal evils of greed, envy, and violence; and the being mode, which is based on love, the pleasure of sharing, and in productive activity. To Have Or to Be? is a brilliant program for socioeconomic change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/to-have-or-to-be-erich-fromm-abridged/">To Have or To Be? &#8211; Erich Fromm (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inventing the Future : Postcapitalism and a World Without Work &#8211; Nick Srnicek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Neoliberalism isn&#8217;t working. Austerity is forcing millions into poverty and many more into precarious work, while the left remains trapped in stagnant political practices that offer no respite. Inventing the Future is a bold new manifesto for life after capitalism. Against the confused understanding of our high-tech world by both the right and the left, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/">Inventing the Future : Postcapitalism and a World Without Work &#8211; Nick Srnicek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Neoliberalism isn&#8217;t working. Austerity is forcing millions into poverty and many more into precarious work, while the left remains trapped in stagnant political practices that offer no respite. Inventing the Future is a bold new manifesto for life after capitalism. Against the confused understanding of our high-tech world by both the right and the left, this book claims that the emancipatory and future-oriented possibilities of our society can be reclaimed. Instead of running from a complex future, Nick Srnicek and Alex Williams demand a postcapitalist economy capable of advancing standards, liberating humanity from work and developing technologies that expand our freedoms. This new edition includes a new chapter where they respond to their various critics.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/">Inventing the Future : Postcapitalism and a World Without Work &#8211; Nick Srnicek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Wellness Syndrome &#8211; Carl Cederstroem, Andre Spicer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-wellness-syndrome-carl-cederstroem-andre-spicer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance, C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-wellness-syndrome-carl-cederstroem-andre-spicer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Not exercising as much as you should? Counting your calories in your sleep? Feeling ashamed for not being happier? You may be a victim of the wellness syndrome. In this ground-breaking new book, Carl Cederstrom and Andre Spicer argue that the ever-present pressure to maximize our wellness has started to work against us, making us [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wellness-syndrome-carl-cederstroem-andre-spicer-abridged/">The Wellness Syndrome &#8211; Carl Cederstroem, Andre Spicer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Not exercising as much as you should? Counting your calories in your sleep? Feeling ashamed for not being happier? You may be a victim of the wellness syndrome. In this ground-breaking new book, Carl Cederstrom and Andre Spicer argue that the ever-present pressure to maximize our wellness has started to work against us, making us feel worse and provoking us to withdraw into ourselves. The Wellness Syndrome follows health freaks who go to extremes to find the perfect diet, corporate athletes who start the day with a dance party, and the self-trackers who monitor everything, including their own toilet habits. This is a world where feeling good has become indistinguishable from being good. Visions of social change have been reduced to dreams of individual transformation, political debate has been replaced by insipid moralising, and scientific evidence has been traded for new-age delusions. A lively and humorous diagnosis of the cult of wellness, this book is an indispensable guide for everyone suspicious of our relentless quest to be happier and healthier.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-wellness-syndrome-carl-cederstroem-andre-spicer-abridged/">The Wellness Syndrome &#8211; Carl Cederstroem, Andre Spicer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Behavioural Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the past decade, governments and corporations have become increasingly interested in measuring the way people feel: &#8216;the Happiness index&#8217;, &#8216;Gross National Happiness&#8217;, &#8216;well-being&#8217; and positive psychology have come to dominate the way we live our lives. As a result, our emotions have become a new resource to be bought and sold. In a fascinating [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/">The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the past decade, governments and corporations have become increasingly interested in measuring the way people feel: &#8216;the Happiness index&#8217;, &#8216;Gross National Happiness&#8217;, &#8216;well-being&#8217; and positive psychology have come to dominate the way we live our lives. As a result, our emotions have become a new resource to be bought and sold. In a fascinating investigation combining history, science and ideas, William Davies shows how well-being influences all aspects of our lives: business, finance, marketing and smart technology. This book will make you rethink everything from the way you work, the power of the &#8216;Nudge&#8217;, the ever-expanding definitions of depression, and the commercialization of your most private feelings. The Happiness Industry is a shocking and brilliantly argued warning about the new religion of the age: our emotions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-happiness-industry-how-the-government-and-big-business-sold-us-well-being-william-davies-abridged/">The Happiness Industry : How the Government and Big Business Sold Us Well-Being &#8211; William Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Architecture of Happiness &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-architecture-of-happiness-alain-de-botton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Architecture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interior Design, Decor & Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Professional Interior Design]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theory Of Architecture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-architecture-of-happiness-alain-de-botton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER From one of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy and The School of Life, The Architecture of Happiness explores the fascinating hidden links between the buildings we live in and our long-term wellbeing. &#8216;Engaging and intelligent . . . Full [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-architecture-of-happiness-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Architecture of Happiness &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NUMBER ONE INTERNATIONAL BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    From one of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy and The School of Life, The Architecture of Happiness explores the fascinating hidden links between the buildings we live in and our long-term wellbeing.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Engaging and intelligent . . . Full of splendid ideas, happily and beautifully expressed&#8217; Independent    </p>
<p>                    What makes a house truly beautiful? Why are many new houses so ugly? Why do we argue so bitterly about sofas and pictures &#8211; and can differences of taste ever be satisfactorily resolved?    </p>
<p>                    To answer these questions and many more, de Botton looks at buildings across the world, from medieval wooden huts to modern skyscrapers; he examines sofas and cathedrals, tea sets and office complexes, and teases out a host of often surprising philosophical insights. The Architecture of Happiness will take you on a beguiling tour through the history and psychology of architecture and interior design, and will change the way you look at your home.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Alain de Botton takes big, complex subjects and writes about them with thoughtful and deceptive innocence&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Clever, provocative and fresh as a daisy&#8217; Literary Review</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-architecture-of-happiness-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Architecture of Happiness &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance : 40th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Robert Pirsig (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Classic Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Motorcycles]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oriental & Indian Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zen Buddhism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed as one of the most exciting books in the history of American letters, this modern epic became an instant bestseller upon publication in 1974, transforming a generation and continuing to inspire millions. A narration of a summer motorcycle trip undertaken by a father and his son, the book becomes a personal and philosophical odyssey [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/">Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance : 40th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Robert Pirsig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Acclaimed as one of the most exciting books in the history of American letters, this modern epic became an instant bestseller upon publication in 1974, transforming a generation and continuing to inspire millions. A narration of a summer motorcycle trip undertaken by a father and his son, the book becomes a personal and philosophical odyssey into fundamental questions of how to live. Resonant with the confusions of existence, Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance is a touching and transcendent book of life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/zen-and-the-art-of-motorcycle-maintenance-40th-anniversary-edition-robert-pirsig-abridged/">Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance : 40th Anniversary Edition &#8211; Robert Pirsig (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Common Sense &#8211; Thomas Paine (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Among the most influential authors and reformers of his age, Thomas Paine (1737-1809) was born in England but went on to play an important role in both the American and French Revolutions. In 1774, he emigrated to America where, for a time, he helped to edit the Pennsylvania Magazine. On January 10, 1776, he published [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/">Common Sense &#8211; Thomas Paine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Among the most influential authors and reformers of his age, Thomas Paine (1737-1809) was born in England but went on to play an important role in both the American and French Revolutions. In 1774, he emigrated to America where, for a time, he helped to edit the Pennsylvania Magazine. On January 10, 1776, he published his pamphlet Common Sense,  a persuasive argument for the colonies&#8217; political and economic separation from Britain.<br />
                    Common Sense cites the evils of monarchy, accuses the British government of inflicting economic and social injustices upon the colonies, and points to the absurdity of an island attempting to rule a continent. Credited by George Washington as having changed the minds of many of his countrymen, the document sold over 500,000 copies within a few months.<br />
                    Today, Common Sense remains a landmark document in the struggle for freedom, distinguished not only by Paine&#8217;s ideas but also by its clear and passionate presentation. Designed to ignite public opinion against autocratic rule, the pamphlet offered a careful balance between imagination and judgment, and appropriate language and expression to fit the subject. It immediately found a receptive audience, heartened Washington&#8217;s despondent army, and foreshadowed much of the phrasing and substance of the Declaration of Independence.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/common-sense-thomas-paine-abridged/">Common Sense &#8211; Thomas Paine (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Locust Effect : Why the End of Poverty Requires the End of Violence &#8211; Gary A. Haugen, Victor Boutros (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-locust-effect-why-the-end-of-poverty-requires-the-end-of-violence-gary-a-haugen-victor-boutros-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Armed Conflict]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Human Rights Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Poverty & Unemployment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-locust-effect-why-the-end-of-poverty-requires-the-end-of-violence-gary-a-haugen-victor-boutros-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Washington Post bestseller While the world has made encouraging strides in the fight against global poverty, there is a hidden crisis silently undermining our best efforts to help the poor. It is a plague of everyday violence. Beneath the surface of the world&#8217;s poorest communities, common violence &#8211; like rape, forced labor, illegal detention, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-locust-effect-why-the-end-of-poverty-requires-the-end-of-violence-gary-a-haugen-victor-boutros-abridged/">The Locust Effect : Why the End of Poverty Requires the End of Violence &#8211; Gary A. Haugen, Victor Boutros (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Washington Post bestseller    </p>
<p>                    While the world has made encouraging strides in the fight against global poverty, there is a hidden crisis silently undermining our best efforts to help the poor.     </p>
<p>                    It is a plague of everyday violence.    </p>
<p>                    Beneath the surface of the world&#8217;s poorest communities, common violence &#8211; like rape, forced labor, illegal detention, land theft, police abuse and other brutality &#8211; has become routine and relentless.  And like a horde of locusts devouring everything in their path, the unchecked plague of violence ruins lives, blocks the road out of poverty, and undercuts development.     </p>
<p>                    How has this plague of violence grown so ferocious? The answer is terrifying, and startlingly simple: There&#8217;s nothing shielding the poor from violent people.  In one of the most remarkable &#8211; and unremarked upon &#8211; social disasters of the last half century, basic public justice systems in the developing world have descended into a state of utter collapse.     </p>
<p>                    Gary A. Haugen and Victor Boutros offer a searing account of how we got here &#8211; and what it will take to end the plague. Filled with vivid real-life stories and startling new data, The Locust Effect is a gripping journey into the streets and slums where fear is a daily reality for billions of the world&#8217;s poorest ,where safety is secured only for those with money, and where much of our well-intended aid is lost in the daily chaos of violence.    </p>
<p>                    While their call to action is urgent, Haugen and Boutros provide hope, a real solution and an ambitious way forward. The Locust Effect is a wake-up call: Its massive implications will forever change the way we understand global poverty &#8211; and will help secure a safe path to prosperity for the global poor in the 21st century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-locust-effect-why-the-end-of-poverty-requires-the-end-of-violence-gary-a-haugen-victor-boutros-abridged/">The Locust Effect : Why the End of Poverty Requires the End of Violence &#8211; Gary A. Haugen, Victor Boutros (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The True Believer : Thoughts on the Nature of Mass Movements &#8211; Eric Hoffer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-true-believer-thoughts-on-the-nature-of-mass-movements-eric-hoffer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Violence In Society]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-true-believer-thoughts-on-the-nature-of-mass-movements-eric-hoffer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Its theme is political fanaticism, with which it deals severely and brilliantly.&#8221; -New Yorker The famous bestseller with &#8220;concise insight into what drives the mind of the fanatic and the dynamics of a mass movement&#8221; (Wall St. Journal) by the legendary San Francisco longshoreman. A stevedore on the San Francisco docks in the 1940s, Eric [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-true-believer-thoughts-on-the-nature-of-mass-movements-eric-hoffer-abridged/">The True Believer : Thoughts on the Nature of Mass Movements &#8211; Eric Hoffer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Its theme is political fanaticism, with which it deals severely and brilliantly.&#8221;   -New Yorker    </p>
<p>                    The famous bestseller with &#8220;concise insight into what drives the mind of the fanatic and the dynamics of a mass movement&#8221; (Wall St. Journal) by the legendary San Francisco longshoreman.    </p>
<p>                    A stevedore on the San Francisco docks in the 1940s, Eric Hoffer wrote philosophical treatises in his spare time while living in the railroad yards. The True Believer-the first and most famous of his books-was made into a bestseller when President Eisenhower cited it during one of the earliest television press conferences.    </p>
<p>                    Called a &#8220;brilliant and original inquiry&#8221; and &#8220;a genuine contribution to our social thought&#8221; by Arthur Schlesinger, Jr., this landmark in the field of social psychology is completely relevant and essential for understanding the world today as it delivers a visionary, highly provocative look into the mind of the fanatic and a penetrating study of how an individual becomes one.    </p>
<p>                    In times of crisis, the great works of philosophy help us make sense of the world. This book is part of the Harper Perennial Resistance Library, a special five-book series highlighting short classic works of independent thought that illuminate the nature of truth, humanity&#8217;s dangerous attraction to authoritarianism, the influence of media and mass communication, and the philosophy of resistance-all critical in understanding today&#8217;s politically charged world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-true-believer-thoughts-on-the-nature-of-mass-movements-eric-hoffer-abridged/">The True Believer : Thoughts on the Nature of Mass Movements &#8211; Eric Hoffer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Risk : The Science and Politics of Fear &#8211; Dan Gardner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/risk-the-science-and-politics-of-fear-dan-gardner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/risk-the-science-and-politics-of-fear-dan-gardner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are the safest humans who ever lived &#8211; the statistics prove it. And yet the media tells a different story with its warnings and scare stories. How is it possible that anxiety has become the stuff of daily life? In this ground-breaking, compulsively readable book, Dan Gardner shows how our flawed strategies for perceiving [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/risk-the-science-and-politics-of-fear-dan-gardner-abridged/">Risk : The Science and Politics of Fear &#8211; Dan Gardner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We are the safest humans who ever lived &#8211; the statistics prove it. And yet the media tells a different story with its warnings and scare stories. How is it possible that anxiety has become the stuff of daily life?    </p>
<p>                    In this ground-breaking, compulsively readable book, Dan Gardner shows how our flawed strategies for perceiving risk influence our lives, often with unforeseen and sometimes-tragic consequences. He throws light on our paranoia about everything from paedophiles to terrorism and reveals how the most significant threats are actually the mundane risks to which we pay little attention.    </p>
<p>                    Speaking to psychologists and scientists, as well as looking at the influence of the media and politicians, Gardner uncovers one of the central puzzles of our time: why are the safest people in history living in a culture of fear?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/risk-the-science-and-politics-of-fear-dan-gardner-abridged/">Risk : The Science and Politics of Fear &#8211; Dan Gardner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finite and Infinite Games &#8211; James Carse (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/finite-and-infinite-games-james-carse-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Metaphysics & Ontology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/finite-and-infinite-games-james-carse-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;There are at least two kinds of games,&#8221; states James P. Carse as he begins this extraordinary book. &#8220;One could be called finite; the other infinite. A finite game is played for the purpose of winning, an infinite game for the purpose of continuing the play.&#8221; Finite games are the familiar contests of everyday life; [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finite-and-infinite-games-james-carse-abridged/">Finite and Infinite Games &#8211; James Carse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;There are at least two kinds of games,&#8221; states James P. Carse as he begins this extraordinary book. &#8220;One could be called finite; the other infinite. A finite game is played for the purpose of winning, an infinite game for the purpose of continuing the play.&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    Finite games are the familiar contests of everyday life; they are played in order to be won, which is when they end. But infinite games are more mysterious. Their object is not winning, but ensuring the continuation of play. The rules may change, the boundaries may change, even the participants may change-as long as the game is never allowed to come to an end.    </p>
<p>                     What are infinite games? How do they affect the ways we play our finite games? What are we doing when we play-finitely or infinitely? And how can infinite games affect the ways in which we live our lives?    </p>
<p>                     Carse explores these questions with stunning elegance, teasing out of his distinctions a universe of observation and insight, noting where and why and how we play, finitely and infinitely. He surveys our world-from the finite games of the playing field and playing board to the infinite games found in culture and religion-leaving all we think we know illuminated and transformed. Along the way, Carse finds new ways of understanding everything, from how an actress portrays a role to how we engage in sex, from the nature of evil to the nature of science. Finite games, he shows, may offer wealth and status, power and glory, but infinite games offer something far more subtle and far grander.    </p>
<p>                     Carse has written a book rich in insight and aphorism. Already an international literary event, Finite and Infinite Games is certain to be argued about and celebrated for years to come. Reading it is the first step in learning to play the infinite game.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/finite-and-infinite-games-james-carse-abridged/">Finite and Infinite Games &#8211; James Carse (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Second Sex (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Simone de Beauvoir, Translated byConstance Borde, Translated bySheila Malovany-Chevallier (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-second-sex-vintage-feminism-short-edition-simone-de-beauvoir-translated-by-constance-borde-translated-by-sheila-malovany-chevallier-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies, Gender Groups]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-second-sex-vintage-feminism-short-edition-simone-de-beauvoir-translated-by-constance-borde-translated-by-sheila-malovany-chevallier-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Vintage Feminism: classic feminist texts in short form WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY NATALIE HAYNES When this book was first published in 1949 it was to outrage and scandal. Never before had the case for female liberty been so forcefully and successfully argued. De Beauvoir&#8217;s belief that &#8216;One is not born, but rather becomes, woman&#8217; switched [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-second-sex-vintage-feminism-short-edition-simone-de-beauvoir-translated-by-constance-borde-translated-by-sheila-malovany-chevallier-abridged/">The Second Sex (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Simone de Beauvoir, Translated byConstance Borde, Translated bySheila Malovany-Chevallier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Vintage Feminism: classic feminist texts in short form    </p>
<p>                    WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY NATALIE HAYNES    </p>
<p>                    When this book was first published in 1949 it was to outrage and scandal. Never before had the case for female liberty been so forcefully and successfully argued. De Beauvoir&#8217;s belief that &#8216;One is not born, but rather becomes, woman&#8217; switched on light bulbs in the heads of a generation of women and began a fight for greater equality and economic independence. These pages contain the key passages of the book that changed perceptions of women forever.    </p>
<p>                    TRANSLATED BY CONSTANCE BORDE AND SHEILA MALOVANY-CHEVALLIER<br />
                    ANNOTATED AND INTRODUCED BY MARTINE REID</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-second-sex-vintage-feminism-short-edition-simone-de-beauvoir-translated-by-constance-borde-translated-by-sheila-malovany-chevallier-abridged/">The Second Sex (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Simone de Beauvoir, Translated byConstance Borde, Translated bySheila Malovany-Chevallier (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Travel &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Guidebooks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel & Holiday Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel Writing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy, From C 1900 -]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER &#8216;Honest, funny and dripping with witty aphorisms. Extremely entertaining and enlightening [&#8230;] all the way to journey&#8217;s end&#8217; Herald One of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy, Religion for Atheists and The School of Life, presents a travel guide [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Art of Travel &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE SUNDAY TIMES TOP TEN BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Honest, funny and dripping with witty aphorisms. Extremely entertaining and enlightening [&#8230;] all the way to journey&#8217;s end&#8217; Herald     </p>
<p>                    One of our greatest voices in modern philosophy, author of The Course of Love, The Consolations of Philosophy, Religion for Atheists and The School of Life, presents a travel guide with a difference &#8211; an exploration of why we travel, and what we learn along the way&#8230;    </p>
<p>                    Few activities seem to promise as much happiness as going travelling: taking off for somewhere else, somewhere far from home, a place with more interesting weather, customs and landscapes. But although we are inundated with advice on where to travel to, we seldom ask why we go and how we might become more fulfilled by doing so.    </p>
<p>                    With the help of a selection of writers, artists and thinkers &#8211; including Flaubert, Edward Hopper, Wordsworth and Van Gogh &#8211; Alain de Botton provides invaluable insights into everything from holiday romance to hotel minibars, airports to sightseeing. The perfect antidote to those guides that tell us what to do when we get there, The Art of Travel tries to explain why we really went in the first place &#8211; and helpfully suggest how we might be happier on our journeys.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Delightful, profound, entertaining. I doubt if de Botton has written a dull sentence in his life&#8217; Jan Morris    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An elegant and subtle work, unlike any other. Beguiling&#8217; Colin Thubron, The Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-travel-alain-de-botton-abridged/">The Art of Travel &#8211; Alain de Botton (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
