<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Science: General Issues Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/science-general-issues/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/science-general-issues/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Science: General Issues Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/science-general-issues/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Behave : The Biology of Humans at Our Best and Worst &#8211; Robert M. Sapolsky</title>
		<link>/behave-the-biology-of-humans-at-our-best-and-worst-robert-m-sapolsky/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/behave-the-biology-of-humans-at-our-best-and-worst-robert-m-sapolsky/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller &#8220;It&#8217;s no exaggeration to say that Behave is one of the best nonfiction books I&#8217;ve ever read.&#8221; -David P. Barash, The Wall Street Journal &#8220;It has my vote for science book of the year.&#8221; -Parul Sehgal, The New York Times &#8220;Hands-down one of the best books I&#8217;ve read in years. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-biology-of-humans-at-our-best-and-worst-robert-m-sapolsky/">Behave : The Biology of Humans at Our Best and Worst &#8211; Robert M. Sapolsky</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The New York Times Bestseller</p>
<p>                    &#8220;It&#8217;s no exaggeration to say that Behave is one of the best nonfiction books I&#8217;ve ever read.&#8221; -David P. Barash, The Wall Street Journal</p>
<p>                    &#8220;It has my vote for science book of the year.&#8221; -Parul Sehgal, The New York Times</p>
<p>                    &#8220;Hands-down one of the best books I&#8217;ve read in years. I loved it.&#8221; -Dina Temple-Raston, The Washington Post</p>
<p>                    Named a Best Book of the Year by The Washington Post and The Wall Street Journal </p>
<p>                    From the celebrated neurobiologist and primatologist, a landmark, genre-defining examination of human behavior, both good and bad, and an answer to the question: Why do we do the things we do?</p>
<p>                    Sapolsky&#8217;s storytelling concept is delightful but it also has a powerful intrinsic logic: he starts by looking at the factors that bear on a person&#8217;s reaction in the precise moment a behavior occurs, and then hops back in time from there, in stages, ultimately ending up at the deep history of our species and its evolutionary legacy.</p>
<p>                    And so the first category of explanation is the neurobiological one. A behavior occurs&#8211;whether an example of humans at our best, worst, or somewhere in between. What went on in a person&#8217;s brain a second before the behavior happened? Then Sapolsky pulls out to a slightly larger field of vision, a little earlier in time: What sight, sound, or smell caused the nervous system to produce that behavior? And then, what hormones acted hours to days earlier to change how responsive that individual is to the stimuli that triggered the nervous system? By now he has increased our field of vision so that we are thinking about neurobiology and the sensory world of our environment and endocrinology in trying to explain what happened.</p>
<p>                    Sapolsky keeps going: How was that behavior influenced by structural changes in the nervous system over the preceding months, by that person&#8217;s adolescence, childhood, fetal life, and then back to his or her genetic makeup? Finally, he expands the view to encompass factors larger than one individual. How did culture shape that individual&#8217;s group, what ecological factors millennia old formed that culture? And on and on, back to evolutionary factors millions of years old. </p>
<p>                    The result is one of the most dazzling tours d&#8217;horizon of the science of human behavior ever attempted, a majestic synthesis that harvests cutting-edge research across a range of disciplines to provide a subtle and nuanced perspective on why we ultimately do the things we do&#8230;for good and for ill. Sapolsky builds on this understanding to wrestle with some of our deepest and thorniest questions relating to tribalism and xenophobia, hierarchy and competition, morality and free will, and war and peace. Wise, humane, often very funny, Behave is a towering achievement, powerfully humanizing, and downright heroic in its own right.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-biology-of-humans-at-our-best-and-worst-robert-m-sapolsky/">Behave : The Biology of Humans at Our Best and Worst &#8211; Robert M. Sapolsky</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Enlightenment Now : The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress &#8211; Steven Pinker</title>
		<link>/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[21st Century History: From C 2000 -]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[C 500 To C 1600]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethics & Moral Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Enlightenment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Medieval & Renaissance]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP TEN SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER &#8216;Bristles with pure, crystalline intelligence, deep knowledge and human sympathy&#8217; Richard Dawkins Is modernity really failing? Or have we failed to appreciate progress and the ideals that make it possible? If you follow the headlines, the world in the 21st century appears to be sinking into chaos, hatred, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/">Enlightenment Now : The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP TEN SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Bristles with pure, crystalline intelligence, deep knowledge and human sympathy&#8217; Richard Dawkins  </p>
<p>                    Is modernity really failing? Or have we failed to appreciate progress and the ideals that make it possible?</p>
<p>                    If  you follow the headlines, the world in the 21st century appears to be  sinking into chaos, hatred, and irrationality. Yet Steven Pinker shows  that this is an illusion &#8211; a symptom of historical amnesia and  statistical fallacies. If you follow the trendlines rather than the  headlines, you discover that our lives have become longer, healthier,  safer, happier, more peaceful, more stimulating and more prosperous &#8211;  not just in the West, but worldwide. Such progress is no accident: it&#8217;s  the gift of a coherent and inspiring value system that many of us  embrace without even realizing it. These are the values of the  Enlightenment: of reason, science, humanism and progress.</p>
<p>                    The  challenges we face today are formidable, including inequality, climate  change, Artificial Intelligence and nuclear weapons. But the way to deal  with them is not to sink into despair or try to lurch back to a  mythical idyllic past; it&#8217;s to treat them as problems we can solve, as  we have solved other problems in the past. In making the case for an  Enlightenment newly recharged for the 21st century, Pinker shows how we  can use our faculties of reason and sympathy to solve the problems that  inevitably come with being products of evolution in an indifferent  universe. We will never have a perfect world, but &#8211; defying the chorus  of fatalism and reaction &#8211; we can continue to make it a better one.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/enlightenment-now-the-case-for-reason-science-humanism-and-progress-steven-pinker/">Enlightenment Now : The Case for Reason, Science, Humanism, and Progress &#8211; Steven Pinker</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Short History of Nearly Everything &#8211; Bill Bryson</title>
		<link>/a-short-history-of-nearly-everything-bill-bryson/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrophysics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Atomic & Molecular Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geology & The Lithosphere]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Space & Time]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-short-history-of-nearly-everything-bill-bryson/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bill Bryson describes himself as a reluctant traveller: but even when he stays safely in his own study at home, he can&#8217;t contain his curiosity about the world around him. A Short History of Nearly Everything is his quest to find out everything that has happened from the Big Bang to the rise of civilization [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-short-history-of-nearly-everything-bill-bryson/">A Short History of Nearly Everything &#8211; Bill Bryson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bill Bryson describes himself as a reluctant traveller: but even when he stays safely in his own study at home, he can&#8217;t contain his curiosity about the world around him. A Short History of Nearly Everything is his quest to find out everything that has happened from the Big Bang to the rise of civilization &#8211; how we got from there, being nothing at all, to here, being us. </p>
<p>                    Bill Bryson&#8217;s challenge is to take subjects that normally bore the pants off most of us, like geology, chemistry and particle physics, and see if there isn&#8217;t some way to render them comprehensible to people who have never thought they could be interested in science. It&#8217;s not so much about what we know, as about how we know what we know. How do we know what is in the centre of the Earth, or what a black hole is, or where the continents were 600 million years ago? How did anyone ever figure these things out?</p>
<p>                    On his travels through time and space, he encounters a splendid collection of astonishingly eccentric, competitive, obsessive and foolish scientists, like the painfully shy Henry Cavendish who worked out many conundrums like how much the Earth weighed, but never bothered to tell anybody about many of his findings. In the company of such extraordinary people, Bill Bryson takes us with him on the ultimate eye-opening journey, and reveals the world in a way most of us have never seen it before.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-short-history-of-nearly-everything-bill-bryson/">A Short History of Nearly Everything &#8211; Bill Bryson</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Something Deeply Hidden : Quantum Worlds and the Emergence of Spacetime &#8211; Sean Carroll</title>
		<link>/something-deeply-hidden-quantum-worlds-and-the-emergence-of-spacetime-sean-carroll/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/something-deeply-hidden-quantum-worlds-and-the-emergence-of-spacetime-sean-carroll/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the Royal Society Winton Prize winner &#8216;An authoritative and beautifully written account of the quest to understand quantum theory and the origin of space and time.&#8217; Professor Brian Cox Quantum physics is not mystifying. The implications are mind-bending, and not yet fully understood, but this revolutionary theory is truly illuminating. It stands as the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/something-deeply-hidden-quantum-worlds-and-the-emergence-of-spacetime-sean-carroll/">Something Deeply Hidden : Quantum Worlds and the Emergence of Spacetime &#8211; Sean Carroll</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the Royal Society Winton Prize winner</p>
<p>                    &#8216;An authoritative and beautifully written account of the quest to understand quantum theory and the origin of space and time.&#8217; Professor Brian Cox </p>
<p>                    Quantum physics is not mystifying. The implications are mind-bending, and not yet fully understood, but this revolutionary theory is truly illuminating. It stands as the best explanation of the fundamental nature of our world.</p>
<p>                    Spanning the history of quantum discoveries, from Einstein and Bohr to the present day, Something Deeply Hidden is the essential guide to the most intriguing subject in science. Acclaimed physicist and writer Sean Carroll debunks the myths, resurrects and reinstates the Many-Worlds interpretation, and presents a new path towards solving the apparent conflict between quantum mechanics and Einstein&#8217;s theory of general relativity. In doing so, he fills a gap in the science that has existed for almost a century.</p>
<p>                    A magisterial tour, Something Deeply Hidden encompasses the cosmological and everyday implications of quantum reality and multiple universes. And &#8211; finally &#8211; it all makes sense.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/something-deeply-hidden-quantum-worlds-and-the-emergence-of-spacetime-sean-carroll/">Something Deeply Hidden : Quantum Worlds and the Emergence of Spacetime &#8211; Sean Carroll</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Licence to Kill : The Science of 007 &#8211; Kathryn Harkup</title>
		<link>/licence-to-kill-the-science-of-007-kathryn-harkup/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Film Theory & Criticism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/licence-to-kill-the-science-of-007-kathryn-harkup/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ian Fleming&#8217;s series of novels based on the adventures of the secret service agent James Bond have thrilled and delighted readers since Casino Royale first published in 1953. And when the film of Dr No was released in 1962, Bond quickly became one of the world&#8217;s favourite secret agents. The character has been through some [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/licence-to-kill-the-science-of-007-kathryn-harkup/">Licence to Kill : The Science of 007 &#8211; Kathryn Harkup</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ian Fleming&#8217;s series of novels based on the adventures of the secret service agent James Bond have thrilled and delighted readers since Casino Royale first published in 1953. And when the film of Dr No was released in 1962, Bond quickly became one of the world&#8217;s favourite secret agents. The character has been through some changes and had a few ups and downs but his popularity endures, and the film franchise is currently the fifth-highest-grossing series in history. </p>
<p>                    Science and technology have always been central to the thrilling plots than make up the world of Bond, and in this book Kathryn Harkup explores this; as in some of her previous books, she takes the angle of death as a starting point to explore the science behind the story. </p>
<p>                    Naturally, there are 007 chapters, covering the full range of Bond&#8217;s exploits, and the arms, technologies, tactics and downfalls of his various foes. </p>
<p>                    In Licence to Kill, Kathryn turns her expert eye on the world&#8217;s favourite secret agent, using the hook of Bond&#8217;s enduring popularity to discuss the realities behind the silver screen. Could our favourite Bond villains actually achieve world domination? Were the huge variety of weapons and technology in Bond&#8217;s arsenal ever actually developed? And would 007 actually escape all those close shaves with his life intact? Readers will see the Bond films through new eyes.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/licence-to-kill-the-science-of-007-kathryn-harkup/">Licence to Kill : The Science of 007 &#8211; Kathryn Harkup</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Future of the Mind : The Scientific Quest to Understand, Enhance, and Empower the Mind &#8211; Michio Kaku</title>
		<link>/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biopsychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiological & Neuro-psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Michio Kaku, the New York Times bestselling author of Physics of the Impossible and Physics of the Future tackles the most fascinating and complex object in the known universe: the human brain. The Future of the Mind brings a topic that once belonged solely to the province of science fiction into a startling new reality. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/">The Future of the Mind : The Scientific Quest to Understand, Enhance, and Empower the Mind &#8211; Michio Kaku</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Michio Kaku, the New York Times bestselling author of Physics of the Impossible and Physics of the Future tackles the most fascinating and complex object in the known universe: the human brain.     </p>
<p>                    The Future of the Mind brings a topic that once belonged solely to the province of science fiction into a startling new reality. This scientific tour de force unveils the astonishing research being done in top laboratories around the world&#8211;all based on the latest advancements in neuroscience and physics&#8211;including recent experiments in telepathy, mind control, avatars, telekinesis, and recording memories and dreams. The Future of the Mind is an extraordinary, mind-boggling exploration of the frontiers of neuroscience. Dr. Kaku looks toward the day when we may achieve the ability to upload the human brain to a computer, neuron for neuron; project thoughts and emotions around the world on a brain-net; take a &#8220;smart pill&#8221; to enhance cognition; send our consciousness across the universe; and push the very limits of immortality.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-future-of-the-mind-the-scientific-quest-to-understand-enhance-and-empower-the-mind-michio-kaku/">The Future of the Mind : The Scientific Quest to Understand, Enhance, and Empower the Mind &#8211; Michio Kaku</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Science Delusion : Freeing the Spirit of Enquiry (NEW EDITION) &#8211; Rupert Sheldrake</title>
		<link>/the-science-delusion-freeing-the-spirit-of-enquiry-new-edition-rupert-sheldrake/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-science-delusion-freeing-the-spirit-of-enquiry-new-edition-rupert-sheldrake/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW EDITION The Science Delusion is the belief that science already understands the nature of reality. The fundamental questions are answered, leaving only the details to be filled in. In this book (published in the US as Science Set Free), Dr Rupert Sheldrake, one of the world&#8217;s most innovative scientists, shows that science is being [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-delusion-freeing-the-spirit-of-enquiry-new-edition-rupert-sheldrake/">The Science Delusion : Freeing the Spirit of Enquiry (NEW EDITION) &#8211; Rupert Sheldrake</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW EDITION</p>
<p>                    The Science Delusion is the belief that science already understands the nature of reality. The fundamental questions are answered, leaving only the details to be filled in. In this book (published in the US as Science Set Free), Dr Rupert Sheldrake, one of the world&#8217;s most innovative scientists, shows that science is being constricted by assumptions that have hardened into dogmas. The &#8216;scientific worldview&#8217; has become a belief system. All reality is material or physical. The world is a machine, made up of dead matter. Nature is purposeless. Consciousness is nothing but the physical activity of the brain. Free will is an illusion. God exists only as an idea in human minds, imprisoned within our skulls.</p>
<p>                    Sheldrake examines these dogmas scientifically, and shows persuasively that science would be better off without them: freer, more interesting, and more fun.</p>
<p>                    In The God Delusion Richard Dawkins used science to bash God, but here Rupert Sheldrake shows that Dawkins&#8217; understanding of what science can do is old-fashioned and itself a delusion. </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Rupert Sheldrake does science, humanity and the world at large a considerable favour.&#8217;<br />
                    The Independent</p>
<p>                    &#8216;Certainly we need to accept the limitations of much current dogma and keep our minds open as we reasonably can. Sheldrake may help us do so through this well-written, challenging and always interesting book.&#8217;<br />
                    Financial Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-science-delusion-freeing-the-spirit-of-enquiry-new-edition-rupert-sheldrake/">The Science Delusion : Freeing the Spirit of Enquiry (NEW EDITION) &#8211; Rupert Sheldrake</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Intelligence & Reasoning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marine Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Oceanography (seas)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Aquatic Creatures]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BBC R4 Book of the Week &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian &#8216;Fascinating and often delightful&#8217; The Times What if intelligent life on Earth evolved not once, but twice? The octopus is the closest we will come to meeting an intelligent alien. What can we learn from the encounter? In Other Minds, Peter Godfrey-Smith, a distinguished philosopher of science [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/">Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BBC R4 Book of the Week<br />
                              &#8216;Brilliant&#8217; Guardian<br />
                              &#8216;Fascinating and often delightful&#8217; The Times    </p>
<p>                                What if intelligent life on Earth evolved not once, but twice? The octopus is the closest we will come to meeting an intelligent alien. What can we learn from the encounter?    </p>
<p>                              In Other Minds, Peter Godfrey-Smith, a distinguished philosopher of science and a skilled scuba diver, tells a bold new story of how nature became aware of itself &#8211; a story that largely occurs in the ocean, where animals first appeared.    </p>
<p>                              Tracking the mind&#8217;s fitful development from unruly clumps of seaborne cells to the first evolved nervous systems in ancient relatives of jellyfish, he explores the incredible evolutionary journey of the cephalopods, which began as inconspicuous molluscs who would later abandon their shells to rise above the ocean floor, searching for prey and acquiring the greater intelligence needed to do so &#8211; a journey completely independent from the route that mammals and birds would later take.    </p>
<p>                              But what kind of intelligence do cephalopods possess? How did the octopus, a solitary creature with little social life, become so smart? What is it like to have eight tentacles that are so packed with neurons that they virtually &#8216;think for themselves&#8217;? By tracing the question of inner life back to its roots and comparing human beings with our most remarkable animal relatives, Godfrey-Smith casts crucial new light on the octopus mind &#8211; and on our own.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/other-minds-the-octopus-and-the-evolution-of-intelligent-life-peter-godfrey-smith-abridged/">Other Minds : The Octopus and the Evolution of Intelligent Life &#8211; Peter Godfrey-Smith (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Life at the Speed of Light : From the Double Helix to the Dawn of Digital Life &#8211; J. Craig Venter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/life-at-the-speed-of-light-from-the-double-helix-to-the-dawn-of-digital-life-j-craig-venter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/life-at-the-speed-of-light-from-the-double-helix-to-the-dawn-of-digital-life-j-craig-venter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In 2010, scientists led by J. Craig Venter became the first to successfully create &#8216;synthetic life&#8217; &#8212; putting humankind at the threshold of the most important and exciting phase of biological research, one that will enable us to actually write the genetic code for designing new species to help us adapt and evolve for long-term [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-at-the-speed-of-light-from-the-double-helix-to-the-dawn-of-digital-life-j-craig-venter-abridged/">Life at the Speed of Light : From the Double Helix to the Dawn of Digital Life &#8211; J. Craig Venter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2010, scientists led by J. Craig Venter became the first to successfully create &#8216;synthetic life&#8217; &#8212; putting humankind at the threshold of the most important and exciting phase of biological research, one that will enable us to actually write the genetic code for designing new species to help us adapt and evolve for long-term survival. The science of synthetic genomics will have a profound impact on human existence, including chemical and energy generation, health, clean water and food production, environmental control, and possibly even our evolution.    </p>
<p>                    In Life at the Speed of Light, Venter presents a fascinating and authoritative study of this emerging field from the inside &#8212; detailing its origins, current challenges and controversies, and projected effects on our lives. This scientific frontier provides an opportunity to ponder anew the age-old question &#8216;What is life?&#8217; and examine what we really mean by &#8216;playing God&#8217;. Life at the Speed of Light is a landmark work, written by a visionary at the dawn of a new era of biological engineering.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/life-at-the-speed-of-light-from-the-double-helix-to-the-dawn-of-digital-life-j-craig-venter-abridged/">Life at the Speed of Light : From the Double Helix to the Dawn of Digital Life &#8211; J. Craig Venter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reality Is Not What It Seems : The Journey to Quantum Gravity &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reality-is-not-what-it-seems-the-journey-to-quantum-gravity-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gravity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relativity Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Theoretical & Mathematical Astronomy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reality-is-not-what-it-seems-the-journey-to-quantum-gravity-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The physicist transforming how we see the universe&#8217; (Financial Times) &#8216;An utter joy&#8217; (Adam Rutherford) &#8216;A hugely engaging book&#8230; Rovelli is a charming, thought-provoking tour guide&#8217; (Manjit Kumar Prospect) Do space and time truly exist? What is reality made of? Can we understand its deep texture? Scientist Carlo Rovelli has spent his whole life exploring [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reality-is-not-what-it-seems-the-journey-to-quantum-gravity-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">Reality Is Not What It Seems : The Journey to Quantum Gravity &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The physicist transforming how we see the universe&#8217; (Financial Times)    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An utter joy&#8217; (Adam Rutherford)    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A hugely engaging book&#8230; Rovelli is a charming, thought-provoking tour guide&#8217; (Manjit Kumar Prospect)    </p>
<p>                    Do space and time truly exist? What is reality made of? Can we understand its deep texture?<br />
                    Scientist Carlo Rovelli has spent his whole life exploring these questions and pushing the boundaries of what we know. In this mind-expanding book, he shows how our understanding of reality has changed throughout centuries, from Democritus to loop quantum gravity. Taking us on a wondrous journey, he invites us to imagine a whole new world where black holes are waiting to explode, spacetime is made up of grains, and infinity does not exist &#8212; a vast universe still largely undiscovered.    </p>
<p>                    Translated by Simon Carnell and Erica Segre</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reality-is-not-what-it-seems-the-journey-to-quantum-gravity-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">Reality Is Not What It Seems : The Journey to Quantum Gravity &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Loonshots : How to Nurture the Crazy Ideas That Win Wars, Cure Diseases, and Transform Industries &#8211; Safi Bahcall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/loonshots-how-to-nurture-the-crazy-ideas-that-win-wars-cure-diseases-and-transform-industries-safi-bahcall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/loonshots-how-to-nurture-the-crazy-ideas-that-win-wars-cure-diseases-and-transform-industries-safi-bahcall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What do James Bond and Lipitor have in common? Why do traffic jams appear out of nowhere on highways? What can we learn about innovation from a glass of water? In Loonshots, physicist and entrepreneur Safi Bahcall reveals a surprising new way of thinking about the mysteries of group behaviour and the challenges of nurturing [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/loonshots-how-to-nurture-the-crazy-ideas-that-win-wars-cure-diseases-and-transform-industries-safi-bahcall-abridged/">Loonshots : How to Nurture the Crazy Ideas That Win Wars, Cure Diseases, and Transform Industries &#8211; Safi Bahcall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What do James Bond and Lipitor have in common? Why do traffic jams appear out of nowhere on highways? What can we learn about innovation from a glass of water? In Loonshots, physicist and entrepreneur Safi Bahcall reveals a surprising new way of thinking about the mysteries of group behaviour and the challenges of nurturing radical breakthroughs.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the science of phase transitions, Bahcall shows why teams, companies, or any group with a mission will suddenly change from embracing wild new ideas to rigidly rejecting them, just as flowing water will suddenly change into brittle ice. Oceans of print have been written about culture. Loonshots identifies the small shifts in structure that control this transition, the same way that temperature controls the change from water to ice.    </p>
<p>                    Using examples that range from the spread of fires in forests to the hunt for terrorists online, and stories of thieves and geniuses and kings, Bahcall shows how this new kind of science helps us understand the fate of companies and empires. Loonshots distills these insights into lessons for creatives, entrepreneurs, and visionaries everywhere.    </p>
<p>                    Over the past decade, researchers have been applying the tools and techniques of phase transitions to understand how birds flock, fish swim, brains work, people vote, criminals behave, ideas spread, diseases erupt, and ecosystems collapse. If twentieth-century science was shaped by the search for fundamental laws, like quantum mechanics and gravity, the twenty-first will be shaped by this new kind of science. Loonshots is the first to apply this science to help all of us unlock our potential to create and nurture the crazy ideas that change the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/loonshots-how-to-nurture-the-crazy-ideas-that-win-wars-cure-diseases-and-transform-industries-safi-bahcall-abridged/">Loonshots : How to Nurture the Crazy Ideas That Win Wars, Cure Diseases, and Transform Industries &#8211; Safi Bahcall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Carrots And Sticks &#8211; Ian Ayres (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/carrots-and-sticks-ian-ayres-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/carrots-and-sticks-ian-ayres-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/carrots-and-sticks-ian-ayres-abridged/">Carrots And Sticks &#8211; Ian Ayres (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/carrots-and-sticks-ian-ayres-abridged/">Carrots And Sticks &#8211; Ian Ayres (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Napoleon&#8217;S Buttons : How 17 Molecules Changed History &#8211; Penny Le Couteur, Jay Burreson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[European History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General & World History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Modern History To 20th Century: C 1700 To C 1900]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum & Theoretical Chemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Napoleon&#8217;s Buttons is the fascinating account of seventeen groups of molecules that have greatly influenced the course of history. These molecules provided the impetus for early exploration, and made possible the voyages of discovery that ensued. The molecules resulted in grand feats of engineering and spurred advances in medicine and law; they determined what we [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/">Napoleon&#8217;S Buttons : How 17 Molecules Changed History &#8211; Penny Le Couteur, Jay Burreson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Napoleon&#8217;s Buttons is the fascinating account of seventeen groups of molecules that have greatly influenced the course of history. These molecules provided the impetus for early exploration, and made possible the voyages of discovery that ensued. The molecules resulted in grand feats of engineering and spurred advances in medicine and law; they determined what we now eat, drink, and wear. A change as small as the position of an atom can lead to enormous alterations in the properties of a substance-which, in turn, can result in great historical shifts.     </p>
<p>                     With lively prose and an eye for colorful and unusual details, Le Couteur and Burreson offer a novel way to understand the shaping of civilization and the workings of our contemporary world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/napoleons-buttons-how-17-molecules-changed-history-penny-le-couteur-jay-burreson-abridged/">Napoleon&#8217;S Buttons : How 17 Molecules Changed History &#8211; Penny Le Couteur, Jay Burreson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Humanistic Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychological Theory & Schools Of Thought]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER** Why do human beings behave as they do? &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER**    </p>
<p>                    Why do human beings behave as they do?     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Awe-inspiring&#8230; You will learn more about human nature than in any other book I can think of&#8217; Henry Marsh, bestselling author of Do No Harm    </p>
<p>                     We are capable of savage acts of violence but also spectacular feats of kindness: is one side of our nature destined to win out over the other?    </p>
<p>                     Every act of human behaviour has multiple layers of causation, spiralling back seconds, minutes, hours, days, months, years, even centuries, right back to the dawn of time and the origins of our species.     </p>
<p>                     In the epic sweep of history, how does our biology affect the arc of war and peace, justice and persecution? How have our brains evolved alongside our cultures?    </p>
<p>                     This is the exhilarating story of human morality and the science underpinning the biggest question of all: what makes us human?    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;One of the best scientist-writers of our time&#8217; Oliver Sacks</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/behave-the-bestselling-exploration-of-why-humans-behave-as-they-do-robert-m-sapolsky-abridged/">Behave : The bestselling exploration of why humans behave as they do &#8211; Robert M Sapolsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Surveillance Capitalism : The Fight for a Human Future at the New Frontier of Power: Barack Obama&#8217;s Books of 2019 &#8211; Professor Shoshana Zuboff (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-the-fight-for-a-human-future-at-the-new-frontier-of-power-barack-obamas-books-of-2019-professor-shoshana-zuboff-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-the-fight-for-a-human-future-at-the-new-frontier-of-power-barack-obamas-books-of-2019-professor-shoshana-zuboff-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP 10 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER A NEW YORK TIMES NOTABLE BOOK OF THE YEAR ONE OF BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S TOP BOOKS OF THE YEAR Shortlisted for The Orwell Prize 2020 Shortlisted for the FT Business Book of the Year Award 2019 &#8216;Easily the most important book to be published this century. I find it hard [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-the-fight-for-a-human-future-at-the-new-frontier-of-power-barack-obamas-books-of-2019-professor-shoshana-zuboff-abridged/">The Age of Surveillance Capitalism : The Fight for a Human Future at the New Frontier of Power: Barack Obama&#8217;s Books of 2019 &#8211; Professor Shoshana Zuboff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE TOP 10 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER<br />
                    A NEW YORK TIMES NOTABLE BOOK OF THE YEAR<br />
                    ONE OF BARACK OBAMA&#8217;S TOP BOOKS OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for The Orwell Prize 2020    </p>
<p>                    Shortlisted for the FT Business Book of the Year Award 2019    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Easily the most  important book to be published this  century. I find it hard to take any  young activist seriously who hasn&#8217;t  at least familarised themselves  with Zuboff&#8217;s central ideas.&#8217; &#8211; Zadie Smith, The Guardian    </p>
<p>                    The challenges to humanity posed by the digital future, the first detailed examination of the unprecedented form of power called &#8220;surveillance capitalism,&#8221; and the quest by powerful corporations to predict and control us.    </p>
<p>                    The heady optimism of the Internet&#8217;s early days is gone. Technologies that were meant to liberate us have deepened inequality and stoked divisions. Tech companies gather our information online and sell it to the highest bidder, whether government or retailer. Profits now depend not only on predicting our behaviour but modifying it too. How will this fusion of capitalism and the digital shape our values and define our future?    </p>
<p>                    Shoshana Zuboff shows that we are at a crossroads. We still have the power to decide what kind of world we want to live in, and what we decide now will shape the rest of the century. Our choices: allow technology to enrich the few and impoverish the many, or harness it and distribute its benefits.    </p>
<p>                     The Age of Surveillance Capitalism is a deeply-reasoned examination of the threat of unprecedented power free from democratic oversight. As it explores this new capitalism&#8217;s impact on society, politics, business, and technology, it exposes the struggles that will decide both the next chapter of capitalism and the meaning of information civilization. Most critically, it shows how we can protect ourselves and our communities and ensure we are the masters of the digital rather than its slaves.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-surveillance-capitalism-the-fight-for-a-human-future-at-the-new-frontier-of-power-barack-obamas-books-of-2019-professor-shoshana-zuboff-abridged/">The Age of Surveillance Capitalism : The Fight for a Human Future at the New Frontier of Power: Barack Obama&#8217;s Books of 2019 &#8211; Professor Shoshana Zuboff (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Big Picture : On the Origins of Life, Meaning, and the Universe Itself &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astrophysics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Brian Cox, Mail on Sunday Books of the Year Where are we? Who are we? Do our beliefs, hopes and dreams hold any significance out there in the void? Can human purpose and meaning ever fit into a scientific worldview? Award-winning author Sean Carroll brings his extraordinary intellect to bear on the realms [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Big Picture : On the Origins of Life, Meaning, and the Universe Itself &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fascinating&#8217; &#8211; Brian Cox, Mail on Sunday Books of the Year    </p>
<p>                    Where are we? Who are we? Do our beliefs, hopes and dreams hold any significance out there in the void? Can human purpose and meaning ever fit into a scientific worldview?    </p>
<p>                    Award-winning author Sean Carroll brings his extraordinary intellect to bear on the realms of knowledge, the laws of nature and the most profound questions about life, death and our place in it all.    </p>
<p>                    From Darwin and Einstein to the origins of life, consciousness and the universe itself, Carroll combines cosmos-sprawling science and profound thought in a quest to explain our world. Destined to sit alongside the works of our greatest thinkers, The Big Picture demonstrates that while our lives may be forever dwarfed by the immensity of the universe, they can be redeemed by our capacity to comprehend it and give it meaning.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-big-picture-on-the-origins-of-life-meaning-and-the-universe-itself-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Big Picture : On the Origins of Life, Meaning, and the Universe Itself &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Smarter Faster Better : The Secrets of Being Productive &#8211; Charles Duhigg (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/smarter-faster-better-the-secrets-of-being-productive-charles-duhigg-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Decision Making]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/smarter-faster-better-the-secrets-of-being-productive-charles-duhigg-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In his international bestseller The Power of Habit, Pulitzer Prize-winner Charles Duhigg explained why we do what we do. Now he applies the same relentless curiosity and masterful analysis to the question: how can each of us achieve more? Drawing on the very latest findings in neuroscience, psychology and behavioural economics, he demonstrates the eight [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smarter-faster-better-the-secrets-of-being-productive-charles-duhigg-abridged/">Smarter Faster Better : The Secrets of Being Productive &#8211; Charles Duhigg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In his international bestseller The Power of Habit, Pulitzer Prize-winner Charles Duhigg explained why we do what we do. Now he applies the same relentless curiosity and masterful analysis to the question: how can each of us achieve more?    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the very latest findings in neuroscience, psychology and behavioural economics, he demonstrates the eight simple principles that govern productivity. He demonstrates how the most dynamic and effective people &#8211; from CEOs to film-makers to software entrepreneurs  &#8211; deploy them. And he shows how you can, too.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Charles has some wonderful advice for increasing productivity . . . the tips he highlights have most definitely played a huge part in helping me to build the Virgin brand.&#8217; Richard Branson    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;In Smarter Faster Better Duhigg finds provocative answers to a riddle of our age: how to become more productive (by two times, or even ten times) and less busy.&#8217; Jim Collins    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;There are valuable lessons in Smarter Faster Better . . . I never felt like putting it down.&#8217; Financial Times</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/smarter-faster-better-the-secrets-of-being-productive-charles-duhigg-abridged/">Smarter Faster Better : The Secrets of Being Productive &#8211; Charles Duhigg (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hidden Figures : The Untold Story of the African American Women Who Helped Win the Space Race &#8211; Margot Lee Shetterly (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hidden-figures-the-untold-story-of-the-african-american-women-who-helped-win-the-space-race-margot-lee-shetterly-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Aerospace & Aviation Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Postwar 20th Century History, From C 1945 To C 2000]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hidden-figures-the-untold-story-of-the-african-american-women-who-helped-win-the-space-race-margot-lee-shetterly-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Top 10 Sunday Times Bestseller NOW A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE Oscar Nominated For Best Picture and Best Adapted Screenplay Set amid the civil rights movement, the never-before-told true story of NASA&#8217;s African-American female mathematicians who played a crucial role in America&#8217;s space program. Before Neil Armstrong walked on the moon, a group of professionals [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hidden-figures-the-untold-story-of-the-african-american-women-who-helped-win-the-space-race-margot-lee-shetterly-abridged/">Hidden Figures : The Untold Story of the African American Women Who Helped Win the Space Race &#8211; Margot Lee Shetterly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Top 10 Sunday Times Bestseller    </p>
<p>                                NOW A MAJOR MOTION PICTURE<br />
                    Oscar Nominated For Best Picture and Best Adapted Screenplay    </p>
<p>                                Set amid the civil rights movement, the never-before-told true story of NASA&#8217;s African-American female mathematicians who played a crucial role in America&#8217;s space program.    </p>
<p>                              Before Neil Armstrong walked on the moon, a group of professionals worked as &#8216;Human Computers&#8217;, calculating the flight paths that would enable these historic achievements. Among these were a coterie of bright, talented African-American women. Segregated from their white counterparts, these &#8216;colored computers&#8217; used pencil and paper to write the equations that would launch rockets, and astronauts, into space.    </p>
<p>                              Moving from World War II through NASA&#8217;s golden age, touching on the civil rights era, the Space Race, the Cold War, and the women&#8217;s rights movement, Hidden Figures interweaves a rich history of mankind&#8217;s greatest adventure with the intimate stories of five courageous women whose work forever changed the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hidden-figures-the-untold-story-of-the-african-american-women-who-helped-win-the-space-race-margot-lee-shetterly-abridged/">Hidden Figures : The Untold Story of the African American Women Who Helped Win the Space Race &#8211; Margot Lee Shetterly (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmosapiens : Human Evolution from the Origin of the Universe &#8211; John Hands (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[States Of Consciousness]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Daily Telegraph and TLS Book of the Year &#8216;An audacious tour of all that science can teach us&#8217; Edward O. Wilson Specialist scientific fields are developing at incredibly swift speeds, but what can they really tell us about how the universe began and how humans evolved to play such a dominant role on Earth? [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/">Cosmosapiens : Human Evolution from the Origin of the Universe &#8211; John Hands (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A Daily Telegraph and TLS Book of the Year    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An audacious tour of all that science can teach us&#8217; Edward O. Wilson    </p>
<p>                    Specialist scientific fields are developing at incredibly swift speeds, but what can they really tell us about how the universe began and how humans evolved to play such a dominant role on Earth? John Hands&#8217;s extraordinarily ambitious quest brings together our scientific knowledge and evaluates the theories and evidence about the origin and evolution of matter, life, consciousness, and humankind.    </p>
<p>                    Cosmosapiens provides the most comprehensive account yet of current ideas such as cosmic inflation, dark energy, the selfish gene, and neurogenetic determinism. In clear and accessible language, Hands differentiates the firmly established from the speculative and examines the claims of various fields such as string theory to approach a unified theory of everything. In doing so he challenges the orthodox consensus in those branches of cosmology, biology, and neuroscience that have ossified into dogma. His striking analysis reveals underlying patterns of cooperation, complexification, and convergence that lead to the unique emergence in humans of a self-reflective consciousness that enables us to determine our future evolution. This groundbreaking book is destined to become a classic of scientific thinking.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmosapiens-human-evolution-from-the-origin-of-the-universe-john-hands-abridged/">Cosmosapiens : Human Evolution from the Origin of the Universe &#8211; John Hands (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agnosticism & Atheism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eclectic & Esoteric Religions & Belief Systems]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body & Spirit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychic Powers & Psychic Phenomena]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Religion & Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An extraordinary book . . . It will shake up your most fundamental beliefs about everyday experience, and it just might change your life.&#8217; Paul Bloom ___ For the millions of people who want spirituality without religion, Sam Harris&#8217;s new book is a guide to meditation as a rational spiritual practice informed by neuroscience and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/">Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An extraordinary book . . . It will shake up your most fundamental beliefs about everyday experience, and it just might change your life.&#8217; Paul Bloom<br />
                    ___    </p>
<p>                    For the millions of people who want spirituality without religion, Sam Harris&#8217;s new book is a guide to meditation as a rational spiritual practice informed by neuroscience and psychology.    </p>
<p>                     Throughout the book, Harris argues that there are important truths to be found in the experience of contemplatives such as Jesus, Buddha and other saints and sages of history-and, therefore, that there is more to understanding reality than science and secular culture generally allow.    </p>
<p>                    Waking Up is part seeker&#8217;s memoir and part exploration of the scientific underpinnings of spirituality. No other book marries contemplative wisdom and modern science in this way, and no author other than Sam Harris-a scientist, philosopher, and famous sceptic-could write it.<br />
                     ___    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A demanding, illusion-shattering book.&#8217; Kirkus Reviews<br />
                    &#8216;A pleasure to read.&#8217; Huffington Post</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/waking-up-searching-for-spirituality-without-religion-sam-harris-abridged/">Waking Up : Searching for Spirituality Without Religion &#8211; Sam Harris (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Evolution of Everything : How Small Changes Transform Our World &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural History]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If there is one dominant myth about the world, one huge mistake we all make &#8230; it is that we all go around assuming the world is much more of a planned place than it is.&#8217; From the industrial revolution and the rise of China, to urbanisation and the birth of bitcoin, Matt Ridley demolishes [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/">The Evolution of Everything : How Small Changes Transform Our World &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If there is one dominant myth about the world, one huge mistake we all make &#8230; it is that we all go around assuming the world is much more of a planned place than it is.&#8217;    </p>
<p>                              From the industrial revolution and the rise of China, to urbanisation and the birth of bitcoin, Matt Ridley demolishes conventional assumptions that the great events and trends of our day are dictated by those on high. On the contrary, our most important achievements develop from the ground up. In this wide-ranging and erudite book, Matt Ridley brilliantly makes the case for evolution as the force that has shaped much of our culture, our minds, and that even now is shaping our future.    </p>
<p>                              As compelling as it is controversial, as authoritative as it is ambitious, Ridley&#8217;s deeply thought-provoking book will change the way we think about the world and how it works.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-evolution-of-everything-how-small-changes-transform-our-world-matt-ridley-abridged/">The Evolution of Everything : How Small Changes Transform Our World &#8211; Matt Ridley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cosmos &#8211; Carl Sagan, Foreword byNeil deGrasse Tyson, Introduction byAnn Druyan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cosmology & The Universe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Meteorology & Climatology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>RETURNING TO TELEVISION AS AN ALL-NEW MINISERIES ON FOX Cosmos is one of the bestselling science books of all time. In clear-eyed prose, Sagan reveals a jewel-like blue world inhabited by a life form that is just beginning to discover its own identity and to venture into the vast ocean of space. Featuring a new [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/">Cosmos &#8211; Carl Sagan, Foreword byNeil deGrasse Tyson, Introduction byAnn Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>RETURNING TO TELEVISION AS AN ALL-NEW MINISERIES ON FOX     </p>
<p>                    Cosmos is one of the bestselling science books of all time. In clear-eyed prose, Sagan reveals a jewel-like blue world inhabited by a life form that is just beginning to discover its own identity and to venture into the vast ocean of space. Featuring a new Introduction by Sagan&#8217;s collaborator, Ann Druyan, full color illustrations, and a new Foreword by astrophysicist Neil deGrasse Tyson, Cosmos retraces the fourteen billion years of cosmic evolution that have transformed matter into consciousness, exploring such topics as the origin of life, the human brain, Egyptian hieroglyphics, spacecraft missions, the death of the Sun, the evolution of galaxies, and the forces and individuals who helped to shape modern science.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Cosmos     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Magnificent . . . With a lyrical literary style, and a range that touches almost all aspects of human knowledge, Cosmos often seems too good to be true.&#8221;&#8211;The Plain Dealer     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Sagan is an astronomer with one eye on the stars, another on history, and a third&#8211;his mind&#8217;s&#8211;on the human condition.&#8221;&#8211;Newsday     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Brilliant in its scope and provocative in its suggestions . . . shimmers with a sense of wonder.&#8221;&#8211;The Miami Herald     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Sagan dazzles the mind with the miracle of our survival, framed by the stately galaxies of space.&#8221;&#8211;Cosmopolitan     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Enticing . . . iridescent . . . imaginatively illustrated.&#8221;&#8211;The New York Times Book Review</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cosmos-carl-sagan-foreword-by-neil-degrasse-tyson-introduction-by-ann-druyan-abridged/">Cosmos &#8211; Carl Sagan, Foreword byNeil deGrasse Tyson, Introduction byAnn Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Vindication of the Rights of Woman (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Mary Wollstonecraft (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthologies (non-poetry)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Civil Rights & Citizenship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Feminism & Feminist Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gender Studies: Women]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Miscellaneous Items]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Discover Wollstonecraft&#8217;s classic feminist text in an abridged, digestible form. WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY ZOE WILLIAMS The term feminism did not yet exist when Mary Wollstonecraft wrote this book, but it was the first great piece of feminist writing. In these pages you will find the essence of her argument &#8211; for the education of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/">A Vindication of the Rights of Woman (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Mary Wollstonecraft (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Discover Wollstonecraft&#8217;s classic feminist text in an abridged, digestible form.    </p>
<p>                    WITH AN INTRODUCTION BY ZOE WILLIAMS     </p>
<p>                    The term feminism did not yet exist when Mary Wollstonecraft wrote this book, but it was the first great piece of feminist writing. In these pages you will find the essence of her argument &#8211; for the education of women and for an increased female contribution to society. Her work made the first ripples of what would later become the tidal wave of the women&#8217;s rights movement. Rationalist but revolutionary, Wollstonecraft changed the world for women.    </p>
<p>                    Vintage Feminism: classic feminist texts in short form</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-vindication-of-the-rights-of-woman-vintage-feminism-short-edition-mary-wollstonecraft-abridged/">A Vindication of the Rights of Woman (Vintage Feminism Short Edition) &#8211; Mary Wollstonecraft (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Demon-Haunted World : Science as a Candle in the Dark &#8211; Carl Sagan, Ann Druyan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Reference Works]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A prescient warning of a future we now inhabit, where fake news stories and Internet conspiracy theories play to a disaffected American populace &#8220;A glorious book . . . A spirited defense of science . . . From the first page to the last, this book is a manifesto for clear thought.&#8221;&#8211;Los Angeles Times How [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/">The Demon-Haunted World : Science as a Candle in the Dark &#8211; Carl Sagan, Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A prescient warning of a future we now inhabit, where fake news stories and Internet conspiracy theories play to a disaffected American populace     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A glorious book . . . A spirited defense of science . . . From the first page to the last, this book is a manifesto for clear thought.&#8221;&#8211;Los Angeles Times     </p>
<p>                     How can we make intelligent decisions about our increasingly technology-driven lives if we don&#8217;t understand the difference between the myths of pseudoscience and the testable hypotheses of science? Pulitzer Prize-winning author and distinguished astronomer Carl Sagan argues that scientific thinking is critical not only to the pursuit of truth but to the very well-being of our democratic institutions.     </p>
<p>                     Casting a wide net through history and culture, Sagan examines and authoritatively debunks such celebrated fallacies of the past as witchcraft, faith healing, demons, and UFOs. And yet, disturbingly, in today&#8217;s so-called information age, pseudoscience is burgeoning with stories of alien abduction, channeling past lives, and communal hallucinations commanding growing attention and respect. As Sagan demonstrates with lucid eloquence, the siren song of unreason is not just a cultural wrong turn but a dangerous plunge into darkness that threatens our most basic freedoms.     </p>
<p>                     Praise for The Demon-Haunted World     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Powerful . . . A stirring defense of informed rationality. . . Rich in surprising information and beautiful writing.&#8221;&#8211;The Washington Post Book World     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Compelling.&#8221;&#8211;USA Today     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;A clear vision of what good science means and why it makes a difference. . . . A testimonial to the power of science and a warning of the dangers of unrestrained credulity.&#8221;&#8211;The Sciences     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Passionate.&#8221;&#8211;San Francisco Examiner-Chronicle</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-demon-haunted-world-science-as-a-candle-in-the-dark-carl-sagan-ann-druyan-abridged/">The Demon-Haunted World : Science as a Candle in the Dark &#8211; Carl Sagan, Ann Druyan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crisis in the Red Zone : The Story of the Deadliest Ebola Outbreak in History, and of the Viruses to Come &#8211; Richard Preston (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Illness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An urgent wake-up call about the future of emerging viruses and a gripping account of the doctors and scientists fighting to protect us, told through the story of the deadly 2013-2014 Ebola epidemic &#8220;Crisis in the Red Zone reads like a thriller. That the story it tells is all true [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/">Crisis in the Red Zone : The Story of the Deadliest Ebola Outbreak in History, and of the Viruses to Come &#8211; Richard Preston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; An urgent wake-up call about the future of emerging viruses and a gripping account of the doctors and scientists fighting to protect us, told through the story of the deadly 2013-2014 Ebola epidemic &#8220;Crisis in the Red Zone reads like a thriller. That the story it tells is all true makes it all more terrifying.&#8221;&#8211;Elizabeth Kolbert, Pulitzer Prize-winning author of The Sixth Extinction From the #1 bestselling author of The Hot Zone, now a National Geographic original miniseries . . . This time, Ebola started with a two-year-old child who likely had contact with a wild creature and whose entire family quickly fell ill and died. The ensuing global drama activated health professionals in North America, Europe, and Africa in a desperate race against time to contain the viral wildfire. By the end&#8211;as the virus mutated into its deadliest form, and spread farther and faster than ever before&#8211;30,000 people would be infected, and the dead would be spread across eight countries on three continents. In this taut and suspenseful medical drama, Richard Preston deeply chronicles the pandemic, in which we saw for the first time the specter of Ebola jumping continents, crossing the Atlantic, and infecting people in America. Rich in characters and conflict&#8211;physical, emotional, and ethical&#8211;Crisis in the Red Zone is an immersion in one of the great public health calamities of our time. Preston writes of doctors and nurses in the field putting their own lives on the line, of government bureaucrats and NGO administrators moving, often fitfully, to try to contain the outbreak, and of pharmaceutical companies racing to develop drugs to combat the virus. He also explores the charged ethical dilemma over who should and did receive the rare doses of an experimental treatment when they became available at the peak of the disaster. Crisis in the Red Zone makes clear that the outbreak of 2013-2014 is a harbinger of further, more severe outbreaks, and of emerging viruses heretofore unimagined&#8211;in any country, on any continent. In our ever more interconnected world, with roads and towns cut deep into the jungles of equatorial Africa, viruses both familiar and undiscovered are being unleashed into more densely populated areas than ever before. The more we discover about the virosphere, the more we realize its deadly potential. Crisis in the Red Zone is an exquisitely timely book, a stark warning of viral outbreaks to come.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crisis-in-the-red-zone-the-story-of-the-deadliest-ebola-outbreak-in-history-and-of-the-viruses-to-come-richard-preston-abridged/">Crisis in the Red Zone : The Story of the Deadliest Ebola Outbreak in History, and of the Viruses to Come &#8211; Richard Preston (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thinking in Systems : a Primer &#8211; Donella Meadows, Edited byDiana Wright (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/thinking-in-systems-a-primer-donella-meadows-edited-by-diana-wright-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cybernetics & Systems Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Development Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainability]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/thinking-in-systems-a-primer-donella-meadows-edited-by-diana-wright-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In the years following her role as the lead author of the international bestseller, Limits to Growth&#8211;the first book to show the consequences of unchecked growth on a finite planet&#8211; Donella Meadows remained a pioneer of environmental and social analysis until her untimely death in 2001. Meadows&#8217; newly released manuscript, Thinking in Systems, is a [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinking-in-systems-a-primer-donella-meadows-edited-by-diana-wright-abridged/">Thinking in Systems : a Primer &#8211; Donella Meadows, Edited byDiana Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the years following her role as the lead author of the international bestseller, Limits to Growth&#8211;the first book to show the consequences of unchecked growth on a finite planet&#8211; Donella Meadows remained a pioneer of environmental and social analysis until her untimely death in 2001. Meadows&#8217; newly released manuscript, Thinking in Systems, is a concise and crucial book offering insight for problem solving on scales ranging from the personal to the global. Edited by the Sustainability Institute&#8217;s Diana Wright, this essential primer brings systems thinking out of the realm of computers and equations and into the tangible world, showing readers how to develop the systems-thinking skills that thought leaders across the globe consider critical for 21st-century life. Some of the biggest problems facing the world&#8211;war, hunger, poverty, and environmental degradation&#8211;are essentially system failures. They cannot be solved by fixing one piece in isolation from the others, because even seemingly minor details have enormous power to undermine the best efforts of too-narrow thinking. While readers will learn the conceptual tools and methods of systems thinking, the heart of the book is grander than methodology. Donella Meadows was known as much for nurturing positive outcomes as she was for delving into the science behind global dilemmas. She reminds readers to pay attention to what is important, not just what is quantifiable, to stay humble, and to stay a learner. In a world growing ever more complicated, crowded, and interdependent, Thinking in Systems helps readers avoid confusion and helplessness, the first step toward finding proactive and effective solutions.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/thinking-in-systems-a-primer-donella-meadows-edited-by-diana-wright-abridged/">Thinking in Systems : a Primer &#8211; Donella Meadows, Edited byDiana Wright (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Mind for Numbers : How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra) &#8211; Barbara Oakley (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The companion book to COURSERA(R)&#8217;s wildly popular massive open online course Learning How to Learn Whether you are a student struggling to fulfill a math or science requirement, or you are embarking on a career change that requires a new skill set, A Mind for Numbers offers the tools you need to get a better [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/">A Mind for Numbers : How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra) &#8211; Barbara Oakley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The companion book to COURSERA(R)&#8217;s wildly popular massive open online course Learning How to Learn     </p>
<p>                    Whether you are a student struggling to fulfill a math or science requirement, or you are embarking on a career change that requires a new skill set, A Mind for Numbers offers the tools you need to get a better grasp of that intimidating material. Engineering professor Barbara Oakley knows firsthand how it feels to struggle with math. She flunked her way through high school math and science courses, before enlisting in the army immediately after graduation. When she saw how her lack of mathematical and technical savvy severely limited her options&#8211;both to rise in the military and to explore other careers&#8211;she returned to school with a newfound determination to re-tool her brain to master the very subjects that had given her so much trouble throughout her entire life.     </p>
<p>                     In A Mind for Numbers, Dr. Oakley lets us in on the secrets to learning effectively&#8211;secrets that even dedicated and successful students wish they&#8217;d known earlier. Contrary to popular belief, math requires creative, as well as analytical, thinking. Most people think that there&#8217;s only one way to do a problem, when in actuality, there are often a number of different solutions&#8211;you just need the creativity to see them. For example, there are more than three hundred different known proofs of the Pythagorean Theorem. In short, studying a problem in a laser-focused way until you reach a solution is not an effective way to learn. Rather, it involves taking the time to step away from a problem and allow the more relaxed and creative part of the brain to take over. The learning strategies in this book apply not only to math and science, but to any subject in which we struggle. We all have what it takes to excel in areas that don&#8217;t seem to come naturally to us at first, and learning them does not have to be as painful as we might think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-mind-for-numbers-how-to-excel-at-math-and-science-even-if-you-flunked-algebra-barbara-oakley-abridged/">A Mind for Numbers : How to Excel at Math and Science (Even If You Flunked Algebra) &#8211; Barbara Oakley (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Rise of Superman : Decoding the Science of Ultimate Human Performance &#8211; Steven Kotler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-rise-of-superman-decoding-the-science-of-ultimate-human-performance-steven-kotler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Extreme Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-rise-of-superman-decoding-the-science-of-ultimate-human-performance-steven-kotler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A razor-sharp analysis of how record-breaking exploits in extreme sport are redefining the limits of being human. Right now, more people are risking their lives for their sports then ever before in history. As Thomas Pynchon once put it in Gravity&#8217;s Rainbow, &#8216;it is not often that Death is told so clearly to f@%* off&#8217;. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-of-superman-decoding-the-science-of-ultimate-human-performance-steven-kotler-abridged/">The Rise of Superman : Decoding the Science of Ultimate Human Performance &#8211; Steven Kotler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A razor-sharp analysis of how record-breaking exploits in extreme sport are redefining the limits of being human.    </p>
<p>                    Right now, more people are risking their lives for their sports then ever before in history. As Thomas Pynchon once put it in Gravity&#8217;s Rainbow, &#8216;it is not often that Death is told so clearly to f@%* off&#8217;.     </p>
<p>                    Over the past three decades, the bounds of the possible in action and adventure sports &#8211; from sky-diving to motocross to surfing and beyond &#8211; have been pushed farther and faster. A generation&#8217;s worth of iconoclastic misfits have rewritten the rules of the feasible; not just raising the bar, but obliterating it altogether. Along the way, they have become a force pushing evolution relentlessly onward.     </p>
<p>                    In a thrilling narrative that draws on biology, psychology, and philosophy, Steven Kotler asks why, at the tail end of the 20th century and the early portion of the 21st, are we seeing such a multi-sport assault on reality? Did we somehow slip through a wormhole to another universe where gravity is optional and common sense obsolete? And where &#8211; if anywhere &#8211; do our actual limits lie?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-rise-of-superman-decoding-the-science-of-ultimate-human-performance-steven-kotler-abridged/">The Rise of Superman : Decoding the Science of Ultimate Human Performance &#8211; Steven Kotler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Charities, Voluntary Services & Philanthropy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Applications Of Scientific Research & Technological Innovation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industry & Industrial Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Other Technologies & Applied Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>TheNew York Timesbestselling &#8220;manifesto for the future that is grounded in practical solutions addressing the world&#8217;s most pressing concerns: overpopulation, food, water, energy, education, health care and freedom&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal). Since the dawn of humanity, a privileged few have lived in stark contrast to the hardscrabble majority. Conventional wisdom says this gap cannot [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/">Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TheNew York Timesbestselling &#8220;manifesto for the future that is grounded in practical solutions addressing the world&#8217;s most pressing concerns: overpopulation, food, water, energy, education, health care and freedom&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).     </p>
<p>                    Since the dawn of humanity, a privileged few have lived in stark contrast to the hardscrabble majority. Conventional wisdom says this gap cannot be closed. But it is closing-fast.     </p>
<p>                    InAbundance, space entrepreneur turned innovation pioneer Peter H. Diamandis and award-winning science writer Steven Kotler document how progress in artificial intelligence, robotics, digital manufacturing synthetic biology, and other exponentially growing technologies will enable us to make greater gains in the next two decades than we have in the previous 200 years. We will soon have the ability to meet and exceed the basic needs of every person on the planet. Abundance for all is within our grasp.     </p>
<p>                    Breaking down human needs by category-water, food, energy, healthcare, education, freedom-Diamandis and Kotler introduce us to innovators and industry captains making tremendous strides in each area. &#8220;Not only isAbundancea riveting page-turner&#8230;but it&#8217;s a book that gives us a future worth fighting for. And even more than that, it shows us our place in that fight&#8221; (The Christian Science Monitor).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/abundance-the-future-is-better-than-you-think-peter-h-diamandis-steven-kotler-abridged/">Abundance : The Future Is Better Than You Think &#8211; Peter H. Diamandis, Steven Kotler (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Atomic Accidents : A History of Nuclear Meltdowns and Disasters: From the Ozark Mountains to Fukushima &#8211; James Mahaffey (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/atomic-accidents-a-history-of-nuclear-meltdowns-and-disasters-from-the-ozark-mountains-to-fukushima-james-mahaffey-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nuclear Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nuclear Power & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nuclear Structure Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Safety In The Home]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Impact Of Disasters]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/atomic-accidents-a-history-of-nuclear-meltdowns-and-disasters-from-the-ozark-mountains-to-fukushima-james-mahaffey-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the moment radiation was discovered in the late nineteenth century, nuclear science has had a rich history of innovative scientific exploration and discovery, coupled with mistakes, accidents, and downright disasters. Mahaffey, a long-time advocate of continued nuclear research and nuclear energy, looks at each incident in turn and analyzes what happened and why, often [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/atomic-accidents-a-history-of-nuclear-meltdowns-and-disasters-from-the-ozark-mountains-to-fukushima-james-mahaffey-abridged/">Atomic Accidents : A History of Nuclear Meltdowns and Disasters: From the Ozark Mountains to Fukushima &#8211; James Mahaffey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the moment radiation was discovered in the late nineteenth century, nuclear science has had a rich history of innovative scientific exploration and discovery, coupled with mistakes, accidents, and downright disasters.    </p>
<p>                     Mahaffey, a long-time advocate of continued nuclear research and nuclear energy, looks at each incident in turn and analyzes what happened and why, often discovering where scientists went wrong when analyzing past meltdowns.    </p>
<p>                     Every incident has lead to new facets in understanding about the mighty atom-and Mahaffey puts forth what the future should be for this final frontier of science that still holds so much promise.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/atomic-accidents-a-history-of-nuclear-meltdowns-and-disasters-from-the-ozark-mountains-to-fukushima-james-mahaffey-abridged/">Atomic Accidents : A History of Nuclear Meltdowns and Disasters: From the Ozark Mountains to Fukushima &#8211; James Mahaffey (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks &#8211; Rebecca Skloot (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bio-ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biochemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Science, Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Black & Asian Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cellular Biology (cytology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Ethics & Professional Conduct]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Her name was Henrietta Lacks, but scientists know her as HeLa. Born a poor black tobacco farmer, her cancer cells &#8211; taken without her knowledge &#8211; became a multimillion-dollar industry and one of the most important tools in medicine. Yet Henrietta&#8217;s family did not learn of her &#8216;immortality&#8217; until more than twenty years after her [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/">The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks &#8211; Rebecca Skloot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Her name was Henrietta Lacks, but scientists know her as HeLa. Born a poor black tobacco farmer, her cancer cells &#8211; taken without her knowledge &#8211; became a multimillion-dollar industry and one of the most important tools in medicine. Yet Henrietta&#8217;s family did not learn of her &#8216;immortality&#8217; until more than twenty years after her death, with devastating consequences . . .     </p>
<p>                    Rebecca Skloot&#8217;s fascinating account is the story of the life, and afterlife, of one woman who changed the medical world forever. Balancing the beauty and drama of scientific discovery with dark questions about who owns the stuff our bodies are made of, The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks is an extraordinary journey in search of the soul and story of a real woman, whose cells live on today in all four corners of the world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-immortal-life-of-henrietta-lacks-rebecca-skloot-abridged/">The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks &#8211; Rebecca Skloot (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the inventor of the most innovative and compelling technology of our era, an international authority on artificial intelligence, and one of our greatest living visionaries. Now he offers a framework for envisioning the twenty-first century&#8211;an age in which the marriage of human sensitivity and artificial intelligence fundamentally alters and improves the way [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the inventor of the most innovative and compelling technology of our era, an international authority on artificial intelligence, and one of our greatest living visionaries. Now he offers a framework for envisioning the twenty-first century&#8211;an age in which the marriage of human sensitivity and artificial intelligence fundamentally alters and improves the way we live. Kurzweil&#8217;s prophetic blueprint for the future takes us through the advances that inexorably result in computers exceeding the memory capacity and computational ability of the human brain by the year 2020 (with human-level capabilities not far behind); in relationships with automated personalities who will be our teachers, companions, and lovers; and in information fed straight into our brains along direct neural pathways. Optimistic and challenging, thought-provoking and engaging, The Age of Spiritual Machines is the ultimate guide on our road into the next century.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-age-of-spiritual-machines-when-computers-exceed-human-intelligence-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">The Age of Spiritual Machines : When Computers Exceed Human Intelligence &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Particle at the End of the Universe : Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-particle-at-the-end-of-the-universe-winner-of-the-royal-society-winton-prize-sean-carroll-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Atomic & Molecular Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Particle & High-energy Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Research Methods: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-particle-at-the-end-of-the-universe-winner-of-the-royal-society-winton-prize-sean-carroll-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books A Best Science Book of the Year for the Guardian, Financial Times, and New Scientist It was the universe&#8217;s most elusive particle, the linchpin for everything scientists dreamed up to explain how physics works. It had to be found. But projects as big as CERN&#8217;s [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-particle-at-the-end-of-the-universe-winner-of-the-royal-society-winton-prize-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Particle at the End of the Universe : Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize for Science Books    </p>
<p>                    A Best Science Book of the Year for the Guardian, Financial Times, and New Scientist    </p>
<p>                    It was the universe&#8217;s most elusive particle, the linchpin for everything scientists dreamed up to explain how physics works. It had to be found. But projects as big as CERN&#8217;s Large Hadron Collider don&#8217;t happen without incredible risks &#8211; or occasional skulduggery. In the definitive account of the greatest science story of our time, acclaimed physicist Sean Carroll reveals the insights, rivalry, and wonder that fuelled the Higgs discovery, and takes us on a riveting and irresistible ride to the very edge of physics today.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-particle-at-the-end-of-the-universe-winner-of-the-royal-society-winton-prize-sean-carroll-abridged/">The Particle at the End of the Universe : Winner of the Royal Society Winton Prize &#8211; Sean Carroll (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Archaeological Methodology & Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Early Man]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The past few years have seen a revolution in our ability to map whole genome DNA from ancient humans. With the ancient DNA revolution, combined with rapid genome mapping of present human populations, has come remarkable insights into our past. This important new data has clarified and added to our knowledge from archaeology and anthropology, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/">Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The past few years have seen a revolution in our ability to map whole genome DNA from ancient humans. With the ancient DNA revolution, combined with rapid genome mapping of present human populations, has come remarkable insights into our past. This important new data has clarified and added to our knowledge from archaeology and anthropology, helped resolve long-existing controversies, challenged long-held views, and thrown up some remarkable surprises.    </p>
<p>                    The emerging picture is one of many waves of ancient human migrations, so that all populations existing today are mixes of ancient ones, as well as in many cases carrying a genetic component from Neanderthals, and, in some populations, Denisovans. David Reich, whose team has been at the forefront of these discoveries, explains what the genetics is telling us about ourselves and our complex and often surprising ancestry. Gone are old ideas of any kind of racial &#8216;purity&#8217;, or even deep and ancient<br />
                    divides between peoples. Instead, we are finding a rich variety of mixtures. Reich describes the cutting-edge findings from the past few years, and also considers the sensitivities involved in tracing ancestry, with science sometimes jostling with politics and tradition. He brings an important wider<br />
                    message: that we should celebrate our rich diversity, and recognize that every one of us is the result of a long history of migration and intermixing of ancient peoples, which we carry as ghosts in our DNA.    </p>
<p>                    What will we discover next?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/who-we-are-and-how-we-got-here-ancient-dna-and-the-new-science-of-the-human-past-david-reich-abridged/">Who We Are and How We Got Here : Ancient DNA and the new science of the human past &#8211; David Reich (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why Is Sex Fun? : The Evolution of Human Sexuality &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anthropology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physical Anthropology & Ethnography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sex & Sexuality, Sex Manuals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sexual Behaviour]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A fascinating insight into how human sexuality came to be the way it is now &#8211; Jared Diamond explains why we are different from the animal kingdom. Why are humans one of the few species to have sex in private? Why do humans have sex any day of the month or year, including when the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/">Why Is Sex Fun? : The Evolution of Human Sexuality &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A fascinating insight into how human sexuality came to be the way it is now &#8211; Jared Diamond explains why we are different from the animal kingdom.    </p>
<p>                    Why are humans one of the few species to have sex in private? Why do humans have sex any day of the month or year, including when the female is pregnant, beyond her reproductive years, or between her fertile cycles? Why are human females one of the few mammals to go through menopause?    </p>
<p>                    Human sexuality seems normal to us but it is bizarre by the standards of other animals. Jared Diamond argues that our strange sex lives were as crucial to our rise to human status as were our large brains. He also describes the battle of the sexes in the human and animal world over parental care, and why sex differences in the genetic value of parental care provide a biological basis for the all-too-familiar different attitudes of men and women towards extramarital sex.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/why-is-sex-fun-the-evolution-of-human-sexuality-jared-diamond-abridged/">Why Is Sex Fun? : The Evolution of Human Sexuality &#8211; Jared Diamond (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Assertiveness, Motivation & Self-esteem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memory Improvement & Thinking Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organizational Theory & Behaviour]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Habits are more powerful than your will &#8211; if you know how to make them work for you Two strings are hanging from a ceiling, one at the centre of the room, one near the wall. You&#8217;re asked to tie the strings together, but you can&#8217;t reach both at the same time. You look around [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/">Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Habits are more powerful than your will &#8211; if you know how to make them work for you    </p>
<p>                    Two strings are hanging from a ceiling, one at the centre of the room, one near the wall. You&#8217;re asked to tie the strings together, but you can&#8217;t reach both at the same time. You look around the room and see a table and a pair of pliers. How would you solve the problem?    </p>
<p>                    When confronted with challenges, most people let habits rule them (in this case, ignoring the pliers, the creative tool at your disposal). That is not surprising when you realise that at least a third of our waking hours are lived on auto-pilot &#8211; ruminating over past events, clicking through websites trawling for updates and the like. Such unconscious thoughts and actions are powerful. But the habits of the mind do not have to control us &#8211; we can steer them.    </p>
<p>                    Drawing on hundreds of fascinating studies, psychologist Jeremy Dean &#8211; the mind behind the hugely popular and insightful website PsyBlog &#8211; shares how the new brain science of habit can be harnessed to your benefit, whether you&#8217;re hoping to eat moreveg, take an evening run, clear out your email backlog, or be more creative when faced with challenges at work and at home.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-habits-breaking-habits-how-to-make-changes-that-stick-jeremy-dean-abridged/">Making Habits, Breaking Habits : How to Make Changes that Stick &#8211; Jeremy Dean (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Disability]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Listening Skills]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Study & Learning Skills: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>BRILLIANT&#8217; Chris Evans, Virgin Radio Breakfast Show When was the last time you listened to someone, or someone really listened to you? This life-changing book will transform your conversations forever. At work, we&#8217;re taught to lead the conversation. On social media, we shape our personal narratives. At parties, we talk over one another. So do [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/">You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>BRILLIANT&#8217; Chris Evans, Virgin Radio Breakfast Show    </p>
<p>                    When was the last time you listened to someone, or someone really listened to you?     </p>
<p>                    This life-changing book will transform your conversations forever.    </p>
<p>                     At work, we&#8217;re taught to lead the conversation.    </p>
<p>                     On social media, we shape our personal narratives.    </p>
<p>                     At parties, we talk over one another. So do our politicians.    </p>
<p>                     We&#8217;re not listening.    </p>
<p>                     And no one is listening to us.    </p>
<p>                    Now more than ever, we need to listen to those around us. New York Times contributor Kate Murphy draws on countless conversations she has had with everyone from priests to CIA interrogators, focus group moderators to bartenders, her great-great aunt to her friend&#8217;s toddler, to show how only by listening well can we truly connect with others.    </p>
<p>                     Listening has the potential to transform our relationships and our working lives, improve our self-knowledge, and increase our creativity and happiness. While it may take some effort, it&#8217;s a skill that can be learnt and perfected.    </p>
<p>                     When all we crave is to understand and be understood, You&#8217;re Not Listening shows us how.    </p>
<p>                    * With a new afterword by the author *    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;This book couldn&#8217;t be more timely. Inspiringly profound&#8230;smart and playful&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;I&#8217;ll be adopting Murphy&#8217;s advice&#8217; Sunday Times, Style</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/youre-not-listening-what-youre-missing-and-why-it-matters-kate-murphy-abridged/">You&#8217;re Not Listening : What You&#8217;re Missing and Why It Matters &#8211; Kate Murphy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Inflamed Mind : A radical new approach to depression &#8211; Edward Bullmore (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-inflamed-mind-a-radical-new-approach-to-depression-edward-bullmore-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-inflamed-mind-a-radical-new-approach-to-depression-edward-bullmore-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Depression will be the single biggest cause of disability worldwide, in the next 20 years. But treatment for it has not changed much in the last three decades. In the realm of psychiatry, time has apparently stood still&#8230; until now. In this game-changing book, Professor Edward Bullmore reveals the breakthrough new science on the link [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-inflamed-mind-a-radical-new-approach-to-depression-edward-bullmore-abridged/">The Inflamed Mind : A radical new approach to depression &#8211; Edward Bullmore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Depression will be the single biggest cause of disability worldwide, in the next 20 years. But treatment for it has not changed much in the last three decades. In the realm of psychiatry, time has apparently stood still&#8230; until now.    </p>
<p>                    In this game-changing book, Professor Edward Bullmore reveals the breakthrough new science on the link between mental depression and physical inflammation. He explains how and why mental disorders can have their roots in the immune system and explores a whole new way of looking at how mind, brain and body all work together in a sometimes misguided effort to help us survive in a hostile world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-inflamed-mind-a-radical-new-approach-to-depression-edward-bullmore-abridged/">The Inflamed Mind : A radical new approach to depression &#8211; Edward Bullmore (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inheritance : How Our Genes Change Our Lives, and Our Lives Change Our Genes &#8211; Dr Sharon Moalem (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inheritance-how-our-genes-change-our-lives-and-our-lives-change-our-genes-dr-sharon-moalem-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inheritance-how-our-genes-change-our-lives-and-our-lives-change-our-genes-dr-sharon-moalem-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking book that will transform how we understand ourselves and our families by revealing that everything we thought we knew about genetics is wrong. Your experiences, no matter how seemingly inconsequential &#8211; from bullies to crushes to what you eat for dinner &#8211; have all left an indelible mark within you. And more importantly, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inheritance-how-our-genes-change-our-lives-and-our-lives-change-our-genes-dr-sharon-moalem-abridged/">Inheritance : How Our Genes Change Our Lives, and Our Lives Change Our Genes &#8211; Dr Sharon Moalem (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A groundbreaking book that will transform how we understand ourselves and our families by revealing that everything we thought we knew about genetics is wrong.     </p>
<p>                    Your experiences, no matter how seemingly inconsequential &#8211; from bullies to crushes to what you eat for dinner &#8211; have all left an indelible mark within you. And more importantly, within your genes.    </p>
<p>                    Inheritance is a guidebook for change. No longer do we have to settle for what we&#8217;ve been given. We can write our own story.    </p>
<p>                    We&#8217;re taught that we don&#8217;t have much of a choice in the matter of what we get or what we give, because our genetic legacy was fixed when our parents conceived us. But that&#8217;s all wrong. Our genes are constantly on the move, some are turning on while others are turning off, all in response to what you&#8217;re doing, what you&#8217;re seeing, and what you&#8217;re feeling. And all of those things can be changed, which means we can change. Genetically.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inheritance-how-our-genes-change-our-lives-and-our-lives-change-our-genes-dr-sharon-moalem-abridged/">Inheritance : How Our Genes Change Our Lives, and Our Lives Change Our Genes &#8211; Dr Sharon Moalem (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>If I Understood You, Would I Have This Look on My Face? : My Adventures in the Art and Science of Relating and Communicating &#8211; Alan Alda (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/if-i-understood-you-would-i-have-this-look-on-my-face-my-adventures-in-the-art-and-science-of-relating-and-communicating-alan-alda-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal Development]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/if-i-understood-you-would-i-have-this-look-on-my-face-my-adventures-in-the-art-and-science-of-relating-and-communicating-alan-alda-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Award-winning actor Alan Alda tells the fascinating story of his quest to learn how to communicate better, and to teach others to do the same. With his trademark humor and candor, he explores how to develop empathy as the key factor. &#8220;Invaluable.&#8221;&#8211;Deborah Tannen, #1 New York Times bestselling author of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/if-i-understood-you-would-i-have-this-look-on-my-face-my-adventures-in-the-art-and-science-of-relating-and-communicating-alan-alda-abridged/">If I Understood You, Would I Have This Look on My Face? : My Adventures in the Art and Science of Relating and Communicating &#8211; Alan Alda (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; Award-winning actor Alan Alda tells the fascinating story of his quest to learn how to communicate better, and to teach others to do the same. With his trademark humor and candor, he explores how to develop empathy as the key factor.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Invaluable.&#8221;&#8211;Deborah Tannen, #1 New York Times bestselling author of You&#8217;re the Only One I Can Tell and You Just Don&#8217;t Understand  Alan Alda has been on a decades-long journey to discover new ways to help people communicate and relate to one another more effectively. If I Understood You, Would I Have This Look on My Face? is the warm, witty, and informative chronicle of how Alda found inspiration in everything from cutting-edge science to classic acting methods. His search began when he was host of PBS&#8217;s Scientific American Frontiers,  where he interviewed thousands of scientists and developed a knack for helping them communicate complex ideas in ways a wide audience could understand&#8211;and Alda wondered if those techniques held a clue to better communication for the rest of us.  In his wry and wise voice, Alda reflects on moments of miscommunication in his own life, when an absence of understanding resulted in problems both big and small. He guides us through his discoveries, showing how communication can be improved through learning to relate to the other person: listening with our eyes, looking for clues in another&#8217;s face, using the power of a compelling story, avoiding jargon, and reading another person so well that you become &#8220;in sync&#8221; with them, and know what they are thinking and feeling&#8211;especially when you&#8217;re talking about the hard stuff.  Drawing on improvisation training, theater, and storytelling techniques from a life of acting, and with insights from recent scientific studies, Alda describes ways we can build empathy, nurture our innate mind-reading abilities, and improve the way we relate and talk with others. Exploring empathy-boosting games and exercises, If I Understood You is a funny, thought-provoking guide that can be used by all of us, in every aspect of our lives&#8211;with our friends, lovers, and families, with our doctors, in business settings, and beyond. &#8220;Alda uses his trademark humor and a well-honed ability to get to the point, to help us all learn how to leverage the better communicator inside each of us.&#8221;&#8211;Forbes &#8220;Alda, with his laudable curiosity, has learned something you and I can use right now.&#8221;&#8211;Charlie Rose</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/if-i-understood-you-would-i-have-this-look-on-my-face-my-adventures-in-the-art-and-science-of-relating-and-communicating-alan-alda-abridged/">If I Understood You, Would I Have This Look on My Face? : My Adventures in the Art and Science of Relating and Communicating &#8211; Alan Alda (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical Issues: Scientific & Technological Developments]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;A gifted and thoughtful writer, Metzl brings us to the frontiers of biology and technology, and reveals a world full of promise and peril.&#8221; -Siddhartha Mukherjee MD, New York Times bestselling author of The Emperor of All Maladies and The Gene<br />
                    Passionate, provocative, and highly illuminating, Hacking Darwin is the must read book about the future of our species for fans of Homo Deus and The Gene.<br />
                    After 3.8 billion years humankind is about to start evolving by new rules&#8230;<br />
                    From leading geopolitical expert and technology futurist Jamie Metzl comes a groundbreaking exploration of the many ways genetic-engineering is shaking the core foundations of our lives-sex, war, love, and death.<br />
                    At the dawn of the genetics revolution, our DNA is becoming as readable, writable, and hackable as our information technology. But as humanity starts retooling our own genetic code, the choices we make today will be the difference between realizing breathtaking advances in human well-being and descending into a dangerous and potentially deadly genetic arms race.<br />
                    Enter the laboratories where scientists are turning science fiction into reality. Look towards a future where our deepest beliefs, morals, religions, and politics are challenged like never before and the very essence of what it means to be human is at play. When we can engineer our future children, massively extend our lifespans, build life from scratch, and recreate the plant and animal world, should we?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hacking-darwin-genetic-engineering-and-the-future-of-humanity-jamie-metzl-abridged/">Hacking Darwin : Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity &#8211; Jamie Metzl (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Grand Design &#8211; Leonard Mlodinow, Stephen Hawking (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-grand-design-leonard-mlodinow-stephen-hawking-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relativity Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-grand-design-leonard-mlodinow-stephen-hawking-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When and how did the universe begin? Why are we here? Is the apparent &#8216;grand design&#8217; of our universe evidence for a benevolent creator who set things in motion? Or does science offer another explanation? In The Grand Design, the most recent scientific thinking about the mysteries of the universe is presented in language marked [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-grand-design-leonard-mlodinow-stephen-hawking-abridged/">The Grand Design &#8211; Leonard Mlodinow, Stephen Hawking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When and how did the universe begin? Why are we here? Is the apparent &#8216;grand design&#8217; of our universe evidence for a benevolent creator who set things in motion? Or does science offer another explanation?     </p>
<p>                    In The Grand Design, the most recent scientific thinking about the mysteries of the universe is presented in language marked by both brilliance and simplicity. Model dependent realism, the multiverse, the top-down theory of cosmology, and the unified M-theory &#8211; all are revealed here.    </p>
<p>                    This is the first major work in nearly a decade by one of the world&#8217;s greatest thinkers. A succinct, startling and lavishly illustrated guide to discoveries that are altering our understanding and threatening some of our most cherished belief systems, The Grand Design is a book that will inform &#8211; and provoke &#8211; like no other.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-grand-design-leonard-mlodinow-stephen-hawking-abridged/">The Grand Design &#8211; Leonard Mlodinow, Stephen Hawking (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Adventures in Human Being &#8211; Gavin Francis (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/adventures-in-human-being-gavin-francis-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physiology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/adventures-in-human-being-gavin-francis-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Sunday Times bestseller We have a lifetime&#8217;s association with our bodies, but for many of us they remain uncharted territory. In Adventures in Human Being, Gavin Francis leads the reader on a journey through health and illness, offering insights on everything from the ribbed surface of the brain to the secret workings of the heart [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adventures-in-human-being-gavin-francis-abridged/">Adventures in Human Being &#8211; Gavin Francis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sunday Times bestseller    </p>
<p>                    We have a lifetime&#8217;s association with our bodies, but for many of us they remain uncharted territory. In Adventures in Human Being, Gavin Francis leads the reader on a journey through health and illness, offering insights on everything from the ribbed surface of the brain to the secret workings of the heart and the womb; from the pulse of life at the wrist to the unique engineering of the foot.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on his own experiences as a doctor and GP, he blends first-hand case studies with reflections on the way the body has been imagined and portrayed over the millennia. If the body is a foreign country, then to practise medicine is to explore new territory: Francis leads the reader on an adventure through what it means to be human.     </p>
<p>                    Both a user&#8217;s guide to the body and a celebration of its elegance, this book will transform the way you think about being alive, whether in sickness or in health.    </p>
<p>                    Published in association with the Wellcome Collection.    </p>
<p>                    WELLCOME COLLECTION    </p>
<p>                    Wellcome Collection is a free museum and library that aims to challenge how we think and feel about health. Inspired by the medical objects and curiosities collected by Henry Wellcome, it connects science, medicine, life and art. Wellcome Collection exhibitions, events and books explore a diverse range of subjects, including consciousness, forensic medicine, emotions, sexology, identity and death.     </p>
<p>                    Wellcome Collection is part of Wellcome, a global charitable foundation that exists to improve health for everyone by helping great ideas to thrive, funding over 14,000 researchers and projects in more than 70 countries.    </p>
<p>                    wellcomecollection.org</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/adventures-in-human-being-gavin-francis-abridged/">Adventures in Human Being &#8211; Gavin Francis (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Game Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetic Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The million copy international bestseller, critically acclaimed and translated into over 25 languages. As influential today as when it was first published, The Selfish Gene has become a classic exposition of evolutionary thought. Professor Dawkins articulates a gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution &#8211; a view giving centre stage to these persistent units of information, and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The million copy international bestseller, critically acclaimed and translated into over 25 languages.    </p>
<p>                    As influential today as when it was first published, The Selfish Gene  has become a classic exposition of evolutionary thought. Professor Dawkins articulates a gene&#8217;s eye view of evolution &#8211; a view giving centre stage to these persistent units of information, and in which organisms can be seen as vehicles for their replication. This imaginative, powerful, and stylistically brilliant work not only brought the insights of Neo-Darwinism to a wide audience, but galvanized the biology<br />
                    community, generating much debate and stimulating whole new areas of research. Forty years later, its insights remain as relevant today as on the day it was published.     </p>
<p>                    This 40th anniversary edition includes a new epilogue from the author discussing the continuing relevance of these ideas in evolutionary biology today, as well as the original prefaces and foreword, and extracts from early reviews.     </p>
<p>                    Oxford Landmark Science books are &#8216;must-read&#8217; classics of modern science writing which have crystallized big ideas, and shaped the way we think.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-selfish-gene-40th-anniversary-edition-richard-dawkins-abridged/">The Selfish Gene : 40th Anniversary edition &#8211; Richard Dawkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh : The Story of Heredity, Its Past, Present and Future &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2018 BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh presents a profoundly original perspective on what we pass along from generation to generation. Charles Darwin played a crucial part in turning heredity into a scientific question, and yet he failed spectacularly to answer it. The birth of genetics in the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/">She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh : The Story of Heredity, Its Past, Present and Future &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>SHORTLISTED FOR THE 2018 BAILLIE GIFFORD PRIZE FOR NON-FICTION    </p>
<p>                    She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh presents a profoundly original perspective on what we pass along from generation to generation. Charles Darwin played a crucial part in turning heredity into a scientific question, and yet he failed spectacularly to answer it. The birth of genetics in the early 1900s seemed to do precisely that. Gradually, people translated their old notions about heredity into a language of genes. As the technology for studying genes became cheaper, millions of people ordered genetic tests to link themselves to missing parents, to distant ancestors, to ethnic identities . . .    </p>
<p>                    But, award-winning science writer Carl Zimmer argues, heredity isn&#8217;t just about genes that pass from parent to child. Heredity continues within our own bodies, as a single cell gives rise to trillions of cells that make up our bodies. We say we inherit genes from our ancestors but we inherit other things that matter as much or more to our lives, from microbes to technologies we use to make life more comfortable. We need a new definition of what heredity is and, through Carl Zimmer&#8217;s lucid exposition and storytelling, this resounding tour de force delivers it.    </p>
<p>                    Weaving together historical and current scientific research, his own experience with his two daughters, and the kind of original reporting expected of one of the world&#8217;s best science journalists, Zimmer ultimately unpacks urgent bioethical quandaries arising from new biomedical technologies, but also long-standing presumptions about who we really are and what we can pass on to future generations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/she-has-her-mothers-laugh-the-story-of-heredity-its-past-present-and-future-carl-zimmer-abridged/">She Has Her Mother&#8217;s Laugh : The Story of Heredity, Its Past, Present and Future &#8211; Carl Zimmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Laws of Thermodynamics: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Peter Atkins (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-laws-of-thermodynamics-a-very-short-introduction-peter-atkins-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Thermodynamics & Heat]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-laws-of-thermodynamics-a-very-short-introduction-peter-atkins-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From the sudden expansion of a cloud of gas or the cooling of a hot metal, to the unfolding of a thought in our minds and even the course of life itself, everything is governed by the four Laws of Thermodynamics. These laws specify the nature of &#8216;energy&#8217; and &#8216;temperature&#8217;, and are soon revealed to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-laws-of-thermodynamics-a-very-short-introduction-peter-atkins-abridged/">The Laws of Thermodynamics: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Peter Atkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From the sudden expansion of a cloud of gas or the cooling of a hot metal, to the unfolding of a thought in our minds and even the course of life itself, everything is governed by the four Laws of Thermodynamics. These laws specify the nature of &#8216;energy&#8217; and &#8216;temperature&#8217;, and are soon revealed to reach out and define the arrow of time itself: why things change and why death must come.     </p>
<p>                    In this Very Short Introduction Peter Atkins explains the basis and deeper implications of each law, highlighting their relevance in everyday examples. Using the minimum of mathematics, he introduces concepts such as entropy, free energy, and to the brink and beyond of the absolute zero temperature. These are not merely abstract ideas: they govern our lives.     </p>
<p>                    In this concise and compelling introduction Atkins paints a lucid picture of the four elegant laws that, between them, drive the Universe.    </p>
<p>                    ABOUT THE SERIES: The Very Short Introductions series from Oxford University Press contains hundreds of titles in almost every subject area. These pocket-sized books are the perfect way to get ahead in a new subject quickly. Our expert authors combine facts, analysis, perspective, new ideas, and enthusiasm to make interesting and challenging topics highly readable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-laws-of-thermodynamics-a-very-short-introduction-peter-atkins-abridged/">The Laws of Thermodynamics: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Peter Atkins (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Brief History of Everyone Who Ever Lived : The Stories in Our Genes &#8211; Adam Rutherford (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/a-brief-history-of-everyone-who-ever-lived-the-stories-in-our-genes-adam-rutherford-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DNA & Genome]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genealogy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medical Genetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/a-brief-history-of-everyone-who-ever-lived-the-stories-in-our-genes-adam-rutherford-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A brilliant, authoritative, surprising, captivating introduction to human genetics. You&#8217;ll be spellbound&#8217; Brian Cox This is a story about you. It is the history of who you are and how you came to be. It is unique to you, as it is to each of the 100 billion modern humans who have ever drawn breath. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-brief-history-of-everyone-who-ever-lived-the-stories-in-our-genes-adam-rutherford-abridged/">A Brief History of Everyone Who Ever Lived : The Stories in Our Genes &#8211; Adam Rutherford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A brilliant, authoritative, surprising, captivating introduction to human genetics. You&#8217;ll be spellbound&#8217; Brian Cox    </p>
<p>                    This is a story about you.     </p>
<p>                    It is the history of who you are and how you came to be. It is unique to you, as it is to each of the 100 billion modern humans who have ever drawn breath. But it is also our collective story, because in every one of our genomes we each carry the history of our species &#8211; births, deaths, disease, war, famine, migration and a lot of sex.     </p>
<p>                    In this captivating journey through the expanding landscape of genetics, Adam Rutherford reveals what our genes now tell us about human history, and what history can now tell us about our genes. From Neanderthals to murder, from redheads to race, dead kings to plague, evolution to epigenetics, this is a demystifying and illuminating new portrait of who we are and how we came to be.    </p>
<p>                    ***    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A thoroughly entertaining history of Homo sapiens and its DNA in a manner that displays popular science writing at its best&#8217; Observer     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Magisterial, informative and delightful&#8217; Peter Frankopan    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;An extraordinary adventure&#8230;From the Neanderthals to the Vikings, from the Queen of Sheba to Richard III, Rutherford goes in search of our ancestors, tracing the genetic clues deep into the past&#8217; Alice Roberts</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/a-brief-history-of-everyone-who-ever-lived-the-stories-in-our-genes-adam-rutherford-abridged/">A Brief History of Everyone Who Ever Lived : The Stories in Our Genes &#8211; Adam Rutherford (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Art of Statistics : Learning from Data &#8211; David Spiegelhalter (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-art-of-statistics-learning-from-data-david-spiegelhalter-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Analysis: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-art-of-statistics-learning-from-data-david-spiegelhalter-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A statistical national treasure&#8217; Jeremy Vine, BBC Radio 2 &#8216;Required reading for all politicians, journalists, medics and anyone who tries to influence people (or is influenced) by statistics. A tour de force&#8217; Popular Science Do busier hospitals have higher survival rates? How many trees are there on the planet? Why do old men have big [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-statistics-learning-from-data-david-spiegelhalter-abridged/">The Art of Statistics : Learning from Data &#8211; David Spiegelhalter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A statistical national treasure&#8217; Jeremy Vine, BBC Radio 2    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Required reading for all politicians, journalists, medics and anyone who tries to influence people (or is influenced) by statistics. A tour de force&#8217; Popular Science    </p>
<p>                    Do busier hospitals have higher survival rates? How many trees are there on the planet? Why do old men have big ears? David Spiegelhalter reveals the answers to these and many other questions &#8211; questions that can only be addressed using statistical science.    </p>
<p>                    Statistics has played a leading role in our scientific understanding of the world for centuries, yet we are all familiar with the way statistical claims can be sensationalised, particularly in the media. In the age of big data, as data science becomes established as a discipline, a basic grasp of statistical literacy is more important than ever.     </p>
<p>                    In The Art of Statistics, David Spiegelhalter guides the reader through the essential principles we need in order to derive knowledge from data. Drawing on real world problems to introduce conceptual issues, he shows us how statistics can help us determine the luckiest passenger on the Titanic, whether serial killer Harold Shipman could have been caught earlier, and if screening for ovarian cancer is beneficial.     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Shines a light on how we can use the ever-growing deluge of data to improve our understanding of the world&#8217; Nature</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-art-of-statistics-learning-from-data-david-spiegelhalter-abridged/">The Art of Statistics : Learning from Data &#8211; David Spiegelhalter (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agricultural Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Farming]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Beverage Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sustainable Agriculture]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is the future of food looking bleak &#8211; or better than ever? At a time when every day brings news of drought and famine, Amanda Little investigates what it will take to feed a hotter, hungrier, more crowded world. She explores the past along with the present and discovers startling innovations: remote-control crops, vertical farms, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/">The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Is the future of food looking bleak &#8211; or better than ever?    </p>
<p>                    At a time when every day brings news of drought and famine, Amanda Little investigates what it will take to feed a hotter, hungrier, more crowded world.    </p>
<p>                    She explores the past along with the present and discovers startling innovations: remote-control crops, vertical farms, robot weedkillers, lab-grown meat, 3D-printed meals, water networks run by supercomputers, cloud seeding and sensors that monitor the microclimate of individual plants. She meets the creative and controversial minds changing the face of modern food production, and tackles fears over genetic modification with hard facts.    </p>
<p>                    The Fate of Food is a fascinating look at the threats and opportunities that lie ahead as we struggle for food security.    </p>
<p>                    Faced with a perilous future, it gives us reason to hope.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-fate-of-food-what-well-eat-in-a-bigger-hotter-smarter-world-amanda-little-abridged/">The Fate of Food : What We&#8217;ll Eat in a Bigger, Hotter, Smarter World &#8211; Amanda Little (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Contain Multitudes : The Microbes Within Us and a Grander View of Life &#8211; Ed Yong (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-contain-multitudes-the-microbes-within-us-and-a-grander-view-of-life-ed-yong-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biology, Life Sciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Life Sciences: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Zoology & Animal Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-contain-multitudes-the-microbes-within-us-and-a-grander-view-of-life-ed-yong-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER FROM THE WINNER OF THE 2021 PULITZER PRIZE Your body is teeming with tens of trillions of microbes. It&#8217;s an entire world, a colony full of life. In other words, you contain multitudes. They sculpt our organs, protect us from diseases, guide our behaviour, and bombard us with their genes. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-contain-multitudes-the-microbes-within-us-and-a-grander-view-of-life-ed-yong-abridged/">I Contain Multitudes : The Microbes Within Us and a Grander View of Life &#8211; Ed Yong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER FROM THE WINNER OF THE 2021 PULITZER PRIZE    </p>
<p>                     Your body is teeming with tens of trillions of microbes. It&#8217;s an entire world, a colony full of life.    </p>
<p>                     In other words, you contain multitudes.    </p>
<p>                     They sculpt our organs, protect us from diseases, guide our behaviour, and bombard us with their genes. They also hold the key to understanding all life on earth.    </p>
<p>                     In I Contain Multitudes, Ed Yong opens our eyes and invites us to marvel at ourselves and other animals in a new light, less as individuals and more as thriving ecosystems.    </p>
<p>                     You&#8217;ll never think about your mind, body or preferences in the same way again.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Super-interesting&#8230; He just keeps imparting one surprising, fascinating insight after the next. I Contain Multitudes is science journalism at its best&#8217; Bill Gates<br />
                    SHORTLISTED FOR THE WELLCOME BOOK PRIZE 2017<br />
                     SHORTLISTED FOR THE ROYAL SOCIETY SCIENCE BOOK PRIZE 2017</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-contain-multitudes-the-microbes-within-us-and-a-grander-view-of-life-ed-yong-abridged/">I Contain Multitudes : The Microbes Within Us and a Grander View of Life &#8211; Ed Yong (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Agriculture & Related Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness & Diet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Drink]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[General Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author). We are in the grip of a food [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A lively argument from award-winning journalist proving the key to reversing health crisis lies in the overlooked link between nutrition and flavour: &#8220;The Dorito Effect is one of the most important health and food books I have read&#8221; (Dr. David B. Agus, New York Times bestselling author).<br />
                       We are in the grip of a food crisis. Obesity has become a leading cause of preventable death, after only smoking. For nearly half a century we&#8217;ve been trying to pin the blame somewhere, fat, carbs, sugar, wheat, high-fructose corn syrup. But that search has been in vain, because the food problem that&#8217;s killing us is not a nutrient problem. It&#8217;s a behavioural problem, and it&#8217;s caused by the changing flavour of the food we eat.<br />
                       Ever since the 1940s, with the rise of industrialized food production, we have been gradually leeching the taste out of what we grow. Simultaneously, we have taken great leaps forward in technology, creating a flavour industry, worth billions annually; in an attempt to put back the tastes we&#8217;ve engineered out of our food. The result is a cuisine that increasingly resembles the paragon of flavour manipulation: Doritos. As food becomes increasingly bland, we dress it up with calories and flavour chemicals to make it delicious again. We have rewired our palates and our brains, and the results are making us sick and killing us.<br />
                       With in-depth historical and scientific research, The Dorito Effect casts the food crisis in a fascinating new light, weaving an enthralling tale of how we got to this point and where we are headed.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-dorito-effect-the-surprising-new-truth-about-food-and-flavor-mark-schatzker-abridged/">The Dorito Effect : The Surprising New Truth About Food and Flavor &#8211; Mark Schatzker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Create a Mind : The Secret of Human Thought Revealed &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-create-a-mind-the-secret-of-human-thought-revealed-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-create-a-mind-the-secret-of-human-thought-revealed-ray-kurzweil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the best person I know at predicting the future of artificial intelligence.&#8217; Bill Gates In How to Create a Mind, Ray Kurzweil offers a provocative exploration of the most important project in human-machine civilisation: reverse engineering the brain to understand precisely how it works and using that knowledge to create even more [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-create-a-mind-the-secret-of-human-thought-revealed-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">How to Create a Mind : The Secret of Human Thought Revealed &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ray Kurzweil is the best person I know at predicting the future of artificial intelligence.&#8217; Bill Gates    </p>
<p>                    In How to Create a Mind, Ray Kurzweil offers a provocative exploration of the most important project in human-machine civilisation: reverse engineering the brain to understand precisely how it works and using that knowledge to create even more intelligent machines. Kurzweil explores how the brain functions, how the mind emerges from the brain, and the implications of vastly increasing the powers of our intelligence in addressing the world&#8217;s problems. He thoughtfully examines emotional and moral intelligence and the origins of consciousness and envisions the radical &#8211; arguably inevitable &#8211; future of our merging with the intelligent technology we are creating.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-create-a-mind-the-secret-of-human-thought-revealed-ray-kurzweil-abridged/">How to Create a Mind : The Secret of Human Thought Revealed &#8211; Ray Kurzweil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cookery For Dietary Conditions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dietetics & Nutrition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health & Wholefood Cookery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Immunology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microbiology (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Health & Preventive Medicine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A clarion call to save humanity&#8217;s most essential fellow creatures &#8211; and our health    </p>
<p>                    Far beneath our skin exists an unfathomable, ancient universe &#8211; an internal ecosystem that is critical to our health. Dr Martin Blaser invites us into the wilds of the human &#8216;microbiome&#8217;, unfurling its inner workings and evolution. For thousands of years, bacteria and human cells have co-existed in a relationship that has ensured the health and equilibrium of our body. But now, much like the natural world outside of us, our internal environment is being irrevocably destroyed. The culprit: some of our most revered medical advances &#8211; antibiotics &#8211; which appear to be linked to the epidemics of asthma, eczema, obesity, certain forms of cancer, and other diseases plaguing modern society.    </p>
<p>                    In a book that stands as the Silent Spring of its day, Blaser sounds a provocative alarm that we ignore at our peril.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/missing-microbes-how-killing-bacteria-creates-modern-plagues-martin-blaser-abridged/">Missing Microbes : How Killing Bacteria Creates Modern Plagues &#8211; Martin Blaser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Double Helix: A Personal Account of the Discovery of the Structure of DNA &#8211; James D. Watson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-double-helix-a-personal-account-of-the-discovery-of-the-structure-of-dna-james-d-watson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Genetics (non-medical)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Biology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-double-helix-a-personal-account-of-the-discovery-of-the-structure-of-dna-james-d-watson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The classic personal account of Watson and Crick&#8217;s groundbreaking discovery of the structure of DNA, now with an introduction by Sylvia Nasar, author of A Beautiful Mind. By identifying the structure of DNA, the molecule of life, Francis Crick and James Watson revolutionized biochemistry and won themselves a Nobel Prize. At the time, Watson was [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-double-helix-a-personal-account-of-the-discovery-of-the-structure-of-dna-james-d-watson-abridged/">The Double Helix: A Personal Account of the Discovery of the Structure of DNA &#8211; James D. Watson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The classic personal account of Watson and Crick&#8217;s groundbreaking discovery of the structure of DNA, now with an introduction by Sylvia Nasar, author of A Beautiful Mind.     </p>
<p>                    By identifying the structure of DNA, the molecule of life, Francis Crick and James Watson revolutionized biochemistry and won themselves a Nobel Prize. At the time, Watson was only twenty-four, a young scientist hungry to make his mark. His uncompromisingly honest account of the heady days of their thrilling sprint against other world-class researchers to solve one of science&#8217;s greatest mysteries gives a dazzlingly clear picture of a world of brilliant scientists with great gifts, very human ambitions, and bitter rivalries.     </p>
<p>                    With humility unspoiled by false modesty, Watson relates his and Crick&#8217;s desperate efforts to beat Linus Pauling to the Holy Grail of life sciences, the identification of the basic building block of life. Never has a scientist been so truthful in capturing in words the flavor of his work.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-double-helix-a-personal-account-of-the-discovery-of-the-structure-of-dna-james-d-watson-abridged/">The Double Helix: A Personal Account of the Discovery of the Structure of DNA &#8211; James D. Watson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Studies: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time (chronology), Time Systems & Standards]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>AN OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR From the acclaimed author of The Information and Chaos, a mind-bending exploration of time travel: its subversive origins, its evolution in literature and science, and its influence on our understanding of time itself. Gleick&#8217;s story begins at the turn of the twentieth century with the young H. G. Wells [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/">Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>AN OBSERVER BOOK OF THE YEAR    </p>
<p>                              From the acclaimed author of The Information and Chaos, a mind-bending exploration of time travel: its subversive origins, its evolution in literature and science, and its influence on our understanding of time itself.    </p>
<p>                              Gleick&#8217;s story begins at the turn of the twentieth century with the young H. G. Wells writing and rewriting the fantastic tale that became his first book, an international sensation, The Time Machine. A host of forces were converging to transmute the human understanding of time, some philosophical and some technological &#8211; the electric telegraph, the steam railroad, the discovery of buried civilisations, and the perfection of clocks. Gleick tracks the evolution of time travel as an idea in the culture &#8211; from Marcel Proust to Doctor Who, from Woody Allen to Jorge Luis Borges. He explores the inevitable looping paradoxes and examines the porous boundary between pulp fiction and modern physics. Finally, he delves into a temporal shift that is unsettling our own moment: the instantaneous wired world, with its all-consuming present and vanishing future.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/time-travel-james-gleick-abridged/">Time Travel &#8211; James Gleick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Astronomy, Space & Time]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mind, Body, Spirit: Thought & Practice]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mind]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Physics Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Time (chronology), Time Systems & Standards]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER One of TIME&#8217;s Ten Best Nonfiction Books of the Decade &#8216;Captivating, fascinating, profoundly beautiful. . . Rovelli is a wonderfully humane, gentle and witty guide for he is as much philosopher and poet as he is a scientist&#8217; John Banville &#8216;We are time. We are this space, this clearing opened [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>THE #1 SUNDAY TIMES BESTSELLER    </p>
<p>                    One of TIME&#8217;s Ten Best Nonfiction Books of the Decade    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Captivating, fascinating, profoundly beautiful. . . Rovelli is a wonderfully humane, gentle and witty guide for he is as much philosopher and poet as he is a scientist&#8217; John Banville    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;We are time. We are this space, this clearing opened by the traces of memory inside the connections between our neurons. We are memory. We are nostalgia. We are longing for a future that will not come&#8217;    </p>
<p>                    Time is a mystery that does not cease to puzzle us. Philosophers, artists and poets have long explored its meaning while scientists have found that its structure is different from the simple intuition we have of it. From Boltzmann to quantum theory, from Einstein to loop quantum gravity, our understanding of time has been undergoing radical transformations. Time flows at a different speed in different places, the past and the future differ far less than we might think, and the very notion of the present evaporates in the vast universe.    </p>
<p>                    With his extraordinary charm and sense of wonder, bringing together science, philosophy and art, Carlo Rovelli unravels this mystery. Enlightening and consoling, The Order of Time shows that to understand ourselves we need to reflect on time &#8212; and to understand time we need to reflect on ourselves.    </p>
<p>                    Translated by Simon Carnell and Erica Segre</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-order-of-time-carlo-rovelli-abridged/">The Order of Time &#8211; Carlo Rovelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Underbug : An Obsessive Tale of Termites and Technology &#8211; Lisa Margonelli (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/underbug-an-obsessive-tale-of-termites-and-technology-lisa-margonelli-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Arid Zones, Deserts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservation Of Wildlife & Habitats]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Insects (entomology)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: Butterflies, Other Insects & Spiders]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wildlife: General Interest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/underbug-an-obsessive-tale-of-termites-and-technology-lisa-margonelli-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Who has the answer to the world&#8217;s fuel problems? How can we bring ruined land back to life? Where do roboticists turn when they try to engineer a hive mind? Termites. Strange though it seems, scientists look to tiny termites for answers to some big ideas. Lisa Margonelli tracks them, deep into their mounds to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/underbug-an-obsessive-tale-of-termites-and-technology-lisa-margonelli-abridged/">Underbug : An Obsessive Tale of Termites and Technology &#8211; Lisa Margonelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Who has the answer to the world&#8217;s fuel problems? How can we bring ruined land back to life? Where do roboticists turn when they try to engineer a hive mind?     </p>
<p>                    Termites.    </p>
<p>                    Strange though it seems, scientists look to tiny termites for answers to some big ideas. Lisa Margonelli tracks them, deep into their mounds to find out how termites can change the world. Underbug: An Obsessive Tale of Termites and Technology touches on everything from meditation, innovation and the psychology of obsession to good old-fashioned biology.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/underbug-an-obsessive-tale-of-termites-and-technology-lisa-margonelli-abridged/">Underbug : An Obsessive Tale of Termites and Technology &#8211; Lisa Margonelli (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Political Tribes : Group Instinct and the Fate of Nations &#8211; Amy Chua (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/political-tribes-group-instinct-and-the-fate-of-nations-amy-chua-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/political-tribes-group-instinct-and-the-fate-of-nations-amy-chua-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A beautifully written, eminently readable and uniquely important challenge to conventional wisdom&#8217; J. D. Vance, author of Hillbilly Elegy Never has our society felt more divided. In Political Tribes, Amy Chua diagnoses the cause of our current political discord: tribalism. In many parts of the world, the group identities that matter most &#8211; the ones [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/political-tribes-group-instinct-and-the-fate-of-nations-amy-chua-abridged/">Political Tribes : Group Instinct and the Fate of Nations &#8211; Amy Chua (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A beautifully written, eminently readable and uniquely important challenge to conventional wisdom&#8217; J. D. Vance, author of Hillbilly Elegy    </p>
<p>                    Never has our society felt more divided.     </p>
<p>                    In Political Tribes, Amy Chua diagnoses the cause of our current political discord: tribalism. In many parts of the world, the group identities that matter most &#8211; the ones that people will kill and die for &#8211; are ethnic, religious, sectarian or clan-based. Time and time again our blindness to tribalism has undermined our foreign policy.    </p>
<p>                    At home, we have recently witnessed the rise of identity politics, a movement that encourages us to define ourselves against, and thereby exclude, others. The shock results of the US election and the Brexit referendum show that tribalism is a social truth that we ignore at our peril. When people are defined by their differences to each other, extremism becomes the common ground, and the grand ideals of democracy have a hard time competing with a more primal need to belong.    </p>
<p>                    If we are to transcend our political tribes, we must rediscover a broader, more nuanced unity that acknowledges the reality of our group differences. Insightful, challenging and provocative, Amy Chua&#8217;s groundbreaking book could not be more timely.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/political-tribes-group-instinct-and-the-fate-of-nations-amy-chua-abridged/">Political Tribes : Group Instinct and the Fate of Nations &#8211; Amy Chua (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Diets & Dieting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Food & Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Social Sciences]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>More than half a billion adults and 40 million children on the planet are obese. Diabetes is a worldwide epidemic. Evidence increasingly shows that these illnesses are linked to the other major Western diseases: hypertension, heart disease, even Alzheimer&#8217;s and cancer, and that shockingly, sugar is likely the single root cause. Yet the nutritional advice [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/">The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>More than half a billion adults and 40 million children on the planet are obese. Diabetes is a worldwide epidemic. Evidence increasingly shows that these illnesses are linked to the other major Western diseases: hypertension, heart disease, even Alzheimer&#8217;s and cancer, and that shockingly, sugar is likely the single root cause. Yet the nutritional advice we receive from public health bodies is muddled, out of date, and frequently contradictory, and in many quarters still promotes the unproven hypothesis that fats are the greatest evil.    </p>
<p>                    With expert science and compelling storytelling, Gary Taubes investigates the history of nutritional science which, shaped by a handful of charismatic and misguided individuals, has for a hundred years denied the impact of sugar on our health. He exposes the powerful influence of the food industry which has lobbied for sugar&#8217;s ubiquity &#8211; the Sugar Association even today promoting &#8216;sugar&#8217;s goodness&#8217; &#8211;  and the extent that the industry has corrupted essential scientific research. He delves into the science of sugar, exposes conventional thinking that sugar is &#8217;empty calories&#8217; as a myth, and finds that its addictive pleasures are resulting in worldwide consumption as never experienced before, to devastating effect.     </p>
<p>                    The Case Against Sugar is a revelatory read, which will fundamentally change the way we eat.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-case-against-sugar-gary-taubes-abridged/">The Case Against Sugar &#8211; Gary Taubes (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Creativity Code : How Ai is Learning to Write, Paint and Think &#8211; Marcus du Sautoy (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-creativity-code-how-ai-is-learning-to-write-paint-and-think-marcus-du-sautoy-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Arts & Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natural Language & Machine Translation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-creativity-code-how-ai-is-learning-to-write-paint-and-think-marcus-du-sautoy-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Du Sautoy&#8217;s discussion of computer creativity is fascinating&#8217; Observer CAN MACHINES BE CREATIVE? In The Creativity Code, Marcus du Sautoy examines the nature of creativity, asking how much of our emotional response to art is a product of our brains reacting to pattern and structure, and exactly what it is to be creative in mathematics, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-creativity-code-how-ai-is-learning-to-write-paint-and-think-marcus-du-sautoy-abridged/">The Creativity Code : How Ai is Learning to Write, Paint and Think &#8211; Marcus du Sautoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Du Sautoy&#8217;s discussion of computer creativity is fascinating&#8217; Observer    </p>
<p>                                CAN MACHINES BE CREATIVE?    </p>
<p>                              In The Creativity Code, Marcus du Sautoy examines the nature of creativity, asking how much of our emotional response to art is a product of our brains reacting to pattern and structure, and exactly what it is to be creative in mathematics, art, language and music.    </p>
<p>                              Exploring how long it might be before machines compose a symphony or paint a masterpiece, and whether they might jolt us into being more imaginative in turn, The Creativity Code is a fascinating and very different exploration into the essence of what it means to be human.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-creativity-code-how-ai-is-learning-to-write-paint-and-think-marcus-du-sautoy-abridged/">The Creativity Code : How Ai is Learning to Write, Paint and Think &#8211; Marcus du Sautoy (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Code Book : The Secret History of Codes and Code-Breaking &#8211; Simon Singh (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coding Theory & Cryptology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Science of Secrecy from Ancient Egypt to Quantum Cryptography From the best-selling author of Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, The Code Book is a history of man&#8217;s urge to uncover the secrets of codes, from Egyptian puzzles to modern day computer encryptions. As in Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, Simon Singh brings life to an anstonishing story of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/">The Code Book : The Secret History of Codes and Code-Breaking &#8211; Simon Singh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Science of Secrecy from Ancient Egypt to Quantum Cryptography    </p>
<p>                              From the best-selling author of Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, The Code Book is a history of man&#8217;s urge to uncover the secrets of codes, from Egyptian puzzles to modern day computer encryptions.    </p>
<p>                              As in Fermat&#8217;s Last Theorem, Simon Singh brings life to an anstonishing story of puzzles, codes, languages and riddles that reveals man&#8217;s continual pursuit to disguise and uncover, and to work out the secret languages of others.    </p>
<p>                              Codes have influenced events throughout history, both in the stories of those who make them and those who break them. The betrayal of Mary Queen of Scots and the cracking of the enigma code that helped the Allies in World War II are major episodes in a continuing history of cryptography. In addition to stories of intrigue and warfare, Simon Singh also investigates other codes, the unravelling of genes and the rediscovery of ancient languages and most tantalisingly, the Beale ciphers, an unbroken code that could hold the key to a $20 million treasure.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-code-book-the-secret-history-of-codes-and-code-breaking-simon-singh-abridged/">The Code Book : The Secret History of Codes and Code-Breaking &#8211; Simon Singh (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Pursuit of the Unknown &#8211; Ian Stewart (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-pursuit-of-the-unknown-ian-stewart-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Applied Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Calculus]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy Of Mathematics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Quantum Physics (quantum Mechanics & Quantum Field Theory)]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Relativity Physics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wave Mechanics (vibration & Acoustics)]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-pursuit-of-the-unknown-ian-stewart-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Most people are familiar with history&#8217;s great equations: Newton&#8217;s Law of Gravity, for instance, or Einstein&#8217;s theory of relativity. But the way these mathematical breakthroughs have contributed to human progress is seldom appreciated. In In Pursuit of the Unknown, celebrated mathematician Ian Stewart untangles the roots of our most important mathematical statements to show that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-pursuit-of-the-unknown-ian-stewart-abridged/">In Pursuit of the Unknown &#8211; Ian Stewart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Most people are familiar with history&#8217;s great equations: Newton&#8217;s Law of Gravity, for instance, or Einstein&#8217;s theory of relativity. But the way these mathematical breakthroughs have contributed to human progress is seldom appreciated. In In Pursuit of the Unknown, celebrated mathematician Ian Stewart untangles the roots of our most important mathematical statements to show that equations have long been a driving force behind nearly every aspect of our lives. Using seventeen of our most crucial equations&#8211;including the Wave Equation that allowed engineers to measure a building&#8217;s response to earthquakes, saving countless lives, and the Black-Scholes model, used by bankers to track the price of financial derivatives over time&#8211;Stewart illustrates that many of the advances we now take for granted were made possible by mathematical discoveries. An approachable, lively, and informative guide to the mathematical building blocks of modern life, In Pursuit of the Unknown is a penetrating exploration of how we have also used equations to make sense of, and in turn influence, our world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-pursuit-of-the-unknown-ian-stewart-abridged/">In Pursuit of the Unknown &#8211; Ian Stewart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life : A Psychologist Investigates How Evolution, Cognition, and Complexity are Revolutionizing Our View of Human Nature &#8211; Douglas Kenrick (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/sex-murder-and-the-meaning-of-life-a-psychologist-investigates-how-evolution-cognition-and-complexity-are-revolutionizing-our-view-of-human-nature-douglas-kenrick-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evolution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Neurosciences]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/sex-murder-and-the-meaning-of-life-a-psychologist-investigates-how-evolution-cognition-and-complexity-are-revolutionizing-our-view-of-human-nature-douglas-kenrick-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#038;ldquoKenrick writes like a dream.&#8221;- Robert Sapolsky, Professor of Biology and Neurology, Stanford University author of A Primate&#8217;s Memoir and Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers What do sex and murder have to do with the meaning of life? Everything. In Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life , social psychologist Douglas Kenrick exposes the selfish [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-murder-and-the-meaning-of-life-a-psychologist-investigates-how-evolution-cognition-and-complexity-are-revolutionizing-our-view-of-human-nature-douglas-kenrick-abridged/">Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life : A Psychologist Investigates How Evolution, Cognition, and Complexity are Revolutionizing Our View of Human Nature &#8211; Douglas Kenrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#038;ldquoKenrick writes like a dream.&#8221;- Robert Sapolsky, Professor of Biology and Neurology, Stanford University author of  A Primate&#8217;s Memoir  and  Why Zebras Don&#8217;t Get Ulcers  What do sex and murder have to do with the meaning of life? Everything. In  Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life , social psychologist Douglas Kenrick exposes the selfish animalistic underside of human nature, and shows how it is intimately connected to our greatest and most selfless achievements. Masterfully integrating cognitive science, evolutionary psychology, and complexity theory, this intriguing book paints a comprehensive picture of the principles that govern our lives. As Kenrick divulges, beneath our civilized veneer, human beings are a lot like howling hyenas and barking baboons, with heads full of homicidal tendencies and sexual fantasies. But, in his view, many ingrained, apparently irrational behaviours- such as inclinations to one-night stands, racial prejudices, and conspicuous consumption- ultimately manifest what he calls&#8221;Deep Rationality.&#8221;  Although our heads are full of simple selfish biases that evolved to help our ancestors survive, modern human beings are anything but simple and selfish cavemen. Kenrick argues that simple and selfish mental mechanisms we inherited from our ancestors ultimately give rise to the multifaceted social lives that we humans lead today, and to the most positive features of humanity, including generosity, artistic creativity, love, and familial bonds. And out of those simple mechanisms emerge all the complexities of society, including international conflicts and global economic markets. By exploring the nuance of social psychology and the surprising results of his own research, Kenrick offers a detailed picture of what makes us caring, creative, and complex- that is, fully human.   Illuminated with stories from Kenrick&#8217;s own colourful experiences &#8211;  from his criminally inclined shantytown Irish relatives, his own multiple high school expulsions, broken marriages, and homicidal fantasies, to his eventual success as an evolutionary psychologist and loving father of two boys separated by 26 years &#8211;  this book is an exploration of our mental biases and failures, and our mind&#8217;s great successes. Idiosyncratic, controversial, and fascinating,  Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life  uncovers the pitfalls and promise of our biological inheritance.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/sex-murder-and-the-meaning-of-life-a-psychologist-investigates-how-evolution-cognition-and-complexity-are-revolutionizing-our-view-of-human-nature-douglas-kenrick-abridged/">Sex, Murder, and the Meaning of Life : A Psychologist Investigates How Evolution, Cognition, and Complexity are Revolutionizing Our View of Human Nature &#8211; Douglas Kenrick (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
