<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Pharmaceutical Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/pharmaceutical-industries/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/pharmaceutical-industries/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:57:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Pharmaceutical Industries Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/pharmaceutical-industries/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biotechnology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Security]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Viruses, Trojans & Worms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime & Criminology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet & WWW Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Biographies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[True Crime Books]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award! There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life. In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A New York Times bestseller and winner of a 2015 Prose Award!<br />
                    There is a threat lurking online. A secret war with the power to destroy your finances, steal your personal data, and endanger your life.<br />
                    In Spam Nation, investigative journalist and cybersecurity expert Brian Krebs unmasks the criminal masterminds driving some of the biggest spam and hacker operations targeting Americans and their bank accounts. Tracing the rise, fall, and alarming resurrection of the digital mafia behind the two largest spam pharmacies-and countless viruses, phishing, and spyware attacks-he delivers the first definitive narrative of the global spam problem and its threat to consumers everywhere.<br />
                    Blending cutting-edge research, investigative reporting, and firsthand interviews, this terrifying true story reveals how we unwittingly invite these digital thieves into our lives every day. From unassuming computer programmers right next door to digital mobsters like &#8220;Cosma&#8221;-who unleashed a massive malware attack that has stolen thousands of Americans&#8217; logins and passwords-Krebs uncovers the shocking lengths to which these people will go to profit from our data and our wallets.<br />
                    Not only are hundreds of thousands of Americans exposing themselves to fraud and dangerously toxic products from rogue online pharmacies, but even those who never open junk messages are at risk. As Krebs notes, spammers can-and do-hack into accounts through these emails, harvest personal information like usernames and passwords, and sell them on the digital black market. The fallout from this global epidemic doesn&#8217;t just cost consumers and companies billions, it costs lives too.<br />
                    Fast-paced and utterly gripping, Spam Nation ultimately proposes concrete solutions for protecting ourselves online and stemming this tidal wave of cybercrime-before it&#8217;s too late.<br />
                    &#8220;Krebs&#8217;s talent for exposing the weaknesses in online security has earned him respect in the IT business and loathing among cybercriminals&#8230; His track record of scoops&#8230;has helped him become the rare blogger who supports himself on the strength of his reputation for hard-nosed reporting.&#8221; -Bloomberg Businessweek</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/spam-nation-the-inside-story-of-organized-cybercrime-from-global-epidemic-to-your-front-door-brian-krebs-abridged/">Spam Nation : The Inside Story of Organized Cybercrime-from Global Epidemic to Your Front Door &#8211; Brian Krebs (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Epidemiology & Medical Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Illness & Addiction: Social Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Manufacturing Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mental Health Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmaceutical Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pharmacology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychiatry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Updated with bonus material, including a new foreword and afterword with new research, this New York Times bestseller is essential reading for a time when mental health is constantly in the news. In this astonishing and startling book, award-winning science and history writer Robert Whitaker investigates a medical mystery: Why has the number of disabled [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/">Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Updated with bonus material, including a new foreword and afterword with new research, this New York Times bestseller is essential reading for a time when mental health is constantly in the news.     </p>
<p>                    In this astonishing and startling book, award-winning science and history writer Robert Whitaker investigates a medical mystery: Why has the number of disabled mentally ill in the United States tripled over the past two decades?     </p>
<p>                    Interwoven with Whitaker&#8217;s groundbreaking analysis of the merits of psychiatric medications are the personal stories of children and adults swept up in this epidemic. As Anatomy of an Epidemic reveals, other societies have begun to alter their use of psychiatric medications and are now reporting much improved outcomes . . . so why can&#8217;t such change happen here in the United States? Why have the results from these long-term studies&#8211;all of which point to the same startling conclusion&#8211;been kept from the public?     </p>
<p>                    Our nation has been hit by an epidemic of disabling mental illness, and yet, as Anatomy of an Epidemic reveals, the medical blueprints for curbing that epidemic have already been drawn up.     </p>
<p>                    Praise for Anatomy of an Epidemic     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;The timing of Robert Whitaker&#8217;s Anatomy of an Epidemic, a comprehensive and highly readable history of psychiatry in the United States, couldn&#8217;t be better.&#8221;&#8211;Salon     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Anatomy of an Epidemic offers some answers, charting controversial ground with mystery-novel pacing.&#8221;&#8211;TIME     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Lucid, pointed and important, Anatomy of an Epidemic should be required reading for anyone considering extended use of psychiatric medicine. Whitaker is at the height of his powers.&#8221; &#8211;Greg Critser, author of Generation Rx</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/anatomy-of-an-epidemic-magic-bullets-psychiatric-drugs-and-the-astonishing-rise-of-mental-illness-in-america-robert-whitaker-abridged/">Anatomy of an Epidemic : Magic Bullets, Psychiatric Drugs, and the Astonishing Rise of Mental Illness in America &#8211; Robert Whitaker (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
