<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Media Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/media-studies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/media-studies/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Media Studies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/media-studies/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</title>
		<link>/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR </p>
<p>                     When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch a cable news network in 1996, American politics and media changed forever. With a remarkable level of detail and insight, Vanity Fair magazine reporter Gabriel Sherman puts Ailes&#8217;s unique genius on display, along with the outsize personalities&#8211;Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Sean Hannity, Megyn Kelly, Sarah Palin, Karl Rove, Glenn Beck, Mike Huckabee, Gretchen Carlson, Bill Shine, and others&#8211;who have helped Fox News play a defining role in the great social and political controversies of the past two decades. From the Clinton-Lewinsky scandal to the Bush-Gore recount, from the war in Iraq to the Tea Party attack on the Obama presidency, Roger Ailes developed an unrivaled power to sway the national agenda. Even more, he became the indispensable figure in conservative America and the man any Republican politician with presidential aspirations had to court. </p>
<p>                     How did this man become the master strategist of our political landscape? In revelatory detail, Sherman chronicles the rise of Ailes, a frail kid from an Ohio factory town who, through sheer willpower, the flair of a showman, fierce corporate politicking, and a profound understanding of the priorities of middle America, built the most influential television news empire of our time. </p>
<p>                     Drawing on hundreds of interviews with Fox News insiders past and present, Sherman documents Ailes&#8217;s tactical acuity as he battled the press, business rivals, and countless real and perceived enemies inside and outside Fox. Sherman takes us inside the morning meetings in which Ailes and other high-level executives strategized Fox&#8217;s presentation of the news to advance Ailes&#8217;s political agenda; provides behind-the-scenes details of Ailes&#8217;s crucial role as finder and shaper of talent, including his sometimes rocky relationships with Fox News stars such as O&#8217;Reilly, Hannity, and Carlson; and probes Ailes&#8217;s fraught partnership with his equally brash and mercurial boss, Rupert Murdoch. </p>
<p>                     Roger Ailes&#8217;s life is a story worthy of Citizen Kane. Featuring an afterword about Ailes&#8217;s epic downfall during the extraordinary 2016 election, The Loudest Voice in the Room is an extraordinary feat of reportage with a compelling human drama at its heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Empire of Illusion : The End of Literacy and the Triumph of Spectacle &#8211; Chris Hedges</title>
		<link>/empire-of-illusion-the-end-of-literacy-and-the-triumph-of-spectacle-chris-hedges/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literacy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Classes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/empire-of-illusion-the-end-of-literacy-and-the-triumph-of-spectacle-chris-hedges/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We now live in two Americas. One,now the minority,functions in a print-based, literate world that can cope with complexity and can separate illusion from truth. The other,the majority,is retreating from a reality-based world into one of false certainty and magic. To this majority,which crosses social class lines, though the poor are overwhelmingly affected,presidential debate and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-illusion-the-end-of-literacy-and-the-triumph-of-spectacle-chris-hedges/">Empire of Illusion : The End of Literacy and the Triumph of Spectacle &#8211; Chris Hedges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We now live in two Americas. One,now the minority,functions in a print-based, literate world that can cope with complexity and can separate illusion from truth. The other,the majority,is retreating from a reality-based world into one of false certainty and magic. To this majority,which crosses social class lines, though the poor are overwhelmingly affected,presidential debate and political rhetoric is pitched at a sixth-grade reading level. In this  other America,&#8221; serious film and theatre, as well as newspapers and books, are being pushed to the margins of society. In the tradition of Christopher Lasch&#8217;s  The Culture of Narcissism  and Neil Postman&#8217;s  Amusing Ourselves to Death , Pulitzer Prize-winner Chris Hedges navigates this culture,attending WWF contests, the Adult Video News Awards in Las Vegas, and Ivy League graduation ceremonies,to expose an age of terrifying decline and heightened self-delusion.    </p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-of-illusion-the-end-of-literacy-and-the-triumph-of-spectacle-chris-hedges/">Empire of Illusion : The End of Literacy and the Triumph of Spectacle &#8211; Chris Hedges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reclaiming Conversation : The Power of Talk in a Digital Age &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In a time in which the ways we communicate and connect are constantly changing, and not always for the better, Sherry Turkle provides a much needed voice of caution and reason to help explain what the f*** is going on.&#8221; &#8211;Aziz Ansari, author of Modern Romance Renowned media scholar Sherry Turkle investigates how a flight [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Reclaiming Conversation : The Power of Talk in a Digital Age &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;In a time in which the ways we communicate and connect are constantly changing, and not always for the better, Sherry Turkle provides a much needed voice of caution and reason to help explain what the f*** is going on.&#8221; &#8211;Aziz Ansari,  author of Modern Romance     </p>
<p>                    Renowned media scholar Sherry Turkle investigates how a flight from conversation undermines our relationships, creativity, and productivity&#8211;and why reclaiming face-to-face conversation can help us regain lost ground.    </p>
<p>                    We live in a technological universe in which we are always communicating. And yet we have sacrificed conversation for mere connection.     </p>
<p>                     Preeminent author and researcher Sherry Turkle has been studying digital culture for over thirty years. Long an enthusiast for its possibilities, here she investigates a troubling consequence: at work, at home, in politics, and in love, we find ways around conversation, tempted by the possibilities of a text or an email in which we don&#8217;t have to look, listen, or reveal ourselves.     </p>
<p>                     We develop a taste for what mere connection offers. The dinner table falls silent as children compete with phones for their parents&#8217; attention. Friends learn strategies to keep conversations going when only a few people are looking up from their phones. At work, we retreat to our screens although it is conversation at the water cooler that increases not only productivity but commitment to work. Online, we only want to share opinions that our followers will agree with &#8211; a politics that shies away from the real conflicts and solutions of the public square.     </p>
<p>                     The case for conversation begins with the necessary conversations of solitude and self-reflection. They are endangered: these days, always connected, we see loneliness as a problem that technology should solve. Afraid of being alone, we rely on other people to give us a sense of ourselves, and our capacity for empathy and relationship suffers. We see the costs of the flight from conversation everywhere: conversation is the cornerstone for democracy and in business it is good for the bottom line. In the private sphere, it builds empathy, friendship, love, learning, and productivity.     </p>
<p>                     But there is good news: we are resilient. Conversation cures.     </p>
<p>                     Based on five years of research and interviews in homes, schools, and the workplace, Turkle argues that we have come to a better understanding of where our technology can and cannot take us and that the time is right to reclaim conversation. The most human&#8211;and humanizing&#8211;thing that we do.     </p>
<p>                     The virtues of person-to-person conversation are timeless, and our most basic technology, talk, responds to our modern challenges. We have everything we need to start, we have each other.     </p>
<p>                    Turkle&#8217;s latest book, The Empathy Diaries (3/2/21) is available now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reclaiming-conversation-the-power-of-talk-in-a-digital-age-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Reclaiming Conversation : The Power of Talk in a Digital Age &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Frenemies : The Epic Disruption of the Ad Business (and Everything Else) &#8211; Ken Auletta (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/frenemies-the-epic-disruption-of-the-ad-business-and-everything-else-ken-auletta-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/frenemies-the-epic-disruption-of-the-ad-business-and-everything-else-ken-auletta-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An intimate and profound reckoning with the changes buffeting the $2 trillion global advertising and marketing business from the perspective of its most powerful players, by the bestselling author of Googled Advertising and marketing touches on every corner of our lives, and the industry is the invisible fuel powering almost all media. Complain about it [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/frenemies-the-epic-disruption-of-the-ad-business-and-everything-else-ken-auletta-abridged/">Frenemies : The Epic Disruption of the Ad Business (and Everything Else) &#8211; Ken Auletta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An intimate and profound reckoning with the changes buffeting the $2 trillion global advertising and marketing business from the perspective of its most powerful players, by the bestselling author of Googled    </p>
<p>                    Advertising and marketing touches on every corner of our lives, and the industry is the invisible fuel powering almost all media. Complain about it though we might, without it the world would be a darker place. But of all the industries wracked by change in the digital age, few have been turned on their heads as dramatically as this one. Mad Men are turning into Math Men (and women&#8211;though too few), an instinctual art is transforming into a science, and we are a long way from the days of Don Draper.      </p>
<p>                    Frenemies is Ken Auletta&#8217;s reckoning with an industry under existential assault. He enters the rooms of the ad world&#8217;s most important players, meeting the old guard as well as new powers and power brokers, investigating their perspectives. It&#8217;s essential reading, not simply because of what it reveals about this world, but because of the potential consequences: the survival of media as we know it depends on the money generated by advertising and marketing&#8211;revenue that is in peril in the face of technological changes and the fraying trust between the industry&#8217;s key players.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/frenemies-the-epic-disruption-of-the-ad-business-and-everything-else-ken-auletta-abridged/">Frenemies : The Epic Disruption of the Ad Business (and Everything Else) &#8211; Ken Auletta (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Trust Me, I&#8217;m Lying : Confessions of a Media Manipulator &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/trust-me-im-lying-confessions-of-a-media-manipulator-ryan-holiday-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/trust-me-im-lying-confessions-of-a-media-manipulator-ryan-holiday-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;ve seen it all before. A malicious online rumor costs a company millions. A political sideshow derails the national news cycle and destroys a candidate. Some product or celebrity zooms from total obscurity to viral sensation. What you don&#8217;t know is that someone is responsible for all this. Usually, someone like me. I&#8217;m a media [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trust-me-im-lying-confessions-of-a-media-manipulator-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Trust Me, I&#8217;m Lying : Confessions of a Media Manipulator &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;ve seen it all before. A malicious online rumor costs a company millions. A  political sideshow derails the national news cycle and destroys a candidate.  Some product or celebrity zooms from total obscurity to viral sensation. What  you don&#8217;t know is that someone is responsible for all this. Usually, someone  like me.    </p>
<p>                    I&#8217;m a media manipulator. In a world where blogs control and  distort the news, my job is to control blogs-as much as any one person  can.    </p>
<p>                    IN TODAY&#8217;S CULTURE&#8230;  Blogs like Gawker, BuzzFeed, and The Huffington Post drive the media agenda.   Bloggers are slaves to money, technology, and deadlines.  Manipulators wield these levers to shape everything you read, see, and hear-  online and off.Why am I giving away these secrets? Because I&#8217;m tired  of a world where blogs take indirect bribes, marketers help write the news,  reckless journalists spread lies, and no one is accountable for any of it. I&#8217;m  going to explain exactly how the media really works. What you choose to do with  this information is up to you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/trust-me-im-lying-confessions-of-a-media-manipulator-ryan-holiday-abridged/">Trust Me, I&#8217;m Lying : Confessions of a Media Manipulator &#8211; Ryan Holiday (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Propaganda]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Does &#8216;fake news&#8217; really exist? Find out from the ultimate insider. After years of working as a respected journalist, Nick Davies, in this shocking expose, reveals what really goes on behind the scenes of this contentious industry. From a prestigious newspaper that allowed intelligence agencies to plant fiction in its columns, to the newsroom that [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/">Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Does &#8216;fake news&#8217; really exist? Find out from the ultimate insider.    </p>
<p>                    After years of working as a respected journalist, Nick Davies, in this shocking expose, reveals what really goes on behind the scenes of this contentious industry.     </p>
<p>                    From a prestigious newspaper that allowed intelligence agencies to plant fiction in its columns, to the newsroom that routinely rejected stories due to racial bias, to the number of papers that accepted cash bribes. Gripping, thought-provoking and revelatory, this is an insider&#8217;s look at one of the most tainted professions.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Meticulous, fair-minded and utterly gripping&#8217; Telegraph    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Powerful and timely&#8230;his analysis is fair, meticulously researched and fascinating&#8217; Observer</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/flat-earth-news-an-award-winning-reporter-exposes-falsehood-distortion-and-propaganda-in-the-global-media-nick-davies-abridged/">Flat Earth News : An Award-winning Reporter Exposes Falsehood, Distortion and Propaganda in the Global Media &#8211; Nick Davies (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Autobiography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A provocative, timely account of the changing face of jounalism from a pioneer of the new-media revolution. For a long time, media organisations have controlled the news, treating their audiences as products for advertisers. Yet as journalism has moved online and behind paywalls, the public is demanding more say in how the news is created. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/">The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A provocative, timely account of the changing face of jounalism from a pioneer of the new-media revolution.    For a long time, media organisations have controlled the news, treating their audiences as products for advertisers.       Yet as journalism has moved online and behind paywalls, the public is demanding more say in how the news is created.       They are using blogs, Twitter, and Facebook to share stories, and selecting their sources to create their own &#8216;front page&#8217;.   In this lively, biting critique, media commentator Tim Dunlop explores the rise of the audience, and how unprepared the mainstream media has been for this changing balance of power.       Drawing on his experiences as prominent political blogger, he argues that the future of meaningful journalism &#8211; the sort we need in order to be informed citizens &#8211; will increasingly rely on journalists and editors taking the audience into their confidence and working with them, rather than against them.   The New Front Page is a passionate plea on behalf of those tired of being talked down to by the fourth estate.       Perceptive and illuminating, it asks audiences and media to work together to hold the powerful to account, and to produce the sort of news and analysis that enriches public debate.   &#8216;A fascinating account of how digital technology has changed Australian media forever.&#8217;       Katharine Viner, editor-in-chief of The Guardian Australia   &#8216;An essential guide to understanding our insurgent new media.&#8217;       Lindsay Tanner, author of Sideshow   &#8216;Dunlop writes with humour, passion, and insight.&#8217;       Gay Alcorn, journalist</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-new-front-page-new-media-and-the-rise-of-the-audience-tim-dunlop-abridged/">The New Front Page: New Media and the Rise of the Audience &#8211; Tim Dunlop (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Aesthetics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Society & Culture: General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Heffernan &#8220;melds the personal with the increasingly universal in a highly informative analysis of what the Internet is-and can be. A thoroughly engrossing examination of the Internet&#8217;s past, present, and future&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review) from one of the best living writers of English prose. This book makes a bold claim: The Internet is [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/">Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Virginia Heffernan &#8220;melds the personal with the increasingly universal in a highly informative analysis of what the Internet is-and can be. A thoroughly engrossing examination of the Internet&#8217;s past, present, and future&#8221; (Kirkus Reviews, starred review) from one of the best living writers of English prose.    </p>
<p>                    This book makes a bold claim: The Internet is among mankind&#8217;s great masterpieces-a massive work of art. As an idea, it rivals monotheism. But its cultural potential and its societal impact often elude us. In this deep and thoughtful book, Virginia Heffernan reveals the logic and aesthetics behind the Internet, just as Susan Sontag did for photography and Marshall McLuhan did for television.    </p>
<p>                    Life online, in the highly visual, social, portable, and global incarnation rewards certain virtues. The new medium favors speed, accuracy, wit, prolificacy, and versatility, and its form and functions are changing how we perceive, experience, and understand the world. In &#8220;sumptuous writing, saturated with observations that are simultaneously personal, cultural, and strikingly original&#8221; (The New Republic), Heffernan presents &#8220;a revealing look at how the Internet continues to reshape our lives emotionally, visually, and culturally&#8221; (The Smithsonian Magazine). &#8220;Magic and Loss is an illuminating guide to the Internet&#8230;it is impossible to come away from this book without sharing some of Heffernan&#8217;s awe for this brave new world&#8221; (The Wall Street Journal).</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/magic-and-loss-the-internet-as-art-virginia-heffernan-abridged/">Magic and Loss : The Internet as Art &#8211; Virginia Heffernan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Espionage & Secret Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[International Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Corruption]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Regional Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Warfare & Defence]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Connection is a story of political skullduggery unprecedented in American history. It weaves together tales of international intrigue, cyber espionage, and superpower rivalry. After US-Russia relations soured, as Vladimir Putin moved to reassert Russian strength on the global stage, Moscow trained its best hackers on US political targets and exploited Julian Assange and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/">Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Russian Connection is a story of political skullduggery unprecedented in American history. It weaves together tales of international intrigue, cyber espionage, and superpower rivalry. After US-Russia relations soured, as Vladimir Putin moved to reassert Russian strength on the global stage, Moscow trained its best hackers on US political targets and exploited Julian Assange and Wikileaks to disseminate information that could affect the 2016 election.     </p>
<p>                    The Russians were wildly successful and the great break-in of 2016 was no &#8220;third rate burglary.&#8221; It was far more sophisticated and sinister &#8212; a brazen act of political espionage designed to interfere with American democracy, and at the end of the day, Trump, the candidate with business ties to Russia, won. And millions of Americans were left wondering, what the hell happened?    </p>
<p>                    This story of high-tech spying and multiple political feuds will be told against the backdrop of Donald Trump and his strange relationship with Putin, and his inner circle of advisers with profitable ties to Russia, most notably Michael Flynn and Paul Manafort.    </p>
<p>                    The Russian Connection will chronicle and examine all these bizarre events and relationships, explain the stakes, and seek to answer one of the biggest questions in American politics: How and why did a foreign government infiltrate the country&#8217;s political process and implant its tentacles in Washington?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/russian-roulette-the-inside-story-of-putins-war-on-america-and-the-election-of-donald-trump-michael-isikoff-david-corn-abridged/">Russian Roulette : The Inside Story of Putin&#8217;s War on America and the Election of Donald Trump &#8211; Michael Isikoff, David Corn (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>All Marketers are Liars : The Underground Classic That Explains How Marketing Really Works&#8211;and Why Authenticity Is the Best Marketing of All &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advertising Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The indispensable classic on marketing by the bestselling author of Tribes and Purple Cow. Legendary business writer Seth Godin has three essential questions for every marketer: &#8220;What&#8217;s your story?&#8221; &#8220;Will the people who need to hear this story believe it?&#8221; &#8220;Is it true?&#8221; All marketers tell stories. And if they do it right, we believe [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/">All Marketers are Liars : The Underground Classic That Explains How Marketing Really Works&#8211;and Why Authenticity Is the Best Marketing of All &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The indispensable classic on marketing by the bestselling author of Tribes and Purple Cow.    </p>
<p>                     Legendary business writer Seth Godin has three essential questions for every marketer:     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;What&#8217;s your story?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Will the people who need to hear this story believe it?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;Is it true?&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     All marketers tell stories. And if they do it right, we believe them. We believe that wine tastes better in a $20 glass than a $1 glass. We believe that an $80,000 Porsche is vastly superior to a $36,000 Volkswagen that&#8217;s virtually the same car. We believe that $225 sneakers make our feet feel better&#8211;and look cooler&#8211;than a $25 brand. And believing it makes it true.     </p>
<p>                     As Seth Godin has taught hundreds of thousands of marketers and students around the world, great marketers don&#8217;t talk about features or even benefits. Instead, they tell a story&#8211;a story we want to believe, whether it&#8217;s factual or not. In a world where most people have an infinite number of choices and no time to make them, every organization is a marketer, and all marketing is about telling stories.     </p>
<p>                     Marketers succeed when they tell us a story that fits our worldview, a story that we intuitively embrace and then share with our friends. Think of the Dyson vacuum cleaner, or Fiji water, or the iPod.     </p>
<p>                     But beware: If your stories are inauthentic, you cross the line from fib to fraud. Marketers fail when they are selfish and scurrilous, when they abuse the tools of their trade and make the world worse. That&#8217;s a lesson learned the hard way by telemarketers, cigarette companies, and sleazy politicians.     </p>
<p>                     But for the rest of us, it&#8217;s time to embrace the power of the story. As Godin writes, &#8220;Stories make it easier to understand the world. Stories are the only way we know to spread an idea. Marketers didn&#8217;t invent storytelling. They just perfected it.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/all-marketers-are-liars-the-underground-classic-that-explains-how-marketing-really-works-and-why-authenticity-is-the-best-marketing-of-all-seth-godin-abridged/">All Marketers are Liars : The Underground Classic That Explains How Marketing Really Works&#8211;and Why Authenticity Is the Best Marketing of All &#8211; Seth Godin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Amusing Ourselves to Death : Public Discourse in the Age of Show Business &#8211; Neil Postman, Introduction by Andrew Postman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/amusing-ourselves-to-death-public-discourse-in-the-age-of-show-business-neil-postman-introduction-by-andrew-postman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television Technology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/amusing-ourselves-to-death-public-discourse-in-the-age-of-show-business-neil-postman-introduction-by-andrew-postman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What happens when media and politics become forms of entertainment? As our world begins to look more and more like Orwell&#8217;s 1984, Neil&#8217;s Postman&#8217;s essential guide to the modern media is more relevant than ever. It&#8217;s unlikely that Trump has ever read Amusing Ourselves to Death, but his ascent would not have surprised Postman.&#8221; -CNN [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/amusing-ourselves-to-death-public-discourse-in-the-age-of-show-business-neil-postman-introduction-by-andrew-postman-abridged/">Amusing Ourselves to Death : Public Discourse in the Age of Show Business &#8211; Neil Postman, Introduction by Andrew Postman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What happens when media and politics become forms of entertainment? As our world begins to look more and more like Orwell&#8217;s 1984, Neil&#8217;s Postman&#8217;s essential guide to the modern media is more relevant than ever.     </p>
<p>                    It&#8217;s unlikely that Trump has ever read Amusing Ourselves to Death, but his ascent would not have surprised Postman.&#8221; -CNN     </p>
<p>                    Originally published in 1985, Neil Postman&#8217;s groundbreaking polemic about the corrosive effects of television on our politics and public discourse has been hailed as a twenty-first-century book published in the twentieth century. Now, with television joined by more sophisticated electronic media&#8211;from the Internet to cell phones to DVDs&#8211;it has taken on even greater significance. Amusing Ourselves to Death is a prophetic look at what happens when politics, journalism, education, and even religion become subject to the demands of entertainment. It is also a blueprint for regaining control of our media, so that they can serve our highest goals.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;A brilliant, powerful, and important book. This is an indictment that Postman has laid down and, so far as I can see, an irrefutable one.&#8221; -Jonathan Yardley, The Washington Post Book World</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/amusing-ourselves-to-death-public-discourse-in-the-age-of-show-business-neil-postman-introduction-by-andrew-postman-abridged/">Amusing Ourselves to Death : Public Discourse in the Age of Show Business &#8211; Neil Postman, Introduction by Andrew Postman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Strategy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Customer Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Market Research]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sales & Marketing Management]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Managing Online Reputation is a comprehensive look at online reputation management. Drawing on recent examples of organizations managing their online reputations effectively and ineffectively, it provides a practical and visual tool-kit of processes and techniques to help limit and respond effectively to negative situations on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/">Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Managing Online Reputation is a comprehensive look at online reputation management. Drawing on recent examples of organizations managing their online reputations effectively and ineffectively, it provides a practical and visual tool-kit of processes and techniques to help limit and respond effectively to negative situations on social media.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/managing-online-reputation-how-to-protect-your-company-on-social-media-charlie-pownall-abridged/">Managing Online Reputation : How to Protect Your Company on Social Media &#8211; Charlie Pownall (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Age of Propaganda &#8211; Anthony Pratkanis, Elliot Aronson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/age-of-propaganda-anthony-pratkanis-elliot-aronson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dance & Other Performing Arts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management & Management Techniques]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/age-of-propaganda-anthony-pratkanis-elliot-aronson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Americans create 57% of the world&#8217;s advertising while representing only 6% of its population; half of our waking hours are spent immersed in the mass media. Persuasion has always been integral to the democratic process, but increasingly, thoughtful discussion is being replaced with simplistic soundbites and manipulative messages. Drawing on the history of propaganda as [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-propaganda-anthony-pratkanis-elliot-aronson-abridged/">Age of Propaganda &#8211; Anthony Pratkanis, Elliot Aronson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Americans create 57% of the world&#8217;s advertising while representing only 6% of its population; half of our waking hours are spent immersed in the mass media. Persuasion has always been integral to the democratic process, but increasingly, thoughtful discussion is being replaced with simplistic soundbites and manipulative messages.     </p>
<p>                    Drawing on the history of propaganda as well as on contemporary research in social psychology, Age of Propaganda shows how the tactics used by political campaigners, sales agents, advertisers, televangelists, demagogues, and others often take advantage of our emotions by appealing to our deepest fears and most irrational hopes, creating a distorted vision of the world we live in.     </p>
<p>                    This revised and updated edition includes coverage of the Clinton/Lewinsky scandal, recent election campaigns, talk radio, teen suicide, U.F.O. abductions, the Columbine shootings, and novel propaganda tactics based on hypocrisy and false allegations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/age-of-propaganda-anthony-pratkanis-elliot-aronson-abridged/">Age of Propaganda &#8211; Anthony Pratkanis, Elliot Aronson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal: to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221; major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal:  to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221;  major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair way.     </p>
<p>                    Breitbart burst on to the national media scene thanks to his coverage of  the ACORN controversy, where a local ACORN community group leader was videotaped giving business advice to a &#8220;gentleman&#8221; who ran a prostitution ring. When the major news media at first tried to bury the story, Breitbart used his extraordinary marketing savvy to make sure the story got full national attention.     </p>
<p>                    More recently, Congressman Anthony Weiner took on Breitbart, claiming that scurrilous photos of Weiner were being sent on the internet by the conservative right. In a new chapter in RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart details how &#8220;Weinergate&#8221; was entirely the personal fault of Congressman Weiner, and how Weiner derailed his own promising career by trying to implicate Breitbart and conservative journalists.    </p>
<p>                    In short, RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart talks about the key issues that Americans face, how he has aligned himself with the Tea Party, and how one needs to deal with the liberal news world head on. Along the way, he details his early years, working with Matt Drudge, the Huffington Post, and so on, and how Breitbart developed his unique style of launching key websites to help get the word out to conservatives all over.     </p>
<p>                    A rollicking and controversial read, Breitbart will certainly raise your blood pressure, one way or another.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Domestic Trade]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Propaganda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Semiotics / Semiology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to the usual image of the press as cantankerous, obstinate, and ubiquitous in its search for truth, Edward Herman and Noam Chomsky depict how an underlying elite consensus largely structures all facets of the news. They skilfully dissect the way in which the marketplace and the economics of publishing significantly shape the news. They [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/">Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Contrary to the usual image of the press as cantankerous, obstinate, and ubiquitous in its search for truth, Edward Herman and Noam Chomsky depict how an underlying elite consensus largely structures all facets of the news. They skilfully dissect the way in which the marketplace and the economics of publishing significantly shape the news. They reveal how issues are framed and topics chosen, and contrast the double standards underlying accounts of free elections, a free press, and governmental repression between Nicaragua and El Salvador; between the Russian invasion of Afghanistan and the American invasion of Vietnam; between the genocide in Cambodia under a pro-American government and genocide under Pol Pot. What emerges from this groundbreaking work is an account of just how propagandistic our mass media are, and how we can learn to read them and see their function in a radically new way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/manufacturing-consent-the-political-economy-of-the-mass-media-edward-s-herman-noam-chomsky-abridged/">Manufacturing Consent : The Political Economy of the Mass Media &#8211; Edward S Herman, Noam Chomsky (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Death of Expertise : The Campaign Against Established Knowledge and Why it Matters &#8211; Tom Nichols (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy: Epistemology & Theory Of Knowledge]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>People are now exposed to more information than ever before, provided both by technology and by increasing access to every level of education. These societal gains, however, have also helped fuel a surge in narcissistic and misguided intellectual egalitarianism that has crippled informed debates on any number of issues. Today, everyone knows everything: with only [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/">The Death of Expertise : The Campaign Against Established Knowledge and Why it Matters &#8211; Tom Nichols (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>People are now exposed to more information than ever before, provided both by technology and by increasing access to every level of education. These societal gains, however, have also helped fuel a surge in narcissistic and misguided intellectual egalitarianism that has crippled informed debates on any number of issues. Today, everyone knows everything: with only a quick trip through WebMD or Wikipedia, average citizens believe themselves to be on an equal<br />
                    intellectual footing with doctors and diplomats. All voices, even the most ridiculous, demand to be taken with equal seriousness, and any claim to the contrary is dismissed as undemocratic elitism.    </p>
<p>                    As Tom Nichols shows in The Death of Expertise, this rejection of experts has occurred for many reasons, including the openness of the internet, the emergence of a customer satisfaction model in higher education, and the transformation of the news industry into a 24-hour entertainment machine. Paradoxically, the increasingly democratic dissemination of information, rather than producing an educated public, has instead created an army of ill-informed and angry citizens who denounce<br />
                    intellectual achievement.    </p>
<p>                    Nichols has deeper concerns than the current rejection of expertise and learning, noting that when ordinary citizens believe that no one knows more than anyone else, democratic institutions themselves are in danger of falling either to populism or to technocracy-or in the worst case, a combination of both. The Death of Expertise is not only an exploration of a dangerous phenomenon but also a warning about the stability and survival of modern democracy in the Information<br />
                    Age.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-death-of-expertise-the-campaign-against-established-knowledge-and-why-it-matters-tom-nichols-abridged/">The Death of Expertise : The Campaign Against Established Knowledge and Why it Matters &#8211; Tom Nichols (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communications Engineering / Telecommunications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[E-commerce: Business Aspects]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human-computer Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world where all the news you see is defined by your salary, where you live, and who your friends are. Imagine a world where you never discover new ideas. And where you can&#8217;t have secrets. Welcome to 2011. Google and Facebook are already feeding you what they think you want to see. Advertisers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/">The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a world where all the news you see is defined by your salary, where you live, and who your friends are. Imagine a world where you never discover new ideas. And where you can&#8217;t have secrets.    </p>
<p>                    Welcome to 2011.    </p>
<p>                    Google and Facebook are already feeding you what they think you want to see. Advertisers are following your every click. Your computer monitor is becoming a one-way mirror, reflecting your interests and reinforcing your prejudices.    </p>
<p>                    The internet is no longer a free, independent space. It is commercially controlled and ever more personalised. The Filter Bubble reveals how this hidden web is starting to control our lives &#8211; and shows what we can do about it.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-filter-bubble-what-the-internet-is-hiding-from-you-eli-pariser-abridged/">The Filter Bubble : What The Internet Is Hiding From You &#8211; Eli Pariser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Press & Journalism]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The captivating, inside story of the woman who helmed the Washington Post during one of the most turbulent periods in the history of American media. Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Biography In this bestselling and widely acclaimed memoir, Katharine Graham, the woman who piloted the Washington Post through the scandals of the Pentagon Papers [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/">Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The captivating, inside story of the woman who helmed the Washington Post during one of the most turbulent periods in the history of American media.     </p>
<p>                    Winner of the Pulitzer Prize for Biography    </p>
<p>                    In this bestselling and widely acclaimed memoir, Katharine Graham, the woman who piloted the Washington Post through the scandals of the Pentagon Papers and Watergate, tells her story&#8211;one that is extraordinary both for the events it encompasses and for the courage, candor, and dignity of its telling.     </p>
<p>                     Here is the awkward child who grew up amid material wealth and emotional isolation; the young bride who watched her brilliant, charismatic husband&#8211;a confidant to John F. Kennedy and Lyndon Johnson&#8211;plunge into the mental illness that would culminate in his suicide. And here is the widow who shook off her grief and insecurity to take on a president and a pressman&#8217;s union as she entered the profane boys&#8217; club of the newspaper business.     </p>
<p>                     As timely now as ever, Personal History is an exemplary record of our history and of the woman who played such a shaping role within them, discovering her own strength and sense of self as she confronted&#8211;and mastered&#8211;the personal and professional crises of her fascinating life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/personal-history-katharine-graham-abridged/">Personal History &#8211; Katharine Graham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Wear the Black Hat : Grappling with Villains (Real and Imagined) &#8211; Chuck Klosterman (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/i-wear-the-black-hat-grappling-with-villains-real-and-imagined-chuck-klosterman-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Literary Essays]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Memoirs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/i-wear-the-black-hat-grappling-with-villains-real-and-imagined-chuck-klosterman-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One-of-a-kind cultural critic and New York Times bestselling author Chuck Klosterman &#8220;offers up great facts, interesting cultural insights, and thought-provoking moral calculations in this look at our love affair with the anti-hero&#8221; (New York magazine). Chuck Klosterman, &#8220;The Ethicist&#8221; for The New York Times Magazine, has walked into the darkness. In I Wear the Black [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-wear-the-black-hat-grappling-with-villains-real-and-imagined-chuck-klosterman-abridged/">I Wear the Black Hat : Grappling with Villains (Real and Imagined) &#8211; Chuck Klosterman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One-of-a-kind cultural critic and New York Times bestselling author Chuck Klosterman &#8220;offers up great facts, interesting cultural insights, and thought-provoking moral calculations in this look at our love affair with the anti-hero&#8221; (New York magazine).     </p>
<p>                    Chuck Klosterman, &#8220;The Ethicist&#8221; for The New York Times Magazine, has walked into the darkness. In I Wear the Black Hat, he questions the modern understanding of villainy. When we classify someone as a bad person, what are we really saying, and why are we so obsessed with saying it? How does the culture of malevolence operate? What was so Machiavellian about Machiavelli? Why don&#8217;t we see Bernhard Goetz the same way we see Batman? Who is more worthy of our vitriol&#8211;Bill Clinton or Don Henley? What was O.J. Simpson&#8217;s second-worst decision? And why is Klosterman still haunted by some kid he knew for one week in 1985?     </p>
<p>                    Masterfully blending cultural analysis with self-interrogation and imaginative hypotheticals, I Wear the Black Hat delivers perceptive observations on the complexity of the antihero (seemingly the only kind of hero America still creates). As the Los Angeles Times notes: &#8220;By underscoring the contradictory, often knee-jerk ways we encounter the heroes and villains of our culture, Klosterman illustrates the passionate but incomplete computations that have come to define American culture&#8211;and maybe even American morality.&#8221; I Wear the Black Hat is a rare example of serious criticism that&#8217;s instantly accessible and really, really funny.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/i-wear-the-black-hat-grappling-with-villains-real-and-imagined-chuck-klosterman-abridged/">I Wear the Black Hat : Grappling with Villains (Real and Imagined) &#8211; Chuck Klosterman (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Distracted Mind : Ancient Brains in a High-Tech World &#8211; Adam Gazzaley, Larry D. Rosen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world-adam-gazzaley-larry-d-rosen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Interdisciplinary Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world-adam-gazzaley-larry-d-rosen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why our brains aren&#8217;t built for media multitasking, and how we can learn to live with technology in a more balanced way. Brilliant and practical, just what we need in these techno-human times.&#8211;Jack Kornfield, author of The Wise Heart Most of us will freely admit that we are obsessed with our devices. We pride ourselves [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world-adam-gazzaley-larry-d-rosen-abridged/">The Distracted Mind : Ancient Brains in a High-Tech World &#8211; Adam Gazzaley, Larry D. Rosen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why our brains aren&#8217;t built for media multitasking, and how we can learn to live with technology in a more balanced way.    </p>
<p>                    Brilliant and practical, just what we need in these techno-human times.&#8211;Jack Kornfield, author of The Wise Heart    </p>
<p>                    Most of us will freely admit that we are obsessed with our devices. We pride ourselves on our ability to multitask&#8211;read work email, reply to a text, check Facebook, watch a video clip. Talk on the phone, send a text, drive a car. Enjoy family dinner with a glowing smartphone next to our plates. We can do it all, 24/7! Never mind the errors in the email, the near-miss on the road, and the unheard conversation at the table. In The Distracted Mind, Adam Gazzaley and Larry Rosen&#8211;a neuroscientist and a psychologist&#8211;explain why our brains aren&#8217;t built for multitasking, and suggest better ways to live in a high-tech world without giving up our modern technology.    </p>
<p>                    The authors explain that our brains are limited in their ability to pay attention. We don&#8217;t really multitask but rather switch rapidly between tasks. Distractions and interruptions, often technology-related&#8211;referred to by the authors as &#8220;interference&#8221;&#8211;collide with our goal-setting abilities. We want to finish this paper/spreadsheet/sentence, but our phone signals an incoming message and we drop everything. Even without an alert, we decide that we &#8220;must&#8221; check in on social media immediately.    </p>
<p>                    Gazzaley and Rosen offer practical strategies, backed by science, to fight distraction. We can change our brains with meditation, video games, and physical exercise; we can change our behavior by planning our accessibility and recognizing our anxiety about being out of touch even briefly. They don&#8217;t suggest that we give up our devices, but that we use them in a more balanced way.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-distracted-mind-ancient-brains-in-a-high-tech-world-adam-gazzaley-larry-d-rosen-abridged/">The Distracted Mind : Ancient Brains in a High-Tech World &#8211; Adam Gazzaley, Larry D. Rosen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things : Mapping the Relationship between Online Trolling and Mainstream Culture &#8211; Whitney Phillips (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Why the troll problem is actually a culture problem: how online trolling fits comfortably within today&#8217;s media landscape. Internet trolls live to upset as many people as possible, using all the technical and psychological tools at their disposal. They gleefully whip the media into a frenzy over a fake teen drug crisis; they post offensive [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/">This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things : Mapping the Relationship between Online Trolling and Mainstream Culture &#8211; Whitney Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Why the troll problem is actually a culture problem: how online trolling fits comfortably within today&#8217;s media landscape.    </p>
<p>                    Internet trolls live to upset as many people as possible, using all the technical and psychological tools at their disposal. They gleefully whip the media into a frenzy over a fake teen drug crisis; they post offensive messages on Facebook memorial pages, traumatizing grief-stricken friends and family; they use unabashedly racist language and images. They take pleasure in ruining a complete stranger&#8217;s day and find amusement in their victim&#8217;s anguish. In short, trolling is the obstacle to a kinder, gentler Internet. To quote a famous Internet meme, trolling is why we can&#8217;t have nice things online. Or at least that&#8217;s what we have been led to believe. In this provocative book, Whitney Phillips argues that trolling, widely condemned as obscene and deviant, actually fits comfortably within the contemporary media landscape. Trolling may be obscene, but, Phillips argues, it isn&#8217;t all that deviant. Trolls&#8217; actions are born of and fueled by culturally sanctioned impulses&#8211;which are just as damaging as the trolls&#8217; most disruptive behaviors.     </p>
<p>                    Phillips describes, for example, the relationship between trolling and sensationalist corporate media&#8211;pointing out that for trolls, exploitation is a leisure activity; for media, it&#8217;s a business strategy. She shows how trolls, &#8220;the grimacing poster children for a socially networked world,&#8221; align with social media. And she documents how trolls, in addition to parroting media tropes, also offer a grotesque pantomime of dominant cultural tropes, including gendered notions of dominance and success and an ideology of entitlement. We don&#8217;t just have a trolling problem, Phillips argues; we have a culture problem. This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things isn&#8217;t only about trolls; it&#8217;s about a culture in which trolls thrive.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/this-is-why-we-cant-have-nice-things-mapping-the-relationship-between-online-trolling-and-mainstream-culture-whitney-phillips-abridged/">This Is Why We Can&#8217;t Have Nice Things : Mapping the Relationship between Online Trolling and Mainstream Culture &#8211; Whitney Phillips (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weaponized Lies : How to Think Critically in the Post-Truth Era &#8211; Daniel Levitin (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/weaponized-lies-how-to-think-critically-in-the-post-truth-era-daniel-levitin-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cognition & Cognitive Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/weaponized-lies-how-to-think-critically-in-the-post-truth-era-daniel-levitin-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A guide to critical thinking in the &#8216;post-truth&#8217; era, from the author of Sunday Times best-seller The Organized Mind We live in a world where the line between truth and lies is increasingly blurred by euphemistic terms such as &#8216;post-truth&#8217;, &#8216;counter-knowledge&#8217;, &#8216;fringe theories&#8217; and others. In a world where anyone can become an expert at [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weaponized-lies-how-to-think-critically-in-the-post-truth-era-daniel-levitin-abridged/">Weaponized Lies : How to Think Critically in the Post-Truth Era &#8211; Daniel Levitin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A guide to critical thinking in the &#8216;post-truth&#8217; era, from the author of Sunday Times best-seller The Organized Mind     </p>
<p>                    We live in a world where the line between truth and lies is increasingly blurred by euphemistic terms such as &#8216;post-truth&#8217;, &#8216;counter-knowledge&#8217;, &#8216;fringe theories&#8217; and others. In a world where anyone can become an expert at the click of a button, we&#8217;re worse equipped than ever to evaluate the  information we encounter and separate the truth from the lies.  Daniel Levitin debunks the idea that truth no longer exists, and shows that we urgently need to learn the skills toeffectively ask ourselves: can we really know that? And how do they know that?     </p>
<p>                    In this eye-opening, accessible guide filled with fascinating examples and practical takeaways, acclaimed neuroscientist Daniel Levitin shows us how learning to understand statistics will enable you to make better, smarter judgements on the world around you.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weaponized-lies-how-to-think-critically-in-the-post-truth-era-daniel-levitin-abridged/">Weaponized Lies : How to Think Critically in the Post-Truth Era &#8211; Daniel Levitin (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Truth : 13 Reasons To Question Everything You Are Told &#8211; Hector Macdonald (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/truth-13-reasons-to-question-everything-you-are-told-hector-macdonald-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Communication & Presentation]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business Ethics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/truth-13-reasons-to-question-everything-you-are-told-hector-macdonald-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>_________________ &#8216;Macdonald zeros in on the slipperiness of factuality, offering an array of case studies from the worlds of history, commerce and &#8211; of course &#8211; politics.&#8217; New York Times True or false? It&#8217;s rarely that simple. There is always more than one truth in every story. Eating meat is nutritious but it&#8217;s also damaging [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/truth-13-reasons-to-question-everything-you-are-told-hector-macdonald-abridged/">Truth : 13 Reasons To Question Everything You Are Told &#8211; Hector Macdonald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>_________________    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Macdonald zeros in on the slipperiness of factuality, offering an array of case studies from the worlds of history, commerce and &#8211; of course &#8211; politics.&#8217; New York Times     </p>
<p>                    True or false?  It&#8217;s rarely that simple.    </p>
<p>                    There is always more than one truth in every story.  Eating meat is nutritious but it&#8217;s also damaging to the environment.  The Internet disseminates knowledge but it also spreads hatred.  As communicators, we select the truths that are most useful to our agenda.    </p>
<p>                    We can select truths constructively to inspire nations, encourage children, and drive progressive change.  Or we can select truths that give a false impression of reality, misleading people without actually lying.  Others can do the same, motivating or deceiving us with the truth.      </p>
<p>                    In Truth, communications strategy expert Hector Macdonald explores how truth is used and abused in politics, business, the media and everyday life.   Combining great storytelling with practical takeaways and a litany of fascinating, funny and insightful case studies, Truth is a chilling and engaging read about how profoundly our mindsets and actions are influenced by the truths that those around us choose to tell.    </p>
<p>                    For fans of Factfulness, A Field Guide to Lies and Statistics and The Art of Thinking Clearly, a fascinating dive into the many ways in which &#8216;competing truths&#8217; shape our opinions, behaviours and beliefs.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/truth-13-reasons-to-question-everything-you-are-told-hector-macdonald-abridged/">Truth : 13 Reasons To Question Everything You Are Told &#8211; Hector Macdonald (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Parenting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child & Developmental Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Child Care & Upbringing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Clinical Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Communication Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computing: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coping With Death & Bereavement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dating, Relationships, Living Together & Marriage]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethical & Social Aspects Of Computing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Family & Relationships]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Office & Workplace]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy & Theory Of Education]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Culture]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Medicine & Health]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology Of Ageing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology: Emotions]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychotherapy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Self, Ego, Identity, Personality]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Interaction]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social, Group Or Collective Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology: General Issues]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Teenagers: Advice For Parents]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology has become the architect of our intimacies. Online, we fall prey to the illusion of companionship, gathering thousands of Twitter and Facebook friends, and confusing tweets and wall posts with authentic communication. But this relentless connection leads to a new solitude. We turn to new technology to fill the void, but as MIT technology and society specialist Sherry Turkle argues, as technology ramps up, our emotional lives ramp down. Even the presence of sociable robots in our lives that pretend to demonstrate empathy makes us feel more isolated, as Turkle explains in a new introduction updating the book to the present day. Alone Together is the result of Turkle&#8217;s nearly fifteen-year exploration of our lives on the digital terrain. Based on interviews with hundreds of children and adults, it describes new, unsettling relationships between friends, lovers, parents, and children, and new instabilities in how we understand privacy and community, intimacy and solitude.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alone-together-why-we-expect-more-from-technology-and-less-from-each-other-third-edition-sherry-turkle-abridged/">Alone Together : Why We Expect More from Technology and Less from Each Other (Third Edition) &#8211; Sherry Turkle (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free : Laws for the Internet Age &#8211; Cory Doctorow, Foreword by Neil Gaiman, Foreword by Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Networking & Communications]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Copyright Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Internet Guides & Online Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Law For The Lay Person]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Cultural Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Filled with wisdom and thought experiments and things that will mess with your mind.&#8221; &#8212; Neil Gaiman, author of The Graveyard Book and American Gods In sharply argued, fast-moving chapters, Cory Doctorow&#8217;s Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free takes on the state of copyright and creative success in the digital age. Can small artists still [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/">Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free : Laws for the Internet Age &#8211; Cory Doctorow, Foreword by Neil Gaiman, Foreword by Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>&#8220;Filled with wisdom and thought experiments and things that will mess with your mind.&#8221; &#8212; Neil Gaiman, author of The Graveyard Book and American Gods     </p>
<p>                    In sharply argued, fast-moving chapters, Cory Doctorow&#8217;s Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free takes on the state of copyright and creative success in the digital age. Can small artists still thrive in the Internet era? Can giant record labels avoid alienating their audiences? This is a book about the pitfalls, and the opportunities, creative industries (and individuals) are confronting today&#8211;about how the old models have failed or found new footing, and about what might soon replace them. An essential read for anyone with a stake in the future of the arts, Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free offers a vivid guide to the ways creativity and the Internet interact today, and to what might be coming next.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/information-doesnt-want-to-be-free-laws-for-the-internet-age-cory-doctorow-foreword-by-neil-gaiman-foreword-by-amanda-palmer-abridged/">Information Doesn&#8217;t Want to Be Free : Laws for the Internet Age &#8211; Cory Doctorow, Foreword by Neil Gaiman, Foreword by Amanda Palmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Risk : The Science and Politics of Fear &#8211; Dan Gardner (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/risk-the-science-and-politics-of-fear-dan-gardner-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Abnormal Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Probability & Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Psychology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Research & Statistics]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/risk-the-science-and-politics-of-fear-dan-gardner-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>We are the safest humans who ever lived &#8211; the statistics prove it. And yet the media tells a different story with its warnings and scare stories. How is it possible that anxiety has become the stuff of daily life? In this ground-breaking, compulsively readable book, Dan Gardner shows how our flawed strategies for perceiving [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/risk-the-science-and-politics-of-fear-dan-gardner-abridged/">Risk : The Science and Politics of Fear &#8211; Dan Gardner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We are the safest humans who ever lived &#8211; the statistics prove it. And yet the media tells a different story with its warnings and scare stories. How is it possible that anxiety has become the stuff of daily life?    </p>
<p>                    In this ground-breaking, compulsively readable book, Dan Gardner shows how our flawed strategies for perceiving risk influence our lives, often with unforeseen and sometimes-tragic consequences. He throws light on our paranoia about everything from paedophiles to terrorism and reveals how the most significant threats are actually the mundane risks to which we pay little attention.    </p>
<p>                    Speaking to psychologists and scientists, as well as looking at the influence of the media and politicians, Gardner uncovers one of the central puzzles of our time: why are the safest people in history living in a culture of fear?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/risk-the-science-and-politics-of-fear-dan-gardner-abridged/">Risk : The Science and Politics of Fear &#8211; Dan Gardner (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Streaming, Sharing, Stealing : Big Data and the Future of Entertainment &#8211; Michael D. Smith, Rahul Telang (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cinema Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Computer Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dance & Other Performing Arts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Digital TV & Media Centres: Consumer/user Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Electronics Engineering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media, Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Radio & Television Industry]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How big data is transforming the creative industries, and how those industries can use lessons from Netflix, Amazon, and Apple to fight back. &#8220;[The authors explain] gently yet firmly exactly how the internet threatens established ways and what can and cannot be done about it. Their book should be required for anyone who wishes to [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/">Streaming, Sharing, Stealing : Big Data and the Future of Entertainment &#8211; Michael D. Smith, Rahul Telang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How big data is transforming the creative industries, and how those industries can use lessons from Netflix, Amazon, and Apple to fight back.    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;[The authors explain] gently yet firmly exactly how the internet threatens established ways and what can and cannot be done about it. Their book should be required for anyone who wishes to believe that nothing much has changed.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;The Wall Street Journal    </p>
<p>                    &#8220;Packed with examples, from the nimble-footed who reacted quickly to adapt their businesses, to laggards who lost empires.&#8221;<br />
                    &#8211;Financial Times    </p>
<p>                    Traditional network television programming has always followed the same script: executives approve a pilot, order a trial number of episodes, and broadcast them, expecting viewers to watch a given show on their television sets at the same time every week. But then came Netflix&#8217;s House of Cards. Netflix gauged the show&#8217;s potential from data it had gathered about subscribers&#8217; preferences, ordered two seasons without seeing a pilot, and uploaded the first thirteen episodes all at once for viewers to watch whenever they wanted on the devices of their choice.     </p>
<p>                    In this book, Michael Smith and Rahul Telang, experts on entertainment analytics, show how the success of House of Cards upended the film and TV industries&#8211;and how companies like Amazon and Apple are changing the rules in other entertainment industries, notably publishing and music. We&#8217;re living through a period of unprecedented technological disruption in the entertainment industries. Just about everything is affected: pricing, production, distribution, piracy. Smith and Telang discuss niche products and the long tail, product differentiation, price discrimination, and incentives for users not to steal content. To survive and succeed, businesses have to adapt rapidly and creatively. Smith and Telang explain how.    </p>
<p>                    How can companies discover who their customers are, what they want, and how much they are willing to pay for it? Data. The entertainment industries, must learn to play a little &#8220;moneyball.&#8221; The bottom line: follow the data.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/streaming-sharing-stealing-big-data-and-the-future-of-entertainment-michael-d-smith-rahul-telang-abridged/">Streaming, Sharing, Stealing : Big Data and the Future of Entertainment &#8211; Michael D. Smith, Rahul Telang (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
