<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Political Ideologies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/political-ideologies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/political-ideologies/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Political Ideologies Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/political-ideologies/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</title>
		<link>/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Business & Industry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information & Communication Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Information Technology Industries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A revelatory journey inside the world of Fox News and Roger Ailes&#8211;the brash, sometimes combative network head who helped fuel the rise of Donald Trump</p>
<p>                    NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER &#8211; NOW A SHOWTIME LIMITED SERIES &#8211; NAMED ONE OF THE BEST BOOKS OF THE YEAR BY NPR </p>
<p>                     When Rupert Murdoch enlisted Roger Ailes to launch a cable news network in 1996, American politics and media changed forever. With a remarkable level of detail and insight, Vanity Fair magazine reporter Gabriel Sherman puts Ailes&#8217;s unique genius on display, along with the outsize personalities&#8211;Bill O&#8217;Reilly, Sean Hannity, Megyn Kelly, Sarah Palin, Karl Rove, Glenn Beck, Mike Huckabee, Gretchen Carlson, Bill Shine, and others&#8211;who have helped Fox News play a defining role in the great social and political controversies of the past two decades. From the Clinton-Lewinsky scandal to the Bush-Gore recount, from the war in Iraq to the Tea Party attack on the Obama presidency, Roger Ailes developed an unrivaled power to sway the national agenda. Even more, he became the indispensable figure in conservative America and the man any Republican politician with presidential aspirations had to court. </p>
<p>                     How did this man become the master strategist of our political landscape? In revelatory detail, Sherman chronicles the rise of Ailes, a frail kid from an Ohio factory town who, through sheer willpower, the flair of a showman, fierce corporate politicking, and a profound understanding of the priorities of middle America, built the most influential television news empire of our time. </p>
<p>                     Drawing on hundreds of interviews with Fox News insiders past and present, Sherman documents Ailes&#8217;s tactical acuity as he battled the press, business rivals, and countless real and perceived enemies inside and outside Fox. Sherman takes us inside the morning meetings in which Ailes and other high-level executives strategized Fox&#8217;s presentation of the news to advance Ailes&#8217;s political agenda; provides behind-the-scenes details of Ailes&#8217;s crucial role as finder and shaper of talent, including his sometimes rocky relationships with Fox News stars such as O&#8217;Reilly, Hannity, and Carlson; and probes Ailes&#8217;s fraught partnership with his equally brash and mercurial boss, Rupert Murdoch. </p>
<p>                     Roger Ailes&#8217;s life is a story worthy of Citizen Kane. Featuring an afterword about Ailes&#8217;s epic downfall during the extraordinary 2016 election, The Loudest Voice in the Room is an extraordinary feat of reportage with a compelling human drama at its heart.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-loudest-voice-in-the-room-how-the-brilliant-bombastic-roger-ailes-built-fox-news-and-divided-a-country-gabriel-sherman/">The Loudest Voice in the Room : How the Brilliant, Bombastic Roger Ailes Built Fox News&#8211;and Divided a Country &#8211; Gabriel Sherman</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Politically Incorrect Guide to the American Revolution &#8211; Larry Schweikart</title>
		<link>/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-the-american-revolution-larry-schweikart/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[bestsellers]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[American War Of Independence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Military History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-the-american-revolution-larry-schweikart/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The truth about the American Revolution is under attack. Despite what you may have learned in school, it wasn&#8217;t a rich slaveholder&#8217;s war fought to maintain white privilege. In fact, the War of Independence wasn&#8217;t about maintaining any status quo&#8211;it was the world&#8217;s first successful bottom-up revolution by the people, ushering in a new dawn [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-the-american-revolution-larry-schweikart/">The Politically Incorrect Guide to the American Revolution &#8211; Larry Schweikart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The truth about the American Revolution is under attack. Despite what you may have learned in school, it wasn&#8217;t a rich slaveholder&#8217;s war fought to maintain white privilege. In fact, the War of Independence wasn&#8217;t about maintaining any status quo&#8211;it was the world&#8217;s first successful bottom-up revolution by the people, ushering in a new dawn of liberty that history had never seen before. But with left-wingers dominating the teaching of history, where can you go for the true story of the unprecedented events that made the United States the worlds greatest nation? </p>
<p>                     Now bestselling historian Larry Schweikart has teamed up with author Dave Dougherty to write the ground-breaking patriotic history you&#8217;ve always wanted to read about the foundation of our unique nation. The Politically Incorrect Guide to the American Revolution reveals:<br />
                     Four key factors that applied only in America, making it impossible to replicate the Revolution anywhere else  Why it matters that the Patriot ghting force was overwhelmingly Scotch-Irish  The key role of Protestantism: which denominations tended to become Patriots, and which Tories How Americans were different from the Europeans and English even at the outset of the Revolution  How the casualties of the deadliest war in American history are routinely underreported  How our Revolution became a model for hundreds of others&#8211;that all failed<br />
                     Schweikart and Dougherty take on the left-wing myths&#8211;starting with the Marxist narrative of the Revolution in Howard Zinn&#8217;s nearly ubiquitous A People&#8217;s History of the United States&#8211;and uncover the truth about America&#8217;s beginning.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-politically-incorrect-guide-to-the-american-revolution-larry-schweikart/">The Politically Incorrect Guide to the American Revolution &#8211; Larry Schweikart</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elections & Referenda]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Globalization]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>IAN BREMMER WAS NAMED LINKEDIN&#8217;S #1 TOP INFLUENCER in 2017 &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; &#8216;Required reading to help repair a world in pieces and build a world at peace&#8217; &#8211; Antonio Guterres, United Nations Secretary General &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211; &#8216;Ian Bremmer is provocative, controversial, and always intelligent about the state of the world, which he knows so well&#8217; &#8211; Christine [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>IAN BREMMER WAS NAMED LINKEDIN&#8217;S #1 TOP INFLUENCER in 2017    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Required reading to help repair a world in pieces and build a world at peace&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Antonio Guterres, United Nations Secretary General     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Ian Bremmer is provocative, controversial, and always intelligent about the state of the world, which he knows so well&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Christine Lagarde, Managing Director of the International Monetary Fund     </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    From Brexit, to Donald Trump, to extremist parties in Europe and the developing world, populism has dominated recent headlines.     </p>
<p>                    But what explains the rise of leaders who stoke nationalist anger in their countries, from Le Pen to Erdogan? How long will the populist wave last? Who will be the winners and losers in this climate, and how can we defend the values of democracy, free trade and international cooperation?     </p>
<p>                    No one is better suited to explore these questions than Ian Bremmer, the CEO of the Eurasia Group and acclaimed Time magazine columnist. Analysing the social, economic and technological forces fuelling this new wave of populism, Bremmer explains why we&#8217;re witnessing a rejection of the democratic, global, cosmopolitan trends of the late 20th century. Us vs. Them is a definitive guide to navigating the shifting political landscape, for businesses looking to weather and survive the populist storm.    </p>
<p>                    &#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8212;&#8211;    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Global politics is a jungle today. Thank goodness Ian Bremmer can be your guide&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; David Miliband, president and CEO of the International Rescue Committee    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;A masterful analysis of why global crashed and populism soared&#8217;<br />
                    &#8211; Adam Grant, author of Give and Take, and Originals and Option B with Sheryl Sandberg</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-vs-them-the-failure-of-globalism-ian-bremmer-abridged/">Us vs. Them : The Failure of Globalism &#8211; Ian Bremmer (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In Defence of Selfishness : Why the Code of Self-Sacrifice is Unjust and Destructive &#8211; Peter Schwartz (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/in-defence-of-selfishness-why-the-code-of-self-sacrifice-is-unjust-and-destructive-peter-schwartz-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business & Management]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/in-defence-of-selfishness-why-the-code-of-self-sacrifice-is-unjust-and-destructive-peter-schwartz-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>From childhood, we&#8217;re taught one central, non-controversial idea about morality: self-sacrifice is a virtue. It is universally accepted that serving the needs of others, rather than our own, is the essence of morality. To be ethical &#8211; it is believed &#8211; is to be altruistic. Questioning this belief is regarded as tantamount to questioning the [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defence-of-selfishness-why-the-code-of-self-sacrifice-is-unjust-and-destructive-peter-schwartz-abridged/">In Defence of Selfishness : Why the Code of Self-Sacrifice is Unjust and Destructive &#8211; Peter Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From childhood, we&#8217;re taught one central, non-controversial idea about morality: self-sacrifice is a virtue. It is universally accepted that serving the needs of others, rather than our own, is the essence of morality. To be ethical &#8211; it is believed &#8211; is to be altruistic. Questioning this belief is regarded as tantamount to questioning the self-evident. Here, Peter Schwartz questions it. In Defense of Selfishness refutes widespread misconceptions about the meaning of selfishness and of altruism. Basing his arguments on Ayn Rand&#8217;s ethics of rational self-interest, Schwartz demonstrates that genuine selfishness is not exemplified by the brutal plundering of an Attila the Hun or the conniving duplicity of a Bernard Madoff. To the contrary, such people are acting against their actual, long-range interests. The truly selfish individual is committed to moral principles and lives an honest, productive, self-respecting life. He does not feed parasitically off other people. Instead, he renounces the unearned, and deals with others &#8211; in both the material and spiritual realms &#8211; by offering value for value, to mutual benefit.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/in-defence-of-selfishness-why-the-code-of-self-sacrifice-is-unjust-and-destructive-peter-schwartz-abridged/">In Defence of Selfishness : Why the Code of Self-Sacrifice is Unjust and Destructive &#8211; Peter Schwartz (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Be an Antiracist &#8211; Ibram X. Kendi (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-an-antiracist-ibram-x-kendi-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ethnic Minorities & Multicultural Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Rights]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Discrimination]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-an-antiracist-ibram-x-kendi-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>**THE GLOBAL MILLION-COPY BESTSELLER** NOT BEING RACIST IS NOT ENOUGH. WE HAVE TO BE ANTIRACIST. &#8216;Transformative and revolutionary&#8217; ROBIN DIANGELO, author of White Fragility &#8216;So vital&#8217; IJEOMA OLUO, author of So You Want to Talk About Race In this rousing and deeply empathetic book, Ibram X. Kendi, one of the world&#8217;s most influential scholars of [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-an-antiracist-ibram-x-kendi-abridged/">How To Be an Antiracist &#8211; Ibram X. Kendi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>**THE GLOBAL MILLION-COPY BESTSELLER**    </p>
<p>                    NOT BEING RACIST IS NOT ENOUGH. WE HAVE TO BE ANTIRACIST.    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;Transformative and revolutionary&#8217; ROBIN DIANGELO, author of White Fragility    </p>
<p>                     &#8216;So vital&#8217; IJEOMA OLUO, author of So You Want to Talk About Race    </p>
<p>                     In this rousing and deeply empathetic book, Ibram X. Kendi, one of the world&#8217;s most influential scholars of racism, shows that neutrality is not an option: until we become part of the solution, we can only be part of the problem.    </p>
<p>                     Using his extraordinary gifts as a teacher and story-teller, Kendi helps us recognise that everyone is, at times, complicit in racism whether they realise it or not, and by describing with moving humility his own journey from racism to antiracism, he shows us how instead to be a force for good. Along the way, Kendi punctures all the myths and taboos that so often cloud our understanding, from arguments about what race is and whether racial differences exist to the complications that arise when race intersects with ethnicity, class, gender and sexuality.    </p>
<p>                     In the process he demolishes the myth of the post-racial society and builds from the ground up a vital new understanding of racism &#8211; what it is, where it is hidden, how to identify it and what to do about it.    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;The most courageous book to date on the problem of race&#8217; New York Times    </p>
<p>                    &#8216;It feels like a light switch being flicked on&#8217; OWEN JONES</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-an-antiracist-ibram-x-kendi-abridged/">How To Be an Antiracist &#8211; Ibram X. Kendi (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Audacity of Hope : Thoughts on Reclaiming the American Dream &#8211; Barack Obama (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-audacity-of-hope-thoughts-on-reclaiming-the-american-dream-barack-obama-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:16:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Leaders & Leadership]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-audacity-of-hope-thoughts-on-reclaiming-the-american-dream-barack-obama-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Before he was president, he was senator. Written two years prior to the election that would change the face of the United States, The Audacity of Hope discusses the importance of empathy in politics, Obama&#8217;s hopes for a different America and how the ideals of its democracy can be renewed. With intimacy and self-deprecating humour, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-audacity-of-hope-thoughts-on-reclaiming-the-american-dream-barack-obama-abridged/">The Audacity of Hope : Thoughts on Reclaiming the American Dream &#8211; Barack Obama (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Before he was president, he was senator. Written two years prior to the election that would change the face of the United States, The Audacity of Hope discusses the importance of empathy in politics, Obama&#8217;s hopes for a different America and how the ideals of its democracy can be renewed.    </p>
<p>                     With intimacy and self-deprecating humour, he describes his experiences balancing his family life with his public vocation. A senator and a lawyer, a professor and a father, a Christian and a sceptic, Barack Obama has written a book of transforming power that will inspire people the world over.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-audacity-of-hope-thoughts-on-reclaiming-the-american-dream-barack-obama-abridged/">The Audacity of Hope : Thoughts on Reclaiming the American Dream &#8211; Barack Obama (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Populism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Cas Mudde, Cristóbal Rovira Kaltwasser (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/populism-a-very-short-introduction-cas-mudde-cristobal-rovira-kaltwasser-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/populism-a-very-short-introduction-cas-mudde-cristobal-rovira-kaltwasser-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Populism is a central concept in the current media debates about politics and elections. However, like most political buzzwords, the term often floats from one meaning to another, and both social scientists and journalists use it to denote diverse phenomena. What is populism really? Who are the populist leaders? And what is the relationship between [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/populism-a-very-short-introduction-cas-mudde-cristobal-rovira-kaltwasser-abridged/">Populism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Cas Mudde, Cristóbal Rovira Kaltwasser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Populism is a central concept in the current media debates about politics and elections. However, like most political buzzwords, the term often floats from one meaning to another, and both social scientists and journalists use it to denote diverse phenomena. What is populism really? Who are the populist leaders? And what is the relationship between populism and democracy? This book answers these questions in a simple and persuasive way, offering a swift guide to<br />
                    populism in theory and practice.    </p>
<p>                    Cas Mudde and Cristobal Rovera Kaltwasser present populism as an ideology that divides society into two antagonistic camps, the &#8220;pure people&#8221; versus the &#8220;corrupt elite,&#8221; and that privileges the general will of the people above all else. They illustrate the practical power of this ideology through a survey of representative populist movements of the modern era: European right-wing parties, left-wing presidents in Latin America, and the Tea Party movement in the United States. The authors<br />
                    delve into the ambivalent personalities of charismatic populist leaders such as Juan Domingo Peron, H. Ross Perot, Jean-Marie le Pen, Silvio Berlusconi, and Hugo Chavez. If the strong male leader embodies the mainstream form of populism, many resolute women, such as Eva Peron, Pauline Hanson, and Sarah<br />
                    Palin, have also succeeded in building a populist status, often by exploiting gendered notions of society.    </p>
<p>                    Although populism is ultimately part of democracy, populist movements constitute an increasing challenge to democratic politics. Comparing political trends across different countries, this compelling book debates what the long-term consequences of this challenge could be, as it turns the spotlight on the bewildering effect of populism on today&#8217;s political and social life.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/populism-a-very-short-introduction-cas-mudde-cristobal-rovira-kaltwasser-abridged/">Populism: A Very Short Introduction &#8211; Cas Mudde, Cristóbal Rovira Kaltwasser (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Biography: Historical, Political & Military]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Journalistic Style Guides]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Media Studies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal: to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221; major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Known for his network of conservative websites that draws millions of readers everyday, Andrew Breitbart has one main goal:  to make sure the &#8220;liberally biased&#8221;  major news outlets in this country cover all aspects of a story fairly. Breitbart is convinced that too many national stories are slanted by the news media in an unfair way.     </p>
<p>                    Breitbart burst on to the national media scene thanks to his coverage of  the ACORN controversy, where a local ACORN community group leader was videotaped giving business advice to a &#8220;gentleman&#8221; who ran a prostitution ring. When the major news media at first tried to bury the story, Breitbart used his extraordinary marketing savvy to make sure the story got full national attention.     </p>
<p>                    More recently, Congressman Anthony Weiner took on Breitbart, claiming that scurrilous photos of Weiner were being sent on the internet by the conservative right. In a new chapter in RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart details how &#8220;Weinergate&#8221; was entirely the personal fault of Congressman Weiner, and how Weiner derailed his own promising career by trying to implicate Breitbart and conservative journalists.    </p>
<p>                    In short, RIGHTEOUS INDIGNATION, Breitbart talks about the key issues that Americans face, how he has aligned himself with the Tea Party, and how one needs to deal with the liberal news world head on. Along the way, he details his early years, working with Matt Drudge, the Huffington Post, and so on, and how Breitbart developed his unique style of launching key websites to help get the word out to conservatives all over.     </p>
<p>                    A rollicking and controversial read, Breitbart will certainly raise your blood pressure, one way or another.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/righteous-indignation-excuse-me-while-i-save-the-world-andrew-breitbart-abridged/">Righteous Indignation : Excuse Me While I Save the World &#8211; Andrew Breitbart (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Weapons of Math Destruction : How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy &#8211; Cathy O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Algorithms & Data Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Data Mining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Econometrics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Statistics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Impact Of Science & Technology On Society]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Machine Learning]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Popular Science]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A manual for the 21st-century citizen&#8230; accessible, refreshingly critical, relevant and urgent&#8217; &#8211; Financial Times &#8216;Fascinating and deeply disturbing&#8217; &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari, Guardian Books of the Year In this New York Times bestseller, Cathy O&#8217;Neil, one of the first champions of algorithmic accountability, sounds an alarm on the mathematical models that pervade modern life [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/">Weapons of Math Destruction : How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy &#8211; Cathy O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A manual for the 21st-century citizen&#8230; accessible, refreshingly critical, relevant and urgent&#8217; &#8211;  Financial Times     </p>
<p>                    &#8216;Fascinating and deeply disturbing&#8217; &#8211; Yuval Noah Harari, Guardian Books of the Year     </p>
<p>                    In this New York Times bestseller, Cathy O&#8217;Neil, one of the first champions of algorithmic accountability, sounds an alarm on the mathematical models that pervade modern life &#8212; and threaten to rip apart our social fabric.    </p>
<p>                    We live in the age of the algorithm. Increasingly, the decisions that affect our lives &#8211; where we go to school, whether we get a loan, how much we pay for insurance &#8211; are being made not by humans, but by mathematical models. In theory, this should lead to greater fairness: everyone is judged according to the same rules, and bias is eliminated.     </p>
<p>                    And yet, as Cathy O&#8217;Neil reveals in this urgent and necessary book, the opposite is true. The models being used today are opaque, unregulated, and incontestable, even when they&#8217;re wrong. Most troubling, they reinforce discrimination. Tracing the arc of a person&#8217;s life, O&#8217;Neil exposes the black box models that shape our future, both as individuals and as a society. These &#8220;weapons of math destruction&#8221; score teachers and students, sort CVs, grant or deny loans, evaluate workers, target voters, and monitor our health.     </p>
<p>                    O&#8217;Neil calls on modellers to take more responsibility for their algorithms and on policy makers to regulate their use. But in the end, it&#8217;s up to us to become more savvy about the models that govern our lives. This important book empowers us to ask the tough questions, uncover the truth, and demand change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/weapons-of-math-destruction-how-big-data-increases-inequality-and-threatens-democracy-cathy-oneil-abridged/">Weapons of Math Destruction : How Big Data Increases Inequality and Threatens Democracy &#8211; Cathy O&#8217;Neil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Plato: &#8216;The Republic&#8217; &#8211; Plato, Translated by Tom Griffith, Edited by G. R. F. Ferrari (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/plato-the-republic-plato-translated-by-tom-griffith-edited-by-g-r-f-ferrari-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Western Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Western Philosophy: Ancient, To C 500]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/plato-the-republic-plato-translated-by-tom-griffith-edited-by-g-r-f-ferrari-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>First published in 2000, this translation of one of the great works of Western political thought is based on the assumption that when Plato chose the dialogue form for his writing, he intended these dialogues to sound like conversations &#8211; although conversations of a philosophical sort. In addition to a vivid, dignified and accurate rendition [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/plato-the-republic-plato-translated-by-tom-griffith-edited-by-g-r-f-ferrari-abridged/">Plato: &#8216;The Republic&#8217; &#8211; Plato, Translated by Tom Griffith, Edited by G. R. F. Ferrari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>First published in 2000, this translation of one of the great works of Western political thought is based on the assumption that when Plato chose the dialogue form for his writing, he intended these dialogues to sound like conversations &#8211; although conversations of a philosophical sort. In addition to a vivid, dignified and accurate rendition of Plato&#8217;s text, the student and general reader will find many aids to comprehension in this volume: an introduction that assesses the cultural background to the Republic, its place within political philosophy, and its general argument; succinct notes in the body of the text; an analytical summary of the work&#8217;s content; a full glossary of proper names; a chronology of important events; and a guide to further reading. The result is an accomplished and accessible edition of this seminal work, suitable for philosophers and classicists as well as historians of political thought at all levels.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/plato-the-republic-plato-translated-by-tom-griffith-edited-by-g-r-f-ferrari-abridged/">Plato: &#8216;The Republic&#8217; &#8211; Plato, Translated by Tom Griffith, Edited by G. R. F. Ferrari (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Be Right : &#8230; in a world gone wrong &#8211; James O&#8217;Brien (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Advice On Careers & Achieving Success]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Demonstrations & Protest Movements]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Activism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Speaking Guides]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The voice of reason in a world that won&#8217;t shut up. The Sunday Times Bestseller Winner of the Parliamentary Book Awards Every day, James O&#8217;Brien listens to people blaming hard-working immigrants for stealing their jobs while scrounging benefits, and pointing their fingers at the EU and feminists for destroying Britain. But what makes James&#8217;s daily [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/">How To Be Right : &#8230; in a world gone wrong &#8211; James O&#8217;Brien (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The voice of reason in a world that won&#8217;t shut up.    </p>
<p>                    The Sunday Times Bestseller<br />
                    Winner of the Parliamentary Book Awards    </p>
<p>                    Every day, James O&#8217;Brien listens to people blaming hard-working immigrants for stealing their jobs while scrounging benefits, and pointing their fingers at the EU and feminists for destroying Britain. But what makes James&#8217;s daily LBC show such essential listening &#8211; and has made James a standout social media star &#8211; is the incisive way he punctures their assumptions and dismantles their arguments live on air, every single morning.    </p>
<p>                    In the bestselling How To Be Right, James provides a hilarious and invigorating guide to talking to people with unchallenged opinions. With chapters on every lightning-rod issue, James shows how people have been fooled into thinking the way they do, and in each case outlines the key questions to ask to reveal fallacies, inconsistencies and double standards.    </p>
<p>                    If you ever get cornered by ardent Brexiteers, Daily Mail disciples or corporate cronies, this book is your conversation survival guide.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/how-to-be-right-in-a-world-gone-wrong-james-obrien-abridged/">How To Be Right : &#8230; in a world gone wrong &#8211; James O&#8217;Brien (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Conservatism & Right-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Funny Books & Stories]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Liberalism & Centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Public Opinion & Polls]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Television]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER The popular FOX News star of Tucker Carlson Tonight offers his signature fearless and funny political commentary on how America&#8217;s ruling class has failed everyday Americans. &#8220;You look on in horror, helpless and desperate. You have nowhere to go. You&#8217;re trapped on a ship of fools.&#8221; &#8211;From the Introduction In [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/">Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>#1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER     </p>
<p>                    The popular FOX News star of Tucker Carlson Tonight offers his signature fearless and funny political commentary on how America&#8217;s ruling class has failed everyday Americans.     </p>
<p>                    &#8220;You look on in horror, helpless and desperate.<br />
                     You have nowhere to go.<br />
                     You&#8217;re trapped on a ship of fools.&#8221;<br />
                     &#8211;From the Introduction     </p>
<p>                     In Ship of Fools: How a Selfish Ruling Class is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution, Tucker Carlson tells the truth about the new American elites, a group whose power and wealth has grown beyond imagination even as the rest of the country has withered. The people who run America now barely interact with it. They fly on their own planes, ski on their own mountains, watch sporting events far from the stands in sky boxes. They have total contempt for you.     </p>
<p>                     &#8220;They view America the way a private equity firm sizes up an aging conglomerate,&#8221; Carlson writes, &#8220;as something outdated they can profit from. When it fails, they&#8217;re gone.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     In Ship of Fools,  Tucker Carlson offers a blistering critique of our new overlords. Traditional liberals are gone, he writes. The patchouli-scented hand-wringers who worried about whales and defended free speech have been replaced by globalists who hide their hard-edged economic agenda behind the smokescreen of identity politics. They&#8217;ll outsource your job while lecturing you about transgender bathrooms. Left and right, Carlson says, are no longer meaningful categories in America. &#8220;The rift is between those who benefit from the status quo, and those who don&#8217;t.&#8221;     </p>
<p>                     Our leaders are fools, Carlson concludes, &#8220;unaware that they are captains of a sinking ship.&#8221; But in the signature and witty style that viewers of Tucker Carlson Tonight have come to enjoy, his book answers the all-important question: How do we put the country back on course?</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ship-of-fools-how-a-selfish-ruling-class-is-bringing-america-to-the-brink-of-revolution-tucker-carlson-abridged/">Ship of Fools : How a Selfish Ruling Class Is Bringing America to the Brink of Revolution &#8211; Tucker Carlson (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inventing the Future : Postcapitalism and a World Without Work &#8211; Nick Srnicek (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social & Political Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Forecasting, Future Studies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Neoliberalism isn&#8217;t working. Austerity is forcing millions into poverty and many more into precarious work, while the left remains trapped in stagnant political practices that offer no respite. Inventing the Future is a bold new manifesto for life after capitalism. Against the confused understanding of our high-tech world by both the right and the left, [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/">Inventing the Future : Postcapitalism and a World Without Work &#8211; Nick Srnicek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Neoliberalism isn&#8217;t working. Austerity is forcing millions into poverty and many more into precarious work, while the left remains trapped in stagnant political practices that offer no respite. Inventing the Future is a bold new manifesto for life after capitalism. Against the confused understanding of our high-tech world by both the right and the left, this book claims that the emancipatory and future-oriented possibilities of our society can be reclaimed. Instead of running from a complex future, Nick Srnicek and Alex Williams demand a postcapitalist economy capable of advancing standards, liberating humanity from work and developing technologies that expand our freedoms. This new edition includes a new chapter where they respond to their various critics.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/inventing-the-future-postcapitalism-and-a-world-without-work-nick-srnicek-abridged/">Inventing the Future : Postcapitalism and a World Without Work &#8211; Nick Srnicek (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fantasyland : How America Went Haywire: A 500-Year History &#8211; Kurt Andersen (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Comparative Politics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Constitution: Government & The State]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of The Americas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re entitled to your own opinion but not your own facts Fantasy is the USA&#8217;s primary product. From the Pilgrim Fathers onward America has been a place where renegades and freaks came in search of freedom to create their own realities with little objectively regulated truth standing in their way. The freedom to invent and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/">Fantasyland : How America Went Haywire: A 500-Year History &#8211; Kurt Andersen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You&#8217;re entitled to your own opinion but not your own facts    </p>
<p>                    Fantasy is the USA&#8217;s primary product. From the Pilgrim Fathers onward America has been a place where renegades and freaks came in search of freedom to create their own realities with little objectively regulated truth standing in their way. The freedom to invent and believe whatever the hell you like is, in some ways, an unwritten constitutional right. But, this do-your-own-thing freedom also is the driving credo of America&#8217;s current transformation where the difference between opinion and fact is rapidly crumbling.     </p>
<p>                    So how did we get to this weird pseudo-reality, where science and objective facts are dismissed in favour of opinions and wild speculation, or indeed, fantasies? The post truth, fake news, free-for-all mentality isn&#8217;t exactly a new phenomenon. If you want to understand Trump&#8217;s America, how the lines between reality and illusion have become dangerously blurred, you have to go back to the very beginning and take a dizzying road trip across five centuries of crackpot delusion and make-believe from Salem to Scientology.    </p>
<p>                    Fantasyland is a journey that connects the dots between crazed franchises of true believers &#8211; a rich freak show tapestry from Mormons to Flat-Earthers and satanic panic, new age quacks to anti-vaxxers, conspiracy theorists of every stripe, creationists to climate change deniers, UFO-obsessives to gun-toting libertarians, showmen hucksters from P T Barnum to Trump himself, all topped off with a dangerous dose of anti-government paranoia and pseudoscience. Along the way, New York Times bestselling author Kurt Andersen has created a unique and raucous history of America and a new paradigm for understanding our post-factual world.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fantasyland-how-america-went-haywire-a-500-year-history-kurt-andersen-abridged/">Fantasyland : How America Went Haywire: A 500-Year History &#8211; Kurt Andersen (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Communist Manifesto &#8211; Karl Marx (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/communist-manifesto-karl-marx-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Science & Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Socialism & Left-of-centre Democratic Ideologies]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/communist-manifesto-karl-marx-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Manifesto of the Communist Party (German: Manifest der Kommunistischen Partei), often referred to as The Communist Manifesto, was published on February 21, 1848, and is one of the world&#8217;s most influential political manuscripts. Commissioned by the Communist League and written by communist theorists Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels, it laid out the League&#8217;s purposes and [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/communist-manifesto-karl-marx-abridged/">Communist Manifesto &#8211; Karl Marx (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Manifesto of the Communist Party (German: Manifest der Kommunistischen Partei), often referred to as The Communist Manifesto, was published on February 21, 1848, and is one of the world&#8217;s most influential political manuscripts. Commissioned by the Communist League and written by communist theorists Karl Marx and Friedrich Engels, it laid out the League&#8217;s purposes and program. It presents an analytical approach to the class struggle (historical and present) and the problems of capitalism, rather than a prediction of communism&#8217;s potential future forms.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/communist-manifesto-karl-marx-abridged/">Communist Manifesto &#8211; Karl Marx (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Human Geography]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Marxism & Communism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Economy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Welfare & Social Services]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The acclaimed labor lawyer and prizewinning author Thomas Geoghegan asks: where are we better off America or Europe? In an idiosyncratic, entertaining travelogue that plays on public policy, Geoghegan asks what our lives would be like if we lived them as Europeans. Sneaking out of his workaholic American life, he takes five trips where he [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/">Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The acclaimed labor lawyer and prizewinning author Thomas Geoghegan asks: where are we better off America or Europe? In an idiosyncratic, entertaining travelogue that plays on public policy, Geoghegan asks what our lives would be like if we lived them as Europeans. Sneaking out of his workaholic American life, he takes five trips where he tries to understand so-called European socialism firsthand. Though he first tries France (which has become a rhetorical stand-in for the continent as a whole in many Americans&#8217; minds), he eventually ventures into Germany to see what some call the &#8220;boring&#8221; Europe. There he finds the true &#8220;other&#8221; an economic model with more bottom-up worker control than that of any other country in the world and argues that, while we have to take Germany&#8217;s problems seriously, we also have to look seriously at how much it has achieved. Social democracy may let us live nicer lives; it also may be the only way to be globally competitive. This wry, timely book helps us understand why the European model, contrary to popular neoliberal wisdom, may thrive well into the twenty-first century without compromising its citizens&#8217; ease of living and be the best example for the United States to follow.    </p>
<p>                    Germany is more generous than the U.S.:    </p>
<p>                    The average number of paid vacation days in the U.S. is 13, versus Germany&#8217;s 35<br />
                    New mothers in the U.S. get three months of unpaid job-protected leave and only if they work for a company of 50 or more employees, while Germany mandates four months&#8217; paid leave and will pay parents 67% of their salary to stay home for up to 14 months to care for a newborn.<br />
                    U.S. life expectancy is 50th in the world, compared to Germany&#8217;s 32nd.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/were-you-born-on-the-wrong-continent-how-the-european-model-can-help-you-get-a-life-thomas-geoghegan-abridged/">Were You Born on the Wrong Continent? : How the European Model Can Help You Get a Life &#8211; Thomas Geoghegan (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Southern Theory : Social Science And The Global Dynamics Of Knowledge &#8211; Raewyn W. Connell (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/southern-theory-social-science-and-the-global-dynamics-of-knowledge-raewyn-w-connell-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Social Theory]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sociology & Anthropology]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/southern-theory-social-science-and-the-global-dynamics-of-knowledge-raewyn-w-connell-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>In Southern Theory Raewyn Connell presents the case for a new &#8216;world social science&#8217; &#8211; one that is inclusive of many voices &#8211; by arguing for a more democratic global recognition of social theory from societies outside the dominant European and North American metropole. Intellectual production of the majority &#8216;southern&#8217; world does in fact include [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/southern-theory-social-science-and-the-global-dynamics-of-knowledge-raewyn-w-connell-abridged/">Southern Theory : Social Science And The Global Dynamics Of Knowledge &#8211; Raewyn W. Connell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In Southern Theory Raewyn Connell presents the case for a new &#8216;world social science&#8217; &#8211; one that is inclusive of many voices &#8211; by arguing for a more democratic global recognition of social theory from societies outside the dominant European and North American metropole. Intellectual production of the majority &#8216;southern&#8217; world does in fact include theory, though its contribution is often marginalised and intellectually discredited by the metropole. Connell shows how social theory about the modern world from peripheral societies is equal in intellectual rigour and is often of greater political relevance to our changing world. Beginning with an examination of the hidden assumptions of modern general theory, Southern Theory looks to the &#8216;southern&#8217; social experience and the theories that have emerged from Australia, Indigenous peoples, Latin America, India, Africa, Islam and other post-colonial societies, as sources of important and vital contributions to world social science.<br />
                    These myriad theories offer valuable perspectives so crucial to the application of social theory in the contemporary world, having the power to transform the influence of the metropolitan hegemony on social thought by mutual regard and interaction. Southern Theory is a major new work in social theory, drawing on anthropology, history, psychology, philosophy, economics and cultural studies, with wide-ranging implications for the social sciences in the 21st century.  Visit  www.raewynconnell.net</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/southern-theory-social-science-and-the-global-dynamics-of-knowledge-raewyn-w-connell-abridged/">Southern Theory : Social Science And The Global Dynamics Of Knowledge &#8211; Raewyn W. Connell (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Business, Finance & Law]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Central Government Policies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fascism & Nazism]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Industrial Relations & Safety]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Control & Freedoms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Oppression & Persecution]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structure & Processes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Politics & Government]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Burnham has real intellectual courage, and writes about real issues.&#8217; &#8211; George Orwell Burnham&#8217;s claim was that capitalism was dead, but that it was being replaced not by socialism, but a new economic system he called &#8220;managerialism&#8221;; rule by managers. Written in 1941, this is the book that theorised how the world was moving into [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/">The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Burnham has real intellectual courage, and writes about real issues.&#8217; &#8211; George Orwell    </p>
<p>                    Burnham&#8217;s claim was that capitalism was dead, but that it was being replaced not by socialism, but a new economic system he called &#8220;managerialism&#8221;; rule by managers.    </p>
<p>                    Written in 1941, this is the book that theorised how the world was moving into the hands of the &#8216;managers&#8217;. Burnham explains how Capitalism had virtually lost its control, and would be displaced not by labour, nor by socialism, but by the rule of administartors in business and in government.    </p>
<p>                    This revolution, he posited, is as broad as the world and as comprehensive as human society, asking &#8220;Why is &#8216;totalitarianism&#8217; not the issue?&#8221; &#8220;Can civilization be destroyed?&#8221; And &#8220;Why is the New Deal something bigger than Roosevelt can handle?&#8221;    </p>
<p>                    In a volume extraordinary for its dispassionate handling of those and other fundamental questions, James Burnham explores fully the implications of the managerial revolution.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-managerial-revolution-what-is-happening-in-the-world-james-burnham-abridged/">The Managerial Revolution : What is Happening in the World &#8211; James Burnham (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Capitalism and Freedom &#8211; Milton Friedman, Foreword by Binyamin Appelbaum (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/capitalism-and-freedom-milton-friedman-foreword-by-binyamin-appelbaum-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic History]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Systems & Structures]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economic Theory & Philosophy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Ideologies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Political Structures: Democracy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/capitalism-and-freedom-milton-friedman-foreword-by-binyamin-appelbaum-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of TIME magazine&#8217;s All-TIME 100 Best Nonfiction Books One of Times Literary Supplement&#8217;s Hundred Most Influential Books Since the War One of National Review&#8217;s 100 Best Nonfiction Books of the Century One of Intercollegiate Studies Institute&#8217;s 50 Best Books of the 20th Century How can we benefit from the promise of government while avoiding [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-and-freedom-milton-friedman-foreword-by-binyamin-appelbaum-abridged/">Capitalism and Freedom &#8211; Milton Friedman, Foreword by Binyamin Appelbaum (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>One of TIME magazine&#8217;s All-TIME 100 Best Nonfiction Books<br />
                     One of Times Literary Supplement&#8217;s Hundred Most Influential Books Since the War<br />
                     One of National Review&#8217;s 100 Best Nonfiction Books of the Century<br />
                      One of Intercollegiate Studies Institute&#8217;s 50 Best Books of the 20th Century  How can we benefit from the promise of government while avoiding the threat it poses to individual freedom? In this classic book, Milton Friedman provides the definitive statement of an immensely influential economic philosophy&#8211;one in which competitive capitalism serves as both a device for achieving economic freedom and a necessary condition for political freedom.     </p>
<p>                     First published in 1962, Friedman&#8217;s Capitalism and Freedom is one of the most significant works of economic theory ever written. Enduring in its eminence and esteem, it has sold nearly a million copies in English, has been translated into eighteen languages, and continues to inform economic thinking and policymaking around the world. This new edition includes prefaces written by Friedman for both the 1982 and 2002 reissues of the book, as well as a new foreword by Binyamin Appelbaum, lead economics writer for the New York Times editorial board.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/capitalism-and-freedom-milton-friedman-foreword-by-binyamin-appelbaum-abridged/">Capitalism and Freedom &#8211; Milton Friedman, Foreword by Binyamin Appelbaum (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
