<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Materials Science Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/materials-science/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/tag/materials-science/</link>
	<description>#1 Free Audiobooks Online Listen</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:56:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/84287349_padded_logo-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Materials Science Archives - Hoardible</title>
	<link>/tag/materials-science/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Making the Modern World : Materials and Dematerialization &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/making-the-modern-world-materials-and-dematerialization-vaclav-smil-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Economics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Environmental Science, Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[History Of Engineering & Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Materials Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mechanical Engineering & Materials]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/making-the-modern-world-materials-and-dematerialization-vaclav-smil-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How much further should the affluent world push its material consumption? Does relative dematerialization lead to absolute decline in demand for materials? These and many other questions are discussed and answered in Making the Modern World: Materials and Dematerialization. Over the course of time, the modern world has become dependent on unprecedented flows of materials. [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-the-modern-world-materials-and-dematerialization-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Making the Modern World : Materials and Dematerialization &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How much further should the affluent world push its material consumption? Does relative dematerialization lead to absolute decline in demand for materials?  These and many other questions are discussed and answered in Making the Modern World: Materials and Dematerialization. Over the course of time, the modern world has become dependent on unprecedented flows of materials. Now even the most efficient production processes and the highest practical rates of recycling may not be enough to result in dematerialization rates that would be high enough to negate the rising demand for materials generated by continuing population growth and rising standards of living. This book explores the costs of this dependence and the potential for substantial dematerialization of modern economies. Making the Modern World: Materials and Dematerialization considers the principal materials used throughout history, from wood and stone, through to metals, alloys, plastics and silicon, describing their extraction and production as well as their dominant applications.<br />
                    The evolving productivities of material extraction, processing, synthesis, finishing and distribution, and the energy costs and environmental impact of rising material consumption are examined in detail. The book concludes with an outlook for the future, discussing the prospects for dematerialization and potential constrains on materials. This interdisciplinary text provides useful perspectives for readers with backgrounds including resource economics, environmental studies, energy analysis, mineral geology, industrial organization, manufacturing and material science.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/making-the-modern-world-materials-and-dematerialization-vaclav-smil-abridged/">Making the Modern World : Materials and Dematerialization &#8211; Vaclav Smil (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rare : The High-Stakes Race to Satisfy Our Need for the Scarcest Metals on Earth &#8211; Keith Veronese (Abridged)</title>
		<link>/rare-the-high-stakes-race-to-satisfy-our-need-for-the-scarcest-metals-on-earth-keith-veronese-abridged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 03:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[summaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chemistry Books]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geopolitics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Inorganic Chemistry]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Management Of Land & Natural Resources]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Materials Science]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Metals Technology / Metallurgy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mining Technology & Engineering]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/rare-the-high-stakes-race-to-satisfy-our-need-for-the-scarcest-metals-on-earth-keith-veronese-abridged/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>How will your life change when the supply of tantalum dries up? You may have never heard of this unusual metal, but without it smartphones would be instantly less omniscient, video game systems would falter, and laptops fail. Tantalum is not alone. Rhodium. Osmium. Niobium. Such refugees from the bottom of the periodic table are [&#8230;]</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rare-the-high-stakes-race-to-satisfy-our-need-for-the-scarcest-metals-on-earth-keith-veronese-abridged/">Rare : The High-Stakes Race to Satisfy Our Need for the Scarcest Metals on Earth &#8211; Keith Veronese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>How will your life change when the supply of tantalum dries up? You may have never heard of this unusual metal, but without it smartphones would be instantly less omniscient, video game systems would falter, and laptops fail. Tantalum is not alone. Rhodium. Osmium. Niobium. Such refugees from the bottom of the periodic table are key components of many consumer products like cell phones, hybrid car batteries, and flat screen televisions, as well as sophisticated medical devices and even weapon systems. Their versatile properties have led manufacturers to seek these elements out to maximize longevity, value, and efficiency, but not without a human price.     </p>
<p>                    In addition to explaining the chemistry behind rare earth metals, Rare delves into the economic and geopolitical issues surrounding these &#8220;conflict minerals,&#8221; blending tales of financial and political struggles with glimpses into the human lives that are shattered by the race to secure them. In the past decade, the Congo has been ravaged by tribal wars fought to obtain control of tantalum, tungsten, and tin supplies in the region, with over five million people dying at the crossroads of supply and demand. A burgeoning black market in China, Africa, and India is propped up by school-age children retrieving and purifying these metals while risking their lives and health in the process. Fears of future political struggles inside China, the world&#8217;s largest supplier of these metals, have already sent the United States, Great Britain, and Japan racing to find alternative sources.    </p>
<p>                    Will scientists be able to create lab substitutes for some or all of these metals? Will Afghanistan be the next big supplier of rare metals? What happens when the limited supply runs out? Whatever the answers, it is clear that our modern lifestyle, dependent on technology, is far from stable.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rare-the-high-stakes-race-to-satisfy-our-need-for-the-scarcest-metals-on-earth-keith-veronese-abridged/">Rare : The High-Stakes Race to Satisfy Our Need for the Scarcest Metals on Earth &#8211; Keith Veronese (Abridged)</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Hoardible</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
